<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3415</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, it's clear as crystal that Scientology is an abusive cult with too much power and influence. I for one am 100% certain if we raided all Scientology compounds we'd find a lot more going on than just locking people up for nine months. 

In the article when police came back with a warrant they were all trying to pack things up and make it look like they did nothing wrong. 

Scientology knows it's fucked, we know it's fucked, now it is just a matter of time until something breaks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How skilled are you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're only reaching 30+ on high with max draw distance then that stands to reason it's a poorly optimized game. 

The standard is 60+ and there is a clear difference between 15, 30, 45, and 60 FPS. 

I'm sitting at about the same specs as you most likely (GTX 660TI 2GB, I5-4690K, and 8GB DDR3 RAM.) 

30+ FPS is good but not great and hardly counts as optimized.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  we're the only one that has invented Star Wars

We don't know that. 

What if there is a mirror civilization on the other side of the our universe doing everything we're doing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But in this case we know for a fact all the McDonald's are serving raw food.

We KNOW Scientology is a cult. We KNOW it's a scam. We KNOW they are abusing their members. We KNOW they are up to tons of illegal activity but because it's all under the blanket of religion and our government is too afraid to touch it they get to continue being pricks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got the Mechanical Cart and was considering trying this method .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking bottom left and maybe a little smaller would work, you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A rule without context and enforced for the sake of said rule is silly. 

When I said this I wasn't aware there was a stand in passenger, my comment still stands though as a personal belief of mine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 13:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No you're good, I try not to take anything personally online. You can disagree with me on anything you want, no worries. 

Apparently there was a standby passenger that I wasn't aware. I'm normally there for supporting the rules but the whole situation just seems fucked from the beginning. 

Maybe they should of made things more clear to the dude then rather than threatening him with jail and putting his kids in foster care... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 13:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I missed the part about the standby passenger...well...shoot. This is a whole fuckery of a situation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 12:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The team didn't go into designing the Necromancer with 2-3-4 person rifts in mind. They just went with what you would expect to find from the Necromancer. Curses, pets, blood, and bone! They want it to be flexible.

In other words no, we haven't balanced it for group play yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 12:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is retarded...if the son had been there the seat wouldn't have been free and he would of been forced to carry the baby. So why does it matter if he isn't there?

This is just a company employee applying shitty rules that make no sense in the context. 

Kicking them off the plane didn't solve anything, they are literally enforcing a rule just to enforce a rule which is silly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 12:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So if said person had been there and the seat had been occupied by a different body then it'd be OK? 

I can understand where the man is coming from it's not like this seat was opening up for anyone and his little switch-a-roo while it may be against the Airlines rules is understandable and in this situation the Airline is fucking up. 

You can be technical all day long but that makes you as much as an asshole as the airlines in this situation. 

I'm sure you wouldn't want all rules in your life being applied this strictly to you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I made a quick video of me fighting the Moon Lord my preferred way on Expert. Forgive me I'm not very entertaining. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 12:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Chess were a FTP game every one would get the same pieces...you can't play chess without the pieces. The only correct box is the last one, there would be a bunch of customization options.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like nearly every major Hollywood release? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean I thought it was amazing! 

I think you're mad you can't load your six shooter using your tits.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just saying give Pepsi a chance.

The protests are retarded anyways so at this point might as well say bullshit to sound good considering the protests are just as bull. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 07:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh you can place the rare plants in the world?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 02:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My comment is an ignorant statement made out of induced and irrational anger. 

In other words, I was feeling salty and said something un true on Reddit with no rational backing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The main issue is why the fuck are we still trying to blow the fuck out of the 3rd world while needlessly risking the lives of our military?

Just because we're a bloated tick of an army doesn't mean we just have soldiers to waste. I hate humanity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're factually wrong. 

It's been proven that eating/drinking with others helps the release of feel good hormones in your body. Sharing a pepsi could in fact bring peace given that both people enjoy pepsi.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're hitting a soft point on Reddit...Reddit doesn't like to admit that women can be wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck?

What kind of rationale is that?

If you punish people for this it's going to happen less often because they are aware that people will be called on their bullshit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 00:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say relevant because Goat Sim is a massively popular game that is popular because it lacks polish and a locked down objective. 

Basically you're saying you want a well made game that isn't that well made?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about Goat Simulator? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a possible context I had not thought of, you're right we may be seeing 1% of the full story here. They could be brothers...this could be staged...who knows? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never personally seen it but I sometimes almost breath in bong water if I hit my pipe too hard. If I over fill my favorite piece and pull too hard the water sometimes will shoot up and get all in my mouth, I'm sure I've breathed in some water before but nothing that would kill me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hard to say if this punishment is appropriate or not. 

The discussion of harshness is coming from the fact that if this were not a young and attractive woman she would of faced much greater sentencing than five years. 

The American Judicial System is fucked beyond belief. 

We allow our politicians and wealthy to commit felony after felony with as little as a slap on the wrist while the average man and woman have their lives ruined over a pipe or some weed or forgetting to pay the state their minor dues. 

I love living in America for many reasons but I'll be the first to say fuck our system, it's like living in a wealthy family full of complete retards. You know you got it good but you're surrounded by so much insanity it makes you want to kill yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah I see what you mean. Well honestly both private and public behavior are big concerns. You're right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My. Fucking. Family. 

Nearly burnt down their home because they seriously left a huge fire unattended in the back yard and thought it'd be fine because it was "at least twenty feet away from the brush!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seem upset. You know they say aggression runs in family that participate in lots of incest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't need to be a smoker to understand. Our mouths have two tubes, one for air and one for food/water. 

When one is in use a flap usually covers the other to keep things from going where they shouldn't. With proper muscle control you can breathe in and then proceed to also drink using your throat muscles to swallow your liquid while holding the smoke in your lungs. 

It can be a little hard and a little harsh but the more you smoke the less harsh it gets to you and the easier something like this becomes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No if the kid doesn't get in trouble for beating the shit out of the bully the cycle continues. 

Kids need to be more open with their parents about their school lives and people really need to sit down with bullies and get them to understand what they are doing is wrong. There is more than the fist in order to teach people humility and understanding.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know who's upvoting you but this isn't acceptable. 

This is how aggressive adults are made.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
