<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1143</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She asked for my opinion, we disagreed on taste, and she asked me to post this on the internet to see what other ppl think. She thinks that the old kitchen is too bland and wants to change it up, but she isn't sure this is the right colour. What colour would you choose to paint this? And what do you think of her design? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No need to apologize :) We agreed that which side that gets more votes will be how the kitchen is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Painted kitchen wall. Thoughts?

http://imgur.com/a/mwKs2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My mom painted her kitchen. Need opinions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> link: http://imgur.com/a/mwKs2

She painted parts of the kitchen wall turquoise. Personally, I don't like the change, the blue is too bright and clashes with the rest of the wall, but she likes it, so we want third-party opinions.

Please tell me if you like the change or not, and why. Also, if you were to paint this kitchen, what colour would you choose?

Like to dislike ratio:  outdated and I'm too lazy to update

Update: it seems more ppl dislike the blue than those who do, taking this into account, we decided the blue should go. Thanks for everyone who pitched in! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] For sale: planet, slightly used. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/chargeyourphone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 17:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What languages do you speak, and why do you study that hard? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the same model as the P45 if I remember correctly, so no it's not too heavy. Still check it out just to make sure though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loogle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you do not eat grapefruit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if i can find it on a dictionary...

...fuck where did i put it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/rjdkg/for_a_homework_assignment_my_identical_twin/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Dyatlov Pass incident](http://www.therichest.com/rich-list/15-conflicting-theories-of-the-dead-mountain-incident/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 03:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna stick my finger in the gun. Sure, it'll blow off my finger, but it will also jam the gun and render it useless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 02:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> got any cool nebulas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 01:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it is nice and simple. whoever made it did a good job. I usually choose nature wallpapers - they're more easy on the eyes - but each to his own </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 00:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So if you open 4 programs it tiles all four? or is the tiling manual? if not, wouldn't the tiling get annoying with many programs open? I realized by this point it might be better to just install it and see for myself, but then I found out it only runs on linux :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 00:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what about [this one](https://static.pexels.com/photos/3247/nature-forest-industry-rails.jpg)? It's my current background. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 00:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it full screens whatever you have open? What if you want two programs on your screen at same time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 00:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> black..screen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 23:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> happy birthday u/iwinalot7. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> mmm pineapple.. what wallpaper do you have right now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 23:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grass Chair </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 22:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 22:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does this mean I can post pictures of pineapples?

*nevermind just gonna do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 18:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something like [this](http://piq.codeus.net/static/media/userpics/piq_36283_400x400.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Make a Globe at bottom left corner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 18:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 18:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I shall join in  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's put the Cross of Lorraine on France!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 18:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asian invasion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The archduke was not assassinated at the parade, it was after the parade, when the driver took a wrong turn, and ended up right in front of Princip, who shot him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been there before. The city is HUGE, it's like  several cities combined together into a mega city. If you can, go in late spring or early fall, the smog isn't that bad then, and there's still greenery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will take a guess and say you live in china, due to the beijing reference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google dictionary translated it as 'silent kidney'?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 06:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much power does a top mod hold over the other mods? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realised pressing space 4 times after * also works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *testing

*testing

how do you get the bullet points??

***

Yes, I believe aliens are out there. The universe is so big that there's gotta be planets that harbor life; out of the trillions of planets, even a minute chance of life would result in thousands of civilizations. Theoretically, there should be plenty of alien civilizations more advanced than us. Earth is a pretty young planet - 4.5 billion years old, the universe reached the ability to harbor life about 10 billion years ago, other planets can be billions of years older and have much more time to develop intelligent life. The thing is there isn't anyone out there - that we know of, and that makes me worried, or anxious, or whatever you're supposed to feel stuck on a wet mud ball in endless space all alone.

About discovering alien life, I would err on the cautious side. God, don't we have enough problems on Earth as it is, to not go looking for more? I don't wanna worry about intergalactic politics. Also, look what happened when the Europeans discovered America. What if the aliens bring a plague? I think if we ever find aliens, we should take things slowly. 

Careers? Translators for sure, I bet the space travel industry will become really popular, and perhaps tourism? Maybe aliens like beer, who knows? Do they have internet, what do they even use to communicate? There will certainly be mailing services, I bet amazon will change their one-day delivery policy, though. The military's gonna go crazy, I'm sure. Send spies to other planets and develop anti-alien-invasion weapons. 

In my opinion, we shouldn't meddle with aliens before we solve our own issues. It will be nice to know we're not alone though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most dangerous weapon in the world? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 23:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 16:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we have the same laptop O_O Mine's a 8 year old Toshiba too. Having the same problems you have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did not know that! Where's the feature? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for this. I love that so many people are answering my questions. Sometimes I never get any answers, so it's nice to see multiple answers from different perspectives. I seemed to have attracted all the nerds in this area :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I say that I love your username? Reminds me of Lothlorien. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 00:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha apart from the ridiculous idea that will probably kill them all, the gun accuracy at that time is so bad that they might actually aim at the moon, and miss. Actually I take that back. Considering naval cannon accuracy of the 19th century, they probably will miss the moon. Oh well, at least they get to land among stars. I will check it out though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 00:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like Return of the King best. Much more action packed than the Two Towers. So much of TT was just walking... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 00:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have one of those, the best thing about them is they don't leave crumbs on your drawings, so you won't accidentally smear your sketches when brushing them off like with a normal eraser. You can use it to dot (is that the right word?) your drawings to lighten overly shaded areas like you would a sponge on paintings. A useful thing to have, although it gradually soakes up more lead and gets harder, eventually to the point you'll have to get a new one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not OP, you can use a thin eraser to create highlights too. Not sure about hair, but when you draw stuff like glass that has a lot of reflections, you erase out the highlights last with erasers. Take my word with a grain of salt though, it's been a few years since my last drawing lessons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, but can you explain why it'll enter the atmosphere every orbit? You can clearly tell I don't know much about physics, but I'm just toying with this idea. Theoretically, can you launch the cannonball at a really high speed, say, 90% of the speed of light (a lil too fast but you get what I'm saying), and have it stay in orbit, or will it just overheat the air and generate plasma and explosions and all that shit due to the atmosphere? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but thats basically how they launch rockets. I was exploring the idea of shooting a canon on the ground, sideways, and have it go into orbit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if its really fast? Is there no way at all? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't need to go high to go to space, you just need to go fast. I think it was 8km per second, correct me if I'm wrong.

Can you launch a cannonball into orbit by firing it at the horizon really fast? Assuming there's no obstacles in the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No its true. Hundreds of thousands of drafted workers got starved and worked to death on those hills. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They say flying is just throwing yourself at the ground, and missing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or those cameras that can zoom to the moon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Potatoes gonna Potate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A goat, a drum, and a rattlesnake fall down a cliff... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ba dum tss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 12:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> giving the the feeling that we were walking through a dark, tight canyon

.

Most wizard's won't touch the eyes though

wizards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 21:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ho, back from a trip, what have I missed? hmm, Malcolm seems fishy, and the throw-up part at the end seems abrupt, how about 'felt sick to my stomach'?

In my head, I could practically here the Jaws theme

hear

Worked overtime everyday this week

every day

He's comes out of retirement to take on a new challenger

wat

shes ready to push back

she's

He jumped up and pinned me on the ground

to the ground </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
