<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3065</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why we go in with HARM missiles first, get them to target our fast high flyers then take them out as soon as they turn on their radar.  Problem solved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm saying that if the US were to invade, not with the intention of stopping a nuclear test but regime change in mind, that it is entirely possible to deploy the MOAB.  Yes it would take some time to clear the way so to speak but time is on our side, not theirs.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 15:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You said it right.  It is not an option to let NK have a payload delivery vehicle that they can lord over their neighbors with the threat of nuclear attack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 15:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be very easy for the US to establish air superiority, then follow up with radar seeking missiles to counter the SAM and AA threat.  Afterwards a C-130 could deliver virtually unopposed.  The problem would be how to handle a land invasion if it came to it and that is NK's ace in the hole.  Hopefully, they will turn over their nuclear weapons and everything will be ok.  China is pushing for this so hopefully it will happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, I showed a couple of my co-workers and Joe (real smart guy) image googled "brass cone knife" and it appears the tool is a cork borer sharpener or maybe the actual borer.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, I'm pretty sure I have seen one of these before!  I can't remember what it was used for but let me look around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or possibly they are going to eat it.  No need to leave good food laying on the battlefield. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Old ladies and gay guys love me.  I also have to wear my wedding ring to the grocery store if my wife isn't with me to keep the single moms off me.  I never really noticed until my wife pointed it all out to me lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 07:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My cousin grew up in Michigan and married a military guy and now lives in Memphis as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 06:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your husband doesn't work in a steel mill does he? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 06:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I joined the military and spent 20 years traveling the world with my wife and kids.  I'm from Michigan and she is from Texas so now I'm retired and live in Texas.  Anyway, it would have been nice to stay by my parents but I had to get the hell out of there and go see some places.  I still don't want to move back there and don't ever plan to.  I have two brothers there and they can take care of my parents when they get old.  I'm about 80 miles from my wife's parents so she is happy to be close to them again but we are far enough away to not go there constantly.  I was fortunate to have grown up close to both sets of grandparents.  I have lots of fond memories of spending time with them and my kids will not have the same experience that I did and I do regret that part.  It is what it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just wanted you to know I downvoted you because you downvoted smiley faces.  Furthermore, I upvoted smiley faces to cancel out your downvote.  Have a nice day!!!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh look at the rich guy with a couch! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 21:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So if I changed my last name to Molester I could put the plates on my white van? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 05:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they are good then you won't  be able to tell.  You will have to set them up and ask a question you already know the answer to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 05:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the way to school on the bus I would imagine myself riding my dirt bike all the way there and back, hitting all the sweet jumps along the way and shredding nice manicured lawns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 04:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was like one of these kids smoking weed every day.  I've seen a lot of people ruin their lives and miss out on too many opportunities because they would rather get fucked up than grow up.  I was lucky and was able to get away from it but most of my old friends weren't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a red and blue flashing tail light.  Saw a guy here the other night and thought a cop had someone pulled over but it was a dude on a bike, saw him from way back in traffic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oops, that was auto correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Captain DePaul.  He graduated from West Point and this guy was hands down the best leader I have ever worked for.  It wasn't his raw brain power, like some kind of autistic savant or anything, but the way he could get a group of people to make things happen were something to behold.  He was never an asshole or never used his authority or wasn't manipulative in any way.  He was just the type of person that you wanted to give 100% to because he believed in you and was never disappointed if you couldn't deliver.  If you got stuck on whatever project he would get the right people to help you.  There is a saying that smart people surround themselves with people smarter than them and he had this down to a science.  He knew all of our strengths and weaknesses and knew how to get all of us to work together and get stuff done.  I haven't met anyone else like him before or since.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I joined the AF after high school back in 95 but I was never in shape to begin with.  They never made us exercise after basic training so I got fat.  I went in weighing 153lbs and blew up to 212 in about a year and a half.  Anyways, I'd be laying in my chair drinking beer and smoking, then every once in a while it felt like my heart skipped a beat.  That was my sign I was headed down the wrong path so I quit smoking and started mountain biking in 97.  Then around 2003 they started making us do PT and I was so glad I had stayed somewhat in shape on my own.  Now I'm retired from the AF and work with a bunch of old out of shape civilians with all kinds of health problems...I never want that to be me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call me old fashioned but try using your words and tell her how her behavior is not conducive to having a relationship and if this shit continues, your outta there.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean like make a new account all the time?  I'm too lazy and don't post enough about myself to personally identify me.  I've seen the Reddit info deal where you put your username in and it gives you all your stats and info you've ever fed Reddit and I'm not worried. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well hell, I know lots of people with a kettle then :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea same here, nobody I knew thought it was gonna stop being cool or anything and just go away.  I kept hearing about the information superhighway and ways it was going to improve our lives.  Email was nice for a while then ICQ came out and you could basically text back and forth with friends or family until texting with phones came around.  Now there are so many shitty apps out there it's hard to find a good one and also now we are drowning in ads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #2 with a coke at McDonalds...I'm easy

Edit:  number 2...never knew the pound sign (hashtag) made things bold lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds delicious!  Kung pow dog meat lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 85dB </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, why wasn't this on the list? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True that, also I don't grab hold of my entire dick like a damn fire hose.  More like pinch it on the nape so really just two fingertips actually touch it.  I'm more worried about touching the door handle on the way out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 17:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100 one dollar lottery tickets! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 17:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pocket $30k and turn the rest in, I could pay off my credit cards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 17:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use your brain to actually think about the problem and come up with a solution...beats "life hacks" every time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 17:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on the circumstances I suppose.  If it were for no apparent reason then of course I would want it over as soon as possible.  On the other hand, if they were going to kill my family if I tapped out, I would endure it for as long as it takes.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 17:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I go there before I read the article to see if it's worth my time to actually read It.  95% of the time I don't read it based on others comments.  If it interests me I'll read it and sometimes I'll find another news source to either corroborate or discredit the posted article.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 17:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure a kettle goes on a stove and it whistles when the water starts to boil.  Maybe the word kettle is getting us hung up here.  Do British people call anything that beats water a kettle or is it like I think and goes on a stovetop? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American here, I don't know anyone who owns a kettle.  My wife has an electric water heater deal that she uses to make tea with.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, you should do your neighbors a favor and shoot all the little yappy dogs that constantly bark.  Also you could practice your sniper shots on street lights at night.  Wouldn't recommend shooting at people or cars, the cops will get you.  Also birds are fun to shoot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The internet.  Everybody thought it would be cool to have all the information you ever wanted to know right at your fingertips.  All I see now are a bunch of lazy kids that don't want to do anything besides stare at a screen.  But maybe that's what my parents said of my generation watching too much TV.  Only time will tell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A couple inbound nukes from Montana would wreck that plan pretty quick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Montana would launch a few nukes from their silos and take out Hawaii just to be dicks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Montana, North Dakota and Wyoming would definitely wipe out the rest of the US with their nuclear missiles if it came down to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is something else that CAN help you.  So yesterday I prayed for you not to kill yourself.  Yes, I believe in God.  I'm not a "religious nut" but I really do believe that if you ask for forgiveness he will take care of you.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on my way to work but I stopped so I can talk to you about this.  So my friend Nick was caught up like you, from what it sounds like, trying to live up to other people's expectations.  It was too much for him to handle and he was looking for an easy way out by killing himself.  We talked it over and like I said earlier, his parents and school were stressing him out.  Do you really think your friends and family would rather have you dead than uneducated?  So Nick is now a truck driver and he loves it.  Who cares what other people think about you, it's your life to live and not theirs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They make a bunch of different ones now, maybe try something else...hell, smoke some weed if you need to.  I used to smoke a lot of weed and it didn't kill me...sounds like you have nothing to lose so consider that as well.  My friend Nick told me he wanted to kill himself so I lit one up and had a meaningful discussion about life in general.  He was under a lot of stress from his parents and school.  He moved out and dropped out of school but now he is happily married and still alive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 04:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you tried medication?  They have stuff that can help you feel better and you don't have to take it forever.  Do your parents care about you?  If so give me their phone number so I can call them so they can help you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 04:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, please don't kill yourself.  My friend Ross killed himself and I will never forgive him for doing that.  I'm gonna kick his ass in the afterlife when I get there.  But seriously, please tell your parents or school counselor that you are planning on hurting yourself.  Don't fuck around and pretend that what you are doing to yourself only affects you.  Think of all your friends and family that like having you around and who care for you.  Let's say you drink some peroxide, yea it burns your throats and now you have to be fed with a feeding tube.  Don't forget that you will be put in a hospital and on suicide watch where you won't be able to hurt yourself anymore which means you will probably be restrained on a gurney.  You will be strapped down and your throat will be fucked up for the rest of your life because your teenage hormones were getting your brain all fucked up.  Trust me, things will get better but it's going to take some time, it could be months or maybe a year or two but eventually you will feel better and be glad that you didn't do permanent damage to your body.  I usually don't write this much but I am hoping that you know that you need to get some help and don't drink that shit.  Go smash your finger with a hammer if you really need to feel some pain but then go get some help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 03:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta take a shit.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 13:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a few more...Voltron, StarCom, Go Bots (shitty transformers), He Man, She Ra, Rainbow Bright (you know you watched it) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 21:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would much rather lose my phone than experience a terror attack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "In this episode, Dave the Explorer takes a trip across the Rio Grande river!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give them a 10 gage shotgun like they use for goose hunting and problem solved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 23:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It reminds me that we are living on this planet together and our population will soon exceed 7.5 billion people.  Some estimate the Earth can sustain up to 10 billion but we won't know until we get there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 23:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This might help:  https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/A_Distant_Shore:_African_Americans_of_D-Day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 05:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for taking the time to lay it all out.  A lot of Americans just want to pull out and be done with it.  In your opinion what would happen if we just left and let things work themselves out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 03:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have one of those old fashioned wooden pants hangar deals.  It all gets thrown over that and I will rewear the clothes as necessary.  Mostly pants and shorts go on it and occasionally a shirt will get buried.  Every once in a while it gets too full so I just usually throw everything in the dirty laundry and start over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 02:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See this comment here everybody, this is how you have a debate.  Name calling and insults never help sway someone's opinion, only enforce their current stance.  Thank you u/gaspingFish for the input.  So we should abandon the Iraqi people to their fate and let ISIS take over or perhaps if we pull out they will all go home since virtually zero ISIS l are actually from Iraq?  http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/worldnews/islamic-state/11660487/Islamic-State-one-year-on-Where-do-its-fighters-come-from.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 01:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your reply, this is what I was looking for, someone to provide an actual counter argument as to why we should not send in more troops instead of the knee jerk name calling.  In addition to preventing more terrorist attacks I feel like we have unfinished business over there seeing how we stirred shit up to begin with.  It's like starting someone's house on fire and then driving away with the fire truck.  But then again maybe we need to cut our losses and let somebody else worry about it like you are saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you just say fuck it, let's pull out and let things work themselves out with ISIS?  Who cares if Americans are killed at home?  Why the fuck did you even join then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You would bet wrong, I spent 20 years in the military and watch as Obama took charge and ran us into the ground so yes, "OBAMA BAD". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What makes you think I'm too scared?  I have already retired from a full military career.  What have you done besides lay on your parents couch? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you rather ISIS attack us here on our own soil?  Because that is exactly what would happen if we just left them alone and pretended they didn't exist.  Downvote me all you want, it doesn't change the fact that there are people in this world that HATE Americans and want to kill as many of us as they can.  I would rather send our troops over to take ISIS apart than have ISIS over here any day of the week.  Our military is a 100% volunteer force and they are more than happy, chomping at the bit so to speak, to go over there and put an end to ISIS.  Obama was too much of a pussy to finish them and now Trump is going to take care of the problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh ok so they don't necessarily look like bath salts then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not actual bath salts you buy to use in your bathtub but the drug looks like them hence the name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Ingalls family from Little House On The Prarie.  Pa worked at the sawmill and ran a farm back in the olden days.  Ma took care of the kids like a good mother and also was the teacher at their school.  Mary went blind but that didn't stop her from becoming a teacher at the blind kid school.  Laura also became a teacher if I remember right.  Willie just faded away...he was adopted anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All great points, especially the last one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your relatives appreciate it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Diesel mechanics here  *fist bump* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are quite a few at the railroad where I work here in Ft Worth...maybe I'm just over exposed to rednecks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Don!  Remember when we graduated and everyone else gathered to throw their caps in the air and we both contemptuously walked off?  Good times! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm old...I was the ONLY kid in school that listened to death metal, nobody else knew what it was.  I wore a Napalm Death or Slayer shirt and camo pants most of the time.  I didn't really talk to anyone so I really don't know how the other kids viewed me until my senior year when I got into drugs and doing dumb shit.  I had friends in the next school over that I hung out with and we would tear shit up in our spare time.  They started going to jail so I joined the military and straightened out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tempelton is that you?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just described 95% of the people in Texas (females included) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm over 40 and don't want to/have time for video chat...mostly the first part.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did that too but now all I get are baby pics from my wife's cousin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.snopes.com/lesbian-ejected-nc-bathroom/

Back in 2015 it apparently happened once.  These might even have been mall cops for all we know.  My point is, whether or not a law is passed, it really doesn't matter 99% of the time...use whatever bathroom you want.  If you feel like pressing the issue, get arrested for using the "wrong" bathroom and see where the lawsuit ends up.  I'm sure there will be lawyers lined up by your side for some pro bono work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really, I break the law EVERY DAY (speed limit) and rarely get hassled by the man about it.  Even if they did make a law about this I'm pretty sure we are not going to have bathroom police and if a woman looks like a guy, they will be able to continue to use which ever bathroom they want to 99% of the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 16:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never say never...the earth will some day be consumed by the sun as it enlarges and I'm pretty sure there willl be no living humans on Earth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 16:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw you looking, Wayne New Jersey... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 15:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *meat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 15:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were both tight spaces. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 15:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just remember hearing some new elements were added fairly recently so I went and looked them up lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 13:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Incorrect, they were both tight spaces. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 13:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were both tight spaces </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 13:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes they were both tight spaces. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 13:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were both tight spaces </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> check this out:  http://www.b17queenofthesky.com/tailgun.htm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I can say is learn from other people's mistakes so you don't do the same thing.  My dad was a pretty bad alcoholic until I was about 13ish.  He sobered up but it was too late by that time for me and my brothers.  I broke the cycle and spend as much time with my kids as possible and rarely drink. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Railroad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ask him what Mc is (hint it was added last year) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 20:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always heard the little guy got put in there because of the small space.

Edit:  Many have pointed out that the ball turret gunner on the bottom of the aircraft was "the small guy".  The tail gunner position was also a tight space so that person would also need to be a small person...and not just a fuck up.  http://www.b17queenofthesky.com/tailgun.htm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 20:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My older kids knew the baby language of their younger brother, to me it was a bunch of jibberish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 20:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So he had someone shave his balls twice?  Lucky guy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 20:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dads truck can beat your dad! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 19:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fury was all fighting if I remember correctly.  The book goes into great detail about the logistics behind maintaining an armored unit.  I especially liked it because I recently retired from a maintenance career field in the Air Force.  I never had to wash the blood off a piece of equipment so the next guy using it wouldn't have second thoughts about what he was about to do, unlike the guys in the book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 19:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://writingexplained.org/mold-vs-mould-difference </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 19:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did a quick google search and recognized it: Death Traps by Belton Y. Cooper. Very good book! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 19:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did a quick google search and recognized it:  Death Traps by Belton Y. Cooper.   Very good book! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 18:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Old Abe is also on the back but very tiny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 18:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a book at home that is all about these guys that pulled the shot up tanks from the battlefield and had to patch them up for the next battle.  It's a very interesting side of the war that you never hear about.  Let me know if you want the title of the book and I'll reply when I get home later today.

Edit:  did a quick google search and recognized it: Death Traps by Belton Y. Cooper. Very good book! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 03:19:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell them straight to their face the thing that bothers you about them.  I worked with a guy who constantly bitched about everything so I callled him out.  He called me an asshole but after that he didn't bitch about stuff anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
