<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject381</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 02:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well when  group something for that long I think they have a pretty good reason to jeep it for themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 02:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey! North Carolina isn't very southern </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Time travel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 01:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 01:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Putin is bringing good change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there any more information on that? It sounds very entertaining </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Otto Von Bismarck, he didn't have complete control, but close enough. He sought to unify Germany though diplomacy not war, if possible. Anytime war was needed, he wanted it to be short and relatively un-damaging. He also initially didn't support taking colonies in Africa, once the Kaiser really wanted colonies Bismarck then supported them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Napoleon only ever declared war on Russia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see that due to no response, I have in fact, won this argument. Another victory for the Blackshirts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 05:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Evil does not exist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 03:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How to become them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Croatian* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you lie! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> User name is a meme. Go to r/eu4, eventually you'll find it.

Who ever said I like Trump, just because I say I am a fascist doesn't mean I like him. Trump is pretty useless, that doesn't mean that im going to "resist" his rule like many others are trying to do. You cant possibly get him to step down by protesting, in the current situation.

Who says Fascism is always racist? Most of the time it was, since that was the whole reason they rose in the first place. Before Italy joined the axis and/or surrendered to the allies (becoming a puppet of Germany), they were much less racist than than most other countries. When they invading Ethiopia in 1935, many of the Italian soldiers felt that they were freeing the Ethiopian slaves. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give me evidence of whenever Trump or Le pen is a fascist, please.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fascism is good. Even when you know, Le pen is not a damn fascist, nor is Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it was the USSRs idea on weapon manufacturing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
