<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2728</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Im so excited to watch the Raps in the playoffs i feel like a kid before christmas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 07:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 01:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one turned out to be true and was actually confirmed by Tarantino himself, he said that they are based in two different universes. So, when characters from reservoir dogs and pulp fiction went to watch a movie, kill bill and from dusk till dawn is what they would go watch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive heard theories about home alone like his fsther worked for the mob, as well as uncle frank set up the robbery  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what are your favorite movie fan theories? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Erik Spoelstra on Demar Defrozen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 08:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the best part of your day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 17:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im experiencing the exact same thing dnt know how to deal with it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 17:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow this is exactly how i feel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 08:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully ill be able yo say the same tbing one day  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 08:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 08:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Answering my own question i would say, "stop wishing you were older/looked older. Because before u know it 10 years have gone by and youll be reminiscing about your life right now, so just enjoy each and every moment as much as you can. Its not like u can go back to being a kid. Enjoy your youth" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could give your younger self (pick whatever age you would like) some advice, what would it be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 07:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 00:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol i was expecting this as top comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best drug to have sex on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 23:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This post was made two weeks ago, im sorry i spoiled a small part of the show for u but u should br smarter than to visit a californication subreddit that is obviously going to have many spoilers, im sure my post was not the only one, fucking relax. I do apologize but in a way its your fault for coming here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I repeat, dont visit this subreddit if u havent finished the show  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This subreddit is full of spoilers, dont read till your finished the show you fucking dunce. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus christ.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 06:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbh i dont really have expectations for anyone else on the team i just have a feeling. He could be a ross x2 i wasnt really sad seeing ross leave cause norm can do what he does but better (other than his shooting) but he can work on that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 05:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like hes one of those players that will all of a sudden becomes amazing one day, like CJ McCollum or something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much potential does Norman Powell have? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 05:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can really see Powell becoming at least an all-star in the future, what do you guys think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 06:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would lovr to see those photos, but has anyone commented on it or? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 06:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No way you wore this out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alex Jones: Master of Self Control </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 21:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 04:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a symptom of withdrawal but when i used to smoke marijuana heavily i would have the best deep sleeps, now after cutting down and only smoming once every two weeks or so ive noticed that i have so many dreams, while before i never had any. Also, its gotten very difficult for me to fall asleep for some reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 17:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wheres jason statham </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 20:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same dude, same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 20:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You messed up, I did not mistype 'my' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 20:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do not understand why you have repeated my question to me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 20:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If asked in an interview 'what is your biggest weakness?' What would be your answer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
