<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1863</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that scientists used to present their research to royal patrons instead of publishing journal articles, and receive gifts in return; the astronomer Tycho Brahe received exotic animals, an island and chemical secrets as well as cash </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 13:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 13:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a bit complicated to sum up in a line or two, but the scientist reports: 
 I used synthetic versions of the Azteca alarm pheromone chemicals to confirm the beetles were indeed using the alarm pheromone to find the ants, regardless of whether they were in my screened-in lab space or the center of a field of coffee. I set out various traps of parasitized, healthy or injured ants to see if the beetles would prey on only the parasitized ants (they did). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that coffee plants host a complex insect ecosystem where a specific beetle is attracted by pheromones to protect ants being attacked by flies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 13:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 13:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For most of us, moral responsibility for the harms of climate change gets diluted, thanks to the sheer scale of the problem. When I drive my car, take a vacation or keep my house warmer than I need, I contribute infinitesimally to climate change through my emissions, and so it is reasonable to think that my responsibility for the consequent harms is relatively minor. Indeed, this is precisely the feature that makes climate change such a massively difficult problem to solve.

This will not be true, however, for Donald Trump.  He has the power, as an individual, to undermine or protect U.S. environmental policy. And so he also bears the moral responsibility for the death and human suffering that may occur as a result.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dear Mr. Trump: Climate policy puts millions of lives and deaths in your hands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 13:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 13:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> August [2016] was the biggest month ever for U.S. gasoline consumption. Americans used a staggering 9.7 million barrels per day. Thats more than a gallon per day for every U.S. man, woman and child.

And before you chide my math, note that the author is converting from barrels in the second sentence to gallons in the third.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the US burns over a gallon of oil each day for every American man, woman and child </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 13:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 21:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I beg to differ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 21:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBH, I did think that 'legal tender for all debts' meant you really could pay for anything, not realizing this loophole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 13:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except you think those officers would not sympathize with the offenders and not the victims? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 13:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A business can reject cash even if it is "legal tender for all debts public and private."

... this statement means that the only circumstance when someone must accept the bill is when a person owes the business a debt. If no debt has been incurred, a person or business is not legally required to take U.S. currency.

And this is why airlines make you pay, with credit cards only, before they give you your drink
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that under US law, companies can refuse to take cash when they charge you before providing the product, but after you get it there's a debt, and they have to let you pay cash </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 13:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harvard University, striking dining hall workers reach agreement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 14:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gene therapy that manipulates neurons to reduce the desire to drink tested successfully in mice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 14:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Children's Hospital gets final approval to build expansion over garden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 13:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 13:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In an academic study of1516 adults: 
Nine fantasies were statistically unusual. Seven of these were rare in women. These included urinating on partner or being urinated on (reported by 3.5% of the sample), wearing clothes of the opposite gender (6.9%), forcing someone to have sex (10.8%), abusing a person who is drunk, asleep, or unconscious (10.8%), having sex with a prostitute (12.5%) and having sex with a women who has very small breasts (10.8%). 
 Interestingly, even among men, just four fantasies are less common: urinating on their partner (8.9%), being urinated on (10.0%), having sex with two other men (15.8%), or having sex with more than three other men (13.1%). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL more men fantasize about having sex with more than one other man than fantasize about a woman with small breasts, when asked by a scientific researcher </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 13:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Massachusetts Counts And Verifies Election Votes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 14:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 18:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harvard doesn't spend enough of that money, but they are actually pretty generous with financial aid if you're smart enough to get in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
