<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3240</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 00:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. So many people are surprised when I tell them because they'll know me for months without knowing I'm an atheist, and a big one at that. It's too annoying to be associated with the idiots on YouTube and in /r/atheism to bother. I just want everyone to believe what they believe and have a good time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 23:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Orange is The New Black, season 4, episodes 12 and 13. I didn't have any spoilers or forewarning that what was coming was going to happen so it absolutely davastated me. It felt like I'd lost a family member and I cried for probably 3 hours. I almost called out of work. Now, in hindsight, I'm not happy with how season 4 turned out at all, but fuck if that didn't still get me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 23:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I probably spend more energy arguing with asshole atheists who are bullying peaceful, religious people than I do getting mad at overly religious people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 20:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I wasn't so late to this thread because boy do I have some good ones living in Mormon occupied AZ. Lynnesy (pronounced like Lindsey) is easily one of the more annoying. A friend of mine knew a girl who was named Mary Christmas and I know probably 8 different ways to spell the name Kaitlin. (Katlynn, Kaytlin, Kaytlyn, Kaitlyn, etc.) But I think my favorite one has got to be the girl whose last name was 'Joy' and her first name was Tearsof. Tears of Joy. Like WHY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 06:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 05:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sunflower Houses, charcoal, 18" x 22" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 04:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
