<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2997</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I feel like one major thing that needs to change in the industry is relying on Nielsen data for ratings

Nielsen ratings are mostly used for pricing the sale of commercials, they're not the only factor any network considers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dafuq? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're reviewing the show before it's officially released you may not have the entire season to watch; this still applies to streaming services, which don't necessarily send reviewers the entire season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is Guggenheim relevant to this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're a plot device that breaks down if you put too much thought into it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soap opera nonsense is cheaper to make, so it can survive on lower ratings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/shield (it's on this sub's sidebar) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Not trying to be a dick

Yes you are </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's reportedly in the X-Men movie universe. Blink being played by a different actress makes sense because this is presumably not set in the future like DoFP.(anyway it's not like characters can't be recast). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Was that the character or the writing?

The writing makes the character, the two are not separable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  How am I not buying things with bitcoin?

I can exchange a guitar for dollars at a pawn shop and then use those dollars to buy things, that doesn't mean I'm buying those things with a guitar. This is the exact same principle (only much quicker). Those merchants are not accepting your bitcoin for their products, they're accepting dollars; that is a very important distinction as far as bitcoin's use as an actual currency is concerned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marvel Drama Pilot The Gifted From Matt Nix Gets Fox Series Order, First Teaser </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quantico is missing the "being wildly popular" aspect that Lost had, for starters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NBC's 'Taken' Renewed for Season 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Shift Card is just a convenient way to convert bitcoin to dollars, similarly with Purse you're just converting bitcoin to Amazon gift cards through a third party. In neither case are you actually buying things with the bitcoins themselves; the merchants are still getting paid in dollars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw lots of ads for it last season, fewer this season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Henao and Deignan would probably have been in the front group a lot longer if it wasn't for Landa's puncture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It probably won't go to Netflix, but you can subscribe to Starz directly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suspect inter-studio politics may have come into play, what with No Tomorrow being from CBS and the CW picking up Supergirl - an expensive WB show - at the last minute. It's possible that No Tomorrow was originally going to be slotted on Monday, where it's lead-in/lead-out would have been much lower but far more compatible, but it got bumped by Supergirl and so the CW gave it the Flash lead-in to compensate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  FWIW i think it would have made more sense to have Frequency air after the flash

It would have made way more sense; Frequency was far more compatible with The Flash than No Tomorrow was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well he does get paid... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Supergirl S2E20 "City of Lost Children" Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Synopsis:** When an alien attacks National City, Supergirl and the DEO learn the alien is a Phorian, an otherwise peaceful race with telekinetic powers. Guardian gets a lead on the Phorians address but instead of finding the culprit, he finds a very scared boy named Marcus (guest star Lonnie Chavis). Marcus will only trust James so it is up to Guardian to stop the attacks on the city. Rheas (Teri Hatcher) plan escalates.

Director: Ben Bray

Teleplay By: Gabriel Llanas   Anna Musky-Goldwyn

Story By: Robert Rovner

**Main Cast:**

* Melissa Benoist as Kara Zor-El / Kara Danvers / Supergirl
* Mehcad Brooks as James Olsen
* Chyler Leigh as Alex Danvers
* Jeremy Jordan as Winn Schott
* David Harewood as J'onn J'onzz / Hank Henshaw
* Chris Wood as Mon-El
* Floriana Lima as Maggie Sawyer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [She's already been cast in a CBS pilot](http://deadline.com/2017/03/peyton-list-cast-cbs-drama-pilot-mission-control-frequency-season-2-1202047472/), so if that gets picked up she still won't be available. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The CW sells hundreds of millions of dollars worth of ad space priced against Nielsen ratings, the idea that they wouldn't matter at all to the network is absurd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 75 episodes? That's about how long the CW tends to give its lower-rated veteran shows. Reign didn't bomb its first season like these did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well they're not keeping Reign, and The Originals has yet to be renewed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They always cancel at least one underperforming freshman show, this isn't really a change in behaviour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A hack? Not at all.

Wildly overrated by this sub? Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Colbert said "cock-holster" on CBS, which you're really not allowed to do. I'm pretty sure the whole purpose of the FCC is to stop people from cursing on TV.

FCC rules only prohibit profanity between 6am and 10pm, Colbert's show isn't on during that time. The question is whether Colbert's comment is considered "obscene" by FCC rules:

 For content to be ruled obscene, it must meet a three-pronged test established by the Supreme Court: It must appeal to an average person's prurient interest; depict or describe sexual conduct in a "patently offensive" way; and, taken as a whole, lack serious literary, artistic, political or scientific value.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would assume it's because of the transfer from Sardinia. In the recent past when the Giro has started in places like the Netherlands and Ireland they've done 3 days there then a rest/transfer day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 08:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AoS was sold into syndication months after it had been renewed for a 4th season which would bring it to 88 episodes, so the 88 episode threshold was in full effect there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Captain Kirk 2.0
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 03:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of all the shows to do musical episodes, OUAT probably makes the most sense. 

That said, I can't speak for the quality of this episode specifically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Realistically there are two types of sports: those that have a reputation for being dirty regarding PEDs (e.g. baseball, cycling, ...), and those that haven't made a serious attempt to uncover/stop PED use (e.g. basketball, football, soccer, ...). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has been, the threshold is ~88 episodes these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not only still being made, it's ABC's top-rated drama of the season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Usually less episode count means that they have a higher overall budget per episode

For broadcast shows not really; they mostly make money on a per-episode basis so their budgets are on a per-episode basis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OUAT looks to have at most one season left, but the other two are still going strong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Is it the ratings?

[It's the ratings](http://tvseriesfinale.com/tv-show/abc-tv-show-2016-2017-season-ratings/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're a plot device that the writers themselves didn't fully think through, so there's little point in trying to do so yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The show still gets better ratings than any other show on broadcast tv. Why would they reboot it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most shows hit their lowest ratings every year; TBBT still gets higher ratings than every other show on broadcast. As for being cancelled after next year, it's already been renewed for the next two years so that ain't happening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  and likely not earlier

Renewal/cancellation news typically comes out the week before upfronts at the latest; by next Friday we should know AoS's fate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's already been renewed for the next two years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No but there is [incorrectsupergirl.tumblr.com](https://incorrectsupergirl.tumblr.com/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only 4 ABC shows have been renewed so far (The Middle, Grey's Anatomy, Scandal, How to Get Away with Murder). They'll probably announce a mass renewal sometime next week, and if AoS isn't part of that then we should get extremely worried. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 08:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as the $$ keep coming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ABC Closes Deal to Revive American Idol </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then record it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, just adjusted up to a 2.5. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only person on earth who [insert one of the most popular opinions on the sub]?

No, you're never the only one.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's ratings have taken a pretty big hit this year, DiNozzo's departure is likely a significant factor in that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it really? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of paying customers watch GoT via streaming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This week's ratings:

TBBT: 2.5

NCIS: 1.5

So no, NCIS did not beat it this week.

Edit: TBBT adjusted up to a 2.5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And is still the highest rated show of the week </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're a poorly though out plot device, don't bother trying to find a consistent explanation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a broadcast network, their target audience is the general public not "television geeks". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  berry

... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 10:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, I would personally have loved if Fox had renewed the series for 5+ seasons. But what I might want and what actually made sense for Fox to do are not the same thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 08:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a fan of Firefly, I agree.

Now I can't condone Fox airing its episodes out of order, but honestly that probably wouldn't have mattered in the end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 06:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Emerald City cancelled (to no one's surprise). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Network upfronts are in less than two weeks, so this is the time when a lot of cancellation news will come out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rise   For God And Country Picked Up To Series By NBC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're talking about shows that ended 14   13 years ago bro... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But did spike have a soul?

By the end, yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's like Berlanti/DC have a pot of money and they keep spreading the money in it over all the shows. 

That's not how their budgets work. However replace 'money' with 'talent' and I think you may have a point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unrounded finals should be available at the beginning of next week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He got overwritten by our Barry, that's how changing the past typically works in time travel stories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adjustment: [0.5 and 1.358 million](http://www.showbuzzdaily.com/articles/showbuzzdailys-top-150-wednesday-cable-originals-network-finals-5-3-2017.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I am not sure if you CAN out-crazy Ollie.

Oh you can definitely out-crazy Ollie, just possibly not while being a CW protagonist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that's pretty much my feeling toward Mon-El. In a vacuum I'm largely indifferent to his character rather than actively disliking him, but I feel his inclusion to the show was unnecessary and has had a decidedly negative effect. Now he may be a symptom of what are IMO problematic changes to the show rather than the cause, but at the end of the day that doesn't really improve my view of him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it really a "decline" if you're pointing out something that has been the case since the beginning? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 0.5, not 0.50. We don't have unrounded numbers yet.

Bear in mind the CW was preempted in LA for baseball, so the final number will likely be lower than the prelims. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 09:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Heck, the main reason why the USA has Florida was because the Spanish needed money.

More that Spain had lost control of Florida's inhabitants (both the Seminoles and the British/American settlers) and it had been occupied by the American Army under Andrew Jackson.

Plenty of modern sovereign defaults have happened without the defaulting country having to sell off land to its creditors. Those sales typically happened due to geopolitical and/or  military reasons rather than financial ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 07:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the producers wanted to end it and HBO did not.

This is exactly why it's a perfect example: it's a case where we know the show is ending because the producers wanted to end it, not because the network wanted to end it (i.e. cancelled it). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 07:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Netflix is paying a fraction of what the show would make if it was aired on CBS.

And that's based on what? Netflix has paid quite a lot for other shows, and again this deal with Netflix is reportedly enough to cover the show's entire budget, which means that the show doesn't have to make that much for All Access to be profitable for CBS.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 06:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Was it an expensive space show?

No, but it also didn't have Netflix paying for international distribution rights in a deal that reportedly is enough to cover the show's entire budget (I would probably take with report with a grain of salt, but still). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 06:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't CBS All Access's only show, and they've already renewed their first original [scripted] show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Why the hell is the CW showing the Dodger game at 8pm Pacific?

Because your local CW affiliate can make more money showing that than Arrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The timing alone tell you that this was a cancellation. When shows actually end because of the producers plan and not the network cancelling them - which is rare, particularly on broadcast - it's known well in advance. This came months after the CW picked up the show for season 8 and well after production on the season had started. Compare that to shows that are actually ending on their own terms rather than being cancelled, where the news that the show is ending comes out when the season renewal is announced if not earlier (for example, we've know GoT will end after season 8 for a while now and season 7 hasn't even aired, and HBO is on record saying they would have liked more episodes if the producers had been willing to continue). Plus if there was ever a time for TVD to naturally end it would have been after the lead actress left.

Networks are all about their PR and will do everything to avoid actually saying that a show was cancelled. But it's not hard to see through their spin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [It was cancelled](http://tvline.com/2016/07/23/the-vampire-diaries-cancelled-season-8-ending/), the CW just made the decision before the season aired as opposed to during/after. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Series regulars still get credited even when they're not in an episode, so that doesn't mean they'll show up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They don't cancel your shows after one season. Heck, they barely cancel shows at all.

This season the CW is nearly certain to cancel two of their three freshman series, and have already cancelled two of their veteran series.

Edit: the CW has cancelled at least one freshman show literally every season of its existence (a trend which will continue with the inevitable cancellations of Frequency and No Tomorrow within a few weeks). But sure, go ahead and think they cancel shows after one season... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  you can add up the percentages to 10% in that day

Which is utterly meaningless. You need to learn how to do basic math with percentages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You fail at basic algebra regarding percentages... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You're telling me that's wrong?

Saying you made a 10% return when you had $100 in profit off of $6000 invested is wrong, yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A poorly developed plot device </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ABC is holding off on renew/cancel news on everything that wasn't already renewed months ago, it's not just an AoS thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But does that count in the live or +6 ratings?

No. But it still gets counted; networks/studios looks at all sources of revenue, not just ad sales. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then get Hulu's ad-free service... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Colbert has made a very similar joke in the past featuring himself as one of the parties. The implied homosexuality is not what what makes the joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 09:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were no "temporary writers", season 2 was just cut short by the strike.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 05:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where is this happening? The earliest comments in this subs live episode discussion are just three hours old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But is the joke even homophobic? The implied homosexuality isn't what makes the joke/insult work; Colbert has made similar jokes in the past featuring himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  How many people work at the DEO? How many have quit in the 2 years since Kara began working there? Kara is not being too careful with her secret identity.

The DEO has known her identity for years, her being careful doesn't matter there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Is he still using it canonically but the we are seeing Tom Cavanagh for the sake of not using another actor?

Yes. He set it so that team Flash still see him as Wells, we're seeing him from their perspective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bear in mind that's one step for a speedster, which may well be longer than ten steps for a regular person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flash and Arrow took the same hiatus and didn't have a big ratings dropoff (Flash was even up from the episode before the break). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 03:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Five years ago Colbert referred to Trump as his [Colbert's] "future scrotum holster" after offering to 'dip his balls in Trump's mouth'. This sort of joke is nothing new for him, and it's not going to get him fired. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 02:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could definitely believe that the show's insistence on being political (and it's lack of subtlety in doing so) is driving viewers away; I find it annoying and I'm not even conservative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 02:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 02:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Its not really speculation as it is trend observation

To observe a tend you need data. What data are you using to draw these conclusions? Specifically, what data allows you to conclude that Supergirl has fewer online viewers than Arrow, when as of the last two weeks they have similar L+SD numbers? (And this is still inductive reasoning, not deductive reasoning).

Your second paragraph is full of tons of assumptions with little backing them up, and no data whatsoever. For instance, how do you know that Supergirl viewers "prefer binging or watching it live" compared to Arrow viewers? That is 100% speculation. Or, by what metric have you determined that Supergirl's fandom is smaller than Arrow's? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not legally </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over the air, with an antenna. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or the time he offered to dip his balls in Trump's mouth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
