<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3901</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 15:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Von einem Ghost in the Shell-Film erwarte ich aber deutlich mehr als "guter Durchschnitt". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 15:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **[Genau diese Frage wird hier aufgegriffen](https://youtu.be/JR_yLANQDL0?t=10m22s)** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 14:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Die Bayern stehen mit 13 Feiertagen sowieso schon an der Spitze. Eine bayerische bzw. schwbische Stadt ist sogar noch privilegierter, wenn es um Feiertage geht - Augsburg hat sogar 14 Feiertage im Jahr. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 13:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Die [Grokonzerne](https://de.wikipedia.org/wiki/DAX#Zusammensetzung) der Bundesrepublik Deutschland, denen wir uns zugehrig fhlen sollen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 11:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wir sind echt *reich*, Mann.

*Gut* ist eine andere Dskussion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 11:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wirtschaftskraft pro Kopf wre noch interessanter (ich finde fast alle Statistiken interessanter *per capita* - vor allem **[diese her](https://twitter.com/ChrisOffner3D/status/848268815335120896)**). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 10:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ich wre dafr! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wirtschaftskraft: Wenn Bundeslnder Staaten wren </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 09:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 15:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 15:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **[NEW PLAN](https://www.reddit.com/r/de/comments/62skrb/meine_damen_und_herren_mesdames_et_messiers_der/)**

Anyone who wants to extend the German flag, **do so to the right of the french flag!**

But leave our French friends' flag in peace! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 15:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **[Vorschlag!](https://www.reddit.com/r/de/comments/62skrb/meine_damen_und_herren_mesdames_et_messiers_der/)**

An alle, die die deutsche Flagge erweitern wollen - **macht rechts von der franzsischen weiter!**

Aber lasst die Flagge unserer franzsischen Freunde heil! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 15:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guter Plan! An alle, die die deutsche Flagge erweitern wollen - **macht rechts von der franzsischen weiter!**

Aber lasst die Flagge unserer franzsischen Freunde heil! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 15:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ich bin dafr! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 14:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man kann ja die Usernames checken, wenn man auf Pixel klickt - und da sehe ich leider schon einige deutsche Accounts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 14:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Momentan hat der Schutz unserer Freunde und Nachbarn aber Vorrang.

Eine Deutschlandflagge, die Frankreich berrennt, will ich auch nicht sauberhalten und einrahmen. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 14:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Verstehe ich auch nicht.

Leute, ich will die deutsche Flagge schwarz umrahmen und sauber halten! Aber wenn Ihr so weitermacht, muss ich weiterhin meine Pixel in Blau verwenden, um die franzsische Flagge zu schtzen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 14:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **[Respektiert unsere Freunde und Nachbarn!](https://www.reddit.com/r/de/comments/62seza/new_goal_germany_3_france_on_rplace_lasst_uns_die/)** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 14:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. I propose **[this](https://www.reddit.com/r/de/comments/62seza/new_goal_germany_3_france_on_rplace_lasst_uns_die/)**! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 14:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm one of the krauts and I'll help defend the French flag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 14:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, fr Operation Europa zwischen unseren Flaggen mag es in der Tat zu spt sein.

Plannderung: https://www.reddit.com/r/de/comments/62seza/new_goal_germany_3_france_on_rplace_lasst_uns_die/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 14:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm afraid you're right.

But this is still an attainable vision: https://www.reddit.com/r/de/comments/62seza/new_goal_germany_3_france_on_rplace_lasst_uns_die/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New goal: GERMANY 3 FRANCE on /r/place Lasst uns die Flagge unserer Nachbarn auf unsere Hhe angleichen und sie schtzen. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 14:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 14:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ich pldiere fr **[Operation Europa](https://www.reddit.com/r/de/comments/62sa8l/bedroht_nicht_unsere_europ%C3%A4ischen_freunde_aufruf/)** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 14:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calling for **[Operation Europe](https://i.imgur.com/KIBwrcG.jpg)**!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 13:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had the same idea: https://www.reddit.com/r/de/comments/62sa8l/bedroht_nicht_unsere_europ%C3%A4ischen_freunde_aufruf/

Could have saved myself some Photoshopping if I'd seen your post. ;)

I'm in! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 13:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deswegen rufe ich auf zur **[Operation Europa](https://www.reddit.com/r/de/comments/62sa8l/bedroht_nicht_unsere_europ%C3%A4ischen_freunde_aufruf/)**! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We must not be enemies but friends! Calling for operation Europe in /r/place </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 13:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bedroht nicht unsere europischen Freunde! Aufruf zur OPERATION EUROPA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 13:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 12:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not that they're a video platform but **[Medium is trying to get away from advertisers as well](https://blog.medium.com/upgrade-your-medium-924b74c36552#.45sp0bwqf)**:

Media is broken. And we need to fix it.

 Its simple. Corporate advertising budgets become the primary funders of our information providers. No matter how skilled or well-intentioned, ad-driven publishers are rewarded on their ability to capture attention and even, at times, to weave a particular corporate-driven narrative. Not to provide informed perspectives, be thorough, or even be factually correct. But to capture attention. As cheaply as possible. For a few fleeting seconds. Click, click, scroll

There is no way to fix this dynamic until we demand better  and decide to pay for it. We need a system that funds stories and ideas not just based on their ability to attract attention, but on their value to readers.

I've long said that an ad-revenue-based internet may be convenient but also super dangerous and volatile. If you're not paying, you're the product. And it's true. The customers are the corporations paying for advertising. Your eyeballs and attention are the product being sold to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philosophy Tube: 1984   Language </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 09:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 08:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is that these big studios set the industry standards. And freelancers as well as small studios who interact and collaborate with them obviously need to have Maya licenses as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Autodesk is not the only game in town there are bigger and better out there.

Better ones is arguable but bigger ones certainly not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 11:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely! That's what I'm doing. I'm switching to Blender and Houdini. Won't happen overnight, but within the next couple of years I plan to be entirely Autodesk-free.

I don't expect this petition to change Autodesk's policy but I do think it helps 3D artists know they're not alone in feeling pissed off and exploited. Start a conversation in the industry, and maybe develop a sense of solidarity - which the VFX industry could really use.

Signing this petition was literally the least I could do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 11:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  
 I admire people who make individual contributions to these issues. However, we can really only make a difference by shifting the way things are done at power centers.

The pressure on these power centres can only reach critical mass once enough people have changed their lifestyle to be more in accordance with those pressures. You won't get industrial farming outlawed in a society whose lifestyle and culture is deeply tied to industrial farming.

We need to *practice* sustainability. Practice as in *train*. It's not a simple binary switch you can turn once you've read a paper on an issue and change your minds. People are animals of habit. We need to change those habits, change the culture - in ourselves, and with it, in our environment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 10:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They also claimed they had **[no plans to remove maintenance subscription](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/C6dhltAWYAAGnlL.jpg:large)** only last September - and now they're actively trying to force people into subscription and giving up(!!!) their perpetual license. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 10:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Danke! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 08:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bei welcher Bank bist Du? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 08:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt Autodesk will respect it - but at the very least they cannot claim that "Nobody cares. People love our price increases and us fucking them over."

**[Ggreg Leuenberger's rant](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sN4GAScoPM0 t=44m35s)** on their new policy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you're pissed off with Autodesk trying to force people off permanent licenses with price increases, sign this petition </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 08:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 08:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt Autodesk will respect it - but at the very least they cannot claim that "Nobody cares. People love our price increases and us fucking them over."

**[Ggreg Leuenberger's rant](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sN4GAScoPM0 t=44m35s)** on their new policy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you're pissed off with Autodesk trying to force people off permanent licenses with price increases, sign this petition </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 08:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 08:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt Autodesk will respect it - but at the very least they cannot claim that "Nobody cares. People love our price increases and us fucking them over."

**[Ggreg Leuenberger's rant](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sN4GAScoPM0 t=44m35s)** on their new policy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you're pissed off with Autodesk trying to force people off permanent licenses with price increases, sign this petition </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 08:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 08:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not my tutorial, no. I'm not Kent Trammell. :)

But I look forward to working through this myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/blackmirror  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Modeling Realistic Characters with Blender </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 21:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Modeling Realistic Characters with Blender </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 21:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Modeling Realistic Characters with Blender </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 21:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Modeling Realistic Characters with Blender </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 21:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gore isn't jabbing at Musk but at Musk fanboys who ignore what Musk says about having to save Earth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your comment is a literal copy of a Vimeo comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this a prank? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The legend of the goat who knew the true meaning of the mountain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The legend of the goat who knew the true meaning of the mountain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 12:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 10:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't say I'm a fan of the personality cult surrounding him but Musk never claimed that Mars would be a *replacement* for Earth.

In fact he emphasized the very opposite. It's other lazy people who don't want to have to change anything about the current system and their habits who continually claim that we don't need to worry because we'll all just chill on Mars once Earth is fully uninhabitable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 10:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm all for space exploration and Mars colonies - but **not** at a *replacement* for Earth! For fuck's sake.

Earth is fucking amazing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **[Relevant song for the German-speakers here.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XTPGpBBwt1w)** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The world doesn't care about right or wrong. It's all about power. And right now, none of us have it."

 - Adam Jensen, Deus Ex: Human Revolution </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are some hard-wired human tendencies in human evolutionary psychology. Things like degrees of tribalism, racism, immediate self-preservation. They *can* be counter-acted culturally, but that takes conscious effort - just like reigning in one's anger and impulse for violence when one is attacked or threatened, etc.

Even bushmen resort to greed and exploitation very quickly once they find themselves in a situation where resources are (or appear) scarce.

I maintain that it's naive to dissociate humanity and human biology from any responsibility for the systems we created. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No doubt about that.

But still, it's obviously not what they feel like, and what they want to hear. Thus, Brexit and Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **[Buy it for only $125](https://www.condenaststore.com/-sp/Yes-the-planet-got-destroyed-But-for-a-beautiful-moment-in-time-we-created-a-lot-of-value-for-sh-Prints_i9318014_.htm)** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And where did this specific environment emerge from?

If humans, in great masses and over generations and centuries, didn't create this environment, and all its 'unnatural' systems, mechanisms and paradigms, out of their own nature (as well as out of a lack of foresight and perspective equally caused by the limitations of human nature, for example as it relates to one's ability to intuitively grasp complex global systems and opaque chains of causality and interrelations) - where did capitalism come from?

I think this is a romanticised view of humanity. **[Chomsky notes](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fFXNnA3KqzA)** how Marx bases some of his theory on the assumption that humans are perfectly malleable beings that are virtually 100% *nurture* (versus 0% *nature*) - which isn't really in line with modern science anymore.

Capitalism, in my view, is a manifestation of some natural human traits being given way too much leeway instead of being constrained to a healthy degree - and other human traits not being fostered and encouraged enough.

As Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn put it:

Gradually it was disclosed to me that the line separating good and evil passes not through states, nor between classes, nor between political parties either -- but right through every human heart -- and through all human hearts. This line shifts. Inside us, it oscillates with the years. And even within hearts overwhelmed by evil, one small bridgehead of good is retained. And even in the best of all hearts, there remains ... an unuprooted small corner of evil. 

I think it's important to remain conscious that we're all susceptible to the urges of greed, tribalism, etc. Because, as Lord Acton notes:

**Power tends to corrupt, and absolute power corrupts absolutely.** Great men are almost always bad men, even when they exercise influence and not authority, still more when you superadd the tendency or the certainty of corruption by authority. There is no worse heresy than that the office sanctifies the holder of it.

Which is why it's so important to decentralise power as much as possible. Thinking there are *good guys* and *bad guys*, and that everything will be fine if only the *good guys* hold the power, is a fallacy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blender Market: What Problem Are You Solving? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course, but the baby boomer generation has exacerbated capitalism into overdrive - and is now in control of most capital.

Capitalism is not some magic artifact descended from the heavens, it's a system invented and implemented by people.

So the problem, at its very core, has to lie in some human traits - some parts of our [evolutionary psychology](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Evolutionary_psychology) that evolved for a different environment than the one we find ourselves in today, and therefore lead to disastrous large-scale problems if left unchecked.

As I said [elsewhere on Reddit](https://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/comments/60awnh/cmv_a_higher_intelligence_doesnt_make_someones/df4ysxi/?context=10000):
This isn't about a simple black-and-white "people are inherently good and civilised" vs. "people are inherently violent and cruel" argument. Both of those statements are utterly reductive and unhelpful.

My premise is that rape and murder **(or, as in this /r/latestagecapitalism context, greed and exploitation)** are behaviours that occurred naturally in humans since the beginning of the species. And probably at no time in history has there been less rape and murder than today (even though there is still way too much), thanks to our collective cultural efforts to counter people's natural impulsive behaviours when they are too harmful.

Just because something is 'natural' doesn't automatically mean it's constructive, sustainable or helpful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 11:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I highly recommend the entire podcast. A lot of great points in there.

Some of it also ties in with this here: https://www.reddit.com/r/LateStageCapitalism/comments/5twa7e/bo_burnhamit_got_completely_commodified_and/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bo Burnham:"The big fucking joke right now is 'poor straight white guys'. But if you're a twenty-three year old white guy right now with $100,000 in debt and no job prospects coming up, and you are told you are privileged - you want to fucking kill somebody!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 11:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 10:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think your analogy is flawed.

A film that (in my view) sucks for the first 90 minutes remains an unenjoyable film even in the unlikely event that it suddenly became *amazing* after those 90 minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
