<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3288</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anybody worried about a 60 buck price tag? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, the game looks badass and it seems to add some cools tuff, but in my ignorant eyes it has the feel of an expansion, not a fully fledged sequel to warhammer 2, and that is how I feel CA sees the game too. I`m not sure that a games that more or less just expands on warhammer 2 qualifies as a proper sequal that begets a full game price tag.
Just my thoughts. Hyoed to the max about the game.
Rome 1 and Shogun 2 were proper sequals, this is not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 20:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) I see what you did there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need some high res wallpapers from the trailer like this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just hope that all land battles won`t be in those open spaces we saw, I would like for the jungle to be very prevalent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Multiple armies fighting on a map is not new, but 3 different armies all fighting eachother would be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 53 minutes to go!

Also, will the twitch stream and youtube stream show the same content, or will I have to follow both streams? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 08:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, and that`s the only way for another empire or a victorian total war game to go, enitire world or not at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the throne on Dragonstone, the targaryens built the fort. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Dany makes it herself, don`t feel like a Stannis thing. Then again, it was the ancient seat of the targaryens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda true, but then warhammer was always ment to be a trilogy that would likely be released back to back. There is no sense in releasing a historical game in between warhammer, that would just divide their playerbase and end up competing with themselves. They ill release warhammer 2 and 3 before the next historical game. But it seems we will get dlc and new content for the older historical games, so I can wait. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shamefully raises hand...

But honestly, their dlc is pretty sneaky, but still pretty decent. Game should recieve WAY more free lc though. I`m a massive warhammer fans so that is why I by everyhting they throw at me (and the fact that I got the main warhammer game for free from afriend, so I don`t mind spending some money on dlc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, the above link is the best site I have found, and most of the book is still missing. Maybe of you get lucky like me you can find it used somewhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, but It still a cool game, as long as they don`t dumb down the historical games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are there noises now?
Edit: neat, just what I wanted and proposed a few days ago. Noices make everything better.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see your Leo Major, and raise you Jack Churchill.

Bloody bagpiping, sword wielding, bowshooting madman.

Some of the shit he did and said:
Churchill gave the signal to attack by cutting down the enemy Feldwebel (staff sergeant) with a barbed arrow, becoming the only British soldier known to have felled an enemy with a longbow in the war

 he is known for the motto: "Any officer who goes into action without his sword is improperly dressed."

As the ramps fell on the first landing craft, Churchill leapt forward from his position playing "March of the Cameron Men"[17] on his bagpipes, before throwing a grenade and running into battle in the bay.

As the Pacific War was still on, Churchill was sent to Burma,[12] where some of the largest land battles against Japan were being fought. By the time Churchill reached India, Hiroshima and Nagasaki had been bombed and the war ended. Churchill was said to be unhappy with the sudden end of the war, saying: "If it wasn't for those damn Yanks, we could have kept the war going another 10 years!"[12] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks good!
But sound could use some improvement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope the pc doesn`t crash again this time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 16:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I though so as well untill he died in the chaos campaign video, got killed by that bird dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 16:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somone should make a coffe-table lore book for fantasy warhammer and includ this images. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 12:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THey should go back to the way they did in bc2, every map was free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 12:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better give us tons of free stuff like they used to back in bc2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 11:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok maybe not many names but untill I see the map Rockstar announces I`m gonna call it fake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How u know they got the same source? And yes, bs release dates are common, but we have nothing else to grasp at right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course it is, but we have nothing else to grasp at. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The leak came in April 2016, and Mafia 3 was revealed in 2015.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like it could be true, multiple game sites have states a late septemer-realy october release date.
Here is a british site: 
http://tech.firstpost.com/gaming/red-dead-redemption-2-release-date-might-have-been-leaked-by-uk-retailer-368863.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 12:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Need the flag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 10:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1.Many of the names, including "New bordeaux" are taken from Mafia 3.
2. I have a hard time believing that Rockstar would mess up and let the entire game map get "leaked" years before the game is released.
3. Rockstar themselves said the game would be set in the american "heartland", and this map is nowhere near the hearthland, but east.
4. I refuse to believe Rockstar would be so lazy as to cope big parts of the rdr 1 map into the new one, I think they will create an entierly new map.
Just my thoughts,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still think the "leaked" map is fake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 15:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha, typ, should of course be donkey. Or Mule, whatever it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 11:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually kinda liked it. Playing online and getting into some trouble, just to watch my donkey run away from me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GTA is badass, and altough I think some of the features should remain a gta only thing, that doesn`t do anything to the fact that it is one of the best games out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone believe that a major part of the story will include an oil company trying to intrude on native american land to get the the oil, and the conflict that ensues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes we are. Rockstars own statement about the game being set in the american "heartland" wouldn`t make any sense if they decide to reuse 1/3 of the old rdr map. Also, imo, I don`t think Rockstar want to be that lazy and retread old ground. We want something new, to explore new ares of their wonderfull world and they now it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 10:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first reveal of a Rockstar game is usually just a tease, the next reveal is more informative and usually a 2 minute + trailer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 10:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can only hope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CA announced last week that they have a team working on more dlc/standalone content for the older historical games, so it seems us history fans will get some love before the next major historical game is released. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
