<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject322</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They won't though.

Between 8Am-12PM eat are prime reddit hours. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 06:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man. You gotta repost this during peek hours tomorrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 06:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man. You gotta repost this during peek hours tomorrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The TLV thing is so true. I'm level 18 with them and people love se </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The One Self Help Group We'd Actually Join - People Watching #7 (this hits close too home) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. "Possible" whereas before, I could just pay real money and get what I want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't a raise structure. This is like, if they said "Everyone who completes these goals while at work, gets a bonus. If you already completed the goals, you get no reward." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You get 20 shards out of a common shard drop, and 100 from a duplicate epic skin. (Epic skins cost 400.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Cap is awful, but makes sense from a Busniess point of view. But I still want all of my hero specific and epic boxes. I earned them didn't I? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean. If you take those away from us, the ones that gives us the best chance of our favourite stuff, that's a huge punishment. Fine, I get not giving us 600 Common loot boxes, that'd just give us everything we want and all the shards we need. 

But the ten or so epics we earned? Common Blizzard. I've paid hundereds of dollars into this game in the old system. (Which I prefer to RNGesus' temple of worship you've change the shop into) I would really like to get what my effort equals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trust me. It's not. 

I'd rather buy the skins than pray to RNGus to get them. The amount of content this game has makes it impossible to dependably get the thing you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/heroesofthestorm/comments/628g9f/new_skins_on_the_new_server/

Here's a complete list without pictures </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/heroesofthestorm/comments/628g9f/new_skins_on_the_new_server/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New skins on the new server </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 05:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol fair. 

I made another buddy on here too.(He saw us talking and wants me to wing man for him haha) Three of us can do a mini reddit meet up if you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah I think that might not go over super well. Which is unfortunate that so many terrible groups have come to associate white pride with racism. I hope BLM doesn't do that to black pride. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pride, though mainly about the LGBT community, is about everyone getting together and supporting everyone. Pride in who and what you are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 23:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will you spot me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Groovy.

How old are you btw? Before I suggest bringing someone underaged drinking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People are being shitty too you about your 40,000 things at once comment and I don't get the hate. Haha

Love this sub, thanks for moderating it.

(Also, what do you mean by xposting? And what's the rule?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah night vision wigs me out.

So, details about me. I'm a dude, 26. Raging geek, awesome wingman. Super good with the ladies. Or dudes. Depending on what you're into. Not judging. Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's a horrifying picture.

Sure lets hang.

I live near Spadina Subway station in the Annex.

Board games or beer? OR both? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 01:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love that site </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came here to mention the same thing. Venom nerds unite. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, as far as I recall it was her popping out from behind a pillar when Colleen and Danny were fighting the two main guards in china and smacking one with those claw dohickies.

Then she smacked an army guy from behind when they attacked the dojo that one time? She never seemed particularly competent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some iconic villain logos much like Venom? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly think Venom might have THE most Iconic logo for a villain, but off the top of my head I can also think of Hydra for Marvel and, Bizzaro and Sinestro from DC and not much else.

Who do you think has an iconic logo that stands on the wrong side of the law? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like I mentioned before Banshee is great against a dive comp. It ruins Illidans, greymane and butchers day.

But by and large Hyperion is the answer. Especially if they have aoe they can use to blow banshee up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 09:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try two or three quick matches with the lane bully ideal in mind. Oh, also don't auto attack the enemy minions or use inspire. If your guys make it too his wall he can safely soak xp from them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 05:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, was looking back at some old threads. How's your raynor game these days? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Last panel of the most recent moon girl comic, there's a Dragon Radar. I love when they put little easter eggs like this in things. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 03:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 06:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ability to give sage advice for everyone's problems no matter the type, while slowly being unable to get his own life together as it all falls apart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 07:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm plat. We could make the stream into a coaching one if you like </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 06:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ultra originally belonged to Zag, so it doesn't need to be psychic haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 05:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My experience with video editing is null.

I'm still getting my sea legs as far as streaming goes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Downvote this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to get into streaming, but I also want to give back to the community, with that in mind I don't want to stream my games. I want to stream YOURS! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to get this to use in DnD campaigns, as a base of sorts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There is a dragon age: Inquisition save editor, but it doesn't work with my saves? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys. So some fine folks at r/Piracy. That is to say, here. Pointed another fellow towards this thread

https://www.reddit.com/r/Piracy/comments/4f1hwr/dragon_age_inquisition_save_game_import/

I downloaded it. And I found my save data (Which is stored in my onedrive folder for some reason) and it just stays blank. Like. I pick the save data, and nothing changes. 

This thread is sadly over a year old. Does anyone have any insight by chance?

Like maybe the original linker /u/TryHardFapHarder would know? Is that how you tag people? u/TryHardFapHarder

One of those two must work. Haha

But if anyone else has any insight, that'd be wonderful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hearthstone Heroes of Korpulu

And it releases a bunch of StarCraft themed cards.

Hearthstone. Heroes of sanctuary. 

Diablo themed cards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 01:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly. I'm on your side.

You put all the effort into organizing this team, you gathered them together. If it wasn't for you they'd probably not have even joined chairleauge.

If they wanted to replace you? Thats shitty. But they have the right to pack up and leave.

You started this team because you wanted to play. You out the effort in so you could play and practice.

It'd be like if you made a baseball diamond for a big game and people decided you weren't allowed to play on it for the big game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck that shit. If I was in a band I'd wear that shirt all the time.

"Why's my shirt say Donkey Cunt Punch you ask? Well. Lemme tell you" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One question I'd love to get an answer too, is will StarCraft players ever get a reward like a mount in heroes of the storm just for playing the game?

Hearthstone has their card back for winning 100 games
WoW has Ironside for reaching level 100
And Diablo 3 has Maelthels Phantom for reaching level 70 with a seasonal character
I know some people argue we have void speeder, but thats for preordering and spending more money. Not playing the game we already love.

I was wondering if there's ever be a reward like a zerfling mount, (Or and overlord designed o be sat on like the treasure goblin) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can answer the second half.

Specialists were good at lane clearing and PvE, but thats just because of the ones released. The real point of the specialist role, is to put the characters that are too weird to fit elsewhere.

Without it, you'd probably squeeze then into a variety of other roles but they'd not quite fit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm not good enough to balance Probius, but here's a fun idea for resource management. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, something people always talk about is how Blizzard hasn't quite nailed the fantasy of Probius. I kind of agree. As much as I love the character, the abilities are lacking.

But I'm not here to talk about that. I'm here to talk about his mana. We've got a bunch if unique mana elements in game so far, and I'd like to give Probius one.

Make it so that whenever Probius is near an enemy minion, hero or structure or ally hero or structure, they drop minerals. Enemy heroes dropping gold minerals.

Then make all of his abilities cost minerals instead of mana, so you spend everyfight running around gathering minerals.

I'd also like to see his auto attack removed, and replaced with either an extra cannon, or a gateway that behaves kinda like a misha. Spawning a single Zealot (at the cost of some minerals) that will behave as his auto attack.

Maybe you could talent into it at 13 or 16 to get a second zealot, or a sentry, or a stalker.

But the main point of this post is minerals for mana.I think running around the battlefield gather minerals while everyone is fighting would a lot of fun!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be honest, the fact that you're working on loosing weight would keep me around too. But maybe for different reasons. I don't mind gals on the bigger side anyway, but just knowing they are working hard to improve themselves is one of the biggest turn ons. I've been surrounded by people all my life who complain and never take action. 

So you pushing yourself? You seeing something you don't like about yourself and changing it? That's an amazing and beautiful thing about you! Even if it's the long game, and taking you a long time, or you have set backs, the fact you keep trying to improve it is seriously an awesome trait to have in a partner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being tall.

"Oooh a love a man who is six feet!"
"Nah I don't need any help, I can get that myself" You say as you reach to the top shelf where the employee needed a step stool just so they could stretch and maybe almost knock it down with their finger tips.

BUT

Houses are not built for us.
Or cars. Straight up. If you ever go on a drive more than 20 minutes with a tall person, give them shotgun so they can push the seat back. PLEASE.
Or public transit. If you ever see a man, sitting kinda sideways so he's sorta taking up two seats worth of space he almost certainly is not doing it to be a dick and if you try to sit next to him he'll straighten out. But just know you're condeming him to smacking his knees against the hard metal/plastic of the seats in front of you. (And the reason he doesn't just stand is because he's got to bend down so as not to hit the ceiling for every bump in the road.)

You will always be called on to get that high thing off the shelf, even though you're relaxed and doing what ever in another room. "It's just easier for you to grab it than for me to get the step stool out and use that."

And pants. DEAR GOD THE PANTS. Good fucking luck finding anything with longer than a 32 leg but still reasonably fitted for your waist.

Shirts are also difficult. The "Big and tall" shop is quite literal. It's not Big OR Tall. No. You get something with the right sleeve and torso length and then you realize it looks like you're wearing an elephant's discarded skin for how baggy it is on you. But lord help you if you shop in the regular person's section. Looks like a regular person shopping in the kids section.

And honestly I could go on and on. But I'll let other tall folks respond with their own issues.

I wouldn't trade being tall, for being average. But there are way more cons than pros. (It's just one of the few things that makes me feel special.)

STORY TIME: I was short until junior high, where I grew from like 5'4 to 6'3 over the course of like, grade 8-9. GROWING PAINS SUCK! It's literally your bones growing faster than your muscles and RIPPING THEM TO FIT. 

But that's not the story. The story is funnier. I was not used to being GIANT so I would constantly walk into street signs that I used to be able to walk under. Just like. For a year and half. Constantly walking into them, because they were "just" above eye level for me. But not forehead level. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 13:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're in Marvelstudios. I assumed it was implicit that I was talking about a marvel studios version of the fantastic four </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 13:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Easy.

They become super between their movie and the most recent other MCU movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 13:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rule 6? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My(brief) take on a fantastic four trilogy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 05:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Film one
Fantastic four are already established, they are jetting around and save an alien from the Skrulls he tells of how they invaded his planet.

UN doesn't believe them. Thinks they're being radicals.
Skrulls show up, UN gets really cosy with them.
FF fights super skrull who was made after their first fight gets beat.
Is revealed by Doctor Doom that the UN has been infiltrated by skrulls. War breaks out.
Show various countries falling to skrulls
Scene of Latveria fighting off skrull armada with doom bots.

FF repels skrull invasion fleet some how with super science after beating the super skrull.


Movie 2
Doom thinks the world is not prepared to defend itself. 
Goes about classic world domination plan based on time travel

He succeeds. Fantastic Four realize he used time travel, but because they were in the negative zone or in a pocket dimension discovered by Reed, they realize they weren't effected by the shift in reality, revealing to reed multiversal theory based on alternate time lines.

They find a way back in time and restore their time line.

Movie ends with Silver warning of the coming of Galactus.

Third movie
FF attempt to communicate with Galactus before he reaches earth, they fight Stardust and Terrax who will serve as his heralds and they are chased back to earth.

Silver surfer tells them of the ultimate nulifier.

They go on adventure to find it.

While searching, reed also searches for planets upon which Galactus could feed.

They threaten Galactus with the ultimate nulifier, with no intention of using it. The heralds realize it and attack them, silver surfer helps and they win this time.

Reed makes a deal with Galactus for earths safety in exchange for the coordinates of these viable but uninhabited planets
 Galactus agrees. For now.


Honestly, the FF should spend as little time on earth or in our reality as possible. Maybe have them fight the mole man in one or two of these movies, but really lean in too the crazy exploration side of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 17:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh gotcha. Neat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 17:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you honestly have players that cause that much of a ruckus, they're not looking for a fun fantasy adventure game. They're just looking to argue to make themselves look superior.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 16:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah man, go for it. The thing about "evolution" and "physics" in these worlds is there are literally dozens of creation stories for the different races and creatures and upside down flowing waterfalls that you can directly ask a god and your god WILL respond. There's very little room for people to refute that "Trexes wouldn't live in this part of the world alongside modern deer" when Bobo the god of doesntgiveashitaboutyouropinion decides hea going to do that, and make the trexes opera singers. While looking your character in the eye.

That and YOU are the final arbiter of even those gods.

You're king of the world. You can make a new god who does all these things if you want. You could literally add Bobo.

OR you can just make rocks fall from the sky until your players agree with you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 06:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For sure. 

If you were in Toronto I'd suggest a Free Form fusion between our mains. That'd look stupid in a fun way haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 06:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. That's a problem I had with my gold skinned alien. I gave him crazy green Raditz Hair and he looked epic. But a lot of his fusions just looked off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 05:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. Aliens are probably the most fun. (Plus their skills are way more fun than any of the others except maybe Namekians but I haven't played one yet!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 05:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there, I dunno if this is still open. But it looks like I'm going to be all alone on my birthday and I'd love some pizza to keep me company.  (People keep canceling on me over facebook, and have been over the last few days.)

I want to stress. I don't need the pizza. But I always eat pizza and watch anime when I'm stressed or sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> APM Through the roof, Keyboard warrior style </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 02:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I know what you're going to be thinking, this guy is here making fun of Keyboard warriors and toxic players he just played with.

BUT NO! Hear now, the Saga of Feed Lord and Local Psycho. (If you boys check the Subreddit, I'm Alabaster.)

These guys had played in around five games together before our match on towers of Doom. I started a game with them once before that. 

Toxic banter blasted back and forth. Either one, or the other was a troll came cries from either side. But LO! I called. "Everyone has bad games. Let's do our best, and play to win!" But the banter continued. 

Lost had we yes, but insight I had gained. For next map was towers of doom, and I refused to be pained. For matched on my Team, were once again these two. Bickering back and forth, oh what too do? 

With glee and a smile "New match! New Start!" 
I said these words, for I believed them from the bottom of my heart. I encouraged play, that would win the day. First and second pick went Support and tank? Hip hip, hooray! Our last three could flex, with last pick being me. Our draft was top notch, and the match...  It was one to watch!

We juked and we roamed. The enemy team, was owned. The bile stopped flying, the enemies. Kept dying. 

We captured forts and mercs, and narry a shrine did we miss. Though when enemies capture two, neither "Troll" did take the piss.

We got wiped once all game, but neither did flame, we bounced back and won, bringing us to the hall of fame! 

A bad game, can be had. One two, or even five! This does not mean that you or he are bad. We learned to work together, and tuck the toxic behavior away. And in the end, positivity and team work did save our day!

Too often we lash out, when someone's day has gone wrong. They fight back, at the feel of your sharpened word prong. We pokes and we prods, we stoke the flames in this game without mods. Allowing one's bad day to feed another, when in a different queue you might have found a brother.

Learn from these two heroes of this day, for they did not let the tilt ruin their play. There is a lesson to be learned here, less you be burned my dear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 01:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a "It just does" attitude.

The gods made it so, and the gods weave the fabric of the natural world. So what ever exists can exist because the gods have willed reality to accommodate such aberrations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 01:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Power Alien. You're just a badass. You could 1v5 most storyline fights honestly. 

You'll probably need to handicap your main with bad fusions to keep the game interesting, but those moments where you just wanna feel like a badass are all yours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 01:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I know your pain. 

In my case, I wouldn't fuse my main with anyone who would push him above A rank, and I'd just use low level people. (Often A rank or lower. Try Fusing Chaitzu and Tien for a super cool/powerful/but not OP character. He honestly has one of the best character designs.)

Chaitzu and Guldo also makes a super cute/cool guy. But that's almost post game content.

Honestly, I just love all of Chiatzu's fusions. (Even though I hate chiatzu.) Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? That's lame </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want a free Mount for playing StarCraft </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 26 [m4f] Toronto - Ontario - Looking to switch the roles and have someone chase me for my birthday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.instagram.com/p/BL3_IXmA-9-/

Let's get that right there out the way. There's me, in all my Rugged, Harry Potter looking glory (Raven Claw for life)

Now, as the post title implies, I want to switch things around for a day. I want people to message me, to suggest dates and just take the lead. To take me out to dinner or drinks or coffee. I am quite happy taking the lead, 90% of the time, and paying when I can and just going down ye old fashioned route. But it's my birthday, and I'd love to see life from the other side. (So also feel free to send me awful messages asking for nudes and the such. Actually don't do that. That'd be awful. Haha)

As to what you get out of the deal, I mean. If the picture of that gorgeous hunk of man meat was not enough to entice you, well. I've got a way with words. Aside from referring too myself as a hunk of man meat. That... That was probably a mistake.

I love conversation, getting to know people, talking about the mundane and the exotic. Discussing fantasy, Sci-Fi, politics (In a discussion kind of way. Not trying to convince you of my way of thinking you not trying to convince me of yours, a healthy exchange of ideas. I'm more left leaning than right leaning just as an FYI.)

I am clever and funny and collected. If you're shy, and you aren't sure if you want to message me copy and paste this.

"I am willing to take you out on a date and take the lead on our first date, I am just a bit shy about the first message"

And I'll take the lead for that. Because though I'm an ambivert 
myself, I don't want to exclude Introverts from messaging me. 

Basically, I want good company and a fun time. I want a date or two too look forward too next week

And I'm looking to fall in love, but I'm not against just enjoying another person's company for the sake of it.

And if you're going out drinking tonight? Have one for me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 26 [m4f] Toronto - Ontario - Looking to switch the roles and have someone chase me for my birthday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.instagram.com/p/BL3_IXmA-9-/

Let's get that right there out the way. There's me, in all my Rugged, Harry Potter looking glory (Raven Claw for life)

Now, as the post title implies, I want to switch things around for a day. I want people to message me, to suggest dates and just take the lead. To take me out to dinner or drinks or coffee. I am quite happy taking the lead, 90% of the time, and paying when I can and just going down ye old fashioned route. But it's my birthday, and I'd love to see life from the other side. (So also feel free to send me awful messages asking for nudes and the such. Actually don't do that. That'd be awful. Haha)

As to what you get out of the deal, I mean. If the picture of that gorgeous hunk of man meat was not enough to entice you, well. I've got a way with words. Aside from referring too myself as a hunk of man meat. That... That was probably a mistake.

I love conversation, getting to know people, talking about the mundane and the exotic. Discussing fantasy, Sci-Fi, politics (In a discussion kind of way. Not trying to convince you of my way of thinking you not trying to convince me of yours, a healthy exchange of ideas. I'm more left leaning than right leaning just as an FYI.)

I am clever and funny and collected. If you're shy, and you aren't sure if you want to message me copy and paste this.

"I am willing to take you out on a date and take the lead on our first date, I am just a bit shy about the first message"

And I'll take the lead for that. Because though I'm an ambivert 
myself, I don't want to exclude Introverts from messaging me. 

Basically, I want good company and a fun time. I want a date or two too look forward too next week

And I'm looking to fall in love, but I'm not against just enjoying another person's company for the sake of it.

And if you're going out drinking tonight? Have one for me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 08:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the thing. He chose you. 

If it causes you too much stress for him to see her, you need to end it.

But he likes her, hell he might still have a crush on her.

But he chose you.

The thing is, love and attraction isn't a binary "You are in love and attracted to this person" or "They are my platonic friend"

There are so many layers. 

But at the end if the day, he chose you. If you think he will cheat with her, then you think he'll cheat with anyone.

But just because he's attracted to other people, and he is. Doesn't mean he'd want to betray you for them.

He wants you more than anyone else. Thats why he is with you.

But he still has friends, and he's probably attracted to several. People often make friends with people who are about as attractive as them selves, but people usually try to date up. So, he can see an attraction and appeal too this person, but she is less than you in his eyes.

Don't another his friendship, but instead reinforce your relationship.

Don't tolerate any betrayal or foolishness.

Don't punish natural attractions or crushes.

You can't help who you're attracted too, but he wants a romance and future with you until he makes you think otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 08:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want a high level ai for when someone drops, instead of the beginner level awful ai we get. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's because he'd die if he spends much time outside the sewers. So like, Venom could call on him if he needs too.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 05:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=C11MzbEcHlw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 05:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And when you disconnect during the MVP screen, which really mucks up my machine sometimes. We've already won, why would I draft dodge? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree five full heroes is much better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 13:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Muradin, rexxar, morales, Raynor and tychus sounds like a potent team too me.

Maybe switch tychus for hammer.

But yes all prtoss sounds rad af </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 21:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for producing fun content (That kinda hits close too home haha) least I could do is spread the word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 21:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u/spanglerBQ just let me know if you want me to take this down so you can post it here. I just wanted to share it with more folks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> u/spanglerBQ made this hilarious "What if there were honest internet porn commercial's" video, and it plays like a hilarious version of one of those prescription drug commercials </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 21:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wise words from r/gaming </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 21:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "When Cod Meets Dark Souls" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 21:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://imgur.com/gallery/H0KWoUF

So. I saw that link, and it got me thinking. Wouldn't that be an amazing game? You and up too three other guys, (Or do it solo) need to work your way though a city and find the source of the monsters.

What would make this interesting, is the source could be literally anywhere each playthrough. It changes everytime you start the game, as well as the locations of bosses. Maybe even bosses roam around, so you've got to run and hide until you're ready for it.

Friendly camps spawn of soldiers and mythical warriors, and you can see them fighting the monsters from time too time. Maybe gangs of looters and criminals and poachers attack you as well.

I'd play the hell out of a game like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 09:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was the loan for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 07:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to break all the heroes though. That's the laugh about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1 I'd love to see a sing off Between Gaston (Beauty and the Beast) and Maui (Moana) singing about how great they are and how much everyone loves them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 05:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love both Gaston and Maui. They're two of the most Charismatic characters around. And their songs, singing about how great they are, are just so much fun! 

I can just imagine the two of them going toe too toe.

Gaston: "While I might not be a Demi god, I most certainly have the bod"

Maui: "With shoulders like that you're too skinny, compared too me you're quite Mini."

Hah and just a back and forth banter as they try to one up one another. Ya know?

What lyrics would you all use? Which background track would be best for it? Who would you vote for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'd love to see a sing off Between Gaston (Beauty and the Beast) and Maui (Moana) singing about how great they are and how much everyone loves them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 05:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 03:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Situation as situation goes.

I like to take out a wall if I'm a ranged hero, because you do that easy and stay out of the range of most towers.

When I'm attacking as a siege hero, I'll usually take the gate first so my minons can get in and circle a tower.

If I'm pushing with a team, I take the towers out because they'll just slow our push down by killing minions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brawls are for broken and stupid fun, we need each brawl to get random Modifies when it starts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 03:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So let's say you load up mage wars. 

"NO COOLDOWNS"

Then next game

"Minions explode on death"

Then next game

"Heroes respawn where they died"

Etc etc etc

Also. We REALLY need a Brawl where everyone has all their talents unlocked I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 01:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that's the thing. It's not part of the game. Not in any meaningful way, certainly not in a way that I should get leaver and loss if I drop during it. 

I'd rather not have it than have the risk of that. T_T </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to play Gazlowe? (Also you shouldn't get Leaver status if you drop during MVP) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I'm in leaver que because I dropped during MVP (I swear something on that screen sets my system off) and I've decided to play Gazlowe.

Does anyone have any solid tips on him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 07:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. As a seven year old I was not super invested in the story. And those are the people I was talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 07:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I always thought that about him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 01:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was talking about people that haven't played Starcraft II. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 23:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah perfect response.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 23:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because people prefer playing Aliens. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 23:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Probius is actually the MOST iconic starcraft character we've gotten </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The year, is 1998. You're seven years old, and you've just gotten the hot new game. Starcraft.

Your older brother teaches you how to play the game. "You need to build probes to harvest minerals, and build things for your base."

He shows you the Arcade after the release of Broodwar. "This game here, it's called cat and mouse. You play a Probe running from the Ultralisks who are the cats"

You didn't care about the story, you just wanted to play with cheats on. Since you had cheats on you loved to to stupid things like build armies of probes, drones scvs etc and trounce your enemies. 

You'd use your precious probes to turtle hard until you could build carriers, your only other unit.

Years go by. You start playing HoTS. "Oh neat! Raynor was in Starcraft right? He's a Marine. So cool. And I remember Kerrigan from the Broodwar splash screen. Artanis? He was a corssair right? Oh Tassadar was the hero model High Templar who could attack? And there's shadow guy who always had his blinds parted slightly to allow only a little light to touch his face. Zeratul. That's in."

You're reminded of all these heroes from the campaign that your brother did years ago while you anxiously awaited your turn to dick around in vs AI or the Arcade.

There are many many Starcraft players who couldn't tell you who Tychus, Dehaka, Nova, or heck Even Stukov or Artanis are. 

But there isn't a single. Not a single Starcraft player who doesn't know who a probe is and what it does. 

"Cannon rush!"
"He walled himself in!"
"Probe rush!"

When it comes to strategy RPGs the story is less important than the replayability. Starcraft has an amazing and epic story that I love. But it has an even better game play, that made it so Broodward is still a beloved and highly played game too this day.

Long after you finished the several hours it took to complete the campagin, you've left the likes of Raynor, Kerrigan, and Zeratul behind. But Probius? He's been at your side or at your gates for hundreds, maybe thousands of hours. Cheesing, mining, even BMing. 

But he's been there. Starcaft's story is amazing and you should play it. But it's gameplay is what made it great. And that's why Probius is the most iconic Starcraft character we've received.

PS: Plus he was already in the Legacy of the Void trailer so he's more cannon(heh) than SGT. Hammer or Morales.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not all. I think Kharazim and Valla had novels about them before hand? Maybe Nazeboo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 07:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To all of the people saying that it would make them a hots hero. No. It wouldn't. Here is how I would do it.


Release an overwatch comic, have the character discussing with one of the main cast in ways they think they could help Overwatch. Or maybe just talking about how awesome it would be to be a superhero or some such. I make this character a giant nerd, with collectables scattered through their home from nerdy properties, (like blizzard games) and overwatch stuff.

They fall asleep and begin dreaming of themselves in a battlesuit with an awesome weapon they've never seen before. 

But, they are in the nexus! Battling characters and monsters from all the games they've known about for years. But now its a battle to the death.

They wake up from their "dream" (was it really a dream? Maybe have a gift from Tyrande fall out of their pocket and roll under a couch so you are left to winder if it is another collectable or an actual artifact from Azeroth) and are inspired! They use their engineering knowhow to produce the same gear they wielded while in the Nexus. They call their friend again and tell them "Give me a few months, I have an idea"


Release this hero in HOTS first, you are playing them in their "dream".

Then release them in overwatch.

They were introduced in overwatch first via a comic, so the character is actually from overwatch.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 07:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Azmodan gets shit Azmo-done in gold league </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 07:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fenix is already done. They were going to release him right after Leoric but didn't want that many death effects in a row.

I assume with the talent updates and other new hero releases he's been changed quite a bit though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 05:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is Venom fused with Creep! Creep, his life long ally who swore a blood oath to forever be by his side whenever he was needed, who gave him the strength to scare the Juggernaut off. Creep whom was never heard from or mentioned again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When a man undoes his belt on his way to the bathroom, you know some serious shit is about to go down. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 01:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is your Team Retreating, or charging? Speed.  


Is the Enemy Winding up an AoE or Skill shot? Speed.  


Is one of your allies poisned and about to die beacuse of it? Health?  


Or you in the middle of a bru-ha-ha with people trading blows back and forth, but no real movement? Health.  


Are you in the backline waiting for your chance to move in? Health.  


Are both teams waiting for the right chance to strike, for the other team to make the first move? Health. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I keep getting dropped during Capture the Flag while defending as bastion. Is there any warning I should look out for when it is about to drop me? How do I prevent this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No more lies only Trix. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 08:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 04:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They throw a cluster that explodes after a  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 01:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a version of this image without the FXX logo in the bottom right? I'd love it for a phone background. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plus, different people are different at different ages. Saying Old people shouldn't hang out with young people is how you get a goddamn age gap.

It's sweet if a teenager makes friends with someone in an old folks home, but not someone twenty years younger? That's taboo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's guys like you I loved growing up. My brother had a bunch of nerdy older friends. (And he was 5 years older htan me) and I loved the moments I got to hangout with them. 

I just didn't enjoy the same things as people my age and I am still glad I spent time with them the way I did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any physical contact with anyone these days is immediate cause for revulsion and disgust it seems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right? I always related to my brother's friends more than my own. I never wanted to do crazy ass shit. I just wanted to play Magic the Gathering and DnD. And Guess fucking what. Some of those guys were easily over ten years older than me and they were, and are still super cool. Letting the kid tag a long and play their nerd games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man I hate threads like this. I'm 25, and I dated a 17 year old last year. 

We had a ton of fun, and enjoyed one another's company. Eventually we parted ways and we still talk. I give her advice and what not. 

People underestimate teenagers. "When I was a teenager I was so dumb lololol so all of them must be" sure. Maybe. 

But there's also young adults making brilliant leaps in engineering or athletics. Young adults are just that, young adults. That's why dating them is Legal. 

Do you look a bit weird? Probably. But does it matter if you're both happy? And yes. There are scum bags who would take advantage of it. But there are also young people who take advantage of the desires of older folks. (Check any dating site for any number of girls looking for a sugar daddy)

It's like bad people come in all ages or something.

Not every teenager should date an adult. And MOST CERTAINLY not every adult should date a teenager. But if two people have common ground and love one another. Live and let live.

Source: I wouldn't be here if my 25 year old father didn't start dating my 16 year old mother, they're still married, have three kids and their own house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lucio's Ribbit Skin has a secret </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lucio's Ribbit skin has a secret. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 16 is legal in most places </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 09:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't want to google that name.

But I want to know who it belongs too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 08:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Friday to Saturday are the perfect time periods for me. Whenever those days are good for me. Earlier in the day is great (Avoids the awkward people falling asleep at their keyboard thing) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 05:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a Instrumental version? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 04:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which ending tho? There are many. 

(New game+ look at the right teleporter for a green magic tab!_ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 04:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey I'm in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 07:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one and only time I had that happen I was shot calling for the first round assuming my team were ignoring me.

When I realized they were bots I grouped up near our healing fountain and let my opponent win super quick. I play to play with people because I have no IRL friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any example as to why we need multiple colour blind modes for Overwatch. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why colour blind modes are important </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since I cannot just link to another page and need to put a preamble, here are a collection of images expressing just how important having a Variety of colour blind modes is for any online game.

https://imgur.com/gallery/UY4kg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 14:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was cute and funny the first time. Then I deleted the app because of how often. It did it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You shouldn't be rewarded for dying. Bad mechanic, unfun to have someone on your team dying on purpose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 07:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 05:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay cool. You'll be running the world as Azmo soon. 

I will stress that in higher ranks, split pushing without thinking will get you killed. But Azmodan get's shit Azmo-done at any rank </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's your battle tag? Are you in US server?

I'll train you how to play carry Azmodan and it'll get you to gold since no one knows how to counter you in those leagues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW when I'm Sombra disguesd as a man and I need to let my allies know who I am without being obvious </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 03:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 19:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fully updated at 1.3.0 sad too say.

I wonder what the issue is.

If I could just use save states that'd be fine. But you need save data to progress the story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 00:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Azmodan. I'll roll over your lanes and I'll rotate into a new lane as you attempt to counter the push I've left behind ages ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 25 [M4R] Toronto - Radical Honesty from a Bi Man. I'm going to put my best foot forward, and trip myself by throwing out the negatives, and I want you to do the same. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 21:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inspired by this video

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=buKMOxNzYjY

Which is funny as it is informative and depressing, I'm going to throw myself out there and just be honest.
               

But the thrust of it is, just share everything about yourself rather than just the generic nonsense. Share the parts about yourself that might be a red flag for one person, or the holy grail for another. Because rather than have this thing come up as a deal breaker later, it happens now, neither of you waste time and you're more likely to find someone who fits your quirks, kinks, and faults.
     

First off. I want someone who thinks two people reading in the same room at the same time counts as doing something together. Stole that line straight from the video (For real, watch it.) but goddamn it's so true. 
     


And it doesn't just have to be reading, like you can be watching videos or playing video games or knitting or what ever. I just like, being with my partner, ya know?

On too the radical honesty part.
I've got depression. I don't let it effect how I interact with people, I'm as charming and smooth as butter. But sometimes I withdraw. I don't text, I don't message I don't call. And I don't just mean the person I'm dating. I mean anyone. I'm honestly not trying to ignore you or make you feel neglected when I do. But it is what it is.

For a job, I'm a Nanny. It's amazing. I love kids.

I'm a Dork, and a geek. DnD, Dad Jokes, Video Games, Anime, comics, hell. Even LARPing.

On the topic of LARPing I love camping. It's great to be in the great outdoors in a tent. Solo or with friends.

I'm 6'3, I've got a red beard and brown hair, and glasses that make me look like Harry Potter.

I love physical affection. I don't mean like, hanky panky either. Holding hands, hugging, ideal touches on the shoulder or head or what ever. Someone scratching my beard (Which I'm not married too by the way. I LIKE it, but if I'm with someone who prefers clean shaven I'm fine shaving it. But only after we've dated for AT LEAST a month. I'm not dropping it for our first date haha)

I'm a performer. not professionally, but I LOVE being on stage. Karaoke, acting and most recently I've been working on a Comedy Set that I think is pretty solid.

I like women of all shapes sizes and age, short girls are great, but being 6'3 MOST women are shorter, and I don't mind gals who are taller.

I'm a little pickier when it comes to men though. I prefer guys shorter than me, little body hair ideally, around my age (In their twenties) and I LOVE the hipster look. 

Trans Male and Female friendly. 

I think it's important we're both attracted to one another. I can be friends with someone I don't find attractive but I cannot date them. It's not fair to either of us, and, unless you're Asexual, I want to be the sexiest mother lover in the world too you.

On the note of Asexuality. I'm a sexual guy with a variety of kinks. I don't need to dive into all of them obviously, and I can get by on minimal sexuality. BUT I do need that in my life. I know plenty of Asexual folks who participate with their partner for that kind of thing even if it does nothing for them, but I don't want to pressure you into doing stuff you don't want too do. I want both of us to be fulfilled in Mental, emotional and physical needs.

Ideally I'll meet someone who is at least a little active. I like being out and about from time to time, and the more active you are the more motivated I become. This if course doesn't limit you if you're physically unable to participate in certain activities. I just want to be as honest as I can about where I'm at with whatever.

Please, ask me questions. Even if you don't want to date me. I will add them into the body of my post so more people can see them. I want to date someone who wants me for me after all.

I'm primarily monogamous but I'm open to a Poly relationship where I'm the primary partner. (I'm also open to dating people in Poly relationships, but long term I will be looking for a primary person.)

Also, here's a joke from my set that is slightly topical.

^"As ^you ^can ^see, ^I'm ^a ^tall ^guy. ^6'3. ^Despite ^that, ^I ^wont ^date ^a ^person ^who ^has ^a ^height ^requirement ^for ^their ^men. ^I ^want ^to ^show ^solidarity ^with ^my ^five ^foot ^brothers.

^Someone ^has ^to ^stand ^up ^for **^^the ^^^little ^^^^guy."** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 03:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Duuude. Thank you! I love this game and its been killing me I cannot play it.

Renaming the game was all it took. You're brilliant! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 20:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys. I'm having two problems. 

Final Fantasy IV The After Years being played on PPSSPP cannot make a standard save file. I thought this was fine so I just state saved, until I realized to continue the game, after each "Chapter" I needed to use the data from my previous "Chapter's" save. I get "Error code: 80110327" whenever I try to save.

The other issue I have is with Suikoden Tierkreis on the DraStic emulator. I accidentally set the language to french, but even going into the system options to change it to english doesn't help. I've uninstalled the app, and I've deleted the game and added it in a new folder but it sill doesn't change to english. Any tips? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 25 [M4R] Toronto - Radical Honesty from a Bi Man. I'm going to put my best foot forward, and trip myself by throwing out the negatives, and I want you to do the same. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inspired by this video

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=buKMOxNzYjY

Which is funny as it is informative and depressing, I'm going to throw myself out there and just be honest.
               

But the thrust of it is, just share everything about yourself rather than just the generic nonsense. Share the parts about yourself that might be a red flag for one person, or the holy grail for another. Because rather than have this thing come up as a deal breaker later, it happens now, neither of you waste time and you're more likely to find someone who fits your quirks, kinks, and faults.
     

First off. I want someone who thinks two people reading in the same room at the same time counts as doing something together. Stole that line straight from the video (For real, watch it.) but goddamn it's so true. 
     


And it doesn't just have to be reading, like you can be watching videos or playing video games or knitting or what ever. I just like, being with my partner, ya know?

On too the radical honesty part.
I've got depression. I don't let it effect how I interact with people, I'm as charming and smooth as butter. But sometimes I withdraw. I don't text, I don't message I don't call. And I don't just mean the person I'm dating. I mean anyone. I'm honestly not trying to ignore you or make you feel neglected when I do. But it is what it is.

For a job, I'm a Nanny. It's amazing. I love kids.

I'm a Dork, and a geek. DnD, Dad Jokes, Video Games, Anime, comics, hell. Even LARPing.

On the topic of LARPing I love camping. It's great to be in the great outdoors in a tent. Solo or with friends.

I'm 6'3, I've got a red beard and brown hair, and glasses that make me look like Harry Potter.

I love physical affection. I don't mean like, hanky panky either. Holding hands, hugging, ideal touches on the shoulder or head or what ever. Someone scratching my beard (Which I'm not married too by the way. I LIKE it, but if I'm with someone who prefers clean shaven I'm fine shaving it. But only after we've dated for AT LEAST a month. I'm not dropping it for our first date haha)

I'm a performer. not professionally, but I LOVE being on stage. Karaoke, acting and most recently I've been working on a Comedy Set that I think is pretty solid.

I like women of all shapes sizes and age, short girls are great, but being 6'3 MOST women are shorter, and I don't mind gals who are taller.

I'm a little pickier when it comes to men though. I prefer guys shorter than me, little body hair ideally, around my age (In their twenties) and I LOVE the hipster look. 

Trans Male and Female friendly. 

I think it's important we're both attracted to one another. I can be friends with someone I don't find attractive but I cannot date them. It's not fair to either of us, and, unless you're Asexual, I want to be the sexiest mother lover in the world too you.

On the note of Asexuality. I'm a sexual guy with a variety of kinks. I don't need to dive into all of them obviously, and I can get by on minimal sexuality. BUT I do need that in my life. I know plenty of Asexual folks who participate with their partner for that kind of thing even if it does nothing for them, but I don't want to pressure you into doing stuff you don't want too do. I want both of us to be fulfilled in Mental, emotional and physical needs.

Ideally I'll meet someone who is at least a little active. I like being out and about from time to time, and the more active you are the more motivated I become. This if course doesn't limit you if you're physically unable to participate in certain activities. I just want to be as honest as I can about where I'm at with whatever.

Please, ask me questions. Even if you don't want to date me. I will add them into the body of my post so more people can see them. I want to date someone who wants me for me after all.

I'm primarily monogamous but I'm open to a Poly relationship where I'm the primary partner. (I'm also open to dating people in Poly relationships, but long term I will be looking for a primary person.)

Also, here's a joke from my set that is slightly topical.

^"As ^you ^can ^see, ^I'm ^a ^tall ^guy. ^6'3. ^Despite ^that, ^I ^wont ^date ^a ^person ^who ^has ^a ^height ^requirement ^for ^their ^men. ^I ^want ^to ^show ^solidarity ^with ^my ^five ^foot ^brothers.

^Someone ^has ^to ^stand ^up ^for **^^the ^^^little ^^^^guy."** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 25 [M4R] Toronto - Radical Honesty from a Bi Man. I'm going to put my best foot forward, and trip myself by throwing out the negatives, and I want you to do the same. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 06:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inspired by this video

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=buKMOxNzYjY

Which is funny as it is informative and depressing, I'm going to throw myself out there and just be honest.
               

But the thrust of it is, just share everything about yourself rather than just the generic nonsense. Share the parts about yourself that might be a red flag for one person, or the holy grail for another. Because rather than have this thing come up as a deal breaker later, it happens now, neither of you waste time and you're more likely to find someone who fits your quirks, kinks, and faults.
     

First off. I want someone who thinks two people reading in the same room at the same time counts as doing something together. Stole that line straight from the video (For real, watch it.) but goddamn it's so true. 
     


And it doesn't just have to be reading, like you can be watching videos or playing video games or knitting or what ever. I just like, being with my partner, ya know?

On too the radical honesty part.
I've got depression. I don't let it effect how I interact with people, I'm as charming and smooth as butter. But sometimes I withdraw. I don't text, I don't message I don't call. And I don't just mean the person I'm dating. I mean anyone. I'm honestly not trying to ignore you or make you feel neglected when I do. But it is what it is.

For a job, I'm a Nanny. It's amazing. I love kids.

I'm a Dork, and a geek. DnD, Dad Jokes, Video Games, Anime, comics, hell. Even LARPing.

On the topic of LARPing I love camping. It's great to be in the great outdoors in a tent. Solo or with friends.

I'm 6'3, I've got a red beard and brown hair, and glasses that make me look like Harry Potter.

I love physical affection. I don't mean like, hanky panky either. Holding hands, hugging, ideal touches on the shoulder or head or what ever. Someone scratching my beard (Which I'm not married too by the way. I LIKE it, but if I'm with someone who prefers clean shaven I'm fine shaving it. But only after we've dated for AT LEAST a month. I'm not dropping it for our first date haha)

I'm a performer. not professionally, but I LOVE being on stage. Karaoke, acting and most recently I've been working on a Comedy Set that I think is pretty solid.

I like women of all shapes sizes and age, short girls are great, but being 6'3 MOST women are shorter, and I don't mind gals who are taller.

I'm a little pickier when it comes to men though. I prefer guys shorter than me, little body hair ideally, around my age (In their twenties) and I LOVE the hipster look. 

Trans Male and Female friendly. 

I think it's important we're both attracted to one another. I can be friends with someone I don't find attractive but I cannot date them. It's not fair to either of us, and, unless you're Asexual, I want to be the sexiest mother lover in the world too you.

On the note of Asexuality. I'm a sexual guy with a variety of kinks. I don't need to dive into all of them obviously, and I can get by on minimal sexuality. BUT I do need that in my life. I know plenty of Asexual folks who participate with their partner for that kind of thing even if it does nothing for them, but I don't want to pressure you into doing stuff you don't want too do. I want both of us to be fulfilled in Mental, emotional and physical needs.

Ideally I'll meet someone who is at least a little active. I like being out and about from time to time, and the more active you are the more motivated I become. This if course doesn't limit you if you're physically unable to participate in certain activities. I just want to be as honest as I can about where I'm at with whatever.

Please, ask me questions. Even if you don't want to date me. I will add them into the body of my post so more people can see them. I want to date someone who wants me for me after all.

I'm primarily monogamous but I'm open to a Poly relationship where I'm the primary partner. (I'm also open to dating people in Poly relationships, but long term I will be looking for a primary person.)

Also, here's a joke from my set that is slightly topical.

^"As ^you ^can ^see, ^I'm ^a ^tall ^guy. ^6'3. ^Despite ^that, ^I ^wont ^date ^a ^person ^who ^has ^a ^height ^requirement ^for ^their ^men. ^I ^want ^to ^show ^solidarity ^with ^my ^five ^foot ^brothers.

^Someone ^has ^to ^stand ^up ^for **^^the ^^^little ^^^^guy."** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 25 [M4R] Toronto - Radical Honesty from a Bi Man. I'm going to put my best foot forward, and trip myself by throwing out the negatives, and I want you to do the same. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 06:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inspired by this video

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=buKMOxNzYjY

Which is funny as it is informative and depressing, I'm going to throw myself out there and just be honest.
               

But the thrust of it is, just share everything about yourself rather than just the generic nonsense. Share the parts about yourself that might be a red flag for one person, or the holy grail for another. Because rather than have this thing come up as a deal breaker later, it happens now, neither of you waste time and you're more likely to find someone who fits your quirks, kinks, and faults.
     

First off. I want someone who thinks two people reading in the same room at the same time counts as doing something together. Stole that line straight from the video (For real, watch it.) but goddamn it's so true. 
     


And it doesn't just have to be reading, like you can be watching videos or playing video games or knitting or what ever. I just like, being with my partner, ya know?

On too the radical honesty part.
I've got depression. I don't let it effect how I interact with people, I'm as charming and smooth as butter. But sometimes I withdraw. I don't text, I don't message I don't call. And I don't just mean the person I'm dating. I mean anyone. I'm honestly not trying to ignore you or make you feel neglected when I do. But it is what it is.

For a job, I'm a Nanny. It's amazing. I love kids.

I'm a Dork, and a geek. DnD, Dad Jokes, Video Games, Anime, comics, hell. Even LARPing.

On the topic of LARPing I love camping. It's great to be in the great outdoors in a tent. Solo or with friends.

I'm 6'3, I've got a red beard and brown hair, and glasses that make me look like Harry Potter.

I love physical affection. I don't mean like, hanky panky either. Holding hands, hugging, ideal touches on the shoulder or head or what ever. Someone scratching my beard (Which I'm not married too by the way. I LIKE it, but if I'm with someone who prefers clean shaven I'm fine shaving it. But only after we've dated for AT LEAST a month. I'm not dropping it for our first date haha)

I'm a performer. not professionally, but I LOVE being on stage. Karaoke, acting and most recently I've been working on a Comedy Set that I think is pretty solid.

I like women of all shapes sizes and age, short girls are great, but being 6'3 MOST women are shorter, and I don't mind gals who are taller.

I'm a little pickier when it comes to men though. I prefer guys shorter than me, little body hair ideally, around my age (In their twenties) and I LOVE the hipster look. 

Trans Male and Female friendly. 

I think it's important we're both attracted to one another. I can be friends with someone I don't find attractive but I cannot date them. It's not fair to either of us, and, unless you're Asexual, I want to be the sexiest mother lover in the world too you.

On the note of Asexuality. I'm a sexual guy with a variety of kinks. I don't need to dive into all of them obviously, and I can get by on minimal sexuality. BUT I do need that in my life. I know plenty of Asexual folks who participate with their partner for that kind of thing even if it does nothing for them, but I don't want to pressure you into doing stuff you don't want too do. I want both of us to be fulfilled in Mental, emotional and physical needs.

Ideally I'll meet someone who is at least a little active. I like being out and about from time to time, and the more active you are the more motivated I become. This if course doesn't limit you if you're physically unable to participate in certain activities. I just want to be as honest as I can about where I'm at with whatever.

Please, ask me questions. Even if you don't want to date me. I will add them into the body of my post so more people can see them. I want to date someone who wants me for me after all.

I'm primarily monogamous but I'm open to a Poly relationship where I'm the primary partner. (I'm also open to dating people in Poly relationships, but long term I will be looking for a primary person.)

Also, here's a joke from my set that is slightly topical.

^"As ^you ^can ^see, ^I'm ^a ^tall ^guy. ^6'3. ^Despite ^that, ^I ^wont ^date ^a ^person ^who ^has ^a ^height ^requirement ^for ^their ^men. ^I ^want ^to ^show ^solidarity ^with ^my ^five ^foot ^brothers.

^Someone ^has ^to ^stand ^up ^for **^^the ^^^little ^^^^guy."** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 25 [M4A] Toronto - Radical Honesty from a Bi Man. I'm going to put my best foot forward, and trip myself by throwing out the negatives, and I want you to do the same. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 05:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes yes that was it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guys stop shitting on the guy. He was unclear about something, and asked for some clarification. Not trolling for upvotes, not even shit posting.

He didn't know the answer too a question and you respond with mockery because the answer is obvious too you? Ignorance isn't a crime, and he was trying to get himself too the point where he'd no longer be ignorant. Ya'all are dicks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 09:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Burter really was the fastest in that game. He was so freaking cool.

I always made a team out of the characters who went from small too super buff.

Garlic Junior, Android 13, Broly, Freeza... And I think there was a fifth whom I cannot place a finger on at the moment. Roshi, maybe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 08:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What makes it so? (He's also my favourite Ginyu force member, and I've got a Venom/Sinestro mashup tattooed on me so I'm not judging.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 08:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mari Mac by great big sea 
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R3sOA6yQc4A
(I'm not sure how to format)

StarDew Valley
Octodad
You mentioned this was from the freedom bundle? Do you maybe have extra keys for the two Cory Doctorow audio books. He's really rad and my mouse broke anyway so I probably can't play either of those games right now and I love books.

Thanks for being so swell and giving things to people. You're a rad fella. (Also. Hot damn that formatting.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. 

Alarak has a skill that does damage AND silences. This one would be either or. I think this ability is quite good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was chatting in google chat, now my track pad isn't working. It IS enabled. Help! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 05:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So. I was using my track pad, just having a grand ol' time. Then hopped into facebook messenger, and when I went to change tabs. It wasn't responding. I'm not sure what to do, my roommate checked to see if it was enabled and it was enabled, and there's this glitch apparently with sleep mode, but it wasn't that either. Any advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course not. It could even be considered a weaker silence since the enemy can choose to take the damage, or not. But it either shuts down a skill or hurts, it's up to the enemy. I think that's fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mana burn inflicts a status that the next time they cast a spell they take mana cost x100 in damage

As a new mechanic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP]Your Childhood/Teenage years OC is introduced to the main cannon of their franchise. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How uncomfortable do they make the main cast? How much do the ruin the universe? How does the main cast deal with it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't remember their blood luckiliy haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 21:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're from New Orleans you might have some Canadian in you.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cajuns#History_of_Acadian_ancestors </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
