<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2013</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Geez, every single one of those mistakes looks like a masterpiece by Otto von Bismarck next to Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IT'S GRABBIN' TIME!

No, Trump, no! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I imagine John McCain just makes statements like that as he does everything.  "I have grave concerns about this steak," he says, in between bites.  "Anyone who makes an illegal U-turn is an idiot," he mumbles as he does so, ignoring the honks around him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, my first few times, I got really invested.  After a while, I became a band of knife-wielding serial murderers who hid in hallways and stabbed people so I could take their parts.  On the bright side, it was also a really fun serial murderer simulator.  I had loads of fun waiting to get one person alone, stabbing them, and then hiding before their friends found us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "How could Strom Thurmond be racist when he had a half-black kid?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ophelia from Divinity: Dragon Commander.  I don't care that she's a skeleton; she's a beautiful skeleton. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out ToonamiAftermath.com.  I think you'll enjoy it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if societies that believe in reincarnation put more effort into infrastructure investment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think insurance companies are more or less moral than the government?  By which I mean, which do you think cares more about saving lives and keeping people healthy, even at the expense of profit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are doctors currently owned by insurance companies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah.  No reason to play 3 when 4 exists.  I was just saying that, starting with 3, it's easy to get into.  1 kicks my ass every time.  4 is my favorite, but 5 is good, too, so long as you go into it without expectations.  I disliked it when I first played it, coming off 4, but I didn't play Tropico for a year, tried 5 again, and loved it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was because the link appears broken when I clicked on it in your reply.  Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tropico 5 has fewer traffic issues, so far as I've noticed, and I love its sense of humor.  (Penultimo saying he wants to motivate some fishermen with a bullet to the back of the head is a pretty good example.)  You can get the whole thing with all DLCs for $10 if you find a sale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's weird.  When I click on the link in my comment, or copy and paste it into a browser, it works, but if I click on the link in your comment, it fails.

EDIT: I was assuming your comment was sarcastic.  If you were sincere then this is really a non sequitur. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The Southern heritage, the Confederate heritage is very honourable."

http://news.bbc.co.uk/2/hi/americas/503579.stm

He also described Strom Thurmond as a person of high integrity, and when Strom's bi-racial love child made herself known, Joe called her claim a smear of Strom's image. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta keep the laws simple.  "Ape shall not kill ape."  A more perfect moral system, there will never be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine how much shorter crime dramas would be if all criminals were Trumps.  "If there was anything that random black guy did, it was to make sure I got my wife's recent and suspiciously large life insurance payout, am I right, officer?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think part of it is how individually useful each person is.  If a million people is just a blip that you won't notice an in-game week later, like in Galactic Civilizations II, yeah, I'll throw a billion people into a meat grinder if I think it'll give me the slightest advantage.  But in something like Banished, where you're constantly on the edge, and losing your only blacksmith creates a ripple effect where suddenly you're understaffed and running out of tools, you care a lot more about them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever tried Tropico?  I think it's a lot easier to get into, starting with 3, at least.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the ingenuousness of this comment.  I can just picture you reading the screen, lifting up your glasses to make sure you're reading it correctly, then sitting back in your chair.  "Wow.  They really don't like those Jews." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His greatest regret is that people keep putting his names on buildings.  All he wants is a little anonymity! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least he was kind enough to use an accurate and descriptive username. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 21:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Okay, you just stabbed my children to death in front of me.  I'm gonna count both of them as just a single strike.  But you better be careful, mister.  Only 8 more strikes left!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 01:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The right people will get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 01:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard gas prices leapt up after the strikes in Syria, so maybe that's  a start.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 05:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Confirmed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 04:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Traded Rituals, Rocket Birds, QUBE, Tower of Guns, and Shutshimi for Lifeless Planet with /u/mcantelon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 04:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can do that.  Anything you want for Highrise? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hey, how about we just stop ruining the lives of gay men so they can't be blackmailed over it?"

"WE NEED A FUNCTIONING GAYDAR NOW!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one else is going to point out that this ruler's in centimeters, not inches?  11 cm = 4.33 inches.  This definitely happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look, a blastocyte may be a human life, but if you can't vote for me someday, can you really be said to be "alive?"  I think the science is out on that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything here for Kingdom or event[0]?  https://www.reddit.com/r/indiegameswap/comments/636yck/h_freedom_bundle_leftovers_including_world_of_goo/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every president remembers his first missile strike.  You see a cute hellhole led by an authoritarian dictator, you think your poll numbers could be a little bigger, and before you know it, you've wasted the best years of your presidency on insurgents and injured war vets... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I recall, you can't even complete your FAFSA without stating that you've registered for the draft if you're a guy, so basically you're fucked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were only there to help make America great, and Trump made America perfect, ahead of schedule!  No more need to have them around.  It's not a demotion, just a lateral shift. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cassius initiated the conspiracy against Caesar after being passed over for a job he wanted...  https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gaius_Cassius_Longinus#Conspiracy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Toy Story 4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just picture the mom pointing and screeching like Invasion of the Body Snatchers.  https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GEStsLJZhzo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, who?  I'll be bummed if it's Asa Akira.

EDIT: Bummed because of the Pro-Trump thing, not the scenes with black guys, thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Great drinking games you can play by picking out things and drinking when you read then there. Like when someone's being racist drink!

Jesus Christ, dude.  The Suicide Prevention Hotline is 1-800-273-8255.  Please call them before you do this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 16:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was there anything else on my list you were interested in?  https://www.reddit.com/r/indiegameswap/comments/636yck/h_freedom_bundle_leftovers_including_world_of_goo/

I'm interesting in Project Highrise and Lifeless Planet.  I don't mind trading multiples. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 16:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus Christ...

Led by General Sam Houston, the Texian Army engaged and defeated General Antonio Lpez de Santa Anna's Mexican army in a fight that lasted just 18 minutes.

Santa Anna, the President of Mexico, was captured and surrendered the following day and held as a prisoner of war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 16:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Trump sucks as much as the next /r/politics subscriber, but is there a specific reason why March is the first month we've seen numbers that Trump had some effect on, or is that just based on the fact that they're worse than expected?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes!  Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japanese porn at a cafe where there are dicks coming out of the walls and table for the female patrons to play with </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 01:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm having a hard time Googling it.  Anyone know what I'm talking about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my stars and garters, how could the minority party ever *obstruct the president?!*  My goodness, it's just unprecedented! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of curiosity, let's say that you were particularly interesting, say a celebrity, and you yourself were an encouragement for people to wander onto your property with their smartphones out.  Would you be mad at yourself or the people on your property? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least we got a good cartoon out of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course, no average cow ever lived like Ubre Blanca did: at her state-of-the-art, air-conditioned stable in Neuva Gerona, she received round-the-clock care and attention from a specially-selected team of handlers, and was watched over by armed military escorts. Soothing music was piped into the stalls during each of her four daily milkings, and her food was tested on other animals before she ate it, lest anyone attempt to poison her. Yet for all his legendary paranoia, Castro couldnt resist showing her off to journalists and visiting dignitaries, who were invited to marvel at that bulging, bounteous udder, which was known to reach over six and a half feet in circumference after calving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Ubre Blanca, the result of a Cuban experiment to breed a cow that could produce 100 liters of milk a day, had armed guards and taste-testers, and after her death, she was given an obituary in the state newspapers and a marble statue. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, the guy who came up with the term drew an uncanny valley with sides: http://spectrum.ieee.org/automaton/robotics/humanoids/the-uncanny-valley </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come on, Hamlet Ending! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama's lowest was 38%, actually, so it's lower. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just like all those plantation foremen wouldn't work with all those slaves if they were *really* racist! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's China Development Aid http://tropico.wikia.com/wiki/Edicts_(Tropico_4) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't calling the president's son-in-law a cuck basically calling his daughter an adulteress? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if they're in solid red districts, they've still got primaries.  Threaten to vote against them there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Double Your Money Guaranteed Casino didn't stay in business very long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, nine minute old account.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is he in a fucking public library?  Where does he think the money came from to build that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there's a better indicator that a guy's going to be attentive to your needs in bed than a shirt that proudly proclaims that he wants all of the conveniences of modern society without having to pay a single cent for it, I've never seen it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Quickly" here meaning "years after Obama came into office, after having 79 individuals blocked from nomination, compared to *68* being blocked prior to Obama."  http://www.politifact.com/truth-o-meter/statements/2013/nov/22/harry-reid/harry-reid-says-82-presidential-nominees-have-been/  And now the Republicans are willing to use it less than three months over one loss? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh, what about seeing into the future? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happened to those rainbow-looking oil slicks in parking lot puddles? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like when I was younger, I'd always see those shimmering, rainbow oil slicks (I assume they were) in the puddles in parking lots after it rained, but I can't remember seeing them recently.  Have things changed, or am I just not noticing them anymore? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, personally, Kushner's only selfish.  He wants the sheep alive so he can keep shearing it.  Bannon wants to kill the sheep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone interested in Alex should read Alex and Me, by Irene Pepperberg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it checks out.  I was about to clear them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I specialize in ape law, but it's mostly concerned with whether or not ape shall kill ape (he shan't). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 06:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just no Dippin' Dots, or Spicer will be pissed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 06:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of curiosity, what way is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 05:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Request for more, please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But they didn't publicly do it.  It was revealed through a memorandum in the Federal Register, not a press conference or anything.  If they wanted to make a show, they picked a weird way to do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 23:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking hell.  As if there's an industry with worse long-term outlook than coal.  *Tobacco?*  Are you kidding me?  You never hear New Englanders talking about bringing back whale oil and textile mills. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel you.  I think they, and to a degree me, want to be welcoming to people who regret voting for Trump.  It's nice to think that they've changed and in the future will be more rational, but honestly, I think it's unlikely.  Nothing changed except they got personally affected.  If they had escaped any personal misfortune, they'd still support all that Trump did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can't all be as brilliant as the man who came up with "Shittary." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christ, I sincerely want these people to participate in a group chat that *isn't* boys only and actually ask the women they know whether or not they fear rape.  I guarantee you that they all know women who fear it and they don't know or want to know it, and the women in their lives don't feel comfortable telling them because they're MAGA idiots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mr Skeltal will be so disappointed.  No doots for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are first dates like for working adults? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you do?  How do they progress?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spartans were actually okay with wife-swapping, according to Plutarch, in order to produce the best possible offspring.  Of course, how true or frequent this actually was, I can't say.

For example, an elderly man with a young wife, if he looked with favour and esteem on some fair and noble young man, might introduce him to her, and adopt her offspring by such a noble father as his p253own. And again, a worthy man who admired some woman for the fine children that she bore her husband and the modesty of her behaviour as a wife, might enjoy her favours, if her husband would consent, thus planting, as it were, in a soil of bountiful fruitage, and begetting for himself noble sons, who would have the blood of noble men in their veins.

http://penelope.uchicago.edu/Thayer/e/roman/texts/plutarch/lives/lycurgus*.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a Battle Toad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a chest-burster comes out of Trump's rib cage during his next press conference, this will all have been worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, so gassing children is wrong, but what about the millions of innocent babies liberals murder every year at Planned Parenthood?!  /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like there's a way to be guilty of a crime without committing the on-paper definition.  I mean, if someone called Hitler a murderer, you'd see where they were coming from, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "haha those cuck liberals sure do hate when people burn their faces off so worth it" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You saved the Global Economy, huh?  But my insurance premiums didn't go to $0, so I vote for Mad Max-world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No idea, unfortunately.  Hopefully she was able to die quickly.  I can't imagine that life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a bastard... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you show up without a sword, Odin might be like, "Oh damn, here you go, just borrow Gungnir for a bit," but if you show up to the battle and people think you already fucked up your sword before anything happened, they're not gonna help you out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Consort Qi had a sucky fate: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Consort_Qi

She then had Concubine Qi's limbs chopped off, blinded her by gouging out her eyes, cut off her tongue and locked her in the pigsty, and called her a "Human Swine" (). Several days after, Emperor Xiaohui saw the "Human Swine", and after realising that it who the "Human Swine" was, the emperor was so sick of his mother's cruelty that he virtually relinquished his authority and indulged in carnal pleasures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might like /r/bois, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think when you encounter that level of stupidity, the moral thing to do is make bets with him.  $100 that Obama shows up in the US without getting arrested in the next month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're hoping for trickle-down armaments.  If the government has enough tanks, one day I'll get my own! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 23:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of this Kids in the Hall sketch, but Dave Foley is infinitely more lovable than Trump: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QGYJyeX-oMc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything here for Patrician IV (+ Rise of the Dynasty)?

https://www.reddit.com/r/indiegameswap/comments/636yck/h_freedom_bundle_leftovers_including_world_of_goo/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Achoo!"

"You want the arsenic, baby?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was warned. She was given an explanation. Nevertheless, she persisted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about us brain-dead slobs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump lying?  I mean, it sounds so implausible... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, nothing I'm interested in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Traded GRAV, System Shock Pack, and World of Goo for WARMACHINE Tactics + DLC, Galactic Civilizations II Ultimate Edition, and Frozen Synapse with /u/mcantelon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Confirmed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep.  Those 3 for your 3? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frozen Synapse, Gal Civ 2, and WARMACHINE all look good, in that order.  What do you want for them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Twilight Struggle is a cold war themed board game with historical cards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Confirmed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Traded Super Meat Boy for Rive with /u/Kapkar123 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Genghis Khan was *way* more liberal.  He promoted freedom of religion and cross-cultural exchange.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Freedom Bundle Leftovers, including World of Goo, Super Meat Boy, Tower of Guns, and others [W] Offers, ideally strategy games </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 16:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  [My IGS Rep page](https://www.reddit.com/r/IGSRep/comments/5wjj8v/saintodhrans_igs_rep_page/)

All games I have are Humble gift links.  I'm really just trying to get rid of them, so I'm not gonna be very cut-throat with these.  I'm willing to trade multiples for anything I want.

**Games I Have**

[A Virus Named Tom](http://store.steampowered.com/app/207650/)

[Dangerous High School Girls in Trouble](http://store.steampowered.com/app/27400/)

[Double Fine Adventure Documentary](http://store.steampowered.com/app/402590/)

[Dusty Revenge%3A Co-Op Edition](http://store.steampowered.com/app/252430/)

[JumpJet Rex](http://store.steampowered.com/app/329460/)

[Monster Loves You](http://store.steampowered.com/app/226740/)

[Potatoman Seeks the Troof](http://store.steampowered.com/app/328500/)

[Streamline](http://store.steampowered.com/app/252850/)

[Super Hexagon](http://store.steampowered.com/app/221640/)

[Team Indie](http://store.steampowered.com/app/302850/)

[Thirty Flights of Loving](http://store.steampowered.com/app/214700/)

**Games I Want**

Axiom Verge

Nobunaga's Ambition: Sphere of Influence

Galactic Civilizations III

Urban Empire

The Magic Circle

Wasteland 2

Furi

Inside

Transistor

Endless Legend

Icey

Europa Universalis 4 DLC

Orwell

Redout

Project Highrise

Feel free to offer anything else and I'll see if I like it, but I'm mostly into strategy and management games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 05:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sperm-induced parthenogenesis? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boxhead (X-post from /r/CoverTheFace) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 03:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 01:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ganondorf doesn't reincarnate like Link and Zelda, do.  He's just the same Ganondorf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell her to try Pizza Lounge.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How could you not mention that "bubblers" are water fountains? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 20:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's give credit where it's due.  Rick Perry is capable of learning new information and changing his view.  https://www.nytimes.com/2017/01/19/us/politics/rick-perry-energy-department.html?_r=0  That's better than a lot of Republicans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 20:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look, just trust me on this, but God told me he was cool with everything I do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 20:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Stanford_prison_experiment  This is probably the archetypical example, unless /u/WhatAnArtist has a better one.  This is just what I first think of, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 20:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to imagine the advisors outside the room, holding up the diseased corpse of Murad and shaking it around, trying to convince Ibrhim he's really dead and not just pretending. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 20:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our TAs got in some minor trouble with the professor when the midterm they designed had a mean of 90 because it fucked up the bell curve.  The average for the previous exam was something like 70.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, he did say "reportedly."  I don't know what more you expect other than that it was reported. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought this was gonna be the ivory guy who wants to buy Stampey, and Homer tells Lisa that he's less likely to want Stampey's ivory than someone who has little ivory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, see, money is like food at an all you can eat buffet.  Eventually you just get full of money and don't want anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only thing I could find was a 2013 story from Maine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cruz consistently acts like he's never going to have to deal with people ever again.  He really needs to learn that compromising today can help you achieve your goals tomorrow.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who invented amazingly accurate cannons!  They were hitting a panda-sized target at incredible distances.  China could probably use that kind of technological innovation.  But *noooooooooooo*, we need to focus on martial arts, instead.  That'll be a big help when the Mongols arrive.  We'll just karate chop them into submission. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Evil, and it doesn't work" is a pretty good motto for GOP policies.  What's even the point of being cruel *and* financially irrational?  At least if you're only one of those you have an excuse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dodge_v._Ford_Motor_Co.  It was more than just the increased pay, but basically Ford was investing profits back into the business and they didn't like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If only he had been the God Emperor of the US and not one congressman out of hundreds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Certainly, gentlemen, it ought to be the happiness and glory of a representative to live in the strictest union, the closest correspondence, and the most unreserved communication with his constituents. Their wishes ought to have great weight with him; their opinion, high respect; their business, unremitted attention. It is his duty to sacrifice his repose, his pleasures, his satisfactions, to theirs; and above all, ever, and in all cases, to prefer their interest to his own. But his unbiassed opinion, his mature judgment, his enlightened conscience, he ought not to sacrifice to you, to any man, or to any set of men living. These he does not derive from your pleasure; no, nor from the law and the constitution. They are a trust from Providence, for the abuse of which he is deeply answerable. **Your representative owes you, not his industry only, but his judgment; and he betrays, instead of serving you, if he sacrifices it to your opinion.**

-Edmund Burke, emphasis mine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if it's what he has in mind, but the big Republican push to nip marriage equality in the bud around 2004 would be a pretty good example to me.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, Ford got sued by shareholders for wasting profits on things like "paying employees decently." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alien Queen 2020 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which hero deserved to lose? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Metroid Prime was my first, and I absolutely loved it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no!  My baby food! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I root for all the Kung Fu Panda villains.  All of them deserve it more than Po does.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Linus_(mythology)  Hercules did murder his music teacher for reprimanding Hercules for his musical errors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Gen. Flynn certainly has a story to tell, and he very much wants to tell it, should the circumstances permit. ... No reasonable person, who has the benefit of advice from counsel, would submit to questioning in such a highly politicized, witch-hunt environment without assurances against unfair prosecution," Robert Kelner, Flynn's lawyer, said in a statement late Thursday.

Isn't immunity "assurances against unfair prosecution?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did some research, and apparently Burdick v. United States "suggested that a pardon carries an imputation of guilt and that acceptance carries a confession of guilt."  So I guess it isn't a definite thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...the article?  Like, this one?  At the top of the page?  

Mike Flynn, President Donald Trumps former national security adviser, has told the Federal Bureau of Investigation and congressional officials investigating the Trump campaigns potential ties to Russia that he is willing to be interviewed in exchange for a grant of immunity from prosecution, according to officials with knowledge of the matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't accepting a pardon considered an admission of guilt, as well?  By pardoning Flynn Trump would be legally saying that the accusations against Flynn are correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happened in 1998?  Are you referring to Lewinsky?  Because considering what Gingrich and Hastert were up to, I'm reasonably sure that Clinton kept the high ground. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you know why Thrawn is loyal to the Empire?  Wasn't he just some random alien they ran into who was disliked by his own people?  Why does he give a shit about the Empire, and why does he care more than the people who grew up in the Republic as it transitioned into the Empire? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't necessarily link that to intelligence so much as experience.  If you just came out of someone's stomach and had never seen that kind of automatic door before, you could be Xenobert Morphstein but it doesn't mean you'd know how the door works intuitively. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Sir, please don't grab the statues." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that gets me Darth Maul first... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They try not to look down.  So long as they avoid mirrors, it's all good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Priest of Moloch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can find lots of stuff about Erin Rommel.  I don't know about any individual soldiers, though, except for some Luftwaffe folks.  Horrido! is just all about some of the top Luftwaffe aces: https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/1320355.Horrido_Fighter_Aces_Of_The_Luftwaffe  I read it in college and liked it a lot.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was actually abducted and murdered after being abandoned at the mall, so luckily it never came up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
