<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2472</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 16:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "Whenever they see the President use the word 'fake,' it ought to set off alarm bells."

Let's call it the Trump Rule!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 21:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for revealing yourself as a fucking Trojan horse, Bernie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 21:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sen. Sanders is being used as Trojan horse to fracture the Democrats.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 18:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Meanwhile, there are several ongoing investigations in Congress, with the two most significant ones carried out by the House and Senate Intelligence Committees. But these inquiries suffer from the same flaw: They are supervised by Republicans. The situation is especially dire with the House Intelligence Committee, now that the escapades of its chairman, Rep. Devin Nunes of California, have revealed him to have a toddlers sense of personal responsibility. Even worse, the ultimate authority in the House, Speaker Paul Ryan, has demonstrated his own lack of integrity by refusing to ask Nunes to recuse himself. The Senate Intelligence Committee has a somewhat stronger track record of conducting thorough, credible investigations, such as its reports on torture and the pre-war intelligence on Iraqs imaginary weapons of mass destruction. But even in these cases their work did not ask obvious questions and took years to complete. If they turn in a similar performance this time, well be past the 2020 elections before theyre done. Moreover, while the committees GOP chairman Sen. Richard Burr of North Carolina, and its ranking member Democratic Sen. Mark Warner of Virginia, are making a public show of bipartisan resolve, Burr was a vociferous 2016 supporter of Trump  and at the request of the White House called media outlets to anonymously push back on their Russia stories. [...] With Congress, the investigations should be conducted not by regular committees, all controlled by the majority Republican party, but by a well-resourced special select committee like the ones that investigated Watergate and intelligence agency abuses in the 1970s, Iran-contra in the 1980s, and alleged Clinton administration misconduct in the 1990s. Many Democrats support this, and Republican Sen. John McCain of Arizona joined them in the wake of the Rep. Nuness peculiar behavior. Ideally such a select committee would have an equal number of members from each party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia Investigation Heading Toward a Train Wreck Because Republicans Dont Care What Happened </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 18:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is Trump attacking the Freedom Caucus? Simple: They won, he lost </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 18:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "I think the biggest problem here is you have the president not wanting to accept the conclusion that Russia tried to interfere in the election and that there is going to be an investigation in this, whether he likes it or not," Todd said. "The source of all of the current problems for this West Wing right now, for this presidency right now, all stems from that tweet where the president accused President Obama of wiretapping him." "This has all been self-inflicted. The Russia cloud is dark enough," Todd continued. "This sort of Nunes Keystone Cop situation has made it that much worse. And again, it all stems from the fact that the president himself will not accept the idea that there is going to be a Russian investigation." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump mocks Chuck Todd's appearance, Russia reporting in Saturday morning tweet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That must be the reason why the FBI is ["investigating the nature of any links between individuals associated with the Trump campaign and the Russian government, and whether there was any coordination between the campaign and Russias efforts. As with any counterintelligence investigation this will also include an assessment of whether any crimes were committed."](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZO8MaaaGYRE) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 01:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If true, that might be the reason why his lawyer went public/leaked the immunity request to the WSJ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 00:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ["I repeat again, the senator from Kentucky is now working for Vladimir Putin.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bcuB42e2eCM) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paramount looks to Disney model to recover after string of flops: Hollywood studio to make more family movies and rebrand TV channel after duds such as 'Ben-Hur' and 'Star Trek Beyond' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 00:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Why are these divisive articles still circulating?

Look at OP account, redditor for 8 minutes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. 

Edit: A redditor for 8 minutes, nothing suspicious here at all. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Several current American officials identified the White House officials as Ezra Cohen-Watnick, the senior director for intelligence at the National Security Council, and Michael Ellis, a lawyer who works on national security issues at the White House Counsels Office and formerly worked on the staff of the House Intelligence Committee. A White House spokesperson declined to comment. Mr. Cohen-Watnick is a former Defense Intelligence Agency official who was originally brought to the White House by Michael T. Flynn, the former national security adviser. The officials said that earlier this month, shortly after Mr. Trump wrote on Twitter about being wiretapped on the orders of President Barack Obama, Mr. Cohen-Watnick began reviewing highly classified reports detailing the intercepted communications of foreign officials. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The Trump administration has told Congress it plans to approve a multibillion-dollar sale of F-16 fighter jets to Bahrain without the human rights conditions imposed by the Obama administration.[...] Lockheed had lobbied strenuously for the sales approval, even as rights groups and pro-democracy activists urged the administration not to jettison human rights conditions. Brian Dooley of the Washington-based group Human Rights First said decoupling the sale from such conditions would encourage further repression and fuel instability during a tense period for Bahrain. The sale will send exactly the wrong signal to the dictatorship: that the White House thinks the political crackdown is not just morally acceptable but also not dangerous, when in fact its whats fuelling the countrys instability, Dooley said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump administration drops human rights conditions to sell fighter jets to Bahrain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 04:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  [Trump](http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-elections/donald-trump-ivanka-trump-creepiest-most-unsettling-comments-a-roundup-a7353876.html): You know whos one of the great beauties of the world, according to everybody? And I helped create her. Ivanka. My daughter, Ivanka. Shes 6 feet tall, shes got the best body. She made a lot money as a modela tremendous amount.


Well, she seems very qualified!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 04:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They didn't need to change the votes all over the country, after all the popular vote is irrelevant when it comes to winning the presidency in our system. What they needed to do is change the vote in some battleground states and guess what? Donald Trump won the Electoral College by just 70,000 votes in three key battleground states.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 04:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the end of the AC360 segment, CNNs whataboutism expert Jeffrey Lord start yapping about ten former presidents who hired family members as advisors or in cabinet positions   mentioned Abraham Lincoln   John Kennedy as examples. The former WH ethics lawyer then shut him down by reminding everyone that all that happened before nepotism law was introduced in the late 60s; and the law came about precisely because of the Kennedy brothers situation.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 02:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just don't think that we should dismiss the possibility that the Russians hacked the voting machines. In Europe,  countries like Netherlands is taking the idea very seriously. 

From [Guardian](https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/feb/02/dutch-will-count-all-election-ballots-by-hand-to-thwart-cyber-hacking) article published last February:

 Dutch will count all election ballots by hand to thwart hacking - Ministers want no repeat of US-Russia controversy in the March poll that could see Geert Wilders far-right party win power: Dutch authorities will count by hand all the votes cast in next months general elections, ditching vulnerable computer software to thwart any cyber hacking bid, a senior minister has said. I cannot rule out that state actors may try to benefit from influencing political decisions and public opinion in the Netherlands, interior minister Ronald Plasterk said in a letter to parliament on Wednesday.[...] Dutch officials are already on alert for signs of possible cyber hacking following allegations by US intelligence agencies that Russia may have meddled in Novembers US presidential polls to help secure Donald Trumps victory. Plasterk told parliament that fears over the vulnerabilities of the software used by the countrys election committee had raised questions about whether the upcoming elections could be manipulated. He insisted in a letter to MPs that no shadow of a doubt should hang over the results of the parliamentary polls, which some analysts predict could result in a five-party coalition. Therefore the interior ministry and the election committee had decided to calculate the results based on a manual count. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but [Admiral Rogers](https://www.nytimes.com/2017/03/20/us/politics/james-comey-mike-rogers-transcript-excerpts.html) also told the committee: 

 "I would highlight we are a foreign intelligence organization, not a domestic intelligence organization. So it would be fair to say, we are probably not the best organization to provide a more complete answer."

Director Comey replied to the same question with one word "No". But given what Comey told [the House Judiciary Committee](http://www.cnn.com/2016/09/28/politics/fbi-james-comey-election-cyberattacks/) back in September, I think that a full and updated answer is needed:

 There have been a variety of scanning activities which is a preamble for potential intrusion activities as well as some attempted intrusions at voter database registrations beyond those we knew about in July and August. We are urging the states just to make sure that their deadbolts are thrown and their locks are on and to get the best information they can from DHS just to make sure their systems are secure  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  In the report, Steele spoke of an "established operational liaison between the TRUMP team and the Kremlin an intelligence exchange had been running between them for at least 8 years." Members of the Obama administration believe, based on analysis they saw from the intelligence community, that the information exchange claimed by Steele continued into the election. "This is a three-headed operation," said one former official, setting out the case, based on the intelligence: Firstly, hackers steal damaging emails from senior Democrats. Secondly, the stories based on this hacked information appear on Twitter and Facebook, posted by thousands of automated "bots", then on Russia's English-language outlets, RT and Sputnik, then right-wing US "news" sites such as Infowars and Breitbart, then Fox and the mainstream media. Thirdly, Russia downloads the online voter rolls. [...] For instance, the US intelligence agencies said last October that the voter rolls had been "scanned and probed" from a server in Russia. But the Russian government was never shown to have been responsible. There are either a series of coincidences or there is a conspiracy of such reach and sophistication that it may take years to unravel.  


The intelligence agencies should really look into the possibilities that the Russians hacked the voting machines on election day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you read the article?

 The other national security leaders didnt like the idea, and White House officials thought the announcement should be a coordinated message backed by multiple agencies, the source says. An op-ed doesnt have the same stature, it comes from one person. The op-ed would not have mentioned whether the FBI was investigating Donald Trumps campaign workers or others close to him for links to the Russians interference in the election, a second source with knowledge of the request tells Newsweek. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the article:

 The other national security leaders didnt like the idea, and White House officials thought the announcement should be a coordinated message backed by multiple agencies, the source says. An op-ed doesnt have the same stature, it comes from one person. The op-ed would not have mentioned whether the FBI was investigating Donald Trumps campaign workers or others close to him for links to the Russians interference in the election, a second source with knowledge of the request tells Newsweek. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, perhaps reality is catching up with him! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  While the presidents approval rating has fallen into the 30s, Melanias has soared. Fifty-two percent of Americans said they have a favorable view of her, while 32 percent view her unfavorably, according to a recent CNN/ORC poll. Three percent have never heard of her, while 12 percent have no opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump: Melania should give me tips on improving poll numbers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Valerian' Trailer Takes Viewers to a 'City of a Thousand Planets' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Public health advocates say those plans at best duplicate those of the Obama White House and at worst could set back efforts to tackle a problem that contributes to more than 47,000 deaths per year. Many experts advocate treatment and support services over jail for drug abusers, saying they reduce the risk of a person committing another crime. The emerging Trump strategy, including failed plans to repeal Obamacare protections that enabled millions to get substance abuse treatment, "doesn't bode well for the public health approach, such as it is," said Leo Beletsky, a law professor at Northeastern University who specializes in health and drug policy. He points to Republican rhetoric about criminalizing the crisis, as well as proposed funding cuts to research and treatment. "This new shift will certainly make the situation much worse," Beletsky added. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After pledging to solve opioid crisis, Trumps strategy underwhelms </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There are already signs that Trumps sagging approval rating is raising the possibility of a stunning upset in an upcoming congressional election in suburban Atlanta. The race, to fill the vacant seat held by Health and Human Services Secretary Tom Price, couldnt be more relevant to the health care debate. One public poll shows the Democratic front-runner, Jon Ossoff, narrowly leading several of his GOP opponents in a runoffthis in a conservative district that has elected Republicans to Congress for over four decades. Fearing an embarrassing defeat, the partys leading House super PAC is spending over $2 million on attack ads connecting Ossoff with Nancy Pelosi. Of the 36 at-risk House Republicans, according to The Cook Political Reports ratings, 28 represent urban or suburban districts where Trump isnt particularly popular. In last years election, most of these GOP representatives significantly outperformed Trump as voters distinguished between the presidential nominee and the record of their own member of Congress. But with Trump as president, that distinction is harder to make. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dems Could Take House in 2018 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I don't love Trump, but there are far greater evils that he's trying to get you all to see.

With all due respect, are you delusional?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for a well   informative comment. Hopefully we'll get out of these war zones asap.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poll: Trump less trusted than news outlets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Obama administration sent a small number of special forces and military advisors to Iraq mostly and Syria. What we are seeing now is rapid increase in both countries. The [Pentagon is also expanding their operations into Yemen](https://www.bloomberg.com/politics/articles/2017-03-05/u-s-military-deepens-yemen-role-in-striking-al-qaeda-affiliate) to assist KSA in the messy civil war inside Yemen.

And I'm not sure if Gen. Mattis will be able to, or even willing, to not drag us into war with Iran for example. From reading about him he seems rather eager to engage the Iranians.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This moron is dragging us into more wars. At this moment US troops are fighting in Iraq, Syria and Yemen as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope.


[Peter Alexander](https://twitter.com/PeterAlexander/status/846782739558928384):

 Monday: Nunes' spox: Comey "couldn't come in tomorrow as we hoped." Today: FBI: No official request for Comey's testimony was ever received. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go back to t_d, your safe place.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're sick, please get help right away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like Nunes finally found Comey's phone number. /s  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Some attorneys believe the Justice Department is intentionally dragging its feet in the Hawaii case because the 9th Circuit rotates the three-judge panels assigned to motions every month, with the next swap-out due Saturday. The 9th Circuit also announces the panels publicly, although not in advance. This months consists of two Obama-appointed judges  Morgan Christen and John Owens  along with George W. Bush appointee Milan Smith. Maybe they looked at the motions panel this month and felt it was maybe, 2-1 [against them]  at best and they didnt see any percentage in that so they figured lets see whats up next month, Tobias said. It does not bespeak a lot of confidence in the merits of their position if the strategy here really is waiting until the calendar flips over on Saturday, University of Texas law professor Stephen Vladeck added. Its both a long shot and strange one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Trump stalling a travel ban appeal at 9th Circuit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why Gen. Flynn was fired? Why they lied repeatedly about their contacts with the Russians? Why the WH is working alongside Nunes to undercut the House investigation?

We don't have clear evidence yet but that's why the FBI and other agencies are conducting their investigations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   It also "appears" shady how the Dems act with all of this, like they are trying to ruin the man to avoid what he uncovered having any impact

Yeah, he "uncovered" something so damaging that he didn't share it with his own committee after a whole week. Something so scandalous that he changed his stories no less than 3 times in a single day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the reason for any coordination? There was a quid pro quo where the Russians help Trump during the campaign and in return he lifts the sanctions and shifts the US policy regarding Ukraine. Guess how Gen. Flynn was caught? He was talking to the Russian ambassador about the sanctions. And that why the investigation covers situation that occurred after the elections to look for evidence of quid pro quo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   House intelligence committee chair Devin Nunes canceled a public hearing on Russian meddling in the election scheduled for Tuesday, saying the time was needed to hear privately from FBI director James Comey and Adm. Mike Rogers, the head of the National Security Agency. But Nunes never scheduled Comeys and Rogers reappearance before the committee  a committee spokesman said Tuesday that Nunes was still trying to set it up  and Democrats now question whether Nunes maneuver was intended to kill momentum the committee had built after its first public session March 20.


Edit: [Peter Alexander](https://twitter.com/PeterAlexander/status/846782739558928384):

 Monday: Nunes' spox: Comey "couldn't come in tomorrow as we hoped." Today: FBI: No official request for Comey's testimony was ever received. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nunes never set private session with Comey, Rogers that he said would be held today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The democrats you say?  The director of the FBI told the entire world last week that they are: 

 investigating the nature of any links between individuals associated with the Trump campaign and the Russian government, and whether there was any coordination between the campaign and Russias efforts. As with any counterintelligence investigation this will also include an assessment of whether any crimes were committed."

An investigation that started in July.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her lawyer sent a letter to White House Counsel Don McGahn and the Justice Department. The DOJ responded by stating that Yates testimony could be covered by executive privilege, her lawyer wrote back that there may not be a reason for Yates to withhold information related to former National Security Advisor Michael Flynn's contacts with Russia because top Trump administration officials have already discussed the situation publicly.  

Then Rep. Devin Nunes the chairman of the House Intelligence Committee canceled the Russia hearing on the SAME DAY the letter is dated. The sequence of events makes it clear that the WH pressured Nunes to cancel the hearing, so in effect the WH blocked her from testifying.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Allegedly my ass, read the [letters](http://apps.washingtonpost.com/g/documents/national/read-the-letters-detailing-how-sally-yates-was-blocked-from-testifying-on-russia/2390/). 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Where are the correspondences from Yates lawyer to the White House or White House to Yates lawyer?

Her lawyer sent [a letter](http://apps.washingtonpost.com/g/documents/national/read-the-letters-detailing-how-sally-yates-was-blocked-from-testifying-on-russia/2390/) to White House Counsel Don McGahn, it's on page 1. The DOJ responded to her lawyer on page 6.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The Trump administration aimed to bar former acting Attorney General Sally Yates from testifying at a House Intelligence Committee hearing on its Russia investigation, according to a letter obtained by NBC News. The Justice Department raised concerns that Yates' possible testimony, which was set to take place this week, could be covered by executive privilege. In a letter to White House counsel dated Friday, Yates' lawyer said she nonetheless intended to testify. The lawyer wrote that there may not be a reason for Yates to withhold information related to former National Security Advisor Michael Flynn's contacts with Russia because top Trump administration officials have already discussed the situation publicly. [...] The House panel's Republican chairman, Rep. Devin Nunes of California, canceled the Russia hearing on the same day the letter is dated. It was originally set for Tuesday.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump DOJ aimed to block Sally Yates' testimony on Russia: Lawyer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Former acting attorney general Sally Yates was notified earlier this month by the Justice Department that the Trump administration considers a great deal of her possible testimony to be barred from discussion in the House intelligence Committee's investigation between Russian officials and the Trump campaign, according to a series of letters reviewed by The Post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Read the letters detailing how Sally Yates was blocked from testifying on Russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To the media, no more distraction please, focus on the real story.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Trump explains uranium](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nCnKtzQpCSs): 

 You know what uranium is, right? Its this thing called nuclear weapons. And other things. Like lots of things are done with uranium. Including some bad things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last week the director of the FBI told the entire world that they are: 

 investigating the nature of any links between individuals associated with the Trump campaign and the Russian government, and whether there was any coordination between the campaign and Russias efforts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 22:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Kushner has deleted ALL of his tweets!](https://twitter.com/jaredkushner?lang=en) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Kushner has deleted ALL of his tweets!](https://twitter.com/jaredkushner?lang=en) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Late December 2016](https://www.nytimes.com/2017/03/27/us/politics/senate-jared-kushner-russia.html?hp action=click pgtype=Homepage clickSource=story-heading module=first-column-region region=top-news WT.nav=top-news _r=0)

 Until now, the White House had acknowledged only an early December meeting between Mr. Kislyak and Mr. Kushner, which occurred at Trump Tower and was also attended by Michael T. Flynn, who would briefly serve as the national security adviser. Later that month, though, Mr. Kislyak requested a second meeting, which Mr. Kushner asked a deputy to attend in his stead, officials said. At Mr. Kislyaks request, Mr. Kushner later met with Sergey N. Gorkov, the chief of Vnesheconombank, which the United States placed on its sanctions list after President Vladimir V. Putin of Russia annexed Crimea and began meddling in Ukraine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was reported in the [New York Times](https://www.nytimes.com/2017/03/27/us/politics/senate-jared-kushner-russia.html?hp action=click pgtype=Homepage clickSource=story-heading module=first-column-region region=top-news WT.nav=top-news _r=0)

 **Senate Committee to Question Jared Kushner Over Meetings With Russians**: ..A White House spokeswoman, Hope Hicks, confirmed those meetings, saying in an interview that nothing of consequence was discussed and that they went nowhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [A timeline of events that unfolded during the election appears to support the FBI's investigation into Trump and Russia](http://www.businessinsider.com/updated-trump-russia-election-timeline-fbi-2017-3) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [John Schindler](https://twitter.com/20committee/status/846392049175859200):

 Gotta say that Team Trump is pretty awful at the whole try-to-hide-the-conspiracy thing. "Meet me on the WH lawn after dark" -- Really? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed. According to [the BBC](http://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-38589427) an intelligence task-force was created in April 2016 after the CIA received a tip from an eastern European country.

 Last April, the CIA director was shown intelligence that worried him. It was - allegedly - a tape recording of a conversation about money from the Kremlin going into the US presidential campaign. It was passed to the US by an intelligence agency of one of the Baltic States. The CIA cannot act domestically against American citizens so a joint counter-intelligence taskforce was created. The taskforce included six agencies or departments of government. Dealing with the domestic, US, side of the inquiry, were the FBI, the Department of the Treasury, and the Department of Justice. For the foreign and intelligence aspects of the investigation, there were another three agencies: the CIA, the Office of the Director of National Intelligence and the National Security Agency, responsible for electronic spying.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Baghdad Sean: "Jared was a volunteer of the campaign" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The POS Grassley is trying to discredit them. 

 When political opposition research becomes the basis for law enforcement or intelligence efforts, it raises substantial questions about the independence of law enforcement and intelligence from politics, Grassley wrote in the letter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jared Kushner had undisclosed meeting with Sergey Gorkov, the head of Russias state-owned Vnesheconombank, which has been under sanctions since the annexation of Crimea in 2014 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coal executive: Trump cant bring mining jobs back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  and the president.

And what happens if the president himself is the subject of the investigation?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ryan is in a weak position now. If the GOP and the White House want the Democrats to help with the Healthcare and tax reform, as they indicated the past few days, then the Democrats must demand an independent commission to investigate RussiaGate as a concession for their willingness to work with the GOP and the WH. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who are you going to believe, Lyin' Donnie or the Germans? 

A rule of thumb when it comes to Trump's White House, if they deny it then it is true.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Is he really that stupid?

Yep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's utterly ridiculous to expect Nunes, a member of Trump transition team, to conduct a fair and objective investigation. Time and again he showed his willingness to help the White House by prejudging his own investigation, working alongside the WH and talking to reporters to downplay the latest media revelations about Trump and his associates and so on. 

The Democrats must demand an independent commission to investigate RussiaGate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who are you going to believe, Lyin' Donnie or the Germans? 

The moron tweeted "Despite what you have heard from the FAKE NEWS, I had a GREAT meeting with German Chancellor Angela Merkel. Nevertheless, Germany owes.....vast sums of money to NATO   the United States must be paid more for the powerful, and very expensive, defense it provides to Germany!"


A rule of thumb when it comes to Trump's White House, if they deny it, then it is true.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 22:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best comment by [Paul Manafort](https://www.nytimes.com/2017/02/14/us/politics/russia-intelligence-communications-trump.html?_r=0) on his connection to Russia: 

 " I have never knowingly spoken to Russian intelligence officers ... Its not like these people wear badges that say, Im a Russian intelligence officer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill Kristol: [Looking forward to @POTUS statement supporting democratic protests in Russia, calling for release of Navalny.](https://twitter.com/BillKristol/status/845973690969927680)


Rick Wilson replied: [@BillKristol @Evan_McMullin @POTUS Good luck with that.](https://twitter.com/TheRickWilson/status/846037916392542208) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Looking forward to @POTUS statement supporting democratic protests in Russia, calling for release of Navalny.](https://twitter.com/BillKristol/status/845973690969927680) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever he's on AC360 I just mute the TV. There is not point in  listening to his nonsense anymore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a previous [Politico report](http://www.politico.com/story/2017/03/boris-epshteyn-television-networks-behavior-235787) comrade Boris comes off as a real jerk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 19:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By giving in to the Freedom Caucus demands he lost the support of the Tuesday group, the moderate Republicans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 19:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Lovett, co-host of podcast Pod Saves America, criticized the panels on the network that include staunch advocates of Trump. You turn it on and theres a big giant panel " "You mean Jeffrey Lord and Kayleigh McEnany?," Stelter asked. **Absolutely, and you look at that giant panel, and its smart person, smart person, smart person, stupid person, smart person, smart person, smart person, bullshit factory.**

Add Jack ~~Johnson~~ Kingston to the list. 

Edit: It's actually Jack Kingston, thanks [TheSubtleSaiyan](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/61moe0/exobama_speech_writer_slams_cnn_for_putting/dffsq9l/) for the correction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-Obama speech writer slams CNN for putting 'stupid' Trump surrogates on panels </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 19:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 19:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've no problem with that as long as the movies are good and they are expanding the SW universe and not focusing solely on Skywalker family. It's a big galaxy with a story that spans ten of thousand of years, get out there and give us something different.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harrison Ford called himself a 'schmuck' after plane mishap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 19:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 18:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You can't tweet your way through it. You can't threaten and intimidate and say I'll walk away. It's more complicated. Schumer said Trump had a basic lack of competence that would prevent him from getting things done in politics.  He also said Trump had gravitated too much toward hard-right wealthy special interests  killing his chances to compromise with Democrats and moderate Republicans. They're going to repeat the same mistake they made on Trumpcare with tax reform, Schumer said about Trump and his far-right cohorts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chuck Schumer says Trump will also fail at tax reform because of basic lack of competence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 18:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 18:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the GOP and the White House want the Democrats to help with the Healthcare and tax reform, then the Democrats must demand an independent commission to investigate RussiaGate as a concession for their willingness to work with the GOP and the WH. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 18:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, the Democrats should demand an independent commission to investigate RussiaGate as a concession for their willingness to work with the GOP and the WH. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 18:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's either going to say 'I don't recall' or follow [Paul Manafort](https://www.nytimes.com/2017/02/14/us/politics/russia-intelligence-communications-trump.html?_r=0)'s lead and says " I have never knowingly spoken to Russian intelligence officers ... Its not like these people wear badges that say, Im a Russian intelligence officer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 17:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Trump's timeline on tax reform.](https://twitter.com/DLin71/status/845466426609684481) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 00:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't even have the courage to use your real reddit account, better to stay in t_d delusional chamber. 

Edit: Liberals talked against drone program during the Obama administration. We didn't cheer on him for expanding the program which led to major civilian causalities. I supported Obama and voted for him twice but I sure as fuck didn't agree the drones policy.

Why don't you people have the fucking decency to stand-up once against your own party, rather than encouraging them? Before going back to your La La land, try to educate yourself about the real world.

[Obamas bloody legacy: 5 years of drone war - On the 5th anniversary of the Obama presidency's first covert drone strike, too many questions remain unanswered](http://www.salon.com/2014/01/23/obamas_bloody_legacy_5_years_of_drone_war/)

[Leaked report shows high civilian death toll from CIA drone strikes](http://www.salon.com/2013/07/22/leaked_report_shows_high_civilian_death_toll_from_cia_drone_strikes/)     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 00:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Senior military and defense officials are investigating reports that scores of civilians  potentially nearly 200  were killed in a U.S. airstrike in the Iraqi city of Mosul last week. Local officials and residents said Thursday that dozens of people were buried in collapsed buildings after the air raid in the al-Aghawat al-Jadidah district triggered a huge explosion, according to Reuters. The strike comes in the same month as two other high-profile strikes in Syria, where the U.S.-led coalition is also fighting ISIS. In total, the three strikes have resulted in unconfirmed reports of upwards of 350 civilian casualties.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CENTCOM Investigates Whether U.S. Airstrikes Killed 200 Civilians In Mosul </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 00:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Three sources briefed on Trumps recent discussions told the Times that the blame for the legislative failure has fallen on Priebus, who was in charge of coordinating an initial plan on ObamaCare repeal with Speaker Paul Ryan (R-Wis.). Health and Human Services Secretary Tom Price was also blamed for the failure, according to the report, while the president was reportedly annoyed with Jared Kushner, his adviser and son-in-law, who returned to Washington on Friday from a family skiing trip in Colorado.

They should blame Barron as well! Anyone but Dear Leader.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Priebus, Price facing blame after healthcare failure: report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Rep. Matt Gaetz to Politico](http://www.politico.com/story/2017/03/republicans-health-care-failure-agenda-future-236495)

 I dont know that we could pass a Mothers Day resolution right now, said Rep. Matt Gaetz, a freshman Republican from Florida who says hes still committed to revamping Obamacare. He spoke of the failure in apocalyptic terms, saying Republicans may have given away the 2018 midterm elections, ensured that Trump will get impeached by Democrats once theyre in power and potentially exiled themselves to years in the minority.[...] **This notion that well just pivot to tax reform and all will be well, I think, is fantasy,** Gaetz said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The original article is from [The Wall Street Journal](https://www.wsj.com/articles/ex-cia-director-mike-flynn-and-turkish-officials-discussed-removal-of-erdogan-foe-from-u-s-1490380426). 

As the Hill point out it was former CIA director James Woolsey, among others, who revealed the new info to WSJ. 

 The Journal report cites former CIA Director James Woolsey, who attended the meeting with Flynn and high-level Turkish officials, and others with details on what happened. Woolsey and the sources said the ideas that were discussed for dealing with Gulen were hypothetical.

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A reporter informed him that the vote had already been called off.

Oops! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A triple agent I guess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Michael Flynn, President Trumps former national security adviser, reportedly discussed ways to take a man wanted by the Turkish government out of the United States without going through the legal extradition process, according to The Wall Street Journal. [...] The Wall Street Journal report cites former CIA Director James Woolsey, who attended the meeting with Flynn and high-level Turkish officials, and others with details on what happened. Woolsey and the sources said the ideas that were discussed for dealing with Gulen were hypothetical. However, one plan was a covert step in the dead of night to whisk this guy away, Woolsey told the Wall Street Journal. He said he had walked into the middle of the conversation, and reportedly found the topic startling and the actions being discussed possibly illegal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flynn discussed how to 'whisk' away cleric wanted by Turkey: report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "He wants to see what happens, if the Democrats will try to come to him and work with him on healthcare." 

Lol, he can't get his own party to pass the bill.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  By Congressman Nunes actions, including his unilateral cancellation of next weeks hearings and his apparent flip-flopping on one of the key issues in the investigation, he has not only reinforced the view that Congress has repeatedly failed to conduct bipartisan oversight of important matters, he has maimed his committees ability to conduct a fair and credible investigation. Unless he changes his way of operating  and decides to be fully transparent with the House Intelligence Committees ranking member, Adam Schiff (D-Calif.) and the committee members from both sides of the aisle  any hearings or work product from the House Intelligence Committee will be viewed as an irrelevant, partisan judgment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Devin Nunes has jeopardized the oversight role of Congress </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually the comments on The Hill are insane but this one by'BecauseReasons' is really funny: 

------------


Conspiracies begin!

* From the Right: He's there to brief Trump on Obama's upcoming arrest.

* From the Left: He's there to warn Trump on Trump's upcoming arrest.

* From Russia: He's delivering Trump our check.

* From Poland: Who is Comey?

* From Mexico: How did he get over the wall?

* From the Secret Service: How did he get over the wall?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to the Hill 

 No meeting with Comey was listed on the president's public schedule. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Rep. Thomas Massie](https://twitter.com/RepThomasMassie/status/845243104554815490):

 If Exec branch tells Legislative branch "when 2 vote" "how 2 vote"   "what it will b allowed 2 work on if vote fails," is that a republic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The president doesnt care, White House budget director Mick Mulvaney reportedly told Paul Ryan when the beleaguered Speaker informed him he didnt have the votes to pass the bill late Thursday night. The president wants a vote.

What a child.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watching The Art of the Deal crumble: Trump finally admits Republicans may fail to pass Trumpcare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Omarosa - 'Every critic, every detractor will have to bow down to President Trump'](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zzSvzTTBALg)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something fishy is going on here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Edward James Olmos Joins Shane Black's 'Predator' Reboot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, no, hold on, hold on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The fact that the National Enquirer says Flynn is a Russian spy likely means Flynn isnt a Russian spy.

No, it means that Flynn is the scapegoat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The First Lady aka Ivanka is ready. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I am deadly serious about that exercise, he said. I do not talk about the government with him, and he does not talk about the business with us. Thats kind of a steadfast pact we made, and its something that we honor. But nearly two minutes later, Trump admitted that he will keep his father up to speed on some aspects of the business. Yeah, on the bottom line, profitability reports and stuff like that, but you know, thats about it, he said, adding that the updates will be probably quarterly. My father and I are very close, he said. I talk to him a lot. Were pretty inseparable.

As idiot as his father.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eric Trump will share business updates with father 'probably quarterly' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, he was a campaign volunteer after all, right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The morning after Inauguration Day, National Park Service communications chief Mike Litterst emailed White House press secretary Sean Spicer offering "any corrective messaging" about the inauguration attendance size, on behalf of acting National Park Service Director Mike Reynolds. The email is one of several released via a FOIA request from E E News. [...] Spicer responded to Litterst's offer, writing, "the aerial photos (Reynolds) mentioned would be great." The National Park Service then sent the White House close-up photographs of the National Mall which cut out the sparsely attended areas near the Washington Monument, making the Trump crowd sizes appear more impressive than the wider shots broadcast by television networks. Instead, these photos only focused on the first few blocks of the Mall right in front of the Capitol. They were also very different from official National Park Service photos released earlier this month -- in response to another FOIA request -- that compared the crowd sizes of the last three inaugurations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NPS worked with White House to push crowd size message </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the point! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top general: Trump State Dept. cuts would hurt military's efforts against Russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Nixon's lawyer John Dean agrees](http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/324940-nixon-wh-counsel-during-watergate-trump-wh-in-cover-up-mode): 

 Theres just never been any question in my mind about that. Ive been inside a cover-up. I know how they look and feel. And every signal they're sending is: Were covering this thing up, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pelosi blasts Trumps rookie error on ObamaCare repeal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Sen. Bob Casey (D-Pa.) announced on Thursday that he will not support Judge Neil Gorsuch's Supreme Court nomination, saying he had concerns about his judicial philosophy.[...] Casey's decision comes after Gorsuch wrapped up his testimony before the Judiciary Committee on Wednesday, with a committee and full Senate vote expected early next month. Republicans are expected to need 60 votes to get Gorsuch through the Senate, including the support of eight Democratic senators. Both sides are focusing on the 10 Democrats, including Casey, who are up for reelection in 2018 in states carried by Trump.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senate Dem facing 2018 reelection to oppose Gorsuch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Rep. Ted Lieu](https://twitter.com/tedlieu/status/844690335418765313)

 Congress doesn't work for @POTUS. Congress conducts oversight on @POTUS. Rep Nunes doesn't understand that and must resign his Chairmanship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's the video: House Intel Chmn Nunes tells @DavidCornDC he's never heard of Carter Page or Roger Stone via @MSNBC](https://twitter.com/kylegriffin1/status/843947131241226240) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [@DevinNunes @realDonaldTrump: Can you use Twitter in jail? Asking for a friend.](https://twitter.com/bravee1/status/844686009380061185)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [John Schindler](https://twitter.com/20committee/status/844630848905396227)

 If we are still a republic of laws, Nunes must be removed from HPSCI, stripped of clearances   prosecuted for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He did it publicly so Trump can claims that he has been "vindicated" like he did afterward.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Chairman Nunes is deeply compromised, and he cannot possibly lead an honest investigation.  Congress must create a comprehensive, independent, bipartisan commission to expose the full truth of the Trump-Russia connection, Pelosi said in a statement. [...] Pelosi called Nunes actions unprecedented and an act of diversion and desperation. Chairman Nunes actions are disrespectful of Ranking Member Schiff and the bipartisan membership of the Intel Committee, she said in the statement. Republicans are grasping at straws because the FBI Director confirmed that President Obama did not wiretap President Trump, and affirmed an investigation of coordination between the Russians and individuals affiliated with the Trump campaign in the election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pelosi: Intel chair Nunes is 'deeply compromised' on Russia investigation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Adam Schiff on Meet The Press: ](https://twitter.com/MeetThePress/status/844669163717246976) 
 
 .@RepAdamSchiff on Trump/Russia connection: "There is more than circumstantial evidence now...and is very much worthy of investigation." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Politico - March 2017

 [**Authorities looked into Manafort protg - An associate of an ex-Trump campaign chairman is suspected of connections to Russian intelligence.**](http://www.politico.com/story/2017/03/trump-russia-manafort-235850): U.S. and Ukrainian authorities have expressed interest in the activities of a Kiev-based operative with suspected ties to Russian intelligence who consulted regularly with Paul Manafort last year while Manafort was running Donald Trumps presidential campaign. The operative, Konstantin Kilimnik, came under scrutiny from officials at the Federal Bureau of Investigation and the State Department partly because of at least two trips he took to the U.S. during the presidential campaign, according to three international political operatives familiar with the agencies interest in Kilimnik. Kilimnik, a joint Russian-Ukrainian citizen who trained in the Russian army as a linguist, told operatives in Kiev and Washington that he met with Manafort during an April trip to the United States. And, after a late summer trip to the U.S., Kilimnik suggested that he had played a role in gutting a proposed amendment to the Republican Party platform that would have staked out a more adversarial stance towards Russia, according to a Kiev operative. The FBI declined to comment on Kilimnik, while the State Department did not respond to a request for comment. Its unclear if either agency launched any kind of official inquiry into Kilimnik, nor is it clear whether the interest from the U.S. authorities is ongoing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Politico - March 2017

 [**Authorities looked into Manafort protg - An associate of an ex-Trump campaign chairman is suspected of connections to Russian intelligence.**](http://www.politico.com/story/2017/03/trump-russia-manafort-235850): U.S. and Ukrainian authorities have expressed interest in the activities of a Kiev-based operative with suspected ties to Russian intelligence who consulted regularly with Paul Manafort last year while Manafort was running Donald Trumps presidential campaign. The operative, Konstantin Kilimnik, came under scrutiny from officials at the Federal Bureau of Investigation and the State Department partly because of at least two trips he took to the U.S. during the presidential campaign, according to three international political operatives familiar with the agencies interest in Kilimnik. Kilimnik, a joint Russian-Ukrainian citizen who trained in the Russian army as a linguist, told operatives in Kiev and Washington that he met with Manafort during an April trip to the United States. And, after a late summer trip to the U.S., Kilimnik suggested that he had played a role in gutting a proposed amendment to the Republican Party platform that would have staked out a more adversarial stance towards Russia, according to a Kiev operative. The FBI declined to comment on Kilimnik, while the State Department did not respond to a request for comment. Its unclear if either agency launched any kind of official inquiry into Kilimnik, nor is it clear whether the interest from the U.S. authorities is ongoing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to come out from wherever you are now to the real world once in a while.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Legally collected and illegally unmasked and spread throughout the government.

Lol, is this the new narrative in Trump's Land?  

 People are going to jail

Yeah, Trump and his team.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you miss the part where it was clearly stated that it was:  

 all legally collected foreign intelligence under the Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Act.

Your guy and his team were in touch with foreign agents and got caught by our intelligence agencies.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Roger Stone as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But we don't know for sure if the information was presented to him through the correct channels. You would think that at least Adam Schiff, the ranking member of the House Select Committee on Intelligence, would be present at the press conferees.  

Given Nunes past   current actions; the fact that he was part of Trump transition team I find it hard to trust him when it comes to matters regarding the investigations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dem: Manafort should testify before House intel panel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Through a leak.  

 [The information was "legally brought to him by sources who thought we should know it," Nunes said, though he provided little detail on the source.](http://thehill.com/policy/cybersecurity/325218-nunes-intelligence-community-collected-information-on-trump-transition) 

And he refused to reveal his "source".   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The more that he ignores facts, repeats falsehoods, demeans institutions and constantly reverses himself, the more the presidency will shrink in power, prestige, relevance and influence. Trumps approach to governing is therefore, ultimately, self-defeating. With every tweet alleging, for instance, that U.S. allies owe us money or that a free press is the enemy of the people, the presidency is diminished. With every press briefing where White House aides insistagainst all evidence to the contrarythat candidate Trump was wiretapped by President Obama, he is making himself less powerful. With every undercooked statement or policy rollout, he is defining the presidency down and charting a course for his own failure. And he is also damaging the institution of the presidency for his successors, who will have the challenging task of rebuilding the lost credibility of the office. He risks making that loss his most lasting legacy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Is Defining the Presidency Down </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I will say we have resolved the future of the franchise and believe me its an incredibly bright future. I think where its going will be the continuation of what the fans really wanted since T2. We have something this year that we will be announcing for the franchise. Its something were incredibly excited about and we think is the direction it needs to head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Major Terminator Franchise Announcement Is Coming in 2017, Says Skydances David Ellison </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I don't mind that, I'd would love to see Netflix or HBO producing Alastair Reynolds book series 'Revelation Space' or 'The Night's Dawn Trilogy' and 'The Commonwealth Saga' by Peter F. Hamilton.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Mass Effect Is the Sci-Fi Opera Television Needs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Star Trek: Discovery' cast in Toronto </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Star Trek: Discovery' cast in Toronto </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Democrats tried but failed Monday to force a House floor vote to push a key committee to request copies of President Trumps tax returns. It was the fourth time in as many weeks that Democrats sought to force the vote. Rep. Jared Polis (D-Colo.) attempted to offer a resolution and trigger a House floor vote, but was cut off by the Republican presiding over the House. Democrats plan to keep forcing debate on Trumps tax returns every week until Tax Day on April 18. Theyre hoping to put pressure on the Republicans who have said Trumps tax returns should be released, most of whom have declined to sign on to Democratic efforts pushing for the documents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP blocks Dem effort to request Trump tax returns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But by the end of the day, Republicans had hit upon their strategy. The longer this hangs out there, the more the cloud grows, House Intelligence Committee Chair Devin Nunes said to Comey near the end of the hearing. The suggestion was that Comeynot Trumphad put this cloud over the White House. This is a remarkable thing to say, given that its Trumps campaign that is under investigation for its ties to Russian intelligence.[...] Nunes also hinted that he would do his part to keep the Houses own investigation shallow and quick. He indicated that he was not interested in investigating people like Carter Page, Roger Stone, and Paul Manafort, all of whom have ties to Russia and Trump. (Incredibly, Nunes told Mother Jones reporter David Corn that he had no idea who Page and Stone were.) He suggested the investigation would be limited primarily to current White House personnel, which would drastically reduce its scope and kneecap the committees ability to get to the bottom of what really happened during the campaign.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The GOP is going to try to rush the Russian investigation. Democrats shouldnt let them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Trump Campaign Has Been Under Investigation Since July </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Focus on leaks meant to serve same purpose as Trump allegation about wiretapping: distract from possible collusion, Fallon wrote in response to GOP lawmakers lines of questioning about leaks to the media. To Members of House Intel deflecting real questions on Russia hack for partisan purposes: this threat isnt partisan, added former campaign manager Robby Mook, who has raised the alarm about Russias election meddling across the world since November. Anyone could be next." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clinton camp unloads on Comey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 20:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given the insane twist at the end of last episode I think they're serious about resolving it and moving on to something different in the next season.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 20:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A real quote from [America's craziest president](https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/828574430800539648) in recent history:

 Any negative polls are fake news </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spoilers - Kiefer Sutherland confirmed that the first season of 'Designated Survivor' would resolve the conspiracy plot that launched the series </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 19:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 16:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Trump](https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/155014799909064704):

 President @BarackObama's vacation is costing taxpayers millions of dollars----Unbelievable!

[Trump](https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/503973652522885120):

 Obamas motto: If I dont go on tax payer funded vacations   constantly fundraise then the terrorists win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 16:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From a report in February:


[Eric Trumps business trip cost US taxpayers nearly $100,000 in hotel bills. President Trump has previously blasted former Presidents' 'taxpayer funded vacations'](http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/eric-trump-business-trip-uruguay-taxpayers-cost-business-interests-president-donald-trump-a7562456.html)

 When President Trumps son, Eric, visited Uruguay for a Trump Organisation business trip in January, the US taxpayer paid almost $100,000 (80,000) to cover his security costs, a new report claims. 
Eric Trump visited the Trump Tower in Punta del Este for as little as two nights, according to local press. The bill for the Secret Service agents hotel rooms for the duration of his stay was $88,320. The US Embassy also paid $9,510 for diplomatic staff to support the Secret Service, bringing the total costs of the trip to $97,470. [...] During his visit, Eric Trump met with local business owners and property investors, and attended a party put on at Trump Tower to honour the VIP visit. One of the highlights of the evening was the performance of a song that Argentinian pop singer, Maxi Trusso, had written in President Trumps honour. The Presidents immediate family members are guaranteed state-funded security details, particularly on trips to foreign countries. However, President Trump has previously questioned whether the American taxpayer should fund extensive security on visits for non-official purposes. During the Obama administration, he took to Twitter multiple times to complain about taxpayer funded vacations which cost the American people millions of dollars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 16:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 16:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This what happen when you put a member of Trump transition team in charge of the House Russia probe!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 16:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What time is the hearing tomorrow?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 16:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not surprising considering that he was a member of Trump transition team   as the Washington Post revealed last month that the White House enlisted his service to undercut the congressional investigations into the Russia connections. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 16:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's doing what the White House asked him to do, to undercut the congressional investigations into the Russia connections. 

Edit: In the last press conference where Nunes repeated that nonsense , Adam Schiff corrected him by stating that they shouldn't prejudge the investigations.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 15:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  At a meeting of policymakers from the Group of 20 major economies around the world on Friday and Saturday, they were forced to drop their long-standing commitment to resist all kinds of protectionism in their communiqu because of U.S. opposition. No one is sure what comes next.[...] While watering down their commitment to trade, the guardians of the world economy failed to agree on how things should look like in the future. And for many policymakers who traveled to this picturesque German town, **the talks that just ended must have felt like a looking-glass experience, with countries like China and Brazil trying to convince the U.S. of the merits of the very economic order that America had created.**[...] Mnuchin was the first country representative to speak at the so-called global economy session; everyone around the table who spoke after him stood up for free trade, a G20 delegation source said, adding that Brazil reminded all of the dark days of protectionism. **It is a strange world when Brazil and China lecture the U.S. on free trade,** the official said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump blows up G20 trade consensus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 15:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [A billionaire makes us pay for his golf weekends and tells us we can't have food, health, science or art. #MAGA](https://twitter.com/originalgriz/status/842343392440901632) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you living in a cave or something? He's already blaming Obama and Clinton for the shit he's doing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  During the election any pro-Clinton would shoot the the front page filled with comments from users I rarely if ever see commenting anymore. Early indications show that support may not have been genuine. 

Fucking nonsense. She won the popular vote with 65 million votes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 22:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Asked about it at the press conference, Trump said, All we did was quote a certain very talented legal mind who was the one responsible for saying that on television. I didnt make an opinion on it. That was a statement made by a very talented lawyer on Fox. And so you shouldnt be talking to me, you should be talking to Fox. Trump was referring to Judge Andrew Napolitano, who made the claim on Fox News. Fox News cannot confirm Judge Napolitanos commentary, Smith said afterward. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News Has No Evidence Trump Was Wiretapped, Shepard Smith Says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 22:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Matrix Reboot Writer Says It May Not Be a Reboot After All: "All I can say at this point is no one could or should REBOOT the Matrix. People who know Animatrix and the comics understand." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 22:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 21:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See you in court! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Shep Smith says Fox News cannot confirm Judge Napolitanos commentary and knows of no evidence Trump was surveilled in any way.](https://twitter.com/mlcalderone/status/842815295291056130) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you really think there is nothing of substance regarding Trump's Russian connections, then ask yourself why Trump's team [kept lying to the American people time and again about contacts with the Russians?](http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2017/03/02/trump-teams-many-many-denials-contacts-russia/98625780/) Since the inauguration we found out more about his team constant contacts with the Russians. So far from the campaign alone we have:


* Paul Manafort, former Trump campaign manager

* Carter Page, former Trump foreign policy adviser

* Roger Stone, informal adviser

* General Michael Flynn, former Trump national security adviser

* Jeff Sessions, Trump attorney general

* Jared Kushner, Trump son-in-law and senior adviser


And ask yourself why did Flynn resigned? If his team was under surveillance, that means a federal judge found probable cause of crime in order to grant the FBI FISA and other warrants  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  By the way, with the CIA, I just want people to know, the CIA was hacked, and a lot of things taken  that was during the Obama years, Trump said. That was not during us.

What a fucking moron.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Three airport security programs implemented after the 9/11 terrorist attacks would get the axe under President Trumps budget proposal. The spending blueprint, released early Thursday, eliminates and reduces unauthorized and underperforming programs administered by [the Transportation Security Administration] TSA in order to strengthen screening at airport security checkpoints. The estimated savings would total $80 million annually, according to the proposal. The budget would reduce the Visible Intermodal Prevention and Response program. So-called VIPR teams sweep transit hubs, often using bomb-sniffing dogs, and are designed to serve as a visible security presence around airports, train stations and ports. Lawmakers increased the number of VIPR teams in an aviation bill last year to beef up aviation security following the bombing of an airport in Brussels. But Trumps proposal says the program achieves few Federal law enforcement priorities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three airport security programs axed under Trump budget </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the quote from the article indicate:

 McDonalds did not immediately respond to a press inquiry. 


The article was updated with a comment from McDonalds after the submission.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Freshman Rep. Brian Mast is linked to a Florida marketing company under investigation by federal regulators for allegedly pocketing millions of dollars in a patent scam. World Patent Marketing and its owner, Scott J. Cooper, are accused by the Federal Trade Commission of defrauding thousands of clients in the last few years to the tune of millions of dollars, and then harassing customers who threatened to report the scam. Mast, a Republican and military veteran who represents part of Palm Beach County, was named a member of the companys advisory board in February 2016, shortly before Cooper donated more than $5,000 to Masts election campaign. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Freshman lawmaker linked to company accused of million-dollar marketing scam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  @realDonaldTrump You are actually a disgusting excuse of a President and we would love to have @BarackObama back, also you have tiny hands, the McDonalds Twitter account posted at 9:16 a.m. It is unclear who tweeted the insult; McDonalds did not immediately respond to a press inquiry. The missive was retweeted more than 1,000 times before it was deleted some minutes later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McDonald's tweets, then deletes, Trump insult: 'Disgusting excuse' of a president </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 23:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Trump defends Obama wiretapping ~~charges~~ lies
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why The Matrix without Reeves would be a journey down the wrong rabbit hole </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 22:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why The Matrix without Reeves would be a journey down the wrong rabbit hole </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 22:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure that Trump will highlight Andrew Jackson contributions which are being recognized more and more! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The prospects for a fourth movie were almost as ambiguous as the trilogys famously complex plot. An article published on Tuesday said that the siblings Lana and Lilly Wachowski, who dreamed up and shot the original Matrix and its sequels, were not yet involved in the possible project. Nor was it clear how the narrative of the new installment, which The Hollywood Reporter described as a relaunch and a reboot, would tie in with the existing Matrix films. The participation of Keanu Reeves, who played the central figure, Neo, in all three films, was also an open question. In February, Mr. Reeves said he would take part in another Matrix film if the opportunity arose and if the Wachowskis were involved. I dunno, thatd be weird, but why not, he told Yahoo Movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 00:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #TrumpCare </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 00:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Donald Trump in 2002](http://nymag.com/nymetro/news/people/n_7912/):

 "**I've known Jeff for fifteen years. Terrific guy,**'' Trump booms from a speakerphone. "**He's a lot of fun to be with. It is even said that he likes beautiful women as much as I do, and many of them are on the younger side. No doubt about it -- Jeffrey enjoys his social life.**" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hulu, A+E Studios Teaming for Afghanistan War Drama 'One Million Steps' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 21:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And lizard people are real, right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
