<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject398</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 20:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once you are there for a while you become friends with some locals and they will help you. If you are moving around a lot it becomes more difficult. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 19:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on the country. Costa Rica is fairly expensive, prices are on par with the US. Most people overlook El Salvador, very cheap and very friendly people. I have spent 6 months there and haven't had or seen any problems. Get out of the bigs cities and into smaller cities.
You can rent a house in Santa Ana for less than $300 a month once you get out of the gringo pricing. Other utilities including good internet total less than $100. Yea you can do it for $1000 but the more you move around the more expensive it CAN be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 19:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What can you do in the meat world? I'm fairly handy and personable so when I contact a place for a long term (1-3 months) stay I always ask how I can help them for lower or more often (kinda) free accommodations. I ask if they have any place that is not for tourists I can stay in so as not to fill up a room they can rent out. I will pay something up front then when I arrive I fix things that need fixing, paint, help entertain guests, cook some, help with tours, help with English and so on. I usually once a week buy food to share with my hosts, $60 - $80 and we all eat well for a week. Even with as busy as this sounds most of my time is free. I can spend 3 months in Latin America for around $500 a month with no problems and I become part of the family if they are good people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 20:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is 2 different places, they are just side by side. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 16:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a friend who drove west from Ohio many time and he always said that just before he would get into Kansas he would stop and get a fifth of whiskey, when he crossed the border he would put his wife behind the wheel and start drinking until the bottle was gone and so was he. He hated the boredom of driving across Kansas and it was the only state he ever complained about.
Side note; Perry drank himself to death in his mid thirties. They said they could do a liver transplant if he quit drinking. He said never mind, that's not happening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 03:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look into Workaway.info and just keep on going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 03:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgot to mention I was in CR for 10 days in 2010 and again in 2015 and the prices now are pretty much consistent with prices in the U.S..
I don't think it is the best for budget travelers. Plus, wherever you go make the visit as long as you possibly can so you really have the time to unwind and get to know the culture. BTW, M/64 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 02:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out El Salvador. Very inexpensive flights and lodging. I have  spent the last 2 winters in Santa Ana and never have felt unsafe. A lot of bang for my buck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 21:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeppers...Forgot to mark this serious.
But thanks for what input you have given. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In which country are the people most satisfied with the government and the way it is ran? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 19:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Figured somebody might be interested in this. I can help you if need be. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 19:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 17:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The DNC and the Clinton machine are panicked right now that she will be booed when she makes an appearance. In talks to have Bernie nominate Hillary. What they don't get is this is no longer party politics, it is tribe politics. If the leader of the tribe turns on his word to the tribe he no longer has control. He was booed before when he mentioned her and he and she will be booed again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 17:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The DNC and the Clinton machine are panicked right now that she will be booed when she makes an appearance. In talks to have Bernie nominate Hillary. What they don't get is this is no longer party politics, it is tribe politics. If the leader of the tribe turns on his word to the tribe he no longer has control. He was booed before when he mentioned her and he and she will be booed again. #boohilary </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 02:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Throw a little butter and garlic salt in that pan first, you're in for a taste sensation.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 21:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And in time it will allow you to pass time.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My hang in Costa Rica last year. Complete ENO setup. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 18:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 23:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a nice sentiment but what data would be necessary and how would Reddit use it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What data would Redditors need to actually accomplish a change for the better in the world? What could that change be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 23:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 23:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've used xoom.com many times while in El Salvador. Works great and not high fees. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 14:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So? The answer is "no". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 00:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I figured so but I thought maybe I'd give the DNs a try first. Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anybody here have very good knowledge of beer brewing ingredients? I may have work for you. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 23:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 16:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like the onion ring in the french fry order. Rejoyce! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 17:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohio old guy (64) here, semi-retired, building an ecommerce site. Never seen the left side of the country. Still fairly adventurous, spent the last 2 winters solo in El Salvador. Would love to do this if I can have a smoke break from time to time. Almost a non-drinker but will have a few threw out the year. PM if you want to know more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
