<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2519</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mermaid didn't call your son a 'weirdo' she is just saying celebs don't go out with obsessive fans because they might be fucked up - might-most are normal but you son stands no chance unless he's a really looking 'lad' type of guy not someone quiet. I'm sorry but he has no chance. And do you see Jeremy Corbyn dating 'fans' lol no. He should be realistic and go out with someone he actually knows he's delusional in the first place for thinking this celeb would go for him  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't ruin you life for someone who is too sad to not live their's and just play video games. I love video games play them every day and as much as I can-when I get 'free time'. Meaning I have nothing else to do-when my friends don't want to do something, when my gf is busy, when I don't have to go gym, or do uni work. Then I play as much as I want. But the fact his life revolves around only playing them and he has to play the latest game at midnight kinda shows he's addicted. Again don't waste your time find someone to enjoy real life with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By the sounds of this you don't actually have a license and you have only been driving for two months ? You are probably a lot worse than you think you are at driving so she has every right to be anxious when in a car with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does he actually know this 'celebrity' in person? If he doesn't he won't have a chance. The girl from primark will probably be way less judgemental and no one really cares if you don't have experience  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 07:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bobby Kennedy with Barry Pepper reprising his role  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 06:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a good thing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 06:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'I moved on her like a bitch' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 06:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best for U.K. (London) : Public transport, Health care, Football culture, relatively uncorrupt political system and political climate (meaning the batshit crazy stuff republicans do in the US mostly couldn't happen here) history, freedom of religion is pretty good and Christianity isn't forced down your throats  

Worst: No inspiring politicians, right wing govt, student loans, student outrage culture, lad culture, tea, gym speak,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 06:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yom Kippur War, Cuban Missile Crisis, Berlin air lift  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 06:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything from Kings of Leon first two albums  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 06:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Most Violent Year - most underrated movie I've seen  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 06:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw a baby burnt up pretty bad by a cluster bomb on twitter (video). You can't unsee some shit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not that it isn't justified but what is the plan? Are you gunna killl Assad? No then what's the point? You gunna help jihadists groups take more territory? Are you gunna target Russian personnel? It's so complicated. I wish we could see greater collaboration between Russia and US to agree to remove Assad after the war. Have a ceasefire and only go after the extremist (proper ones) like al-Nusra and IS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I nap a lot and my sleeping schedule is fucked-usually get up at 16:00 go to bed at 6am. Yeah I get annoyed when I get woken up by someone playing excessively loud music butt I understand most people have normal sleeping schedules. If it's not before 12 then I don't have a problem with it even though it's annoying-you should tell your friend this and your life doesn't revolve around when she wants to sleep  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 16:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like a bitch  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nearly everyone has slept around get over yourself  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this isn't the issue but can't you just go for drinks and not drink. I always drive to the bar and barely ever get anything and it's still a good time  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know really my great grandma was the last one who properly knew him and she died in 2000 (I was born in Nov 1995) so never got the chance to ask her properly but my dad says She didn't have too much of an opinion because she was only a kid when the rising happened (born in 1903). But my dad did tell me their family benefitted a lot from the English and his great great grandad ran the fist automobile taxi in the area and they were relatively wealthy-so I think that's why they didn't really like his radicalism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My great great great (uncle) was the main guy who planned the uprising, Sean MacDiarmada, and was the second last executed. His family didn't really support what he did with the IRB. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 08:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah you are right I think a lot of communities that do have right wing Republican/Conservative beliefs (rust belt) paid a heavy price in the Iraq and Afghan wars as the army is a lot more popular there so they obviously don't want anymore pointless never ending wars. I don't actually think Trump has an ideology except whatever is best for Trump. If the military industrial complex are filling his coffers, or the Saudis are - both are pushing for war so he probably wants to keep them happy. Everything he has ever said in his presidency there is usually a tweet saying the complete opposite. He's a con man, and he said what you guys wanted. He understood people were sick of Washington but at the end of the day he's only looking out for himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 08:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least your finally seen him for what he is - a fraud. He does what his donors say and is so easy to manipulate. Trump probably doesn't even understand the dynamics of the war.

I get why'd you vote for him but from day 1 he's screwed over his voters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 08:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trading in one insane person for another  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny she actually said she would have bombed their airfields today... just because Trump is aweful don't think Hilary isn't a war hawk-her mentor was Kissinger  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 00:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought not. It's not a story the Thieves Guild would tell you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UNLIMITEDDDD POWAAAAAAAAAA!!!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 09:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your probably gunna have to start of slow if your knees and back are bad  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If my girlfriend asked me to do more things like this I would try but I wouldn't do it all the time - think your expecting too much - the love noted stuff makes me cringe maybe your bf is the same? A lot of boys hate being loved up  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 02:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look like Anthony Soprano Jr </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From your experience with birthdays you just have to realise most people don't care. I usually use my birthday to make my friends do something I want but I would never expect them to plan something for me. My parents are always nice and we get a meal - maybe just do something like that? 

Tbh you just sound salty no one is ever fawning over you on your birthday and this rarely happens to most people unless their friendship group thinks their in a movie  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You saw me fantasticccccc  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 19:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah your more lucky than us! It insanely cool to walk places by memory and not looking at the game map  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if you are from London but if you are the game is even better!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> World War 2 is the only way to go - the audience in general is sick of jump packs  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 09:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And hey look Indians serving in France ! https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Indian_Army_during_World_War_I#/editor/1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 09:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They only served as pack mules really ? Where did you learn your history if you think Indians didn't serve on the front lines? And yeah a lot of Indians didn't want to fight the caliph but good thing most Indians are also Hindu and Sikh then eh? 

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Indian_Army_during_World_War_I </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 09:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Chechens do have a lot of good reasons for hating Russia  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 08:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1,000,000 Indian troops served in the war and 70,000 died - does this debunk your theory that 'Zero of the empires' had large numbers of colonial troops? This is also not including the Gurkhas, the Egyptians or any of the blac African colonies. And 'precisely' my god how can you be so arrogant yet so wrong!?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 08:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol I was thinking Chechens  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 08:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Britain had a huge number of Indian troops, and America had a significant number of African Americans. Russia had a lot of Asians and the French had a lot of Arabs and Africans. Yes some had more than others but they played a role (especially the Indians)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 04:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have played it it's a decent game nothing special. Way more like the Arkham series. And being confined to Mordor and largely orcs is pretty annoying  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 03:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the main thing to remember is that most people don't give a shit what your doing in the gym. If your unsure of the equipment let your friend show you how to use it. If you just go to a gym and use everything normally no one will notice  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would expect most high ranking Nazi's would be able to speak English anyway  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like my history lecturer said, Connor would have never ever sided with the Americans (if he stayed true to his heritage) and the way the game portrays his tribes as sellouts to the British is wrong as the British where the only ones promising to secure territory just for the natives (mainly in Canada). And the guy you assassinate who communicates with the natives was a great person in mediating their grievances with the British. 

Overall I like Connor but this ^ is always in the back of my mind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 20:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm craving a Witcher or Skyrim style LOTR game - why hasn't this happened yet?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The coloured soldiers in Battlefield aren't meant to come from the countries the fight for they are part of the empires  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might get a Muslim/Asian soldier  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 09:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think you should even think about sex until you learn to properly communicate with people. You college existence seems extremely lonely you definitely have to try talk to people even if you hate it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The original article if from a whistleblower information to the intercept? What is sketchy about that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Key word necessity - did the Europeans need to enslave Africans ? No. Did it help them? Yes. Not necessary though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh okay because it Al Jazeera it can be true  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here you go

http://america.aljazeera.com/articles/2015/10/15/new-leak-of-us-intelligence-highlights-contours-of-us-drone-program.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of war yes, but this is a new age of warfare and one sec I'll go dig up the source for you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surely this is a joke? Necessary evil? What is necessary about bear total genocide of a group of people?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't generalise 'all of history' and slavery being a necessity...   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rate they kill civilians makes them unnecessary evil. Seriously some of the rates I've seen are insane sometimes run as high as 80%+ civilian casualties in a month. Read up about EKIA where they just lump in unidentified casualties as the enemy despite not knowing who they were. Drone strikes are one of the best recruiters for anti-western/US terror organisations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 03:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what a Filipino Jew would say! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 03:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Witcher 3-did not want to stop playing and pretty much haven't stopped on and off since it's release almost 2years ago  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 03:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't use the horn if you can help it, stay calm. Also don't be afraid to use the break and go abit slower when you are going quite fast (or even the speed limit) on a road sandwiched by parked cars on one side and  by oncoming cars on the other. People might get annoyed but worth doing if you aren't the most confident driver </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 03:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Hilarious' Reddit comment threads and their shite jokes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 03:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah just a lot of stuff I have read I've never even realised was a thing. The internet has de sensitised me to most stuff but found this sub enlightening to say the least  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 01:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just seems like your a porn addict and your expectation of sex is equal to what your watching but in reality it's not-that's why you probably struggled when you actually had sex  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 01:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just learning a lot about humanity haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 19:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I am pretty good at talking to strangers and stuff and what I find most is people will talk about themselves none stop and rarely ask you anything back (if they do you have found yourself a great person). So for me I just keep asking them questions about everything and anything generic and when they answer I ask more questions on their answers. Most people won't realise that they are not even asking you anything back. This works to help keep a convo up with a stranger, normally when I find someone more likely to be a friend we have an equal convo but hey sometimes it's just about getting through the awkwardness  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 19:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UK parliamentary reform and changes to voting laws throughout the 1800's greatly reduced corruption and the influence of money in politics  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 10:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Played me like a God damn fiddle! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 05:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sub man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 02:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It the episode after him and Foggy have a fight when he finds out he's DD. It's after Karen brings him a get well soon balloon  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol I am actually rewatching this because of Iron Fist being bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 20:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are still pretty terrible  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 20:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bet your K/D is below 1 bitch  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mood: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 07:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing worse than religious parents feel bad for you, just make plans to move out when your 18  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 07:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get why you are living with him and his family? What is the actual point in that? Judging by the way you talk your parents are fine so why don't you just stay with them?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 00:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh okay nice I thought it was gunna be the ancient Egyptian empire or something  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AC Empire-I really hope it isn't ancient Egypt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I have faith in Ubisoft to make an authentic setting does anyone want it to be set in Egypt during another period? 

I would love it to be set in Egypt during one of the Crusades but they could also do the British occupation that started in 1882. Maybe you could be involved in the uprising against the French that happens before he British took over or maybe you could be involved in the turmoil of the 1950's? 

Ancient Egypt just feels way to alien maybe even do Roman controlled Egypt ? Now that would be cool! What do you guys think?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just forget it dude not your fault  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well done! I've never got a 'runner high' before but getting better feels great mentally. Keep going!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadat was a hero  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he retired right there would be remember as a hero, his style of warfare and treatment of the people during the war is really interesting. Shame he was such a horrible, tyrannical leader </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 22:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did my first run since I've been sick got all the way to 9.5km and my stomach was running on empty through lack of food. Had to stop before 10km but happy I nearly got through a usual run on my first day back - hoping April is the month I break my monthly record after a bad March!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some atheists are like this, but the sub is a big place had plenty of really good conversation on there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get more pissed off when they hear it but don't commit genocide to save my life after </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been doing this workout for a year and a bit and my biceps and shoulders have gotten way bigger you condescending asshole </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or maybe I can't afford to buy new weights... I've said I do then at home... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coups in Turkey have usually helped stopthe country from becoming communist or becoming Islamist. The army usually carry out their coups to protect its secularism-this happened a lot from the 1960's-1980's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reagan actually was a pretty bad President saved by his foreign policy, which contributed to ending the Cold War, but in itself was pretty bad (Iran-Contra, massive arms race, Lebanon). He was lucky he had good people working with him and lucky he was the president at the height of the USSR's power or he would have payed for his reckless foreign policy. Many in the world genuinely believed Reagan would plunge the world into nuclear war. Hindsight I lovely but a lot of people viewed him like Trump, even his daughter led protests against his foreign policy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't tell the wife if they have kids. I know it's shitty but you are destroying their lives aswell  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carter was a great President but I feel being an American President really led to his downfall. Americans are so emotional when voting it seems they can't see reasons a lot of the time. And this doesn't just apply to Ronald Reagan and Trump but also to people like Bill and Barack, who were both good Presidents in their own way. Hell even Reagan had some good aspects (defo shouldn't be remembered as well as he is though)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you watched Iron Fist-he barley knows what the hand is  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just want to role play as Lee Harvey Oswald  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever tried doing intervals? I used to do for 1km I run 10km/h, for 2km I do 10.5, and so on until about 15km/h. Obviously you could adjust it for your preferred speeds but might help you go further? I used to do this before then was able to run without stopping for longer. Now I usually run 5km straight then do the rest in intervals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for micro transactions  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two months is not a long time just keep going. I used to be dead after doing 5km now I do 10km like it's nothing. Just keep at it you'll get there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't phantom pain when your limbs hurt but they aren't there anymore?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been really ill since Sunday thought I would be finally better today. Woke up to go gym but don't feel 100%. Running is annoying feels like you always have to have a perfect mindset and feel physically good to do it properly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Throw in some Elvis songs from Blue Hawaii and I'm in!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha yes Stick and Jessica-but Stick and Danny more because Danny is so naive about the fight against the Hand and living in the real world and his appearance make him a perfect target for Stick's insults  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Matt and Stick's conversations are always written pretty well! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Matt: I've learnt a lot since you've been gone 
Stick: Like what? 
Matt: You're a dick 

Not the best example of writing in Daredevil but it gave me a good laugh. So much better than Iron Fists writing-hopefully the Defenders does Danny justice, hopefully he will have some fun convos with  Stick as well!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not even joking I would buy one just for this. If it's going to succeed it needs to incorporate games like Rocket League </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should be all right -I feel it's all in your head anyway. I hadn't run 10km for 2weeks because I was ill then was able to run it 3 times in 5 days when I got back into it. Not saying it was easy but kept telling myself I'd done it before and it helped </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Great-Grandad on my mums side was from Dublin and fought at the Somme-got his tongue shot out I never met him. My great great uncle on my dads side was Sean McDermott who planned the Eater Rising and was executed for doing so. Ireland is interesting in this respect. Both sides, North and South joined up quickly into the war (remember their was nearly a civil war in Ireland just before WW1) and the IRB weren't actually that popular when they carried out the Easter Rising. Anyway an interesting piece of Irish history and cool my different relatives were on different sides  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 12:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you let him treat you like this!? He sounds like a loser dump him  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 07:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My point is it's a good game I could see myself getting lost in, but when there are two higher quality open world games that I have bought in the last month I kinda want to finish the one I like least quickly to spend more time with the others. If those two haven't come out I'd try to as much as possible in ME-currently I'm just doing the main quests and some character ones  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 01:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I thought we all hated the new one right!? I don't think it's bad but for its budget and money it's feels quite low quality  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have too much to play atm just gunna try complete ME as quick as possible so I can go back to finishing Zelda and Horizon. Annoying they all came out in the same month as the other two are way better than ME. Any other time of year I defo take my time with Andromeda  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No this is bullshit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do multiplayer 'packs' turn people off a game for good? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 16:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I absolutely hate the new packs system that has made its way into every multiplayer game. The only game it's kinda makes sense in are the EA sports games as they are sort of like sports trading cards. But this system has absolutely ruined multiplayer in two of my favourite franchises - Halo and Gears. Why is the whole fucking multiplayer designed around getting these bullshit packs? It makes the whole thing feel overcomplicated and stupid. I shouldn't have to get a Halo vehicle in a fucking pack I could pay money for. I shouldn't have to unlock/buy packs for every skin. I don't have a huge problem with some micro transactions (I love BF1 but the stuff they are selling is so pointless) but when you design the entire multiplayer in getting more money from players who already bought you game it's puts me off. Never enjoyed Halo 5 and Gears 4 the way I did in previous entries  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 08:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just be glad it wasn't longer and move on. I came out of a super long relationship when I was your age hurt Lot but after about 6 months felt pretty good despite her getting a new bf almost straight away. You'll forget about it eventually  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 22:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol you have to be joking  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We like sports and we don't care who knows  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you never read your emails or the crews messages to eachother your missing out! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 05:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daredevil is a good show period. Iron Fist is a bad superhero show and even worse 'show' overall. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 03:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think what makes Daredevil stand out for me in terms of the genre is that it's a good show on its own. Most of the non-superhero aspects are really well done and interesting (Matt and Foggy lawyering, Karen being a journalist, the trial of Frank etc). This is on top of the fight scenes being some of the best I've ever seen (movies and tv) and the genuine superhero stories being great (Frank Vs DD, Stick, Elektra and Matt vs the Hand) and yes I really love season 2 even though I know many are mixed. Where Iron Fist fails is that all the boardroom stuff is so dull and because he doesn't have a secret identity it's hampers the actual superhero stuff. Iron Fist had some good stuff with the Hand too up until episode 7, then it got even worse. There are no likeable characters apart from Coleen and you don't really care what happens to any of them.

I think someone said Iron Fist might have been a good show maybe 10+ years ago but now the standard is way to high for something like that to be seen as good. Rewatching DareDevil S1 now and the difference is amazing. Matt is way more interesting, likeable and cool than Danny. I feel DD has changed what a superhero show can be. Jon Bethnal's performance as Frank was seriously Emmy worthy but obviously it could ignored because it was in a marvel property.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 22:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SS-GB is incredibly grounded and I think the BBC always hire great writers for period dramas. Man in the High Castle is abit more Hollywood so yeah some of it is more over the top I think more catered to an American audience (you could never make an Archer type character work in this world) anyway I sill like it. Maybe just think of it as historical science fiction more than anything else? I don't feel it's meant to be that realistic although they have made a convincing world  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 22:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I find funny about Christianity and Islam in particular is that you literally stolen the history of the Jews but suddenly think their god favours you over them!? Like at least with Jews they can look at it and go 'that's my history' even if you take all the bs religious stuff out. Islam and Christians today largely can't do that (possibly some arabs at a stretch). That's why Hinduism and stuff makes more sense to me as it's based on myths and everything specific to that country-which Hindu acknowledges and has led to Hindu nationalism/fascism. But still all nonsense but the two most cancerous Christianity and Islam barely relate to the people who follow them  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay if you hate all religion then fine-just can't stand the Christian who will say this is Islam but not condemn their own religion  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the next mass shooting happens in a planned parenthood you will right call it 'Christianity' right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would not generalise this much (they don't do this in Turkey and Egypt) but yes women rights in most Islamic countries are pretty terrible and forcing them to wear the burka is basically saying they deserved to be raped if they don't wear it because men can't help themselves. But let's remember we are rightly not friends with Iran but Saudi Arabia is even worse and we sell them millions of dollars worth of weapons  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe let them have it all? Who like Fallon anyway  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
