<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3859</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just finished this painting of my favorite GOT character </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 18:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EVERYTHING]. Just finished this painting of my favorite character </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 18:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 16:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh wow. Spotify needs to step it up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 15:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha wow I'm glad you got to see those pieces. That's humbling. Let me know if there's anything I can do to help you on the journey. Its a great one

-Raman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 15:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really did want to hit the hair harder but was advised to simplify it for the overall impact of the values and lighting.  I had the curls done in the early stages but at the end went over them with a big brush And it made sense. Maybe in  different context I would add more detail but for this piece the focus really needed to be on just the face, I simplified the ear an even the neck structure to make it happen  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 03:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They hold the linseed oil and turpentine :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 03:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha you're all hilarious. And yes I'm in my second week at the Florence academy of art. I'm only here for a month but am having a blast. Insane skills here  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 03:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm okay. Woah, those down votes lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 23:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! I'm traveling until September though so not until then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alis. Oil on linen. 16"x20" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 19:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 19:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's incredible  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 19:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 30 hours. 3 hours  a day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 19:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OmH IMG Havana banana banana bag oh mg god hahahabababa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 19:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only been here two weeks. Taking a summer portrait course. Class was $3200. Its amazing though. It is everything I dreamed of learning. I've been painting awhile and have never had such a great foundation for materials and process. Worth every penny. The studio is open to me24/7 and I am taking full advantage. Basically do a painting a day outside of class. Class is3 hours every day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 17:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Florence academy of art. I don't think I could have made a better choice  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 14:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) thank you!  It was a tough process. First time doing something like this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just finished my first painting in Florence, Italy. "Alis" 16x20. oil on linen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 13:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IDAP of a friend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 13:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just finished my first painting in Florence, Italy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 13:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Love. 24"x30. Oil on canvas. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 20:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 16:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Foggy morning was about two nights, I cranked it out fairly quickly because I understood the values exactly how I wanted them and because of the limited color palette. 

Warmth in winter was a transformation over time.. first it was just the building in cool greys and depressing moods, I went back in and added the flaming windows, textures and the person to lifen it up. probably about a month's work on and off.

Light on the horizon is still a piece I am unsatisfied with, it went through many stages. The first being just the girl looking out.. and then I added warm lights on the horizon, then the darker clouds.. and lastly came the ship. very experimental painting, about a month on and off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 16:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started painting about 8 years ago in 10th grade, I always had a love for drawing but my teacher forced me to start painting and I loved it. I just graduated from VCU last year having dual degrees in Art Education and Communication Arts. I am a first year Art teacher and a working painter. I'm doing commissions/shows same time as teaching.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 01:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of the photos aren't full quality(I'll be taking those tomorrow) but 8x10's are best choice... you can try moving up from there. The higher quality ones will print just fine, see what the file sizes are.   Use luster settings instead of glossy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 01:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hmmm pictures are NOT the best way to get that mood and correct feeling and capturing of the impression. You want to be able to react to the space from life itself and then after a lot of experience you can use photos as a shortcut.    Just be in a space and start. just STARTing is the most important.. and keeping consistency. Before you know you will have developed a method in how you handle materials and process.   I paint from life just to stay sharp with observing colors and learning to create a feeling and then use photos that I"VE taken as inspiration to merge the worlds.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 01:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are all for sale! Let me know which ones you might be interested in... They go up tomorrow for the show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 01:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can keep em. I appreciate the love. Some paintings took a few weeks... paintings like "Beauty, then Reality" took 3-6 months.   the NYC piece took many layers as well, probably 2 months.. any particular you want to know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 01:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the next portfolio themes after this show is over. thank you for the feedback </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 01:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha! I feel I was in love with it while doing it but it is pretty much overpowering the rest of the work. People are always talking about that one and it's a great feeling but some of the work I've spent MONTHS on don't get as much love. I probably did that in a few weeks.    

Besides that, the concept holds very dear to me, mans lone journey, both spiritual and real. It represents sometimes the narrow paths we must take as much even though we may be afraid or don't see the end of the path itself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 01:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! responding asap to those requests! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 01:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha! Thank you, I am honored. I love listening to a lot of different kinds of music. A lot of nujabes...watsky...21 pilots...linkin park....and relaxing dubstep. (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E1e3XtQ7D5Q)


Some albums...
"All you can do"-watsky
"Vessel"-Twenty one pilots
"Spiritual state"-nujabes
 "A Thousand Suns"- Linkin park </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 01:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be so great, thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 01:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you! I appreciate the kind words </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 01:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They range from ~$500-~4,000.    The 18"x24" are closer to the $500-$600 range and the bigger ones such as the woman in "Beauty, then reality" which is closer t 40"x40" is $4,000. It also depends on the amount of time and layers, I spent 3 months on that one while some may take a night.  Any specific one you are interested in?  I am finalizing prices atm, so I can get back to you with a better answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 01:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you:).  go ahead, frame them. How are you printing them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 01:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 01:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't updated it in forever! I can tell you my instagram though which I update everyday.  art_of_raman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 01:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> actually, that's my next subject matter/ theme. I want to walk around the find places that are not so well known and shed some light on them. bball courts, alleyways, certain neighborhoods and the people from them as well as create a contrast of downtown busy life dc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 01:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey! the date is actually april 2nd! Opening reception is on this saturday, we will see </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi guys, I"d like to share my paintings from my first solo show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 14:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 13:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prints ??? Or the original painting themselves ?  The prints are here on my portfolio site www.ramandipsingh.com. just hover over the photos to see print options.  Shipping may be a lot overseas. I'm trying to find a better solution for that at the moment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 13:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet let me know and thank you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 13:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soul from the land is from a photo I took and the one with the land is more imagined  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi guys, I'd like to share my paintings from my first solo show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 13:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi guys, I'd like to share my paintings from my first solo show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 13:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi guys, I'd like to share my paintings from my first solo show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 13:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi guys, I'd like to share my paintings from my first solo show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 13:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 12:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. It's been a lot of work I'll need the luck: ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 12:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just imagined it. But now that I looked up the work, it'll definitely be an on going influence </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 12:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most from photos that I've taken with my canon. Others are imagined or from observation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 12:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 12:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe I can mail you one ? Shipping is general sucks overseas:(. Which one did you want ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 12:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you annn no I have not but now I shall </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 12:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go ahead. Its an honor  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 07:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! thanks!  I usually sell prints through my portfolio site, www.ramandipsingh.com and am working on another print site as well. Let me know if you need help or anything!  Just hover above the image and the print options should show up.

Raman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi r/india, I wanted to share my paintings from my first solo show with you </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 07:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 17:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to find a way to use them without being so overpowering. I know it can be a cheap goto for stylizing an image but I still like some of them  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just got PS, here's one of my first creations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 16:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just got PS, here's one of my first creations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 16:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 18:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its one of my good friends haha! But I could what you're saying. The lighting is similar to his work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My paintings in progress from this week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 19:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My paintings in progress from this week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 19:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IDAP of tomorrow's superbowl winner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 02:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did this fun watercolor piece to get hyped for tomorrow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 02:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did this fun watercolor piece to get hyped for tomorrow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 02:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 19:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kal ho na ho. Easily my favorite Indian movie and is really a gem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 01:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah sorry. Don't know why nothing was working yesterday.   http://imgur.com/gallery/HZBoM1i </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 01:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/gallery/HZBoM1i </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 01:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw the picture somewhere, just didn't know what it was from. Having a weird time posting things, nothings working </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IDAP of snoopy, yoda and a lonely man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 02:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Created these 3 paintings today, Merry Christmas! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 02:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 05:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know. I've never had anyone order a print outside the u.s. but the printing company I use on the site actually does do international shipping. Try it out. I don't think there would be a problem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Self-portrait. Oil on wood. 24"x30" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 01:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 09:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you're right, you're right. It is actually a piece I initially overworked and I tried to save it. I can see there are plenty of flaws but had to let it go :/ and move on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 09:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've posted it incomplete with a few others in an album. To be honest I think its the more weaker of my works. I was criticized last time for the perspective /other formal things. By abstracting more of it, I tried to redeem the style a little bit. I think I may have initially overworked it so its hard to get a piece back sometimes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 00:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its actually people walking down the street but I did let the sunset look fire like. Its whatever you want it to be haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Idap of busy streets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 00:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Streets of Punjab". Oil on wood. 24"x30" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 00:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A painting I just finished of back home, punjab </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 00:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A painting I just finished of back home. "Streets of Punjab". 24"x30". Oil on Wood </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 00:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 00:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :D. Omg. Thank you!!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 00:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 24"x30" and yes its for sale :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 22:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Follow me on instagram! Art_of_Raman. I always post progress and videos of myself working </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 20:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one I worked on and off. Probably a total of 2 weeks. Some take a night. Some take 2 months ;p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 20:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi. Yes of course !  I'm in the u.s at the moment so sometimes Its hard to accept universal commissions because of shipping costs etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 20:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahahahahahahahahaahhaa you win </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 07:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started out with realism and hyper-realism in mind and i don't know, I think my lazyness drifted me into a phase of leaving things unfinished and more expressive. I then started using a palette knife to paint because I didn't want to waste time cleaning brushes, just mixed colors with the paint and also threw it on canvas an moved it around with the knife. It was very efficient and I learned to break down important lines and shapes of value without blending and taking forever on it. I also loved the texture it allowed me to obtain. The brush feels a lot like drawing almost and sometimes doessn't leave too many chances to let the expression and artist's hand show through because you get caught up in refinement. The palette knife is all about the marks/strokes and being in the moment to react to a subject. Sorry, for the short answer, I think yeah, it's a mixture of expressionism(faces) and impressionism(places) and I choose areas to refine in the end to build up the focus in one area such as the eyes or face.      I feel like I just threw up in this comment, I'm actually in the studio right now working to finish up pieces late at night. and thanks I'll need the luck for the show! keep stenciling and spraying...safely that is, out in the open </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 07:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! Yeah, painting is my passion and life. I teach it full time and also am working to establish myself as a professional artist. I'm actually preparing for my first solo show.  heres my portfolio site: www.ramandipsingh.com         FB:  the art of raman singh   and insta: art_of_raman

Thank you and let me know if you have other questions:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 07:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks and yupp, Oil paint. It's all done in palette knife and some parts I smudged around with my fingers too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi r/India, I wanted to share this recently finished piece. It's my home, the sometimes peaceful but mostly chaotic bazaars of punjab </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 06:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Inwards" Oil on wooden panel. 24"x30". Needs a bit of work still </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 22:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My reflective piece in progress. oil paint </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 22:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 20:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ah Thanks! yes, I've been trying to tackle all the problems but the painting was so far in, I kind of had to let it go but will hold on to all the crits and your feedback for future pieces. I can see it's a very conflicting piece because I tried to do a lot of things at once, went for a realistic street scene but wanted to more impressionistic, it's like the elements are fighting a little bit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 20:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an aspiring painter, I would love some feedback/advice on how to go about starting a business around my work. When I say business, I mean making a living off selling paintings alone. I've sold paintings to people I've known and some online but can't seem to establish a following or exposure.
Here is my work: www.ramandipsingh.com instagram: art_of_raman
any advice is appreciated. Thank you!

My question. How do I increase sales and exposure? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 20:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an aspiring painter, I would love some feedback/advice on how to go about starting a business around my work. When I say business, I mean making a living off selling paintings alone. I've sold paintings to people I've known and some online but can't seem to establish a following or exposure.  

Here is my work: www.ramandipsingh.com
instagram: art_of_raman

any advice is appreciated. Thank you!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "City Lights" 24"x30", Oil on Wood </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 16:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My recently finished "City Lights" Oil Painting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 16:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> City Lights, 24"x30", Oil on Wood </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 16:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-07 07:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hm no. I took the photo myself and painted it myself. Maybe someone has done one from the same street before ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-07 01:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome. Thank you for the great feedback. I'll move on. It's just so tempting to just sit on one piece and try to develop it as I learn more about color.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "City Lights" 24"x30", Oil on Wood w palette knife </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 21:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> N.Y.C painting with a palette knife </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 21:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My N.Y.C painting with a palette knife </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 21:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IDAP of that feeling when your girl moves away </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 22:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sunset piece using palette knife </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 01:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some stages of a recently finished piece </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-28 23:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-26 05:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! phones can do wonderful things on their own these days!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some process on a 45 minute painting study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-26 03:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 45 minute painting study and process </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-26 01:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 45-min Self-portrait study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-25 18:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 20:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes , I tried to make the foreground most detailed and high in contrast. I didn't the scooter guy had become that prominent, I think I'll tone him down just a little bit to balance that pull. Thanks for the perspective ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 18:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Crazy that you recognized that. My initial came from looking at his work and he handles depth. Cortes,Kim kogan, and Turner were also inspirations.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've been working on this piece a while. Would love some feedback before I call it "finished" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 18:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IDAP of a busy street </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 18:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi r/painting, I would love some constructive criticism on this almost finished piece. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 18:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 04:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. I'm actually working on 20. These were the first 3. I think "Impressionism" is still the right word. Google it and you'll see similar works.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
