<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1989</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] A sci show episode that talks about different plant parts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 07:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> esp in the context of food and how you can group up different food groups, not the classical way, but by how the parts we eat can botanically be sorted into different parts of the plant anatomy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 06:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Money isn't tight but I am in a college town away from home and thus, my mechanic of choice (nothing against my buddy though). The climate control was running fine when my buddy turned the car back on himself and made the point of turning climate control off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We've heard about putting a monkey behind a typewriter, but what about handing him a Rubik's cube? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 06:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 06:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! Also, edit2, how would that change things?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 05:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sauce? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 05:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sauce? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 05:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to my buddy (but I'm open to second opinions, that's why I'm here), the smoke was just burning rubber. It doesn't look like anything seized but that's only my untrained eye talking, not my buddy. What do you think might have?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: If you live in or near a college town with Greek life, check out what philanthropies they put on. These are usually fun events like performances and socials where proceeds from ticket sales all go to charity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 05:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 05:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My roommate is a car guy. That was his hunch too and we have the belt. It just snapped. I was running on battery power all day. We're replacing the belt tomorrow and he's driving. Would auto parts stores like O'Reilly's would have what I'm looking for....?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [02 Acura MDX] it's driving fine right now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 03:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was driving on the highway and a few things all happened at the same time. I was putting black smoke out of my exhaust, a squeaking sound started up, and my break light and battery light came on simultaneously. The lights are still on my dash but the smoke stopped and the squeaking stopped at the same time. What happened? What should I do? 

Edit:  more dash lights keep coming on, one at a time. I also lost AC and all the internal displays, headlights, and the fuel gauge all died on me.   

Edit2: It's also worth mentioning that I continued to drive. Not the wisest decision I have ever made but I was on a tight schedule today and nothing *appeared* to be stopping me from getting to my destination. Things started going out AS I was pulling up to my parking spot, just in the nick of time but I haven't the slightest idea how much potential hidden damage I may have done. (rough estimate is about 25 miles worth of driving after the sound, smoke, and first couple dash lights came on) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE think that Ted Danson looks like Anderson Cooper's shoulder angel? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 03:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [inspiration](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9vn4H0-yEVg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 21:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone from r/math explain whats going on here?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ladies' men, what goes on in your head? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 18:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT][Artist] Someone who put a line of pieces out that was the same work of art in a bunch of different mediums. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 04:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 09:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speak for yourself. I can't accept it. Sandwitches are unisex and awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 09:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does everyone know the back of their hand so very well? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, it's always been as difficult as remembering streets in a city or something of the kind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even the mighty [peregrine falcon](http://giphy.com/gifs/bath-falcon-peregrine-2SAhyng9zX8d2)?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What crosses your mind every day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 09:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The craziest thing I've ever done for money. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 08:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that there is an organization that will donate rice to charity for all the studying you do on their website. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 07:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How is this not a thing?! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 06:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What songs should I learn to play on the guitar to impress girls? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 01:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been playing for years but only really catered to my friends and their tastes. I'm at the point in my life where I really don't have the time to play but I can make time if it means going back to those hopeless roots of what brought most to start playing all those years ago - being impressive. Call me vein or superficial - I don't think I am, but this is the internet, you can think of me what you want. I just want to know if there are any must know songs that all/most girls love or if we could get a decent list together that is (close to) all encompassing, that'd be cool too. 

Your's truly,
ImNotATool_ISwear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 00:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Birdie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dr. Seuss Erotica </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 21:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [crosspost](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/5sskfe/dr_seuss_now_writes_erotica_what_are_some_of_his/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Is bedside manner taught in med school or are medical professionals just expected to be good at it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 20:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never had a bad experience with someone but I just had a really good interaction. I also know that bad bedside manner is a thing even though I haven't witnessed it myself. Is there actual training for it or is it just something that is expected of you if you are entering the profession? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors with unisex names, what's it like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 09:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If they play music while you are on hold, you should be able to choose the music. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 00:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 23:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wtf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What the village idiot was really thinking after that new food item didn't kill him after all. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 08:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Things you learned in college that aren't going on your resume </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 08:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What songs should I learn on the guitar to impress girls? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 06:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 05:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [You don't.](https://gfycat.com/gifs/search/nicolas%20cage/detail/OddMadeupAnemonecrab) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 01:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/woahdude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 01:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you are talking in hypotheticals. I was curious what already exists and is established.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 21:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then what reasoning do the Eagles and Raiders have for breaking the norm in that regard? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Superb Owl? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recently in the news, there has been a lot of talk about this species of falcon that has been getting obliterated by American patriots. Why are Americans killing these animals and where is the outrage from animal rights activists? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 16:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 15:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand, just asking. I also realize that I mistakenly gave the impression that I wasn't part of the Greek community. I just happen to be a new member and notice a lot of talk about other fraternities and sororities. I don't  care to stereotype, but if everyone else is, I would at least like to keep it all straight in my head.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 15:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't usually go to Starbucks. I mean when I go to any coffee shop, I can almost taste the difference between two different baristas' styles. You can still burn a bold roast further. I've drank dark roasts for years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 10:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mind me asking which one you are a member of?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] A hybrid of interpretive dance and sign language that came out of European school systems. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 10:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] A writing system that substitutes letters and words for images that either are or are pronounced similarly. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 09:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does every NFL logo but that of the Raiders and Eagles face right? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 09:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 08:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean alphabets - like, how many other ways are there to represent the English alphabet? e.g. - Your mention of semaphores just added to the list.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've gotten to the point in my coffee-drinking career that I can actually taste burnt coffee and it's bitter sweet. (pun kinda intended) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 08:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 07:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Insanity: doing the same thing over and over again and expecting different results." - Albert Einstein   

[Also Relevant](http://www.brighthubeducation.com/english-homework-help/105856-understanding-pragmatic-vs-semantic-meaning/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The reactions of the people in the print shop that Cards Against Humanity outsourced to. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 07:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New World Order leaders on their first day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 07:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 06:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm shooting for overall fitness so that's good to know! A beach bod and Olympic-athlete skill sets would be nice, but I'm also realistic - I just want to be healthy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Success is walking from failure to failure with no loss of enthusiasm" - Winston Churchill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 06:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 06:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a big list tho. haha. Patience is a virtue I guess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 06:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, take it with a grain of salt. They are going to try to sell product. But I don't think that's inseparable from the exercise regimen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 05:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, I know that this list and that page exist, I was wondering what some of the most prevailing stereotypes were of each chapter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 05:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why Ohio specifically?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You guys got a lot of look-ups tonight by confused redittors that don't get puns. I'm one of those people. Well played internet, well played. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 05:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who has tried the Body for Life challenge? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [link](http://bodyforlife.com/challenge)  

I wanna try *something* like this and it seems like a good program. Anyone here have any experiences they can speak to?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many iterations exist of different languages? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 00:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I struggled a bit to find a way to not ask 'how many languages exist?' because that's not the question. I was wondering about like, Morse code, the binary ascii alphabet, the military phonetic alphabet, sign language, braille, etc. What all is encompassed by 'etc.' that I'm forgetting? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 00:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HUMAN, THAT IS WHAT WAS SAID IN THE ORIGINAL POST.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So are cats and dogs simply not bothered by their bare butt holes contacting the ground and stuff all the time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 00:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: Or any animal for that matter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a world where everyone knew the skeletons burred in everyone else's closets, we would either be much more or much less compassionate. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Video] Pom Wonderful gracefully and tactfully replies to john oliver's Criticism. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The part of the job that wasn't listed in the job description </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 22:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: What is each fraternity's and sorority's reputation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 22:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Movie titles that describe cast members' sex lives. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 22:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CMV: The Harry Potter universe is the most expansive, comprehensive, and well put together fictional universe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 22:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MY ANCESTOR AND I HAD LITTLE TO DISCUSS TOGETHER AS THE LANGUAGE BARRIER HINDERED DISCOURSE. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 06:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ME:  

01001000 01100101 01101100 01101100 01101111 00101100 00100000 01100111 01110010 01100001 01101110 01100100 01110000 01100001 01110010 01100101 01101110 01110100 01110011 00100001

ANSESTOR:  

--- .... / .. ..-. / .. - / .. ... -. .----. - / -- -.-- / -.. .- .-. .-.. .. -. --. / --. .-. .- -. -.. -.-. .... .. .-.. -.. / ..-. ..- .-.. ..-. .. .-.. .-.. .. -. --. / - .... . .. .-. / ..-. .- -- .. .-.. .. .- .-.. / --- -... .-.. .. --. .- - .. --- -. ... .-.-.-

ME:  

01011001 01100101 01110011 00101100 00100000 01110011 01101001 01101101 01110000 01101100 01111001 00100000 01110111 01100001 01101110 01110100 01101001 01101110 01100111 00100000 01110100 01101111 00100000 01101001 01101110 01110001 01110101 01101001 01110010 01100101 00100000 01100001 01110011 00100000 01110100 01101111 00100000 01111001 01101111 01110101 01110010 00100000 01110111 01100101 01101100 01101100 00101101 01100010 01100101 01101001 01101110 01100111 00101110 00100000

ANSESTOR:  

-- -.-- / .-- . .-.. .-.. / -... . .. -. --. / .... .- ... / ... .. --. -. .. ..-. .. -.-. .- -. - .-.. -.-- / .. -- .--. .-. --- ...- . -.. / .- ... / --- ..-. / .-.. .- - . / -.-. --- -. ... .. -.. . .-. .. -. --. / - .... . / .- .-. .-. .. ...- .- .-.. / .- -. -.. / .. -. --.- ..- .. .-. -.-- / --- ..-. / -.-- --- ..- .-. ... . .-.. ..-. .-.-.- / - .... .- -. -.- / -.-- --- ..- / ..-. --- .-. / -.-. .- .-. .. -. --. .-.-.-
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There should be a filter option by search bars in websites that helps you find content you've seen before and are trying to find again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 06:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quite literally, there is no one who has seen thing from my perspective - our viewing angles will always be slightly different. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 06:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AN EXEMPLARY AMOUNT OF SEX HAS GONE SUCCESSFULLY UNNOTICED BY PASSERS-BY </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 01:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 08:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Happy birthday asshat! Just kidding. His name is Mike." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Innapropriate times to suggest turning it off and on again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 22:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here, reporting from the Jedi temple, the smoke is white. We don't have a chose one yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Its easy to fake not being able to do something but not to fake being able to do to something. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 18:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are ya ready, kids?!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 08:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A news app that gives you side-by-side comparisons of how different stations are covering the same event. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 08:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> War does not determine who is right  only who is left.- Mahatma Gandhi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 07:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: Its a Bertrand Russell quote. Honest mistake. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 19:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Puerto Rico and D.C. get voting rights.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: Coffee takes time to enter the bloodstream. Disolve powdered caffeine and use a syringe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 19:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What concepts, when you learn them, have the potential to change the way someone views the world? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 19:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 09:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget Prince Harambe Fisher.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would you like to be asked about consent? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 09:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, in my experience, when guys are reminded of how important consent is, that's usually paired with a reminder that it's okay to be blunt about it. But the problem we then run into is that being frank isn't exactly equated with being suave and sexy (especially for the 007 fans among us but that's neither here nor there. Point is, in a lot of guys' minds, Its a mood-killer) and not enough guys have the right idea of what the best way to go about it is. If a man wants verbal consent and straight up asks "do you want to have sex?", how would you feel about that? Independent of weather or not you wanted to is appreciating how he went about asking, or am I wrong there? I don't think enough young men can appreciate that doing the right thing regardless of how demasculating it might *feel*, but this is just some affirmation-seeking for those young men.  

Edit: I was just trying to make the point to friends that it's not unsexy. I didn't mean to scrape up against rape-culture or act like it is in fact, actually emasculating to go for verbal consent. The consensus in the comments so far seems to be with me there, so thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some people are cat people, some people are dog people, but I'm a pet rock person because... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 06:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't usually give beggars spare change, but when I read his sign, I just had to/ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 20:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 15:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds good and I'll try it next time I make oatmeal but I have only heard of people dropping salt and butter in instead of sugar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would you like to be asked for consent? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 09:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What about Calvin Klein makes it sexier than Victoria's Secret? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 08:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fortune cookie fortunes that hit too close to home. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 08:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guys, the people born after 12/21/12 are not even 5 years old yet. It's not too late to get our act together and come up with a story of how Doomsday played out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 08:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 07:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bloody hell, someone crashed their fuckin car. You're gonna be 20 minutes late.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it just me or is Calvin Klein often sexier than Victoria's Secret? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 05:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was your 'no guts, no glory' moment that ended up being glorious? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 05:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was your 'no guts, no glory' moment that ended up being glorious? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 05:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 04:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Abolish the penny!   

Commission more street art!  

Enter diplomatic relations with the DPRK!  

Speeding tickets and similar fines will now be set at a level proportionate to your income!  

Internet access now gets the same legal status as a utility.  

Allocate a portion of the discretionary budget to a second space race!  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 04:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Careless Whisper is my actual ringtone and I don't mind at all forgetting where the volume is set on my phone when I am in public.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 02:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have had 2 separate professors in two different departments at my university warn us that they can catch cheaters with statistical analysis and one who did.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Celebrities who were not the first choice for the product they are sponsoring. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 01:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know about the statistical models they actually run to catch cheaters? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 01:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like asking my stats professor this would arouses suspicion but I am actually just really curious. I know that if no one cheats, it's a normal distribution of grades, but it can't be that simple. How do they know who cheated? What data analysis do they run on test answers? I can imagine it either being a trade secret, held under lock and key, and the other part of me really doubts that. I don't know which part to listen to. Lol. Any statisticians or college administrators out here?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk though if he is a redditor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which movie's soundtrack makes for good listening? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 03:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend says that Pepe is his favorite. Help me help him regret that. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 01:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "It's too early to start day drinking. Maybe tonight." - Anonymous </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 00:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 20:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> credit to u/bigmeat on the original post.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Crosspost from r/science] We're famous </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 20:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 07:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: So I just found her on a dating app. after reading it, I don't know any more or less about how interested she might be in me but at least we know she is available. ... Thoughts?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what's an example of when you just didn't get the hint? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 02:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 09:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Advisers may have ulterior motives. I don't know your school's policy but something I have seen was academic advisers at community colleges pushing students to complete a 2 year degree before transferring even though it's not entirely necessary. Something about the numbers makes it look better that way. In any case, I would look up the policies and maybe run your plan by a professor you trust.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 05:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I'm thinking of had wood trim.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 05:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely modern.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] A car with an asymetrical interior. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 05:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not just the fact that there is a steering wheel on one side but the paneling in from of the passenger was designed in a pecurliar way. It's a compact car, maybe a concept sesign, but I definitely remember seeing it at a car show and sitting inside one. From the outside it may or may not have looked kind of BMW-esque. My main take-away from this car though was the design of the interior was very modern and contemporary. I'm also not entirely certain but fairly so that the brand is fairly recognizable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE have a frame of mind that you relapse back into that makes them feel exactly like you are a suddenly a lot younger? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 05:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not quite deja vu but reeaallly close to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 20:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's legalized, it's no longer a controlled substance.    


False. 


Also, breathalyzer came on the scene a few years after prohibition ended for a few reasons. Namely the prevalence of cars. But even if you ignore that fact, giving police a way to check that someone isn't doing what they shouldn't be behind the wheel saves lives and the data proves that. If you are thinking of reminding me that it's still illegal to drive under the influence, don't, because we have no breathalyzer equivalent to weed YET and that's the problem. We have an unenforceable law. And when it comes to controlled substances, that's not an okay thing. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 20:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 18:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Women and men alike have pressure to keep appearances up but men aren't allowed to have a 'beauty regimen'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not wrong at all. I dont want to rehash answers across the comment section. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are male summpliment pills solving a problem that actually exists or is it just clever marketing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 10:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Possible but improbable. I have a good amount of faith in science. But to answer your 'just in case' scenario, if we were to eventually prove that such a device were impossible, then I'll refer you to the conversation elsewhere in the comments between me and u/CanvassingThoughts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 09:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We currently measure for marijuana metabolites, the problem is those can stay in someone's system for over a month.




I know. I'm not a scientist, but those guys can do and learn some pretty amazing things. Especially if we throw some good R and D money at them. The possibility for such a device hasn't been ruled out, and not caring enough to try is as irresponsible as the status quo war on drugs.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NSFW] Lets pretend like these pills work as advertised... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 09:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you know of any actresses, models, or stars that have been in both the soft and hardcore worlds? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 08:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thinking of anyone that has ever crossed the threshold between hard and softcore seems like it shouldn't be hard but I can imagine why that's a line most professionals don't hop back and forth between. I can see a pornstars doing some lite nude modeling but that's about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Music apps should have environment settings so that you don't get sound effects (like fake sirens or screams) mixed up with ambient noise (like real sirens or screams). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 08:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 08:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> probably interested. 


In all seriousness... If she says yes, doesn't that confirm that it's more than probably? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Grunt work begets glory." - Jeff Fox </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 08:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 08:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch honest game trailers. Any one of those that fits.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 07:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Playboy's miss July 2011 from a quick Google </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 05:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it's too much to ask for both at the same time though. Unrealistic? Probably. But if we complacently wait and hope for an emerging technology vs spur innovation with tax incentives, research grants, and maybe some private sector help, then I'll go so far as to say that we are being as irresponsible as before with the mandatory minimums and wasted billions. .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 04:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read my comments to other responses but sorry for implying that I'm in favor of repealing decriminalization.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 04:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^^ the most eloquent non-answer I've heard so far. ... Fair point, but you didn't CMV.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 04:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a field sobriety test is enough and the data shows it, I'll concede. Honestly hadn't done that research.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 00:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regardless of the legal or empirical nuances that you are eluding to, the fact is that making something illegal doesn't make it less likely to happen (war on drugs itself per example) but enforcing that law sure does. What's wrong with wanting to equip officers with the ability to tell if someone on the road is high?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 00:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) Read the original post, this isn't an anti-drug pro-war-on-drugs manifesto. I just think we can handle the legislation more responsibly.  

2) Having an available sobriety test like a breathalizer significantly reduces drunk driving accidents. It's a free country and it's illegal to drink and drive, yada yada, what's the point of making something illegal if you can't enforce it?  

3) see my reply to u/ElysiX 's comment.  

4) Again, this isn't a proposal to roll back legalization, just to tred with caution as we go forward with better legislation in the states that have yet to legalize and maybe revise it in states where recreational and medical weed is legal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 00:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you be more specific? There are a lot of laws at play here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 23:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Water under the bridge? Mistakes were made, that's not a productive debate to have. May be an educationally valuable one, but I don't see the value of that happening on the context of this post. I'm open minded though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 23:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But alcohol is not the substance, in the status quo, that we have to wait for technology to catch up with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 23:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, sure, double standards suck. I'm sure that other medical prescription like Xanax is it's own animal (and yes, I can recognize the medical marijuana side) so lets, for now, and with the info available to me, go with yes. I would advocate for better testing across the board.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 23:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, there would need to be a scientific data-driven precedent for the law change... but sure. why not?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 23:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if that's malpractice or your doctor giving you those perscriptions with the understanding that you wouldn't drive, I don't know your circumstances. But data speaks for itself, the plural of anecdote is not data.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 23:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it is.... and?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 22:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And those 20 years, I'm presuming, we're a lot deadlier than they could have been. Why shouldn't we wait?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 22:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Acontrolled substanceis generally a drug or chemical whose manufacture, possession, or use is regulated by a government, such as illicitly used drugs or prescription medications that are designated aControlledDrug."  



That status of marijuana doesn't change with it's legality. It's not circular. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE listen to enough of one artist to catch the lyrical snippets that they throw into multiple song? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 22:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And feel really accomplished when you notice?! Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 22:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's special because it is a controlled substance. Prescription medication, if it impacts your ability to operate heavy machinery (e.g. a car), then that's what your doctor or the commercial is supposed to tell you to release themselves from liability. In other words, it's definitely illegal. Driving tired is **as** dangerous as driving drunk but the day we start legislating that people aren't allowed to do stuff is they are too tired is the day that the economy tanks, pigs might also start flying that day, but I'm no expert.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 22:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be it a breathalyzer, field sobriety test, or just reckless driving, driving under the influence of alcohol is illegal too, but we have ways of proving that people are too drunk to drive in real time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 22:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see all the pros of legalization clearly and I want us all to enjoy them. But the fact is that driving under the influence is illegal  despite there being no effective way to test for it. Independent of the data that shows how dangerous it is or isn't, I can pull up more studies that support my side, and I'm sure you could do the same, but independent of that is the fact that the ban on driving under the influence makes us feel safer on the roads. Not to the same extent of false security as 'security theater' at the airports because it's effectiveness has been thoroughly debunked by studies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CMV: The legalization of marijuana should not precede the availability of a reliable, legal, and market-ready field-sobriety test. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 21:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My main issue with the push to legalize isn't some overarching war-on-drugs stance, but the hastiness. [Here](https://www.drugabuse.gov/publications/research-reports/marijuana/does-marijuana-use-affect-driving) is some evidence that driving under the influence of marijuana is dangerous. [This](https://www.reddit.com/r/todayilearned/comments/5q2suc/til_marijuana_levels_in_the_bloodstream_do_not/) post reminds us all that officers have no reliable way yet of knowing except for using their best judgement. So we have a chemical that can give a false positive with urine and similar tests, a false negative with blood tests, and can still cause actual damage if a driver is high. My view is that we should have funded the research and development, created a accurate, cost-effective marketable solution (akin to breathalyzers for BAC), and prepared officers and civilians alike to make better decisions on the road just as we do with alcohol BEFORE legalization bills ever hit the ballot, let alone pass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 21:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you do the same with mercury? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Credit goes to those who execute ideas, not to those who thought of them. Creative people are doers, they recognize a good idea and execute with their own personalized touch" - Jeffrey Fox </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 20:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A cute classmate laughs at all my bad jokes, should I make my move? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Firstly: This is almost an exact copypasta of my [same post](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskWomen/comments/5q23mh/a_cute_classmate_laughs_at_all_my_bad_jokes/) in r/askwomen. A mod removed it and told me to take it here.   

___
Pertinent details : both college aged, we work in a group together, I've been told I'm not as funny as I think I am, I've heard that laughing at the bad jokes is a way girls flirt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TMW you realize that playing fetch with a dog that doesn't play fetch is just throwing stuff at a dog and mildly pissing it off, like the most innocent version of animal abuse ever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 17:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't expect people to dress **for me** but there is a cultural phenomenon here that might belong in r/DAE  .... Wasn't trying to offend anyone. Fully expected to, but didn't mean to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Androgynous redditors, why not dress in a way that stop confusing passers by? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 17:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 16:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I go to the same school as library girl (it's an nsfw thing if you don't know what I'm talking about.) well on day one of one of my business classes, my prof says that the library is a great place to study because apparently
 there is also *entertainment* in there. We chuckle, and he continues with **I don't know why she got in trouble for such an entrepreneurial endevour.** God. That was a good class. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 16:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Head scratches are my kryptonite.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 09:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My thoughts exactly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A cute classmate laughs at all my bad jokes, should I make my move? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 09:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 08:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To add to this, different universities lay out the types of classes (major-specific vs gen ed) differently. If you don't understand something, don't hesitate to reach out to an academic adviser for clarification. They understand their school's system, requirements, and academic tracks very well, it's their job.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This website is going to be invaluable to you if you plan on getting groups together outside of class. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 07:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bob's Affirmation Box </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 06:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Music apps should have environment settings so that you don't get ambient noise and sound effects in the song mixed up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 04:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially sirens in the song that you listen to while driving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every time I see handwriting in a used textbook... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 04:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think of the half blood Prince and immediately lament the fact that I don't have and liquid luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 08:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ouch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If money were no object, what would your next gun purchase be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 08:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If money were no object, where would be the next place you would visit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 07:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] If money were no object, what would your next watch purchase be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 07:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If money were no object, what would your next watch purchase be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 06:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If money were no object, what would your next gadget purchase be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 06:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 06:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> national average gas price in 2015 dollars   


... 
r/crappydesign  
Just call it inflation-adjusted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If money were no object, what would your next fitness-related purchase be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 06:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] If money were no object, what would your next guitar purchase be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 05:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If money were no object, what would your next wine purchase be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 04:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If money were no object, what would your next watch purchase be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 03:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If money were no object, what would your next mixology-related purchase be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 03:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If money were no object, what would your next knife purchase be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 03:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If money were no object, what would your next gun purchase be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 03:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If money were no object, what would your next fitness related purchase be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 03:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If money were no object, what would your next cycling purchase be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 03:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If money were no object, what would your next computer purchase be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 03:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If money were no object, what would your next car purchase be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 02:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If money were no object, what would your next cigar purchase be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 01:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sunset On The Parliament Building In Victoria, Canada </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 01:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But how quickly can 'land mass' status change due to volcanic activity and island colapse? I know, for example, that the Hawaiian chain has a new addition on the way, but it's not due to reach past sea level for [several tens of thousands of years](http://geology.com/usgs/loihi-seamount/).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pretty much the entire globe  

Well we pretty much already have a Google-able answer without the counting - not exact enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Annnnnnd I upvoted. Lol. Pretty picture and pretty piece. I wasn't going to not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How is there no exact count on the number of land masses on earth? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the afro-eurasian continent to the smallest islands of Greece, Canada, Malaysia, and the Philippines, We've had all of human history to take land from one another so it's hard for me to imagine that there aren't enough interested parties in an exact answer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TV dads like Homer Simpson and Peter Griffin are probably on par with the amount of monetary damage to their respective universe as a Marvel Superhero. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to upvote but it's at 777 right now and I'm not gonna be the one to screw that up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sunset On The B.C. Parliament Building In Victoria, Canada [4928x3264] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 19:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeeeeeeesssss. Must try!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh. Okay. That makes a lot more sense. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but there are less characters in a Dewey decimal code than an ISBN, is there not? What about when the library acquires a new addition? Am I understanding something incorrectly where I can picture a library acquiring a new addition to an already extensive collection in a certain category and simply not being able to put in on the shelf out of a lack of codes?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do libraries prefer to sort books with the Dewey decimal system instead of ISBNs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 21:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When it comes to diversity in the workplace, what do women have to bring to the table in traditionally male roles? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 19:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to suggest that I ever thought the answer was 'nothing' but I am just trying to better understand in what ways the workplace could start changing as a result of different diversification and equal opportunity efforts.  

Edit: I never meant to suggest that women *need* to bring **more** to the table or that the double standard is justified. Biases and prejudices are stupid.  In light of some of the diversity efforts I have actually seen around my college campus and work place, there is actual talk about the different perspectives and mindsets that women can bring to the table (and it's all talked up in a positive light) so it's shocking to hear the opposite on this forum.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not your traditional reading list </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 19:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope I'm not the only one that really likes the more fleshed-out wikis of some of the bigger subreddits. The following are some of my favorites. I know it's not technically a reading list in the strictest sense but hey, what else would you call it? 

r/askmen  
r/askwomen  
r/cigars  
r/coffee  
r/fitness  
r/getmotivated  
[r/guns](https://www.reddit.com/r/guns/wiki/faq)  
r/legaladvice  
r/travel  
r/wine
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You can get away with being drunk in public (kind of), and you can get away with being disorderly in public (sometimes)with, but being both at the same time is illegal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 23:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 23:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does he take requests? I know some salty people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that why packing them away in violin cases became a thing?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
