<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2621</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 12:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A reddittor said I look like Snowden lol http://i.imgur.com/miDTtmg.jpg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 12:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're very welcome, good luck out there :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I learned from my ex that sells cologne, I'll look for a source 

Edit: what I found so far http://www.medicaldaily.com/smelling-colors-our-brains-associate-odors-color-fruity-smells-are-pink-294002
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So much fun  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :) 
You're sweet :3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck :) I'm sure you'll find a wonderful group of people out there  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First off, you sound cool (ever in northern Indiana hit me up) 
Start disk golfing, really easy to make friends with people there. It's not odd to do it alone (happens a lot) and it's common to get invited to a larger group. It usually takes place in parks. 
Go to a movie rental place and chat with the people that work there, you might make friends that way. Just do the things you like alone until you find some other people doing it, then do it with them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happened to me with a guy, turns out he just didn't have a car but had a huge crush on me and was hoping to keep me on the back burner until he got a car.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I don't know why I did...probably out of obligation and not having sex for 4 months  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been walked in on a few times, nothing sexy ever happens after lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you into? What are your hobbies and interests? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is actually a trick to cologne. 

Blue: every day

Green: clubs/parties where you're active 

Brown: weddings and that kind of thing

Anything in glass that's a minimum of $30 is going to be fine. Just choose what you like best.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never heard that one lol is that good? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You hit the nail on the head there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a nice way to frame that, why you didn't choose to write it that way is beyond me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :) I will </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 13:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time to move on my friend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 13:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 12:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep I made an autocorrect error.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 12:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are plenty of reasons someone could be ashamed of sex </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 12:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol thanks, all you have to do to get it is have massive amounts of body hair everywhere  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 12:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) I really like your comment. Thank you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 12:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 12:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Done and done ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 07:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :)
That made me smile  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 07:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Change of heart maybe. I could see a lot of scenarios where I might do this. I'm sorry bro, I thinks it's best you move on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 07:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blocked or he deleted his profile most likely  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 07:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure :) I like bath tub company  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 07:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 07:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as you're comfortable with it then all is going to be fine. You may regret it in the future but remember that there is no reason to be the sane person you were five minutes ago (favorite quote). If you don't like what you did then be someone who doesn't do that anymore. Good luck out there and stay safe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 07:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad you are feeling better. I really do wish you all the happiness in the world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 07:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope so. I need to get my shit together and start studying for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 07:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The painting has definitely helped a ton. I like tooling at a blank canvas and then looking at it finished thinking 'this only exists because of me'. I'm really grateful for your reply, thank you for spending some time on me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 07:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll definitely be your friend :) 
Thank you very much  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 07:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That episode of dexters is actually the reason I grew a beard lol
This is me pre beard  http://i.imgur.com/BXkQORO.jpg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't in a good place tonight and your comment is really helping get me out of there. Thank you :) 
And don't just get one beer, get two so we can share the moment ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is the first time I've been called chap and you know it really made me feel better lol
I try not to put out but I'm always driven there, it's usually not even the other guys, it's me thinking 'I should do this for you' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my first time trying it, I'm not usually an emotional guy but damn I am now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks :) 
You really have made my night better you know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, I grew it myself lol
I learned to shape it with a lot of trial and error. 
Really though, thank you for taking the time to read my blubbering mess up there. You must be wonderful to read through that and want to help me :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All we really are, are the stories we carry around with us. Don't shy away from something because the story might be bad, they can't all be good after all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really do wish you all the best. He was probably just being an idiot and doesn't know how to explain that. He probably just wasn't entirely in the mood for sex and thought he would get into it but you know that sometimes you just want to go without. He may have been trying to be sweet and keep it going for you but then his mind began to wonder and he thought he could sneak in an email because he's an idiot, like we all are. I'm not saying don't be mad at him, be mad at him, definitely be mad at him but you could use this moment to bring your relationship closer instead of drive it father apart. 
You're hurt and he knows he's in the wrong, you feel used and mistreated. He doesn't know how to explain himself and is thinking about how much he fucked up. Right now is not the time to put up a wall, you need to tear them down. Yell at eachother, cry together and fall in love. You have a chance to be completely honest with him, use it. 


Ps: since my last comment I've had wine and I've been thinking about how lonely I am lol so take my advice with that in mind...though he's still an ass, but who doesn't love an ass right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  http://i.imgur.com/gfj0Z1D.jpg http://i.imgur.com/UbXgh6Z.jpg http://i.imgur.com/BSh5CgS.jpg http://i.imgur.com/76OdJLD.jpg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm drinking wine lonely in the bathtub surrounded by candle lights but everything is going to be fine. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now before you picture some fancy ass guy here please know that I bought both the candles and wine on clearance and I can hardly fit in my tiny apartment bathtub (actually I think the tub is normal sized I'm just 6'4"). 
I keep making stupid decisions, I choose guys for the wrong reasons and when I choose right I'm constantly terrified that I'm about to loose them. Then the actions I take to keep them from leaving end up driving them away. 
I grew up in s trailer park and spent most of my life moving from apartment to apartment. I went to college for applied mathematics and finished the course program in December but I still need to pay them $1000 and take a test to pass out of Spanish so I can get the degree. I don't speak Spanish but I can't afford to take the class so I need to pass out. 
I work at a Walmart where I hate myself and do as little work as possible. My new boss hates me and her bosses have never liked me. I have two places where I'm trying to get a job and I'm waiting to hear back on both. I live pay check to pay check with no savings and very little food in my kitchen. I try to stay away from home as much as possible so it just gets dirty. My apartment stoped being my sanctuary and became the place where I sleep and fuck. 
I'm not over my ex. He broke up with me on my birthday. I don't know why but I can guess at a couple reasons. I used to be over 300 lbs but I've lost a lot of it. I still see a fat piece of shit in the mirror but everyone tells me otherwise. I see these guys I date and feel guilty, like I've conned them into going out with me. 
It's not all bad though. I started painting in January and I love it. I rekindled a friendship and removed a toxic person from my life. Just joined a gym, I'm going to go through with getting healthier (promise to myself). I met a guy and went on a nice date with him. I'm hoping we can keep doing this and I for once in my bloody life didn't fuck him on the first date...there was plenty of play and blowing but no dick in ass (that's a big accomplishment for me). I usually fuck early on because I'm good at it and feel like these guys are lowering themselves to be with me do I have to show them their money's worth. I never put that into words before...damn I'm a bit pathetic lol 
Even though I think I look like shit I know that I'm decently handsome and I have one hell of a wit. My personality has to be alright or I wouldn't have so many people like me. But for some reason I feel like I'm sinking. There is something wrong with me that's pulling me deeper and deeper into despair. I still get happy and feel close with people but there is something lurking there under the surface waiting to pull me under. I know I have it pretty good and that I shouldn't complain but I really want to complain right now. I want to read your replies. God only knows if I'll comment on them but I really like reading when someone who doesn't know me tries to help. I think it's because I have this air of manipulation about me, I feel like everyone who is my friend and that knows me has been tricked into it. My closest friends don't like me too much but that's ok, we built our friendships not off of liking eachother. I posted some pictures in the comments as a way to sucker you all into giving me compliments lol

To:dr I'm hosting a pity party and want your attention so I stop feeling lonely. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Picture yourself five years from now. You've gone to college and have all new friends; you've gained a new kind of relationship with your parents, more of a friendship. Then picture yourself at a beach bonfire with your friends and think 'is this a story I'd be ok telling'. If it is then go for it, if it isn't then still feel free going for it but remember one day you may be ashamed of these actions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 05:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make sure he knows what an ass he is  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 05:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My ex used to describe me as a straight guy that likes to suck cock lol
I'm pretty masc. I fix my car when it breaks, build shit, go to the gym, go camping and have massive bomb fires at the beach. I also paint and write. 
Here is a pic of me and one of my latest paintings (just started painting in January so be nice lol)
 http://i.imgur.com/tND9nph.jpg http://i.imgur.com/Bj35vcl.jpg 

Edit: if you can't tell I'm a fucking idiot lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've gotten every cut dick I've encountered off easily but the guy I've gone on a couple dates with is uncut and I can't seem to get him off with oral :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't matter what gets you in the gym as long as it keeps getting you there  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's just innocent texting then you having nothing to worry about. You need to take a step back and chill  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as you have enough money to get home on your own of things go bad then go for it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always thought it was a little weird that some people don't like certain races but I don't like larger people so I sorta get it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm bi but when given the option I choose men. They are just so much easier. Plus the sex is better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tend to give longwinded advice that is supposed to help you come to your own decisions but this time I'm going to start with my opinion of what you should do. You should break up. Break up in a nice way, do it gently and make sure you're financially independent. Tell him that you wanted to make things work and you'd like to try again but there are things that need to change and we can't change them while together. I'm sorry bro  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell him that you don't know how to describe your feelings yet. That you care about him so deeply and that hearing him say I love you made feel the same bitter flies in your stomach you felt with your first kiss. Tell him your favorite things about him, mention the little things he does without even noticing. Just keep telling him these things and say to him. 
"I care about you deeply and I want to use love to describe you when I'm sure, far beyond sure. Like the old couple that gets married and wonder why they didn't do it sooner. I want to make sure my deceleration to you is without the slightest hesitation." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought most people have a healthy mix of friends  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember that a kiss isn't just in the lips. You pull him closer, you grab him by the collar. Push him away and pull him back in. Hold him by the small of his back, squeeze his ass, grab his cock, run a hand up his thigh. Brush his hair out of his eyes, idly stroke his cheek. Hold his hand and squeeze, play with his fingers. Play with his hair, hold his arms down. Do anything on this list that turns you on ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like a fungus  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome. Good luck out there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You text him a day or two later and just say "round two?"  Couple days later "round three" and just keep on doing this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
