<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1397</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 20:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not going to happen. Too gerrymandered.  The only "hope" are the state level in 2018, which will redraw the 2020 maps.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Notice that it's not "your wealthy, educated and entrepreneurs" 

It's an invitation for the exact opposite. Those that need help, not those who will benefit us. (though we do benefit in the long run, it's not about that, it's about compassion for the less fortunate) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you have instead? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 16:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should get the lawsuit. Have Donald Trump try to prove in court his lies. The media corps have more money than him to pursue lawsuits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 16:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And second amendment people will take care of Hillary </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 15:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were 90K in friggin st Paul MN.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 15:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one is about the weather, not the size of the crowds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 15:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was funded by fraud and embezzlement, so...Mixed muddled messages </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 15:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, do you mean a white guy over 50 who is named for the Confederate president (and general) and denied judgeship because of his racially insensitive comments and views and was the earliest and most vocal supporter of a white nationalist for president? 

Is that the guy we don't want? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 14:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Narcissism is a mental disorder. That's him personally, the assholes were all the people that voted for him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 08:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My job is to keep reporters informed, and I'm all out of information.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 04:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or like the princess in princess Bride.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 04:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you see that ankle nut? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 04:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It won a bunch of Oscars, so it wasn't just reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 03:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In an old docu on him, it showed that he had an weird relationship with his mother </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 01:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically one is a subset of the other.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 17:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, if you listen to him he wants the country unified. 

It's just that his vision of unity is unity behind him.and his policies. He thinks the rest of the country need to fall in line with him. And that the onus is on us to come to him, and not himself as a leader to cross the divide and reach out. 

When he says "it's time for the country to get together" he hasn't yet realized that as a leader, he needs to be doing that work. 

But hes too stupid to realize that leadership requires work, and that most of country aren't going to back his stupid and racist policies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 04:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for that, though I guess it'll still be significantly slower than current, where the distance is likely less than a couple of miles. 

Los is line of sight, the device typically needs line of sight to satellites, like GPS (I could on about 5g, beam formation, etc, but suffice to say, it'll have to be a very large wavelength, and therefore carry very little information at a time) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: why is universal caller ID not common for cellphones after becoming common for landlines in the 90s? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 04:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 04:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are ancient Jews "Israelites" and modern people from Israel called "Israelis"?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 04:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a constitutional question that comes up every inauguration, including Obama (especially because he flubbed the oath).

Does the hour cause the president to be, or the oath.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 01:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sessions want savvy enough since 1986 when denied a judgeship because of racism to be somewhat introspective and stay as far away from any perceived racism, racist people or policies. 

But no, he not didn't shy away, but was usually first in line to support any policy or person that is racist. Up to and including being the first and consistent supporter of Donald Trump and his agenda. 

He clearly does not intend on changing now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a prog Dem, I'm trying to focus my concerns, because it's clear that most will get through, but which would be worst, or cause the most harm. 

First off, *Jeff sessions* and *Scott Pruitt.* By far the worst, and then ability to cause immediate, long term harm to humanity and the democracy/civil rights. Then *Flynn* because he is crazy AF. 

Next, *Devos* and *Carson*. Eminently unqualified, with potential to harm everyday people, everyday, and also, with education, harm generations of children. 

The rest are either qualified or competent enough to get qualified people and listen, or, in some cases, corrupt, which all things given could be said to be moderately OK. Even Rex Tillerson, I think (hope?) Is smart enough to get qualified, and is corporate enough to crave stability, and might be corrupt, but what can you do?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 14:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Current satellite internet ping is extremely laggy. Has Elon mentioned how he will get around that? Also LOS? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 04:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The GOP knocked him on his humility (or leading from behind, apologizing for America ,etc)

He also was extremely humble in the sense of kowtowing to traditions and cultures of the office etc. 

He always mentioned and owned up yo his failings and shortcomings, he was extremely humble. 


Imho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 04:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Without Lincoln's expansion of the executive, plus some interesting constitutional maneuverz, we'd still be a slave country. 

So, swings and roundabouts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 04:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And speeches, too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 04:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The trailer feels like American hustle or dallas buyers club which tapped out the 70s style audience for a while </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 03:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't fuck mean seal? As in the mammal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 03:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is there an o or u at the end of each word? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 03:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And waifu  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 14:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have those factions, they're called Caucasus. There are a lot of them, and they often stick together on issues that are important to those groups. 

Like the Congressional black caucus, the freedom Caucasus, the blue dog Caucasus (dying), the progressive Caucasus etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 03:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was special about your tooth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 01:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBH, they seems to make a lot of sense, and doesn't sound creepy at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 15:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump for President </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 13:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not about appeal, it's about defining what the party stands for. 

Reagan defined the GOP in terms of lower taxes (supply side), fear of government, hawkish foreign policy and Christian religion.

FDR defined the Democratic party as "new deal" or generally government safety net programs and concern for the poor, government choreography of economy (fed), etc.


Obama while a fine president did not change or redefine the Democratic party, just furthered its goals that had already been established.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 13:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget leap years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 01:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/zgHHph-CrC8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 18:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clearly this guy wasn't famous enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 16:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's where I find to be troubling. 

If we were to give him the most benefit of the doubt about his real beliefs on race, then For most people, after being explicitly rebuked and rejected by the Senate for racism, they would then have some self-reflection and wonder where people get the idea that you're racist. Then, make sure to run as far away as possible from anyone or anything that even smells of racism. 

Yet he seems to constantly accidentally having racist opinions and first to stand up together with racists, and very enthusiastically so. 

If the smoke is damnably not pointing to fire, then why does smoke seem to constantly billow from you. 

Even your name, Jefferson beureaugard, are for the president and first general of the Confederacy. You don't choose your name, but if you bear them, and are accused of racism, why didn't you make sure to be seen as little racist as possible, instead of as most.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 14:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one under 60 would ever buy a Lincoln or a Cadillac. Like not even on the radar of want or desirability. 

And when you add the competition of BMW, mercedes, Lexus, heck, even Audi, American autos can't even begin to compare. 

If you are looking downmarket, you'd really only consider corrolas, civics, Camrys and accords. SUVs you've got CR-V, Rav 4 etc. 

Basically the only American cars that people actually want are pickup trucks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 14:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was he Orthodox-jewish? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 14:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddiquette </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 01:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps a constant flow of yellow journalism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 01:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a big deal, but bugs me: "bloc" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 23:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uhhh, that's where we got the current situation. Gaza was part of Egypt, West Bank was part of Jordan and Golan was part of Syria. 

Israel took them during a defensive war (anyone who tells you that because Israel was the aggressor in 67 is ignorant (willfully or otherwise) of the context of that war), until that point there were no calls for an independent Palestinian nation (outside of getting rid of Israel), and there were certainly no calls for Jordan and Egypt to end their "occupation" of those territories, including Jerusalem (which was supposed to be a neutral, internationally administered territory for everyone, until Jordan unilaterally conquered it in 48 and kicked out the Jews). 

So essentially these peoples did have their own "countries", which were conquered defensively after being attacked. But here we are. So I don't think that's the goal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 23:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ireland did it. The two Germanies did.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Russia Loves the Idea of California Seceding </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 14:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 04:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know life's unfair. But why isn't it ever unfair in my favor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 14:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Emails and not enough racist or penis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 14:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A little of both wasa quote from the hearing. It was his response to rubios inquiry whether he didn't know or didn't want to answer the question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could plaid mode be focused on 60-130 instead of 0-60? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 06:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking, as teslas approaches the theoretical maximum acceleration for standard vehicles, there may not be any room for a plaid mode. 

The 1 area where tesla loses to other high end sports cars is the continuing acceleration after hitting 60 (tesla racing channel vs Aventador). Tesla p90dl is 60-130 in 11.6, whereas the Aventador is 7.1. Huge difference. 

Additionally in the movie, the modes were about does not necessarily acceleration. 

Could plaid mode be longer acceleration power? Or maybe 200+ top speed?

Anyways, just thoughts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 22:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess this is why people with ADHD have longer life expectancies  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 19:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think if Dunkirk turns out well, we will see a couple of copycars, and maybe good ones, doing specific battles or moments from various wars from mid 19th century through mid 20th </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 16:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> does bowie bergdahl also belong among this company? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 16:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jokes notwithstanding, Playboy was actually quite the journalistic force back in the day, writing on Vietnam and such, that's how they landed such big interviews like President Carter and other cultural icons from Frank Lloyd Wright to Ian Fleming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 15:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> During the election, I followed a rule: Anything The D accused anyone else of, not only was it false, it was ultimately true of himself, and worse. 

This rule has held steady for a long time, and I think my worst fears were confirmed now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 14:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think, even if we were to give mr sessions the full benefit of the doubt that he wasn't racist in his past, you'd think that after being rejected for the judgeship he would have at least put in some extra effort to prove them wrong or to go as far away from perceived racism as possible. But no, the opposite, he continues to hold views and company with racists and things that are questionable. 

That alone is what gets me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 14:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/EKhhKkffXzE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 14:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just like with anything today, it's all about authenticity and rarity. Like why do people insist on diamonds instead of cubic zirconium, or a Prada t-shirt vs a j crew or white gold vs aluminum and orange juice not from concentrate. 

They likely did so that to achieve a purple, and have a knockoff dyes, but only the royalty had the *real* designer purple. And perhaps there were even qualities in the purple dye that made it special, like some sort of iridescence or some way of it being special.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 21:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He literally is named for the president of the Confederacy and Confederate general. 

He is not responsible for his name, but does give insight to the environment his views are formed by </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 17:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> does safer mean solitary? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 16:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The longue duree theory is a way of thinking of history through these geological terms and how they affect smaller events. Particularly braudels *the Mediterranean* which talks about this concept in particular </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 14:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's easy, just greet with a cheerful "Yap T'vayeh Mott" and you'll be good to go. Or in more formal situations, a sincere "Ad'nah a Choi" will class it up (hard ch) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 05:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> architects.

they all hate their clients and the public ie the people who pay them. they all think they, and their designs are gods gift to mankind. Ayn Rand wasnt far off the mark about architects - she just somehow thinks its a good thing.

source: am architecting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 04:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it is actually a common tattoo:

https://www.google.com/search?q=mastodon+leviathan source=lnms tbm=isch sa=X ved=0ahUKEwiK-4So1bbRAhWG6IMKHXhWB0YQ_AUICCgB biw=1787 bih=822#tbm=isch q=mastodon+leviathan+tattoo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 04:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a fluent Yiddish speaker and knowledgable in the culture (I'm jewish etc) the translation misses a good number of words and definitely doesn't convey all the nuances that the language and mentality and conversation that is flowing here.

This part alone is so true to spirit and to tone its a masterpiece. Even fiddler on the roof doesn't quite capture it as well as this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 14:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is an online grocery in new York region (aimed at kosher) that has offered snap payments for at least 6 years now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 04:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But when I was 7 I super wanted that stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 03:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Orthodoxy Jew here: 

Never had dairy and meat together (cheeseburger, pepperoni pizza etc)

Never had shellfish (crab, lobster, shrimp etc)

Never had fast food or any food from any restaurant you've heard of (KFC, MCD, BK, IHOP, Wendy's etc)

Never had the back half of a cow 

Never had pig (pork, ham, bacon)

Never had Doritos or Lucky Charms 

I'm sure there's more. It sucks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 16:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish more movies had an inverse extended cut. Where they cut the movie to 75-90 minutes. 

It's about my max attention span and for non-artsy movies, enough to tell a story (action, comedy, horror) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 15:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am actually quite familiar with this, as well as have some knowledge of hareidi economics as studied academically. 

A) among super hareidi, an apartment is part of the dowry. Families are expected to acquire a property for their children as they marry. 

B) hareidim don't typically use banking system, they have their own (unregulated) banking system called gemach (gemilat chasaidim) which lends out money for stuff, including housing, interest free and without requiring good credit. 

C) they usually are in very cramped and tiny quarters

D) charity and gov housing subsidies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 15:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They didn't cancel, just delayed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 13:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see you have also spent geography period fantasizing your heroship in case of attack </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 13:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to pay attention to the road and physically handle a steering wheel and pedals to drive. And you had to pass a test and be 16 years old </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 13:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And sometimes decides to try and kill you by getting a little too swollen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 03:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take one, leave one rule </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 03:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the way the world works </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 03:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reince repeibus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 02:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But so weird to see their characters reversed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 22:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I now destroy buildings. I'm the Demolition Man formerly known as architect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 22:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No they don't. I just did a Google search, first 1tb SSD is 265 retail. Prices are way down, and this is meant to to be a high performance computer. Or absolutely need to be SSD. 

https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1287124-REG/wd_wds100t1b0a_00h9h0_1tb_blue_sata_iii.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 16:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe yes, maybe no.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 04:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun story: mom lost iPhone. Went to log on, but had setup two step authentication. Authentication to iPhone. But don't know where it is. Stuck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 21:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, we need a storm back story that makes us empathize (cars is less dark than toy story 3), and somehow in the end everyone is happy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 02:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the old version, it plowed into a semi because autopilot couldn't handle trucks easily (signs, etc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 17:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't quite understand the context of this. Can anyone explain a bit?

Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 15:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HO vs N </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 15:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Revit vs Archicad (mostly regional, though)

(And rhino vs SketchUp; grasshopper vs dynamo) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 06:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you buy anything, a portion goes towards other people's healthcare (and more). 

For example, when you buy your Starbucks coffee, a portion of that profit goes towards salaries and benefits of the employees and the employees of the suppliers. Including their healthcare. 

And not just Starbucks, also your duck dynasty themed wife beater. If it makes profit, it's paying for someone else's healthcare.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 22:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The question is, is he be paid as much now, and is his reach/influence as much as it could have been? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 21:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am intrigued by the "my" qualifiers only being associated with "dog" and "phone." 

Can you elaborate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 19:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or Tom Cruise in topic thunder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 16:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No only as just a touch said, but you can change the shape to fit in, for example, as an architect, if forced to work with this project might have added a small reveal on the perimeter of the wall/ceiling, this would heighten the effect of the coffered ceiling being continuous, and not just cut off at the wall, then in the reveal stick several 4"x36" registers. 

Also, in line with the go with all the lights, could stick some cove lighting there, too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 15:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You forgot to mention the 'male gaze' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 15:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly the headline. They could succeed, or all could go wrong. That's literally reality for everything in the world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 21:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grand slam? Score, love-love </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 15:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Howabout when you have a slight stiffy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 15:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure that the number is equal for the black side, as well. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An 'Avatar'-themed park is coming to Disney World next summer  here's how it will look </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 02:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 02:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not exactly with that phrasing, but I'm not a movie person. I usually watch movies as a way to zone out when stressed out tired. Mild entertainment, and not too emotionally or intellectually invested in the movie. I only really watch, maybe once a month, at most. 

Therefore I don't watch many dramas or thrillers etc. Just stupid comedies and some action films and family animation films. 

It doesn't mean I don't appreciate those other films, or enjoy them, when I have the time or emotional space to give them. 

It's just not a high priority for me, and not how I choose to watch. 

Therefore, if recommended a "serious" or "artsy" film, I won't get around to it for a very long time, and if I boiled the reason down, it would be that I have to pay attention to it, and I don't feel like paying attention. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 01:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone seems to be talking about the Suzuki method, 10000 hours of practice, etc. 

That's not the question here. The question is why, within and among those who practice, there are some who outshine their peers, and also some who seem to have a head start. Clearly, Mozart, who began performing at 3 had innate talent - after all, he wasn't even alive for 10000 hours yet. 

Starting with the latter, it might be that some people have better hearing (more in tune, including up to pitch perfect hearing), some have better fine motor skills (pick up intricate finger motions and delicate dexterity), some have better rythm or math skills to understand the underlying scale and complexity of music, with, when combined with a more creative mind and problem solving skills, can create music that is great. 

With sports, obviously, tall people have more "innate" basketball talent; people with enlarged hearts can perform better at stamina and aerobic sports (marathon; racing; swimming). People talk about Phelps odd body, which is uniquely suited to swimming fast (long arms, wide hands and toes, tapered torso, etc)

So there are physical aspects to becoming great at something. With some sports, like football, Tom Brady is known to be great because he understands the psychology of football, which means he can exploit certain things better. This means, being intelligent and creative makes for a better or more talented player, not just body. If course, some people are naturally stronger, faster and more fit, which will definitely help with sports. 

This is why, it's not just practice, people at professional level of sports, music, art etc all practice for thousands of hours, yet there is only one Gretzky, Jordan, Mozart, Picasso etc. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 01:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mozart wasn't even alive for 10000 hours before he was known as a musical prodigy and composing music. Was he not talented?

I guess the question op is asking semantics, but what makes some people savant?

Clearly, in professional sports, they are all putting in thousands of hours of practice, and besides for physical uniqueness (like Lance Armstrong and Michael Phelps), there is a reason Michael Jordan and Wayne Gretzky dominate their sports, and it's not just the practice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 16:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Full autonomous driving (Punch in coordinates, go to sleep).

I would like to visit space once. 

More stretching it: flying as a normal from of daily transport/commute

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 22:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must have been all that meme magic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 15:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct. Which is why I specifically mentioned it. It also should be noted that it wasn't a guest oped, but from the journal's staff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 13:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Rangoooooo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 13:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having tried to do this with my credit card, its totally not worth it. It's all manual paperwork, a lot of it, needs to be mailed in (not emailed). Needs to be a minimum amount ofomey difference, and there is also a max, and then it needs to get reviewed by someone, and it's all in all big hassle. Not worth the 50$ it gives you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 13:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would schoolyard tavern be for older patrons only? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 13:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have been cleverly using specific terminology to frame normal views as radical. 

The other week an op-ed from WSJ called Bernie and Warren "Alt-Left"

Semantically, it does several, complex and contradictory, things at once. 

1. It makes it seem that normal, if populist, views are radical. 

2. It makes alt-right seem more mainstream

3. It makes it seem that Warren and Sanders are evil (if alt-right is, then by extension....)

4. It makes a false equivalence between more left and racist right  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 12:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jews have been providing the gentiles with celebration assistance, starting with jesus himself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 12:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meshulachim are Israeli charity collectors. Shluchim are chabad rabbis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 16:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like your written film essay better than the YouTube ones. We should have more of these. No more efap knockoffs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 16:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 16:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not going to bother trying, but you can have an online account without purchasing a subscription on nytimes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 15:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Civil asset forfeiture </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 04:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, he wasn't a *real* American President </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 04:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the 10 year old seduced him. It isn't Saint donalds fault.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 04:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does any of this make Cooper and the Dems look bad? It's completely one sided?

This false both sides are bad is driving me insane.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 19:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We probably would be friends </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 18:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Collapse of oil will make many crazy countries desperate. Do you really want desperate Saudi Arabia; Iraq; Russia; Nigeria and Norway? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 16:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, the only real way trump will be out in 2020 is through a gop primary challenge.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 15:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is the cue to back out of the conversation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 15:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poe's law </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 14:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The context of this conversation is wwii </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 03:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ashkenazi_Jews

"90% in in 1930" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 02:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. The remaking of Hebrew is only in context of natively speaking and in common parlance of a nation. 

Hebrew was regularly spoken and studied and used in prayer from ancient times through today. Most jewish scholars published, and they are almist all in Hebrew. 

The Mishna, rashi, tosafot, rishonim, tur and shulchan aruch, and even all the writings of the maharal himself was written in Hebrew. 

The majority of prayers, which are about 60 pages recited by jewish people daily is in Hebrew. 

If anything, Aramaic is less commonly used because of how few books and prayers were written in it, even though it wasn't entirely uncommon, as mentioned above. 

This is why Kabbalah is written in Aramaic, because it's slightly less accessible than Hebrew to the common folk. Also, according to jewish lore, angels can't understand Aramaic, so to bypass angels, and go directly to god, they believe in using Aramaic. Hence the use of Aramaic in kabbalist magic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 01:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. The Zohar was written in Aramaic. Jews have always spoken and studied in local languages, but also in Hebrew, Yiddish and Aramaic. The Talmud is in Aramaic, as are other texts and liturgies. 

So, basically all Jews everywhere were familar with the language to some extent (kaddish, one of the most basic and famous prayers is in Aramaic). They would not have considered Aramaic to be foreign or exotic at all. 

The Zohar is the seminal kabbalist text. Written in Spain (Moses de Leon or something) in Aramaic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 20:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maharal lived in Prague. Kabala is jewish mysticism. Maharal was a mystic. Jewish mystic writing is in Aramaic. 

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kabbalah

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Judah_Loew_ben_Bezalel

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 17:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you sure that the dentist will be available then?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 17:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. There were more Ashkenazi than Arab Jews. There are other jewish hybrid languages such as ladino and judeo-arab </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 17:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. Thats the point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 17:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure golem was Aramaic, language of kabala.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 17:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very close. Any modern Hebrew speaker can pick up an ancient Hebrew text and read it fine. Some technical words would be different or semantically different. There was basically one grammar change to accommodate creation of new words (-on suffix to imply relation).

Ancient Israelites could drop in and read modern Hebrew, but many words would be new for new inventions and concepts. 

All in all remarkably similar.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 16:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess that's all fine then, after all the current president elect is doing the same thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snowden is still in contact with Russian intelligence, House report charges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 16:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 02:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Question on a similar vein: 

Food with heat have capsaicin which activate heat receptors in the mouth.

Food with cold like menthol trigger the cold receptors. 

What do sharp foods trigger? Ie mustard, wasabi and horseradish. 

They're not exactly hot, and the sensation, which clears the sinus, is quite intense, so it's not just taste/flavor. What is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 02:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True story:

Went to Hawaii. 

Got a case of pineapples. 

So excited. 

Tastes fine. 

Look at box. 

Am disappoint. 


Box says "product of Florida". 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 14:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kafka </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 14:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But at the same time repeatedly punching yourself in the nuts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 14:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're also collecting bets from everyone, and giving different odds to different countries, to ensure maximum spending </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 14:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically how you start fascism and dictatorships. Stifle dissent. 


Congress is too scared to be a check on his power </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 05:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't care for the aztek, but it did invent the crossover suv, perhaps the most profitable vehicular product category ever since </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 05:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Always found it weird that their board was made up of old diplomats and government people. Like, hey, why not scientists, doctors and engineers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 03:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. Totally ruined the film for me. Bro, do you even premise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 03:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or, you know, Kafkaesque </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 18:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think trump is literal hitler (a bit store brand knock off, though), but honestly, if they were smart (big if), there would try to get"eagles of death metal". The band are big trump supporters, they hate Muslims, love conspiracy theories (the same ones trump likes) and surviving a terrorist attack makes them American heroes to them, it would be huge marketing coup. 

On the other hand, they're not smart.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 14:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's going to be embarrassing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 14:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She didn't win by the largest margin ever. She simply had the largest margin of winning the popular vote while still losing the electoral </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 04:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's about a baby. A baby who is also Alex Baldwin/jack donaghy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 03:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like sausage party? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 03:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are some realistic white ass nipples </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 03:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Latkes and chocolate coins. And dreidel gambling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 03:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just jelly donuts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 03:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always found that reasoning odd. People hate paying the mortgage, but don't really hate the banker who gave it to them. 

Sure the Jew charged interest and the Christian didn't, but at the end of the day the Jew didn't force the Christian to take out a voluntary loan on the condition of repayment with interest. Why would you hate someone who you voluntarily agreed to their terms.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This bakery is taking politics to their products. Not sure if good or bad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 21:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Make America Eat Cake Again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 21:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 20:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Much of the word clock fun is directly related to its informal and idiomatic, imprecise telling of time, including its 5 minute increments (of course, this German op couldn't handle too much ambiguity, and added the four dots for exact minutes) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 02:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Squash in America is a vegetable. Gourds and pumpkins </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 02:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, that's gay. Lets just bone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 01:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering the CEO or chairman or whatever was ruled by the court as being too senile to make decisions, he probably is watching lots of Nickelodeon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 01:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not by choice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 01:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, too tired. Can we reschedule for 2:30pm? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 22:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun fact, knock knock jokes don't work in Germany.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 22:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess mcrory is still bitter about not getting invited out to parties in Charlotte </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 20:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Minnesota had colder winters than Sweden </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 19:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that duck family </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 15:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bitburg_controversy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 15:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mall of America in Minnesota (cold) has no central heating.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 05:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, sock distributer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 05:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mizrahi (lit eastern) is only Iraqi and Afghani. Syrian are halab (allepo), Yemenite are teimani (southern). North African are maghrebi (from Maghreb).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 04:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Medicaid. Medicare is old people. Medicaid is less wealthy people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 04:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am architect. This is basically correct.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 20:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or, you know, commemorating nazi SS officers, and publicly stating that he didn't want to visit a concentration camp because he didn't want the Germans to feel guilty about the whole thing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 19:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The margins were so tiny in the rust states, that anything could have flipped the election </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 16:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The authors underlying reason why we should take this seriously is because of its implications on how arrive at knowledge and decisions, based upon expertise, consensus and scientific method. 

Clearly he hasn't been paying attention the election. Because all of those were completely thrown out, trump supporters do not, and explicitly do not, agree or use these methods to arrive at decisions and discernment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 15:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That wasn't just garage.  It was Michael Gove.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 14:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is apparently what we get when the Dems have a candidate who has emails. It's our own fault really. 

/S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 14:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only because how much influence and potential for a global scale version the US has </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 06:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else imagine Putin at the keyboard running CMD and'hacking,' while his underlings egg him on with an unsubtle house music beat in the background </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 03:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About 2 months ago, Reddit emailed me that my account was hacked or something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 14:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pop Pringles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 13:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? What/who is the subject, and what is the predicate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 06:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have bad timing.  Don't know when to start a conversation, don't know when is time to stop the conversation. Don't know when "nows not the time" or when to tone it down. I speak too forcefully, comes across as intense. 

I'm a one-upper, an interrupter and an interjected of irrelevant tangents. 

I'm needy and need approval, but also a know it all and unconfident egotist. 

I guess I'm socially clueless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 03:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to go all reverse Godwin, but this is what trump feels like.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 03:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A woman killing her children is what it takes to get you to watch a movie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 02:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look up variolation. They basically just took a group of orphans, and infected them. Then sent them on ships around the world to inoculate people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 00:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, as progressive, the best chance moving forward is to support a conservative primary challenger in 2020. 

Kasich/Romney/Cruz (Rubio is too puny) can beat Trump in 2020, and I would take any of them, even Cruz, over Trump. At least his damage is reversible, and will prevent more consolidation of power/disruption than Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 05:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently not a career breaker, though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 20:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They look like they have Parkinson's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 15:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you weren't so angry, you'd be able to see past yourself. 

A) lighting affects mood. 

B) moods and other correlated factors affect pupil dilation, edict affect light reflection and intensity. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 03:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We'll probably see the March towards universal in an incremental fashion. 

Through gradual expansion of medicaid at the federal and state level, and the expansion of medicare, as well. 

Something like this:

Medicaid: as already happening:

gradually raise the floor, so more and more middle class people become eligible, also, children specific Medicaid under other names will be expanded. Both will also be expanded by having tiers ranging from free to higher premiums as parents are better off, this will eventually include standard Medicaid. Eventually this will expand to include more and more income brackets. 

Medicare: eventually we will get the option for 55 and older to buy in (for money) info medicare. This will be sold as away to save Medicare financially (infusion of cash, infusion of less frequent users in the pool).

The age will gradually come down, and the cash cost will eventually become a tax, and will just be regular medicare, watch over time will expand to include more and more ages.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 02:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They rely so little on fact, as it is, and only perception. Trump, the master salesman that he is, will easily be able to say the country is improved, regardless of its actual state. Just as he was able to say its in terrible state now, even though it's relatively fine. 

I, one who fears trump like Hitler, do not honestly believe he will lose in 2020 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 02:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One thing that people seem to miss, and this goes for Giuliani and Gingrich, is that most cabinet and other high level positions rarely last as long as the administration. 

By turning down appointments they feel are beneath them, they retain top consideration for positions that open up down the line.

Christie wanted to be VP, but considering his current toxicity (bridge+Kushners), he realized he couldn't get the top position. But he probably figures that down the line, it will be old news, and he can slide into AG or SoS in two-for years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 00:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Among the many reasons mentioned, they actually saw a big increase in implementation in passenger jets in 2002ish. 

Reason being that there was a plane crash (shortly after 9/11) in Queens new York shortly after takeoff. It was determined that this incident was caused, in part, by excessive turbulence in the air from a jet that took off just before it. 

Winglets were found to dramatically decrease turbulence caused by the close confluence of differently pressurized air at the wing tips. This would have prevented the crash, and it was found to increase flight efficiency and stability, etc. 

Military planes have different mission requirements.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 21:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that why McMullin was an intelligence agent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 17:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whic is unfortunate, IMH(unpopular)O. In making Jurassic World, Spielberg told him to make it more action film, and less horror/suspense/thriller. Which it delivered on in spades. 

Honestly, I prefer the action version too the suspenseful version. Just more fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
