<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1565</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Season 1 of The Wire </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Nicolas Cage is in it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is normal now? Good question. From one side of the table you could argue that this is it and rates won't rise for 20 years. The level of mortgage debt alone here in Canada would cripple our economy if rates spiked, and Poloz knows this. Never mind the trillions that the US government has to contend with on their balance sheet. I somewhat believe the FED has only forced a few rates hikes in order to have some ammo in their pocket should the shit hit the fan again. Imagine the economy taking a nose dive with rates at zero? Then what? How do you stimulate an economy with rates at zero? But I'm not an economist so I start to tail off on this topic pretty quickly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. The theory is sound, but only based on a specific set of underlying fundamentals. When the fundamentals change, so must the application.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry mate. Your prof regurgitated some nice books, but she forgot to teach you the most important class..... real life application. The market is currently full of people taking on more risk than they may want because THEY HAVE TO. Bond yields are in the toilet, and cash pays nothing. So from a real return standpoint, the asset allocation laid out above generates shitty, if not negative real returns. Why have dividend paying stocks done so well since 2008? Hmmm, well with interest rates at zero, along with bond rates, where are conservative investors supposed to go? What about retirees looking for that 5% cash flow? It's not coming from bonds or cash, so they have been forced to buy blue chip dividend paying stocks. Mark my words, as interest rates normalize over the coming years or decades, money will absolutely flow out of dividend paying stocks and back into bonds, especially given the number of retirees in the baby boom generation. But that could take forever. Until then, where else to you go but the highest quality stocks. Utility companies have been a perfect example. Strong balance sheets based around things people need. Given some of their low payout ratios as well, there is no wonder why they have been doing so well. They have represented the lower risk option in the equity markets for income investors. But they are still equity. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 03:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the important thing was that I had an onion tied to my belt, which was the style at the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 13:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> APH could have a good day today. Support was at $6.50 as that was the bottom of the trend line on the weekly chart, and while it broke that support intraday, hitting a low of $6.29, it rallied hard and closed above that support line. Technically that's bullish and we could get a little relief rally today. However, I believe it has to finish the week above that number to truly confirm that support. We shall see.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
