<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2840</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm not dying without doing this" basically. If it ends bad, I probably won't be affected for long.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 05:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the difference between Jesus and a hooker? 

The sounds they make when getting nailed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 05:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol my friend did this thing with a pig. Still does if thou, it's disgusting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 05:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out at sea, they'll probably see a wave that's maybe 0.5-1m(probably less) high, that's what tsunamis look like so far out. The reason for this is that tsunamis have all the water in the ocean moving in a particular direction. Since the ocean is so deep, moving all the water will only cause a slight rise in height, but near the shore, where it's extermely shallow, it has to put all that water somewhere, so it put it in its height. We could work backwards from the height at sea(let's say 1m) and the distance to figure out how high the wave will be when it hits.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 05:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vegas. Now you're thinking of gambling and drunk people and bachelor parties. Nope, that's not in Vegas. You're thinking of paradise. Paradise is an official, non-officially occupied territory, that's where all the casinos are, that's even where the "welcome to Las Vegas!" Sign is. The reason is that the casinos didn't want to pay taxes to the town, the town tried to forcibly take over, the county made it officially non-official territory so that they can't just take over.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man my schools AP bio teacher does this. The entire fucking year is based on evolution and she's a Catholic and she always says that it's not true and God created all life, it didn't evolve out of water(talk about unbiased opinions will you?)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boy why do they even do that? I don't think there is a  single male person who has friends that're girls that he DOESNT want a romantic relationship with. Even I, as a horny teenage male, have female friends that I don't wanna go out with. It's fucking crazy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People clapping on a plane. It fascinates me how some people would do that, it's kinda stupid. Does the entire restaurant clap when your waiter brings you food? Why clap when the guy presses a button and lets autopilot do the work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And an idiot like that is now leading the most powerful country on earth. Yippie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in Bahrain and it only happened to me once. It really annoyed the shit outta me but it never really happened again lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a big fucking difference between debating your point and offending you. I was speaking to my friends about the political situation in Syria, and after telling him that he's outright wrong, everyone reacted like I've slapped him "Hey man, respect him opinion, don't try to offend him." Yes I'm so sorry that facts are offending you. Gravity is a social concept. Have a good day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh holy shit this is so true. If there's anyone behind me, I would walk out, and hold the door open. It's common courtesy. I don't care if it's a guy or girl behind me, I do it more out of habit. Say "thanks" not "FUCK YOU YOU SEXIST PIG".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bahrain(where I live) is in a small civil war("small" as in there's no active conflict, 120+ killed since the Arab Spring) and whenever I see these "protests" I despise it. We're literally getting killed and tortured for rioting. Y'all do it just because you're allowed to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever we have class discussions, I will always quickly shut my friends Down if they're undermining the person, not the arguement. I try to limit the amount of personal attacks, and keeping it to the argument.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This right here. Non of my favorite artists main points are sex/drugs. For me, music is something to relax to while doing something else, like playing a game. I don't wanna hear "AND THEN I FUCKED HER IN THE MOUTH AND SNORTED COKE OFF HER ASS!!!" Woodkid is a fucking genius, every single song he's written is connected to another song, he even found a way to connect his album to a movie soundtrack, using a single line. We need more people like him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Girls can't be themselves online. If you've ever been on 9gag, you'll know what I mean. Girl has a selfie as her DP, guys are like "hey babe wanna fuck?" And shit like that. You know she won't respond, you know nothing good is coming out of this, so don't do it. Teens are so hyped up on sex that they don't have any manners to girls. Part of the problem is in the parenting of course, they should've learned some fucking manners from their parents.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 05:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cut out all the unnecessary details, just get right down to it. You can add jokes or something, just nothing unnecessary. 

"when we went down to the beach that Anna and Jake recommended which had all the food trucks" then you never come back to the trucks. This is a bad example, but you get the gist of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 05:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chocolate milk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 05:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a man who bombed an administration building in Amsterdam, if he didn't, hundreds, maybe thousands, of Jews would've been identified. He was gay and did it partially to prove that gays aren't bad, or weak, or cowards. Ik this isn't what you asked, but I felt like he should be known.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically, the French were prepared for a WWI trench warfare. They got a heavily mobilized attacks with jeeps, tanks, and planes instead. The nazis were creeping through a forest that wasn't protected by the maginot line(like the Great Wall of china, the maginot line was meant for defense, but they left the forest aside since it's like a natural defense) the tanks and planes destroyed the French.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 07:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> subject2840 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 06:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Elephants are one of the animals you really don't wanna fuck with. This elephant is super young, give it a few months and try doing this, expect broken bones. Male elephants get a kind of period, once a year that lasts around a month. Imagine an animal that literally would kill anything within sight, regardless if it's someone from their pack. They have to be restrained until their "period" is over. Don't. Fuck. With. Elephants.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 06:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nooooo you're not, I'm sure you're a great person :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
