<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1323</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 09:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it's way off. Despite Trump's recklessness and any repercussions it might have on Israel's inside man in ISIS, the US remains an important ally to them and NATO countries. You still have a massive intelligence body that generates a lot of info that benefits these allies. You also have much more resources than they do, allowing you to analyze emerging info efficiently. And lastly, more than any other country in the world, you have the ability to act on intel provided quickly and efficiently. Even if Israel felt skeptical about Trump's administration and its relationship with the Russians, they'll come back to you because you have a massively powerful security apparatus and, unlike most other countries, are very eager to use it when the need arises. They could take the same info to Germany, China, UK, France, Canada, Australia, all of which have decent militaries, but those countries are far more cautious than you are when it comes to engaging targets in foreign territory. So, no, the media and a lot of other people are exaggerating when they suggest that America's allies will stop sharing their secrets because of this reckless act by Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 07:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the ricin is also a giveaway. seems to be a signature weapon of theirs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 14:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome. :). I loved it too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 13:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't do it ... but if I did it, there wouldn't be anything wrong with that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 13:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you sure, you're not gay? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
