<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3323</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two lost souls are sitting on a hill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 06:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soul 1: Hey wanna play the ghost game?

Soul 2: Sure!

Soul 1: That's the Spirit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 19:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who says video game jokes can't make it to number one, because I think anything is possible! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just because I'm below grade average and my family is poor, doesn't mean I won't be applying to colleges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 09:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's bound to be one college with an opening position as a janitor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 08:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Billions of light-years away </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You know Shia Lebeouf really wasn't kidding in his TED talk, a lot of kids really are lazy look at all of the scholarships that are unused each year. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 07:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A father buys a lie detector </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 06:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idiot, doesn't even realize he waisted $400 on a sham. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I got arrested for killing a black man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 04:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My death penalty is tommorow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 07:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a limo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It was pajama day at school today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 06:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rachel showed up in onesie, looked rather warm and comfortable.

Roger showed up in a sleepingbag and wiggled around school like a caterpillar.

Jeff showed up in a white tee and underwear, no pants.

Rachel asked Roger if he could talk to Jeff about his "spirit wear". So Roger wiggled over to Jeff and asked "dude, why'd you wear that to pajama day?"

Jeff replied, "It's pajama day?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 06:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a man of many suits either I see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 06:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ughh just stop please </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girl: "Draw me like one of your french girls" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hate it when people pronounce "Uranus" correctly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 06:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hate it when people ask me what life is going to be like in three years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 07:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't see into the fucking future </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You know what grinds my gears? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 08:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing, I'm not a fucking robot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some people call me crazy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 03:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tell them my name is Steve, and that they should've read my fucking name-tag. It's literally on my work uniform, the thing I just happen to be wearing when they call me this. Seriously the nerve of some people, they stand at least 5 feet away from me from my work station and somehow can even read the right fucking name, WHERE THE FUCK DO THEY GET CRAZY IT DOESN'T SAY CRAZY ON MY FUCKING NAME-TAG!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Antijokes are like lightbulbs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 06:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no punchline </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 07:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's moved on, dude, but hey cheer up. I'm sure you'll meet another dude named Stacy who identifies themselves as a female, who'll take you in and tie your shoes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thanks for explaining the phrase "a lot" to me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 20:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it means many </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why don't squirrels mate in the summer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 05:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they're storing their nuts for the winter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 06:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can spot a repost when I see one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do riot police get to work early? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 06:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To the beat the shit out of all night protesters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 10:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't teach you that in 5th grade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I know that the placebos is supposed to help with testing pills and medicines if they actually work... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 06:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But who's smart-ass idea was it to try it with Birth Control!?!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 08:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get why it's engineers and lawyers though, is there a reason, or could it just be replaced with any other two groups of people in this context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As an artist, I choose smart AP courses in high school that way I'm always the best artist in the class. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 08:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An 80s singer caught himself on fire, what does he do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 01:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop, Drop, and Rick-Roll </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 05:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol I love this joke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I got just got raped by a gang of mimes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 09:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They scarred me for life and I know I'll never be able to forget the damage the did. So here's a helpful info guide to avoiding rapists.

*wikiHow to Prevent a Potential Rape* 

Rapists are predators. Period. By following these steps, you can try to make your world a little safer from those predators. You will get information and skills you need to protect yourself psychologically and physically. Remember, although being aware of your surroundings and knowing how to defend yourself is important, rape is ultimately the rapist's fault, not the victim's. This article is not meant to justify a rapist's actions in any wayit simply provides tips that can help you feel safer. In an ideal world, the best way to prevent a potential rape is to educate all members of both sexes to respect and help each other. However, being informed can also go a long way in helping you avoid dangerous situations.

*Part 1 Setting the Record Straight*

1) Know that nothing you do will ever make rape your fault. Before you even start thinking about preventing a potential rape, you have to understand that if you are raped, it is 100% the rapist's fault, and that nothing you did, wore, or said could have caused you to be raped. There is no such thing as "asking for it," and anyone who leads you to believe otherwise is deeply misguided. Though you can certainly take measures to improve your chances of avoiding danger and staying safe, in the end, nothing you can do can "cause" you to be raped.

2) Understand that the best thing that can be done to prevent rape is to prevent people from raping. In today's culture, there are many things that can be done to prevent rape, and it starts with the way women are perceived. If we work, as a society, to raise men who are respectful of women and stop contributing to a culture that objectifies and belittles women constantly, then we can slowly start to turn things around. Sometimes, adolescent boys think "rape jokes" are funny and that it's okay to joke around about sexual assault, and it's important to let them know that this is not the case. Men can also be raped, but society has taken into itself that men "can't possibly be raped", and so most men are ashamed and afraid if they speak out.
Many people feel that giving women guidelines about things that can be done to stay safe actually shames them and makes them feel like avoiding rape is all about having women act "the right way," and that if they make a misstep, it is basically their fault that they got raped. This is the intention of this article. This article intends to empower women by giving them some sensible advice on how to avoid danger. However, women are not the only sex to be raped. Men can be raped, but it just isn't as prevalent. Society doesn't believe "petite little women" can rape "big strong men", and yet it still happens.

3) Don't ever stop living your life. It can be overwhelming to read the advice about preventing rape. You'll start to feel like there's no place you're safe -- not your grocery store parking lot, not a restroom at a bar, not your car, and not even your own home. You might start to wonder where one can go to be completely safe from rapists. But you can't think like this. Though you should take some precautions, you can't be afraid to leave home by yourself, to be outside late at night, or to go to some of your favorite places. You can still enjoy your life and feel secure without the constant paranoia that you may feel after reading about how to prevent rape.[1]

4) 
Know that the majority of rapes are committed by a person the victim knows. The statistics vary, but it is said that only 9%-33% of rapists were complete strangers to the victim.[2] This means that the vast majority of women are raped by men that they know, whether they are friends, people they are dating, co-workers, acquaintances, or even family members. This means that it's far more likely for a person to get raped by someone he/she knows instead of a stranger in a dark alley. Therefore, while it's important to take precautions when you're alone, you shouldn't completely let your guard down when you're with people you know.
When you're in a social situation with someone you know, be extra careful and don't fully let your guard down unless you feel truly safe with the person. Even then, rape can occur. Know that if your gut tells you the situation is not okay, you should leave as soon and as safely as you can.
Date rape is also extremely common -- according to one study, nearly 1/3 of rapes are committed by a date.[3] When you're dating someone new, understand that no absolutely means no, and don't ever let anyone make you feel guilty about knowing what you do and don't want. Don't be afraid to communicate your needs clearly and loudly, if necessary.

Just go to wikiHow to get the rest of the parts, but until then avoid rapists at all costs!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Electricity is really just organized lightning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 08:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 08:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/showerthoughts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 08:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fuck you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 08:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> than* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 07:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my inner 8 year old has resurrected  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 08:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Nicely done* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My manikin doll for drawing has a pole up its butt. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 05:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interviewer: So what's your high school gpa? We're looking for the best students applicable for this job. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 04:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Student: Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A farmer walks into a pet shop... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 04:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He walks over to the clerk and says, "I'm looking into buying a sheep dog, I need help herding my 196 sheep."

Well, the clerk responds, "We've got just the dog you need!"

"Really?!?" the farmer replies with amazement.

"Absolutely fucking not, all we sell here is goldfish and snakes. Read the sign next time dumbass!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 02:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh if only the world wasn't so confusing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chuck Norris has more will power than Jesus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 02:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both went into the Judaean Desert and both encountered Satan there.

 Jesus lasted forty days and nights never taking any of Satan's temptations. 

While Chuck Norris left after only forty one days because Satan gave into Chuck Norris' temptations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A farmer had 196 cows in the field </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 02:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then he rounded them up, and even though it took four hours of rounding cows, he eventually rounded all of cows into their enclosed fencing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They say the Titanic was a tragedy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 17:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure it's a boat though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 21:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All MLKS matter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
