<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1497</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, yes - I remember that bit. He was asking WTF he should do because he was scared to open it. How much did he have? Was it something like 0.025 g or 0.0025 g? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I'm getting out of my depth here but no, I don't think that is correct. A normal individual will produce the required amount of acid and enzymes at the right time, but no more. Perhaps very fatty food disrupts this process - it's possible but I cannot say because I don't know for sure.

When you are getting acid reflux, that indicates a problem with the valve/shincter that lets food into the stomach but not back out. When it is not functioning correctly, the stomach contents can be forced back out, the wrong way.

Again, I'm certainly no medical expert so you may want to do your own research.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I was told, most people start on 40 mg and then go back to 20. I did this. I find that only about one day a month I get serious breakthrough. So I don't worry and just keep taking 20 mg. 

I have also found that if I take too much, my food doesn't digest properly and I throw up pretty much what looks like the food I ate, with the consistency of peanut butter. Last time it happened I gorged myself on cashews and I reckon I could have put them back together after they came up. 

I have GORD, you might too. I would go back to the doctor. You may need more. But I'm not a doctor, so you should really speak to an expert. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 14:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 14:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HCl is a strong acid - it completely separates into H+ and Cl- ions in water - that is the definition of strong with regard to acids. But you must remember that the concentration of the acid in any situation is just as important. Yes we have 'strong' acid in our stomach but it it isn't that concentrated - hence the enzymes that help out.

If you made a solution of HCl at the same concentration as is in our stomach, you would find that you could stick your hand in it for quite a while before it really hurt. You notice it burns and stings a bit when you vomit - it's coming into contact with some pretty sensitive mucous membranes but it isn't that bad, just unpleasant. 

I can personally say I know, because I have done it many times, with both hydrochloric and sulfuric acids. It gets on your skin and after a while it starts to itch and burn so you just wash it off. You will know when it's really concentrated, trust me. 

I used to work with it all the time and was never very careful with safety. It's your eyes you must worry about. Wear those fucking goggles if you value your eyesight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 14:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. I'll keep that in mind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 14:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks mate. Yes, I do have the DLCs but I'm only at level 18 right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 12:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is the turboshaft to the fan decoupled? Is it just a big fuck-off clutch like on a car or something more exotic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 11:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's it. The H+ is what makes a solution acidic. I'm no medical expert but yeah, special cells pump out those protons. And fuck it is painful when you get too many. Nexium FTW! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Witcher 3][PC] Is it possible to get enough points to max out all the skills? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 11:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm having trouble deciding what to choose. In addition to that, I have lots of differnt mutagens from different enemies just sitting there. Are they useful after you make the decoctions or should I just sell them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 11:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Islam has no place in Western society. At all. Ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 11:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 10:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heroin is not particularly injurious in its pure form. Neither is fentanyl. But both drugs are almost always cut with shit that is. You can't really say one is worse than the other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Insulting that AFIC exists. There's nothing Australian about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your stomach acid isn't very strong (or more properly, concentrated), in the scheme of things. Much of the work is done by enzymes, in conjunction with the acid. Furthermore, the acid is produced as needed. You don't walk around with half a litre of concentrated acid sloshing around.

The acid is produced by special cells. Some people, like me, have over active ones. We take drugs known as proton pump inhibitors, so we don't make too much acid (protons). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough - looking at you made me laugh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm down to 2 or 3 litres of beer (5% volume) a night. It used to be two bottles of rum a day and as much beer and port as I could scoff before passing out. I would skoll middie glasses (285 mL) of port if I felt I was not drunk enough. Just drank the rum straight from the bottle, all day. Then go to the pub and sink piss with me mates until it closed.

Then I got caught drink driving. I'd been to the pub that morning. Probly had 10 or 11 schooners (425 mL) of beer. But not before I'd had half a bottle of rum before I got there. Then I went home and drank a bottle of port and went to sleep. Went to buy some drugs and got nabbed because I forgot to put my headlights on.

After that, I decided that perhaps this wasn't the life for me. Drinking less is hard but I'm no fan of this idea that because you had a problem you can never drink at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep goin' man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A good mate of mine died recently from exactly the same thing. He just couldn't stop drinking. We tried to get him to eat food - we would cook up real nice stuff and literally beg him to eat even one bite. But he couldn't. He'd just politely decline.

By the end, he was skeletal, suffering from severe pancreatitis and in agonising pain. Drinking made the pancreatitis worse but not drinking was impossible. All he would do was shuffle around wherever he was (him and his best mate, Warbs would cruise around in a van, from house to house selling drugs - Paedo and Warbs went everywhere together) and continue to drink cheap apple cider. 

The last time I ever saw him, he was carrying a 2 litre bottle of cider which he could barely lift and making jokes about his health. He left behind a missus and four kids.

We miss ya, Paedo. But you did this to yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 08:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It can be inhaled or absorbed through the skin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 08:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Respiratory depression/failure. You stop breathing. Many of the opioids do this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 08:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would you rather smuggle across state or international borders? 1 kilo of heroin or one poofteenth of fentanyl? Makes perfect sense from trafficking/dealing perspective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 08:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He inhaled some of the dust as he added it to water, if I remember correctly. And he was being cautious not to do just that. Had a makeshift mask but it wasn't enough. He bought a tiny amount and added that to water. Can't remember how much but it was four fifths of fuck all.

I read that post and just thought what the fuck happens when customs carelessly tear open a package with a large amount of it. You could kill many people at once, just by accident. Or on purpose... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 08:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, that would be it. Cheers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you starting with? You could recrystallise it:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N_ZWx2mWvRM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 06:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No longer. Got stung the first three times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 06:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good. Not because I think they're morally wrong, I just personally don't like them. Tom Waterhouse Can Get Fucked:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l0XalOuQPeg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 05:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. Disable that crap, compress the links, disable thumbnails, disable spotlight, trending, additional details, adblock ON. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 05:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get the program called Ownership:

http://www.softpedia.com/get/System/OS-Enhancements/Rizone-Take-Ownership-Shell-Extension.shtml

http://www.afterdawn.com/software/system_tools/misc_system_tools/take_ownership_shell_extension.cfm

Once you install it, you just right click on the folder you want and let it do all the work. I have it but I can't remember where I got it. So you may find a better source than the ones I just gave.

It works extremely well. Fuck Microsoft and their never ending bullshit. Now you can cut and paste wherever you want. No more being denied access on your own machine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 05:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, you don't take faulty goods back to the shop? You mustn't be entitled enough. What's wrong with expecting something to work when you pay for it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the games. I hate the company. How many times do I have to say it? I don't pay for games unless they are near perfect. And Bethesda have a long way to go in that regard. Yes, I put up with the bugs. No, I am not paying for the privilege, anymore.

Take, for instance, Witcher 3 - absolute ball-tearer of a game. Bigger and better than any Bethesda game and almost completely devoid of bugs. NO game breaking ones and only the most minor of other ones. Will I pay for that? Fucken oath I will. I'm playing it for the second time at the moment. Those guys have their shit together from the outset. They did everything right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Having some trouble with some equilibrium questions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first one is very simple but I got it wrong. It simply states a reaction has Kc = 1.5 where A(g) = 2B(g)

What happens when 3 moles of each are put into the flask?

I said A decreases and B increases, as the ratio is 1:2. But the answer is the opposite of what I thought. Why?

The other question says Kc = 1.6 x 10-10 for the reaction:

2SO3(g) = 2SO2(g) + O2(g)

Then it asks what Kc is for:

SO2(g) + 1/2O2(g) = SO3(g)

It's the same reaction, just backwards. I thought the rate would be the same but opposite. Apparently, that is not the case. The answer is 7.9 x 104. Can someone tell me why?

Also - how do you do subscripts here?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't sell faulty products. I refuse to pay for shit that's broken. Every single Bethesda game I have ever played has horrendous bugs. They need to stop it with this pre-order crap and release games when the fucking things are actually ready. 

Would you expect your money back if you bought a shirt and it fell apart after wearing it a few times? I would. Steam can take your money for a game and refuse to give it back after only two hours of play - if the bugs manifest themselves after that, you're fucked. And that has happened to me once too often. Fuck Bethesda and fuck Steam.

I mean look at the giant day one bug for Fallout 4, just for a quick example. Go near certain areas and the game crashes to desktop. Happened across multiple platforms. They simply MUST have known about it, yet they release the game, anyway. Suckers like me pay for it and get stung on day one. Sorry, but I do not pay for that, anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you figure that? I like playing them but the bugs are bad enough for me to refuse to pay. Pretty simple.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope she does win. And subsequent actions "force" these fucktards to act. Stir them up enough so that when they really start their shit up, they can be met with an iron fist. No more lenience. No more tolerance. Just do what needs to be done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because you are muslim. Simple.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries mate. Just don't fall for those snake-oil engine oil/fuel treatments. 99% of the time, you do not need fuel additives and do not use oil additives. Change the oil as per the manufacturer's directive. Put the right fuel in your car, in terms of octane rating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're completely 'moderate'. Nothing to worry about... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tiny minority. Nothing to worry about. We need to import more of these people to the West... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hideous. I must have one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever I try and log in. The same bullshit about whether I am who I say I am. Every time. No exceptions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does it make me get a confirmation code EVERY time I try and log on? Even on the same day. Fuck Steam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I refuse to pay for any Bethesda game, anymore. Overpriced and full of fucking bugs. Every single one of them. Pirating until Bethsoft and Steam change their tune. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest, toluene probably won't help you in a naturally aspirated road car. Modern fuels have enough knock resistance to drive any average car pretty hard. Toluene would let you advance timing significantly but it's still probably a waste of time.

High performance turbocharged engines would be a different story - but you aren't going for economy there - you are going for performance and reliability. That's where you you would use toluene - so you can wind up the boost pressure to stupid levels without the thing shitting itself in an instant.

The fuel blend you buy at the pump is pretty damn good. If it weren't, some company would capitalise on that real quick. And if you use fuel that is significantly different, your car's management system would not be able to cope and something might be damaged. Most engine management systems are designed to advance the timing until the onset of knock, retard it and repeat that process. Using some exotic fuel would be outside the window of their capabilities.

You could approach the various oil companies if you wanted to try it out but I doubt it would be worth it. At high levels of toluene, the fuel doesn't vaporise properly and you need to heat it - I'm not sure at what point that would be - you'd have to consult the tables to see what vaporises at what temperature and compare it.

Sorry to disappoint but basically fuel companies have this sewn up. No one is going to sell or use TEL, which would in theory be the answer to your question.

Feel free to ask any other questions you have. I'll do my best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that a bad thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EVERY time I want to do anything with fucking Steam, I have to get a code from my email to verify it's me, on the same computer, on the same fucking day. Every time, without fail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buzzfeed? Are you for real? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 09:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. Cumulative revs. That's it. Make a mistake and your done for the day. I saw Gerhard Berger saying you had to get on the throttle up to two seconds early and try and anticipate when the power would come on - power could literally double in the space of 1000 revs on the tacho. One mistake and you just slide off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 09:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rest was n-heptane to meet the FIA requirements. Toluene isn't really any better or worse than the blends of petrol we use anywhere else (it is also a component in most blends of petrol) in terms of safety. It's just super effective at preventing detonations. 

Try not to get it on yourself and don't wash your hands in it, etc. The usual safety precautions. Many octane boosting products contain large amounts of it. Yes, it is carcinogenic like a vast array of hydrocarbons but it's not a huge problem if you handle it safely. It's very similar to benzene - it's just a benzene ring with a methyl group attached. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two questions I am having trouble with (equilibrium reactions) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 09:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first one is very simple but I got it wrong. It simply states a reaction has Kc = 1.5 where A(g) = 2B(g)

What happens when 3 mol of each are put into the flask?

I said A decreases and B increases, as the ratio is 1:2. But the answer is the opposite of what I thought. Why?

The other question says Kc = 1.6 x 10^-10 for the reaction:

    2SO3(g) = 2SO2(g) + O2(g)

Then it asks what Kc is for:

    SO2(g) + 1/2O2(g) = SO3(g)

It's the same reaction, just backwards. I thought the rate would be the same but opposite. Apparently, that is not the case. The answer is 7.9 x 10^4. Can someone tell me why?

Also - how do you do subscripts here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 06:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish people would learn the difference between turbo lag and boost threshold. 

That thing never had 1500 hp, either. None of them did. No one had a dyno that went that high. They just estimated it - and it was closer to 1300 hp in qualifying guise.

They were running up to 5.5 bar (80 psi) boost, so they had to use fuel that was ~84% toluene (methylbenzene) to combat knock. From what I had read, the engine life at that much boost was ~25,000 *cumulative* revs. That's it - two to three minutes for qualifying runs and then it died. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 06:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An RUF. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 06:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, doing that will not leave any useful amount of N2 in the petrol - and I don't see how somehow dissolving nitrogen into petrol would do anything, anyway. All you will do is speed up the evaporation rate. 

Ethanol does not contain nitrogen. I'm not sure how that idea is supposed to work in therms of 'nitrogen enrichment' - whatever that is. Ethanol is an oxygenate - a fuel that already contains oxygen. You need to use more of it to get the same power. It also has lower energy density. It is a poor choice for a normal road going car. But it has excellent knock characteristics for racing.

What would really help would be TEL - tetraethyl lead. A fantastic knock combating compound. But obviously you can't use it anymore. It is an excellent anti-knock compound. One of the best.

The chemical I would use is toluene (methylbenzene). Toluene is possibly the best hydrocarbon fuel you could get for a petrol engine. In the 80s the Formula 1 cars used to it to allow them to run stupendous boost levels in the turbocharged cars. Some cars could run up to 5.5 bar (80 psi) of boost for short periods. 

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Toluene </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did you delete your other comments? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no! What will happen to everyone if she is elected?! She's practically the next Hitler. Concentrations camps for all, huh? What exactly do you think will 'happen to other people'? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck instagram. No volume control on PC.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, a complete waste of time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nigger, you just went full blown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why couldn't you put US in the title? The World doesn't revolve around America. It's a lot different, everywhere else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Says the person that diagnoses the problem I have with 'not running Windows 10'. If you read the fucking question, you would understand that it was after a change of settings. But no, it's simply because I run an OS you consider inferior, LMFAO!!! Fuck off and wake up to yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All-jizz. LOL fuck off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck Windows 10. I will never use it, given any other choice. Fucking spyware, bloatware garbage. I only use Windows for games. And 8.1 is perfectly adequate for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 11:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 11:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 8.1.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 11:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, what's your solution to it, genius?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 10:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, we ban it for everyone because of the few that are unable to use things in moderation. Where have I heard that before...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 09:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What part of I don't care do you not get? I care about pokie addicts about as much as I do heroin addicts. Not my fucking problem and they are free to seek help. I don't remember anyone banning alcohol when I was a slave to it. No, I picked myself out of the gutter. And I'm happy for alcohol to be just as accepted as pokies are. Why should my inability to manage my consumption infringe on anyone else's right to enjoy it? Thanks for your worldly input, le smartarse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 09:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 15 minutes and mash that cunt up with curry and mayo, please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 09:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I already said task manager won't work when this happens. Are you saying kill the program with task manager instead of the normal way? Might be worth a try, I suppose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 09:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed. I do not watch TV. I really don't need reality shows peppered with more ads than actual show time. Advertisers had their chance to be reasonable. But they just couldn't help themselves but try and take advantage of people. They shall get nothing from me, if I can help it, forever more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 09:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't even go on most major news sites now, without intrusive ads and autoplay videos. No, I don't go to shitholes like Buzzfeed very often. But if I do, the adblocking software is worth its weight in gold. 

How would you know what my browsing habits are, based off one sentence, anyway? Intrusive ads are fucking everywhere. So now I block ALL ads (if I can). Advertisers had their chance to play nice. They blew it. They can all fuck off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 09:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's supr? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 09:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only 'victims' of pokies I feel sorry for are kids whose parents gamble all their money away and the kids don't get food and clothes, etc. Everyone else, I couldn't really give a fuck about. We derive vast sums of money from these people. I'd rather it come from them than me. There are help programs in place. They know the odds. If they are too stupid to help themselves, I don't see why anyone else should step in. I like the revenue, personally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Witcher 3][PC] Since I changed to full screen mode (so I can adjust gamma) the game will not shut down properly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 08:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It disappears and the desktop shows but I can't do anything. Can't even get to task manager. Have to hold down the power button and restart the PC. Anybody else had this shit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 08:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If your server is serving up intrusive ads, that tab most certainly will stay closed. Nothing of value lost. Joke's on you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 07:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I know. Red light cameras stop them doing just that - so why are they whining about them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 07:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 07:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm perfectly happy with separating fools from their money. How is drinking any different to gambling? Some people will be addicted. Most won't. That's life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do people post comments with nothing at all in them? No characters whatsoever. Just blank. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can hold on for the first hundred yards... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So long as you keep citing one place at one time, yes. Maybe we should get rid of police because they can be corrupt. Lots of things can be corrupt(ed). How the fuck are red light cameras causing a bribery scheme? They aren't. Your law enforcement in one little place is doing that.

The red light cameras where I live are just fine. No corruption is involved and if a fault is found, it will be immediately fixed and the relevant fines dismissed - as has occurred on some very odd occasions. 

Don't run a red light like a fucking moron and you won't be fined for putting others in grave danger. You seem to have a problem with that - why?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Johnny Dumfries is a British peer and actually named John Colum Crichton-Stuart, 7th Marquess of Bute and is ranked 26th richest in Scotland (2006) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, you have a problem with law enforcement in one place on the planet. What is your argument? Red light cameras cause corruption or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'SO' is worse. Husband/wife gf/bf. Is that hard? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Effeminate men. I fucking cannot stand limp wristed weirdos. Either talk and act like a man or fuck off away from me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good. It's his car. No matter what he does to it, it can be rebuilt. Just like any other car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So a fraction of these things had a fault. And that fault is likely to be rectified. Is that your argument against them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope she wins - just to watch the tantrums and shitsorm it will produce. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure it's required in Australia. I used to drink at a certain place and one day the licensing police came in and demanded cameras be installed. So the publican put fake ones in. They came back and busted him for it. Also fined him something like $12,000 for having the poker machines visible from outside the establishment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? If you run a red light, fuck you. You absolutely deserve to be punished. I see zero problem with red light cameras, so long as they are ONLY used for that purpose - no logging plates or shit like that. Fuck people who run red lights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, people should pre-buy a few 2 dollar SIM cards and have them ready to go? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Instantly closes tab.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A victory at massive cost to the Russians. You think they're going to go back for some LGBTIXYZ cause that has no benefit to them? Personally, I think they should level Grozny for a third time - just to teach them not to be separatists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who's 'we'? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With an islamic enclave that does shit like this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *islamic arseholes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Islam in action. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good. Please stay on strike forever. Take your autoplay videos and shove them and your lame content up your collective arse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The original attention seeker.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is this tagged as NSFW? Fuck's sake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They need to prove the allegations and then get cooperation, if the other country you reside in has an extradition treaty. 

Take, for instance, piracy of software/copyright - there is no fucking way in hell an Australian agency is going to cooperate with the US.

There was a famous case called the Dallas Buyer's Club (some lame US movie) - DBC marched into the Australian court system and demanded they be able to sue people under US style law. They were literally laughed out of court. The US plaintiffs thought they could sue people in Australia, just like they do in America. 

But it doesn't work like that. In Australia, we don't have punitive damages - you can't say someone is liable for untold amounts of money because they shared the movie dozens of times. All you can do is sue them for one copy of the movie. So, the DBC lawyers quickly found out that they could only sue people for about 30 bucks each. And the presiding judge made them apply for each and every case through him. Needless to say, the DBC lawyers quickly found out that we don't dance to American tunes.

US law stops at US borders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. It's fucking funny when dickheads get caught. I used to take great delight in reporting them when I worked in retail. Be a pro or don't fucking bother, you useless cunt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about it? It has absolutely no jurisdiction with any country that isn't part of it. It's almost entirely (or possibly entirely, I couldn't be bothered reading more) contained to the US. You think the US have jurisdiction outside US borders? Think again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers, mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No face. Next... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No face. Next... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. Who gives a rat's arse about downvoters, anyway? Maybe they're the ones who are worried about 50 bucks a week because they over-borrowed. Joke's on them - bank's gonna take it, one way or another. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
