<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1369</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 05:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Injuries and bad roster moves made the team worse, not regression from healthy individual players. 

Edit: also the coach was trash </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 04:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I distinctly remember reddit making fun of Thibs for playing Butler so many minutes.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 04:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> John is my best friend. Just wish he'd text me back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 04:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do people think the Wizards are perennial losers? They were a John Wall broken hand from reaching the eastern conference finals 2 years ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/RjZaUIS.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I doubt he has any say in what direction the team takes.

Do you actually believe this? That is a pretty extreme statement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/RjZaUIS.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its called the Delmar**VA** Peninsula for a reason, map maker!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite part is Virginia having three teams and one of them is Virginia Tech :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I love Devin Booker.](https://www.reddit.com/r/nba/comments/3vhunf/post_game_thread_in_a_close_game_the_phoenix_suns/cxno8n4/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh, I want it so bad. Targaryen family is my fav.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't expect so much backlash to this question. I just wanted to know if Jazz fans thought the name was strange because of its origins. 

Obviously all the names are "strange" in one sense or another, but the only other team that was named after a local characteristic and then moved but kept the name is the Lakers. From my experience those fans don't consider it a weird situation and I was wondering how that compared to Jazz fans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone knows jazz is illegal in Utah.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 19:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only one who realizes these are two different situations? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 19:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the real tragedy. New Orleans deserves that name.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 19:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean Jazz was born in New Orleans. Honestly I think The Utah Jazz makes less sense than the Toronto Raptors because dinosaurs are a part of western pop culture, including Toronto. Jazz has no connection to Utah (obviously).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do Jazz fans recognize its a strange name right? Despite how catchy it is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really doubt this happens. A Dunk and Egg adaptation would inevitably be much different from Game of Thrones, it includes less action. Ultimately I think HBO execs would think an adaptation would alienate GoT viewers and not be nearly as popular as GoT. Though book readers would love it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wizards won't even make the playoffs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 05:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to Reddit I beat you to this comment by 4 seconds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 05:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No thank you, I'm full.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 04:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mostly in Chicago and New York.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 03:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I don't see HBO execs signing off on a show with Dunk and Egg as the main characters. No broad appeal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 03:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was reporting that it was possible. HBO refused to confirm it with the hope of convincing D D to make more than 13. This is the first time it has been confirmed by the executive producers.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 03:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd prefer the Dance of Dragons to Robert's Rebellion, though I think the rebellion is more likely. (They already have a young Ned). 

It would be cool if they did an anthology series with a new story each season. Though I doubt that would ever happen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 03:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a huge gap between the rebellion and the start of the series. The gap is even larger in the show than in the books. 

I don't see why they couldn't expand upon the existing show cannon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 03:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tony Danza </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 02:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> \#NeverRemember </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 02:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How often do you clip your eyes?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 02:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol I considered it and decided it was not worth it. Graphic just came back btw.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 02:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like I'm watching a game in the 80s.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 02:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> League Pass is being weird right now. There is no score graphic on the Rockets broadcast.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 02:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the score graphic on the Rockets broadcast missing for anyone else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 00:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is this written in verse?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a third of a year ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Garden State is 13 years old.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mad Men is written by Matthew Weiner one of the writers and producers of The Sopranos. They share similar themes and storylines. Mad Men is very much the spiritual successor to The Sopranos and is indeed one of the greatest shows ever. 

I think it isn't as popular on Reddit as The Wire, The Sopranos and Breaking Bad simply because it does not involve guns.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 09:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 09:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 09:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> aww bud, sorry to be the one to tell you this but no, it does not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 09:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ancient Egypt is like the OG Mediterranean ancient powerhouse civilization they go back like 5000 years.  

King Tut was only like 3500 years ago. 

Cleopatra was a vassal to the Roman Empire and fucked Caesar and Mark Antony, even though she was probably really ugly. That was only like 2000 years ago.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 09:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://twitter.com/dankmtl/status/221978990720724992?lang=en </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 08:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol are you knew here?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 07:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ummmmm... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 07:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  fake win

FAKE NEWS. SAD! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 07:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Black Mirror is an anthology show. Every episode is very different from one another. Almost every episode is directed by a different person and is working on different themes. 

It should not be a surprise that the reaction to episodes are so polarizing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 07:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All three wrestle with the American dream and the human condition in profound ways. The Great American novel on the small screen. 

When I think of A+ television I only think of these three. There is a lot of A, A-, B+ TV out there but in my mind these are the only three that deserve a perfect grade.  

Mad Men went off the air almost two years ago. It has been two years since A+ TV. I miss it. But I am confident we will get a successor.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 04:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Twilight Zone is my favorite short story.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 02:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright /r/nba place your bets.

Who will lead each team in scoring?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 21:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As soon as I get an answer I will happily answer your question. Tick tock.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 21:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are you afraid to answer the question?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 21:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When do you think the abolitionism movement began?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 20:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weird that you're on reddit when slavery still exists, huh?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 08:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok first off, FX is owned by 21st Century Fox. Fox is also owned by 21st Century Fox. The have the same parent company. 

But both networks are run by different executives.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 07:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> uh, duh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please explain to me what you think Watergate is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol sure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Need a safe space?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 06:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why can no one spell definitely?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm sure they remember what happened without the need for dramatic recounts.

Can I introduce you to [HBO's drama *Recount*?](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Recount_\(film\))  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you read the article? This will not premiere for years. 

The book the miniseries is based on is still being researched and written. Only after it is published will they be on their way to completing a script. The book probably is still about a year away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They live there. I have a picture with them both.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She said "you're impossible." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean it as the name for the concept, but I think you know that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 05:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What makes you think that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 05:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seem to agree with the concept but disagree with the label. What does that tell us?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 05:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're ignorant because you've created your own reality. A reality where you are never wrong and are justified in your own hate. Arguing with you is like dealing with a moody four-year-old. Read a book. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 05:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 05:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It must take a good deal of work to be this ignorant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 05:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course I have seen the video. It is telling that you keep dodging the question. It is a simple yes or no. Answer it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 05:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please just answer this question. Yes or no. 

If Abraham Lincoln, a northern liberal, magically showed up in 2016 do you think he would support Trump and the modern GOP?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 05:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you know who Strom Thurmond is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 02:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure you probably find it hard, but please educate yourself. 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s8VOM8ET1WU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 02:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm, that is a little difficult to say. 

There are numerous images of dead soldiers and occasionally images of severed limbs. 

There is also a great deal of racism (in the form of confederate writing being read).

I'd say probably 9/10 and up, though it may help to watch the first 45 minutes alone to see if you're comfortable with it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 01:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just go to voat the_donald fan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 00:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> delete this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 00:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coates is infinitely more intelligent than I am so I cannot speak for him. 

Foote was a product of the early 20th century American South - a place where the government had been defined by white supremacy for decades. To deny that is to deny history. 

Frankly, if you're not operating in bad faith this stuff really isn't that difficult to grasp.

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 00:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you may have gotten to the core of the negative reaction to Coates' argument.  

You write that Coates is attacking whiteness, when in fact he is simply presenting a historical analysis. I assume you are white and see that as an attack on yourself, which in turn evokes an emotional reaction. 

Dr. Robin DiAngelo would [define this as white fragility.](http://libjournal.uncg.edu/ijcp/article/viewFile/249/116) 

White Fragility is a state in which even a minimum amount of racial stress becomes
intolerable, triggering a range of defensive moves. These moves include
the outward display of emotions such as anger, fear, and guilt, and behaviors such
as argumentation, silence, and leaving the stress-inducing situation. 

I encourage you to read her paper.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 00:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you elaborate? It is impossible to find literary criticism from an author who has no particular viewpoint.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 23:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If someone wants to argue that Foote is overly sympathetic to the Confederate cause they should critique Footes actual words, like you did by posting that paragraph from him, not by claiming that his "whiteness" prevented him from reaching the right conclusions.

I pulled the Foote quote directly from Coates' article. If you followed the link you could clearly see Coates addresses Foote's actual words. I really didn't add much to the argument, it all comes from Coates. I explicitly wrote that you need to read the entire thing to get context.

Ta-Nehisi Coates article is racist, plain and simple. I happen to agree that Foote was a bit to sympathatic to the "Cause," but that is due to my analysis of his arguments, which I can attribute to his attitudes, upbringing, and values, not the color of his skin.

To declare Coates' analysis of Foote as racist is baffling, again please read the entire article. In analyzing Foote's view of the Civil War you can not separate his upbringing and values with his race - they are, in essence, one and the same.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ta-Nehisi Coates' Atlantic piece [The Convenient Suspension of Disbelief](https://www.theatlantic.com/national/archive/2011/06/the-convenient-suspension-of-disbelief/240318/) argues that ultimately Foote was sympathetic to confederate figures and not to slaves, simply because he could see himself as a confederate and not as a slave. 

He gave twenty years of his life, and three volumes of important and significant words to the Civil War, but he he could never see himself in the slave. He could not get that the promise of free bread can not cope with the promise of free hands. Shelby Foote wrote The Civil War, but he never understood it. Understanding the Civil War was a luxury his whiteness could ill-afford.

I pulled this passage from an interview that accompanies the story, it is important to read the entire thing to get context.   

INTERVIEWER:
 
Had you been alive during the Civil War, would you have fought for the Confederates? 

FOOTE: 

No doubt about it. What's more, I would fight for the Confederacy today if the circumstances were similar. There's a great deal of misunderstanding about the Confederacy, the Confederate flag, slavery, the whole thing. The political correctness of today is no way to look at the middle of the nineteenth century. The Confederates fought for some substantially good things. States rights is not just a theoretical excuse for oppressing people. You have to understand that the raggedy Confederate soldier who owned no slaves and probably couldn't even read the Constitution, let alone understand it, when he was captured by Union soldiers and asked, What are you fighting for? replied, I'm fighting because you're down here. So I certainly would have fought to keep people from invading my native state. There's another good reason for fighting for the Confederacy. Life would have been intolerable if you hadn't. The women of the South just would not allow somebody to stay home and sulk while the war was going on. It didn't take conscription to grab him. The women made him go. 

Foote is an excellent story teller but it is difficult to agree that he did not contribute to a body of text from which, in part, white nationalism claims. 

P.S.: If this discussion interests you check out [Vox's piece of the famous Ballou letter.](http://www.vox.com/culture/2017/1/21/14338656/chuck-schumer-inauguration-speech-sullivan-ballou)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol did you just unironically link to Zero Hedge?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ken Burns' epic nine part masterpiece "The Civil War" has returned to Netflix </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the greatest documentaries ever made is once again available to stream. 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FN2huQB-DmE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 06:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to be a special kind of stupid to believe this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 06:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weird how its always conservatives who complain about people calling Russia evil.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 21:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [You're a bad troll.](https://www.reddit.com/r/RightwingLGBT/comments/5vq6es/how_do_liberals_harm_lgbt_people_and_how_do/de7jzlj/?utm_content=permalink utm_medium=user utm_source=reddit utm_name=frontpage)

The main problem the LGBT community faces from the the progressive left is the victim mentality it creates. You are starting to see the gay community start to suffer from being one of the token demographics that the left uses to make a grab for power. If you look from the point where the left started to use blacks(1930's) and women(1960's) you start to see a deteriation of that sections of the US. You see the left pushing these groups into their corner using benefits and empty promises of equality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 21:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tribe mentality can be a destructive thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 21:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ellison and Perez ran on essentially the same platform. But judging by your post history it seems you're just a conservative trying to divide liberals.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 21:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The break-in happened about 5 months after this cartoon was published. So, no.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 19:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Larry Sanders Show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 04:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Horizontal integration yo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 04:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This comment made me so mad I almost downvoted it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 00:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, not a surprise. They'd love Stalin if he came out against "the media."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 04:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, I just need to know. 

Did you think Ben Franklin was a president?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 03:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I just think words have meanings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 03:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Championship runs aren't possible until the playoffs. The all-star break just ended. 

And to say they have a "clear path" to the EC finals is insane.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 02:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No the Wiz is not making a championship run.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 02:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Washington Post is literally the best daily paper in the nation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 02:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DC is the capital on cynical journalism. And I love it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another Celtic funeral?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell yes! Fuck the Celtics! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who are saying Denver are crazy. LA all day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> delete this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 14:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As soon as the Magic announcement came Twitter lit up with his old retweets. Dozens of people came to similar conclusions. You'd have to be deluded to think WaPo used OP's content (literally just links to 6 tweets) without credit.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sad! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you guys have Krispy Kreme? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol he's not even the most powerful man in the White House </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of shit comment is this? Downvoted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paul ^G^^eo^^^rge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats a really cool story. Do you have any more?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So is the president.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Butthungry for Buddy. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What universe are you living in?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Reddit post is literally just links to 6 tweets. 

The article has 15 tweets and over 500 words of analysis. 

So I'm going to say no. Not every news article is plagiarism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 02:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this sub has gone insane  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Over/Under: Three trades before midnight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 00:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 05:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was created for NBC. Eventually the network reworked their comedy block and decided Kimmy Schmidt didn't fit. Netflix lucked into it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 04:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hes barely an ok Paul George.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 02:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well duh he tore his ACL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 02:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fey is attached at the hip to NBC. I don't see this ever happening. Though if she did I would never miss an episode.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What have been the best games this season? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 00:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has only been a few days but I miss NBA games. I want to go back and watch old games on league pass. Could you recommend your favorite games of the year? Best individual performances? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol this reads like an ad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 04:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I could say I understand where you're coming from, but I don't and I never will.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 04:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> rude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 01:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You were convinced without evidence? 

Are you our president?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 22:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but the best point guard in the east is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 18:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> JFK's decision not to often wear hats is one reason everybody stopped wearing hats all the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 06:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its FAKE SCIENCE! Stop telling us dinos have feathers. They aren't birds. Science is the enemy of the people. SICK! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 06:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Victim blaming on Reddit? What a surprise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 03:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> k </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 03:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Standing is hard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
