<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2257</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Solely to reinforce the dark double entendre of 'getting to the other side,' as once the chicken is struck by a motor vehicle, he will be on 'the other side." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the bright side, there was probably worse stuff in your food regardless </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Somewhat wholesome memes begin to invade twitter. At this rate, they may be fully wholesome by the end of the month! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 03:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frankly, the best part of that fight was when they zoomed in on the frozen pile of blood at the end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably a cough. I get a cough every time I get a cold or I have allergies, so I can already see myself coughing up blood at the ripe age of 80, rolling over, and fading off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was five, and I was too lazy to take off my shoes and place them next to the door. Instead, I slid them off, and from about 7 feet away, flip both shoes, from my feet, perfectly next to each other in the perfect spot next to the door. It was such a minor thing, but 13 years later, I still haven't forgotten my amazement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was already fairly drunk, and I was trying to get into a bar, and instead of pulling out my drivers license, I pulled out my high school student ID that I had never taken out of my wallet. 

They let me in anyway without saying a word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The real question is whether or not Jerry Dipoto stayed the entire came of not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *The year is 2217. The Catholics, after a long and bloody war with Muslims, have won due to their sheer numbers. The pope reigns supreme, and the inevitable end of secularism is here.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 06:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about your mom? Is that still fair game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 06:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  OP's mom

FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 05:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> STEP 1: COPY KEY
STEP 2: STEAL BOOZE
STEP 3: ????
STEP 4: PROFIT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With the caption "My mind just exploded." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP's mom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP's mom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Insert poisoned needles here* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, are we just picking random words out of a hat to put in a headline at this point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do the same concept while driving. While I don't just carry around hot sauce with me everywhere, if I'm starting to fall asleep at the wheel I'll start biting my finger so that the pain keeps me awake. Works surprisingly well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP's penis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, isn't that why we're all on this thread </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With Boaty McBoatface set to sail today, what are some other memorable Internet troll incidents that have had an impact on the real world? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 13:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *wakes up*

*sees 'Boaty McBoatface'*

*goes back to sleep with newfound attitude about enacting change in the world* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 04:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> especially when you've got a very apparent smegma problem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 04:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just hopefully they don't have a pea-cock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 20:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like "How big are your real boobs?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 20:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aviator glasses. While they do make women look cuter for the time being, they drop my expectations because  after being bamboozled by the glasses on multiple occasions, I automatically assume the worst for when the glasses come off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched the Attack of the Clones for the first time in a while the other day, and it genuinely pissed me off that they used CGI for the clones in the action scenes. Like really? How hard can it possibly be to make those costumes? You could even do that in the 1970's! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if I am already a multi-tool AKA a really douchey schizophrenic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is a post worthy of someone with the name 'beyonceisacowboy' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frankly, I'm just waiting for this to devolve into an r/The_Donald sponsored gun debate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least your pants are gonna be warm for a little. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 20:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This man got 13 years, AKA over $600 worth of Reddit gold from this one comment alone. And he deserves every penny of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You're the drug dealer: what are you going to name the next new hot party drug? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You're a drug dealer: what are you going to name the next hot new drug </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you are trapped on a deserted island for the rest of your life and you can only bring one person with you, who would you bring? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *your </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will Ferrell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Porque no los dos? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, it's really our fault for expecting a Raiders fan to have any amount of class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would need somewhere to store this money, because under the crazy scenario that I have a trillion dollars, I won't be able to store it in banks, as this sole despising would multiply any of their total cash flows. Further, if I have a trillion dollars, this most likely won't by the government, so it is largely unrecognized currency in circulation, so putting it in a bank could trigger an abrupt increase in money supply and potentially trigger accelerated inflation rates.

Instead of a bank, I would now need a physical structure to store this cash. Given that a 10,000 dollar stack is 6"x2.5"x.43", a cubic foot block of cash would be worth approximately 2.79 million. Given this, I will need approximately 358,400 cubic feet of space to be able to store the trillion dollars. Given that the average warehouse is 25 feet tall, I will be able to comfortably stack the cash 20 feet tall, this means I will need at least 18,000 sq feet of warehouse space, and that's not even accounting for the necessary pathways in the cash for forklifts to get through. 

However, having a warehouse full of cash simply isn't flaunting the fact that I have my miraculous wealth, so I will opt for a different option. Given that the average person is 6 cubic feet (~6'x8"x18"), and only half of a person sits in a stadium seat, I will buy Wembley stadium and put 3 cubic feet of cash in every seat in the stadium, and the pit the remaining 90,000 cubic of feet spread out throughout the pitch. Given that the pitch is 345x225 ft, this means I would spread a foot tall layer of cash  over the entire field. 

TL;DR: I don't trust banks with a million dollars, so I would buy Wembley Stadium just to store my cash in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Minnesota was a year and a half ago tho

EDIT: No hook was off After da boat, so the point still stands that it's been a while and it'd be nice to see them do something again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lil Yachty and Quavo seen hanging out on Yachty's snap story. Is there a chance we get a collab at some point? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 07:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THE PRINTING PRESS WAS A LIE PERPETUATED BY THE HOLY ROMAN EMPIRE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 07:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wait I'm not married </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 07:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go ask r/relationships. I'm sure they can explain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 06:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Daniel Kristiansen and his father, Klaus, 

are these not the most danish names ever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fourthed my grandma got stage 4 colon cancer and the only reason they caught it is because her doctor basically forced her to get one in order to sign her physical for her bus drivers contract </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, there isn't one, but the fact that there are 8 different conspiracy theories as to who killed JFK. Personally, even though this one isn't widely discussed, I think there's a chance the KKK did it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We filled a bunch of condoms with helium and let them go in our school during finals. What we didn't know was that there was a big fifth grade field trip to our school that day, so administration was especially unhappy. The only reason they didn't press charges for trespassing was because the SRO managed to calm down our principal and convince him not to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like this also spurs from the change in societal perceptions of college. In the past, everyone had a relatively predetermined path, most of which didn't involve going to college, because it was okay not to go to college. Now that everyone expects to go to college, institutions such as the ACT and GPA emphasize perfection and, at some levels, do not allow for even the tiniest failure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jazz Cartier hints at upcoming release of his newest project "Fleurever" over snapchat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dihydrogen Monoxide causes thousands of deaths each year due to suffocation and needs to be banned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People who have cheated on your spouse/fianc, why did you do it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 03:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> jeez are you trying to date rape me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 01:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus, that's not even a roast, that's just dark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My dorm floor nicknamed me Chad because my real name wasn't considered to be douchey enough. Roast me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 01:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's always fun when you understand Kansas City references </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 23:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was this perhaps in mission hills? Also, does your username mean Overland Park, Kansas City? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 02:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The tissue is behind his head! What a dumbass! Hah, I'm smarter than a baby! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 02:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really important question here, is that dog in your crotch? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 01:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do your homework out in the floor lobby, assuming you have one. You'll always see people getting off the elevators or walking to the stairs and you'll know almost all your floor by the end of the month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 23:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your last name is Surname? That's *so* cool and ironic! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 18:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the most incredible action series I've seen just because of its relative historical accuracy and it's complex storyline. Keeps you on the edge of your toes the entire show. Only show I would ever give a 10/10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 15:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Narcos. People started getting killed right off the bat, and I knew it was going to be intense. 

Spoiler: it was intense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jay Pharoah- Various Freestyles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 05:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jay Pharaoh goes hard in 15 minute freestyle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 05:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 00:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Properly scaled? There's no way that falcon is four times the size of that cheetah, duh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a guy that I was absolute enemies with in middle school, and it was almost a big dick contest. Everyone liked him, but I thought he was stuck up, and he knew that I thought he was stuck up, so needless to say we did not get along. We were both on the debate team freshman year, hated each other all through the year, and then our coach purposely paired us as partners for our sophomore year. Shockingly enough, we both realized that this situation wouldn't change, so we put our differences aside and started working together and we actually ended up becoming pretty good friends.

EDIT: realized this didn't really answer the prompt, but I still feel as if it is a wholesome story of two people overcoming their differences! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 13:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a real note, has Dwayne Johnson ever starred in an original movie (this excludes fast and furious 7/8) that didn't suck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 07:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the scope of kinetic energy, also consider curling. Even though it is traveling at just a few miles an hour, it weighs 44 pounds, so it's kinetic energy is likely very, very high. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 06:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ,Baseball isn't exactly correct. Because the chart title is "fastest moving balls in sports," the baseball chart should also include batted balls, not just the fastest pitch never thrown, which was indeed Aroldis Chapman. Instead, it should go to Giancarlo Stanton, who once hit a ball 123.9 MPH, which is the fastest batted ball ever recorded, and is a significant difference from Chapman's 106. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 23:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 18 and I shaved two weeks ago, and nothing has grown back. It's a tough life, but some of us have to live it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 23:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, way to take the good out of the bad. Absolutely incredible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Five bucks says he could spell immigrated right tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean that's why I asked this question, it was supposed to be uplifting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad you guys hit it off and now you've got a new best friend! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad you took the initiative! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I've also got his Amazon order too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I mean, same for me, because otherwise I wouldn't be here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im really glad it all worked out! It's funny how it seems like if you give it enough time, things will usually come around;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, this sounds absolutely incredible. You met your wife, your best friend, got a job, and served the community all at the same time. This one takes the cake so far, I'm really happy for you man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it might've been the FedEx guy, but I've still got a package for your mom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always been kind of afraid of weirding people out when doing this, so I'm especially happy that you worked up the courage to maintain the friendship you had just started and you broke out of your shell! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm at the door. Come let me in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad to hear you helped the people who cared about you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PICUMCHU! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds like you gave him a very good 19 years as well, I'm glad his time was well spent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP's bed, 20 minutes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see you, ave fun with your free time and live it up a little extra for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a college kid, this is the one thing I want in a relationship, just to have her be my best friend. I'm glad you found yours! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Orgy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's good to hear that you are a great parent! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad you find immense joy in parenting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope you feel better though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good to hear that your clean! I hope you are loving life now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trying not to sound pretentious. Whenever there's a test and everyone did like shit and one of the smart kids did well, you notice all the ones who aren't dickheads go like "I did okay," even though if you look at their score they most likely got a 95%. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP's mom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, you don't hear this very often, but I'm really happy that so much good came out of a normally bad situation! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP's mom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, this is so close to the ending scene of Superbad. Congratulations Michael Cera! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP's mom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's really good to hear, I was hoping there would be responses like this on here :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that took a sharp left turn:/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations, I'm happy for you man, it must have really been something if you remember it 21 years later </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP's mom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would you say is the best thing to have ever happened to you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HANNAH MONTANA HANNAH MONTANA HANNAH MONTANA HANNAH MONTANA HANNAH MONTANA HANNAH MONTANA HANNAH MONTANA HANNAH MONTANA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soon as I pull up and park the Benz, We get this bitch shaking like Parkinson's 

Kanye just has such a way with words, man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right next to OP's mom, because I was tired from fucking her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey that means they gave you a .5% performance raise too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well sounds like you're someone's mami now  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In honor of this sub hitting 16 million subscribers, what would be the worst thing to have 16 million of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 06:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 03:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone's pissed about the contents of emails, but why tf is the Vice President of the United States still on AOL? This isn't 1995! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Even a poison dart frog needs a friend :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree for a different reason. I played practically every day last summer, and it wasn't the endurance that got to me toward the end, I just started overthinking it, and then proceeded to implode. It was a good time in those last few tournament. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, and then I start thinking about how it even became a word?

For example, the word 'couch.' Just repeat it over and over again and next hung you know you'll be questioning the roots of language. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Ken Burns feature on Jack Johnson, who was the first African-American heavyweight, who became it around 1900. Incredible to see his Uber-confident attitude despite the overt racism he faced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 16:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, the "I hate you" song was pretty popular among everyone in my elementary school, and the black may have just been pre-adolescent angst. I wouldn't be quite ready to convict this kid of murder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 08:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This honestly just sounds like one of those upbeat country songs where the singer is just listing random things off  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 02:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a good thing we're getting rid of gerrymandering, but I would just like to highlight this is not a righteous fight by the democrats, they're just the most recent party to lose at gerrymandering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Theo Epstein proves he can go oppo. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Andrew Jackson had a scar across his face from being slashed across the face by an English general as a child, and then went on to lead the US to victory in the Battle of New Orleans. That, and he's a racist asshole, and racist assholes tend to be more prone to violence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
