<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2482</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good try woodtick.  But, this person is obviously worshiping the idol of Trump, and won't be dissuaded with facts.  Good try though.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank goodness, the *Guerrillas* are safe then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you (we) are a simulation, you simply have the illusion of consciousness.  

After all, the last person to know they are insane, is the insane person them-self. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 07:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More specifically...which one, is what I wonder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 07:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, Prusa is like the Elon Musk of the 3d Printing Community. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 07:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, it states a doubling in size between 40 and 80...but the rate of growth is not defined after that. It could be any growth, even if by a gram or two per year, and the statement would still be accurate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 07:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one here is going to want to hear this...but the "Service Dog" moniker is almost useless these days.

You can register your dog as a service dog, simply by filling out a form and mailing it in, along with your check for approx 80 bucks. Boom, you now have an "officially registered" service dog in the legal eyes of pretty much everyone.  It can even accompany you a flight for free!

No training needed for the dog. No anything. It's akin to the old "Buy a star for your loved ones" star registry scam.

Granted...of course there are actual trained dogs meant to assist disabled persons.  They are, however, legally, in the same category of Service Dog as your toy poodle you just registered so you could carry it in your purse on the way to Paris. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You win this round, Positive Polly, you win this round. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always wondered.

Is it supposed to be a combination of:
Pets Mart or Pet Smart ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did not put him down. I simply said that I, me, cannot tell a difference. I did not say there was no difference. Simply that the pictures were incongruous, to the point where they are not comparable. One is in resting state, the other is in flex state.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not trying to sound bad or anything, but I can't tell a difference. Since you're flexing in the after picture, I can't compare the two very well. Everyone looks better flexing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those of you immediately siding with her, thinking it's wrong that had custody taken away....keep in mind how absolutely one-sided and complimentary this article paints her in.  Make sure you're looking at this critically, and not in a "Awwww, poor lady...all mothers are wonderful" type of way.

There is nothing from "his" (husband) side of the story in this, and honestly, this article really sugar coats some serious issues that this woman had with substance abuse and mental problems. It blames the substance abuse and mental problems on her losing custody....but, let's be real here. Those things were probably already present, and just exacerbated by the stress of losing custody, and the trial.  In fact, the article calls it a suicide...and says she died in bed from an overdose.  This is also possibly sugar coating. It's quite possible that she "overdosed" the old fashioned way...by being a substance abuser, and they made her character look better by saying she must have done it on purpose. 

Also keep in mind, a verdict of not guilty can be gotten by any shadow of doubt.  The entire jury could have thought she did it, but with a lack of concrete evidence, and only hearsay to go upon, they would be forced to find her not guilty. 

Yes, it's tragic those kids no longer have a mother. However, just because someone commits suicide (or accidentally overdoses), does not automatically make them the victim. 

Source: Dealing with substance abusing wife that I gained custody of our kids from to protect them from her.  Hearing it from her "side" though, people think I'm a monster for "taking the kids away from their mother".   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got scammed. This is a common scam, where a vendor will put a product significantly and even ridiculously lower than all the competition. Buyers, such as yourself, end up placing an order, and now the scammer has your address and name and phone number. They then take that information and can sell it to the kind of people that buy that information. You will never receive that product. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does not make someone evil at all.  

Is someone evil if they ball up a sheet of paper and throw it in the trash, thus ending it's usefulness?  Of course not.
To us...a sheet of paper has the same sentience as lines of code.  

I.e. none. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 05:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course you are, of course you are. Definitely not a program at all. No sir, definitely not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 04:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate your responses, that's good stuff.  We'll have to agree to disagree though.  And now, I must head to my simulation of sleep, and hope I can catch a glimpse, however fleeting, of our evil benefactors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 04:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You completely miss my meaning.  Your statement is human-centric, based on what we know about conscious.  If we're programs, we were made to think we're conscious, and it's all artificial.  We would not and could not comprehend the true nature of the programmers reality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 03:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem with your argument, is that it is completely human-centric.  You are applying *our* morality code to our possible programmers.  It could be that suffering and pain is simply a construct introduced into this version of the simulation, as a variable, to test something different from the last time the simulation was run.  

We, being part of the simulation, would not even be able to comprehend the non-existence of suffering, due to it being the only reality we know.

Perhaps the physiology of the programmers, or even their society, revels in suffering.  Maybe suffering to them is the ultimate thing in life, as it makes them aware of being alive. (i.e. loosely, the Klingons from Star Trek)

Ultimately, there is no way to ascribe suffering in our reality to the morality of our potential programmers.  To do so only takes into account our limited frame of reference (Our own reality) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a bunk idea.

#5 is complete malarkey.

I don't think twice when I set my Sims house on fire, and end up killing him. I don't consider myself evil.
You know why?....because to me, he's not real. He's code. He's computer code, no matter how "lifelike" he appears in my Sims "simulation".  

If we are in a simulation...to the programmer, creator, player...whatever, we wouldn't be "real".  We are code...., hence causing us to suffer would be meaningless to the creators sense of morals.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just introduce her as your ex-girlfriend everywhere you go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And much like boomerangs, this repost comes right back! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 13:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ..."Daddy, what does this mean?"

"You are reading this."

"No I'm not, you are!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 13:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoosh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Psshhh.

"Hey, take this paint, that wood, and go make some SLBM's for the parade."
"Ok boss".

That's the extent of NK's SLBM technology. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see you lost a spouse in the meantime, what happened there?

It's Inappropriate Question Day btw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Spoiler on The Long Walk ahead]

King's story The Long Walk, I read it back in the early 90's in high school.  I loved it...it was the first time I'd experience a "twist" in a story.  (Not a traditional twist, but more like a..."Oh, a race..ok...hmm, they're all kids...wait..what's that mean...OMG THEY ARE KILLING THEM" type of twist.

I, and my 13 year old mind, thought the story was amazing.

I haven't read it again in my life...because I'm afraid that it won't hold up now that I'm an adult, and I'd prefer to have good memories of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or Tobey McGuire </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll save you the trouble by describing it.

Picture...a lithe and agile tarantula, with long legs..hairy...and what looks like the ability to jump from two feet away and land on your face.  That's about right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All Your Food Belong to Us </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're disregarding the reality of a nuclear explosion on American soil or in a port. 

Let's wargame this a second...a nuke explodes a short distance away from Norfolk Naval Station in Virginia, which wipes out a large part of our ships in port.

What now?  Who did it?  How did it get there?  Was it on a boat?...on a sub?....was it a missile that came in from farther offshore?  We'd have no idea.  The evidence would be destroyed in the explosion.

Who do we blame?  What if every known adversary in the World denies doing it...who do we retaliate against?  

We would be like a hornets nest getting poked by a stick...and we would have no outlet for our rage, except blame and accusations.  I think, soon after that, we'd start a nuke exchange with..someone...and then it's the end of the book of humanity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the other hand, playing Battlefield in real life will be easy.  And mandatory.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure this guy doesn't understand how a toilet works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Forehead smack*  

I just read over what I wrote.  Nothing was said of "a good way to get calories"...simply that it's one of the cheapest way to get calories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No there doesn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 15:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh, you only need to do it at a 50-55 degree angle, and it'll glide back almost right to the place you threw it from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 15:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sunday is the day after everything will pop off.  Good strategy by them...diffusing the situation by saying the VP will be there....but if things pop off on Saturday, obviously, his trip will be cancelled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 06:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A can of Coke is 140 calories.  A case of Coke is about $4.50 on average.  

A case of Coke is 1640 Calories.  You'd be hard pressed to find something that gives you 1640 Calories for only $4.50.

So, yes, soda is a very efficient way to get more Calories per $. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, I guess grass IS no carb, who knew!

Don't mind me, just a fellow sheep. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This post makes me question all the posts in here now =( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair...the price per calorie on soda is very very efficient...so they are just using our tax money wisely is all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tough follow up question incoming!  

If I could only read one of your books, Legacy or Feather...which one should I choose to read? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you have another book coming just some months away...does this second book continue The Dragon's Legacy, or is the Dragon's Legacy a standalone story? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not World News Front page worthy in my opinion.

This is a political maneuver by Trump trying to show strength.

If it was a tactical or strategic move to actually fight the war on terror, then we shouldn't have known anything about it even happening.
But, instead, we get to watch video of it practically live?

Plleeeaassse. This was purely political.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not World News Front page worthy in my opinion.  

This is a political maneuver by Trump trying to show strength.  

If it was a tactical or strategic move to actually fight the war on terror, then we shouldn't have known anything about it even happening.  
But, instead, we get to watch video of it practically live?

Plleeeaassse.  This was purely political. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be your friend.

As long as we don't have to shake hands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We Aim (at the Target) to please! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ROFL, whatever man.  Adolescent Privacy Laws cover disclosing identities, etc.  This person has already been disclosed.  Behavior isn't covered under that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 05:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh, your mileage may vary. If I eat at my desk, I can charge that time as working.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like someone once told me....there is always one crazy person on every bus. If you look around and can't spot the crazy person, then you're that person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's just like OP...selfishly only considering his/her self...all the while doomed to be alone until the sweet release of death. 

Next time, spring for the dessert, you cheapo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep...what I don't think most people realize, is that if that happened, it's almost an extinction level event for humans.  Many, many people would die, and society would break down.  

Once people realized there is no more food, except for what they can take from others, that's when it all would break down pretty quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Target has stores pier-side now?!  Man, they are really expanding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Umm, more please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 01:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harsh dude.  Saying "I think" is equal to "spreading false information"?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I could give 19 upvotes to this.  

King fans know what's up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> China: "150k troops?  That's a lie, and not true."

World: "Ok, thanks for clearing that up."

The truth: It was 250k troops </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Naw.  

I think that China is being complicit in all this now...simply because Trump promised that China would be able to annex NK once it falls.  

It would be a win/win for China and Trump.

China gets a bunch of new real-estate...when, let's face it, there isn't any new land to go around.

China doesn't look like an aggressor, and comes out squeaky clean.

Trump gets to look decisive, flex his might, and appear powerful.

Yep.  It works out for everyone, except for the untold people in NK that will die, and 10's, possibly 100's of thousands in SK that will die from the last gasps of the NK military machine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only wrench in the works possible is that crazy guy in NK.  What could go wrong! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: If you enjoy flying kites, buy a cheap, half-length fishing pole and tie the fishing line to your kite. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Advantages:
It makes "spooling in" the kite almost effortless, as you just reel it in.  
You can fit much more line in a fishing reel than you can in a kite string spool. (Higher flying kites!)
Fishing line is much lighter than kite string. (Higher flying kites!)

You can get higher test strength fishing line if you have a bigger kite or the wind is super strong.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you enjoy flying kites, buy a cheap, half lengthed fishing pole and tie the fishing line to your kite. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I die, I'm going to haunt OP, and just take his money at the front door over and over, so the cops will hate him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's up with those, anyways?  

Why do stores think that would bring in business?  Speaking personally, I would avoid going to a place that advertised that way, because it reeks of desperation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
