<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject366</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 06:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His resume listed his last job as a
"Saltay" at a restaurant.  In the description it was mentioned that he had experience at the "Saltay Station" and that he was able to keep orders going even during the dinner rush.  

Saltay...
Saltay...
Saltay...

It was weeks before I realized he was a Saute cook.  He had applied for a warehouse job.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 16:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look, I'm no expert, but a video that explains the project is a good start.  Even if it is just a few people talking about being vegan fitness people and their struggles.  You need to visually tell a story about the need for this product.  Backers don't want to read much.  You have to tell them and the video is the way to do it.  As for the rewards, they should be incremental.  $15 buys one pack of donuts, $25 buys two and so on.  People who give more should get more.  

If you are going to develop some donut recipes, why not offer people the ability to be early taste-testers?  For $25 you will be sent three different donut recipes and a survey card to determine which you like best  

By the way, you can learn a lot about running a successful Kickstarter campaign online.  I'm not a genius and I've only done four campaigns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 16:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt the whole thing is "fake" as in these people are going to take all of the money and spend it on strippers, but I think this project looks way too early to be on Kickstarter.  Too many 3D models in the images and the gear shifting in the video looks horrid.  I do like how the guy has a black suit on and an old pair of nikes though.  This project is definitely a high-risk proposal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 16:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the comments.  The mat material is standard PVC, just like most of the mats sold at Target, Walmart, Sporting Goods stores.  The quality and stickiness are not out of the ordinary.  

Hugger Mugger has a bunch of different mats and its a great site for folks who are really serious about their yoga, but I don't think we are dealing with the same people.

Our target customer is just a regular guy that does some yoga and has found he is much too large for the mat.  They didn't seem to interested in the material of the mat, just the size and price.  That's why the price is only $39.  They aren't going to go for a premium priced mat and our price doesn't really indicate that it is the top of the line.  

As far as mention of the extra thickness we just say twice as thick in most of the description.  In the technical specs it is listed at 6mm which is twice the thickness of the majority of mats you will find on the shelves of retail stores 3mm.  

We are hopeful that after the Kickstarter that we can find a place for our products at retail stores and websites around the country.  The four items we have will fit well and look really masculine next to offerings by Gaiam and such.  We would look OK on a site like Hugger Mugger because the pricing would be attractive next to the other mats.

Does that make sense?  It is nice to communicate with you.  If you still know anyone at Hugger Mugger, have them contact us.  We may have wholesale product in time for the holiday season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 05:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The links worked. Thank you.  It looks pretty straightforward.  I hope you make it across the finish line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 03:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that you have made some Kickstarter mistakes.  First is the you do not have a video.  People really respond to the video, it shows that you have put some effort into the product.  Second, your rewards are a bit strange.  For $5 you get a pack of donuts and for $25 you get a pack of donuts.  It is no surprise that not a lot of people have gone for the $25 pack of donuts.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 03:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks pretty cool!  The pricing is really good.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 03:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have home stretch advice but I do have experience with the survey process.  I had a $15,000 project and the process of collecting and exporting all of the data was a nightmare.  People gave bad addresses, didn't answer the survey requests (repeatedly), etc.  I will be using third party tools next time.  I apologize that i don't know which ones, but anything will be better than the KS process.  It was really, really labor intensive.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 03:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thing is really cool.  I could see myself using all three of its main features and using them often.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 03:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you have done an excellent job of telling your story.  It looks nice too.  It is fairly elegantly done.

One issue is that it doesn't tell the customer's story.  You don't mention the benefit to the customer.  Most marketing is done in the voice of the customer, not in the seller.  You should make an attempt at telling how it would work for your potential clients.  "Instead of paying too much for a mechanic to diagnose, order parts for, and then repair your vehicle, you could let the collective knowledge of the internet do the first two steps and save money..." 

Just my 2 cents.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 03:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I might suggest you post a link in the comments.  The one in the title is hard to work with.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 16:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have never launched a Kickstarter before, it is really exhilarating.  We've done a lot of work with this project and I hope it takes off. Of course I believe in it, otherwise I wouldn't have worked on it, but what will others think?  I hope you can follow along with me, watch the stats and see how it goes.  Thanks.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just pushed the launch button for Yeoman Gear - Yoga Gear for Men (and people who are not tiny) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 16:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 04:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think ShopInPrivate.com is original.  It's a store that only sells embarrassing items and does so privately.  Brown box delivery and no email list.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 04:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sell some candies on Amazon and have tried to get approval for a category and failed.  I even spoke to an actual person in support and they gave me this advice.  Stop trying to resubmit a failed application and start over.  I guess it is easier to get approval on the first shot.  If you fail the first time, you get escalated to a real "expert" and they hardly ever bend the rules.  So, try starting the ungating application again.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 04:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is fantastic advice.  You can even get someone to pledge a dollar to your campaign on Fiverr.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 04:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could see how this game might (might?) be popular with people who have disabilities.  It might also be the cause for divorce.  Could you imagine being in the same home as someone who plays this game often?  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 03:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found someone through Craigslist.  I asked them to submit their "reel" and I watched them.  Some reels were amazing.  Some were horrendous.  It was usually entertaining either way.  In the past I have paid $100 per finished minute.  I am in the Detroit area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 06:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your standard mat is 3mm thick, look for one that is 6mm.  It'll feel great in a lot of places, such as outside, on tile, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 05:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It might be "If we don't raise $35k, we are calling it a day and keeping our day jobs."  The goal isn't always the tooling costs, sometimes it is just a number that convinces you to do the project.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 05:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the project side, it's a set fee to be features in the message.  $379 I think.  If they don't help you raise $379 they don't charge you.  It's not unfair, but the average amount raised is less than $2,000 so you aren't going to get rich on the back of it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 05:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know I am going to sound strange when I say this, but I recently went to my local library and took out Kickstarter for dummies and while it was a bit wordy, it is tough to replace the ability to skim through a book.  I absorbed the whole thing in probably less than an hour.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 05:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are services called "Freight Consolidators" They take a bunch of parcels, say a pallet full of them, bring them across the border and then put the in the Canadian postal system.  They can save you a bundle, probably more than 50% but you will probably need to ship 150 units or so to make it worthwhile. My company has met with this one before:  http://www.reallycoolsolutions.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
