<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3535</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just brought back a ton of memories with Animorphs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> caped Joel is a good one. Comic Pop has good content, especially their series like Back Issues, The Elseworld's Exchange Podcast and The Weekly Pull, which are more along the lines of what you're looking for. The only thing is that sometimes, they can be pretty cynical about events and storylines and tend to go on rants, which may or may not annoy you, like me. Jawiin is my favorite, however, mostly because its a husband and wife ran channel and they make really good and in-depth reviews of the CW shows.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn it, you're right. I guess so long as Jar Jar gets indoctrinated, I'll be cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you also have to consider Reaper tactics as well. Their whole doctrine is based on using their opponents own resources against each them, either in the form of turning troops into reaper combatants or indoctrination. The Reapers also attack in massive waves similar to the Flood, who the Covenant have had trouble with before. Also, if the great schism caused the stalemate, then imagine what an indoctrinated prophet or Elite can do. There could be 3 great schisms at once.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hated the Cardassians for those qualities you just listed not to mention what they did to the Bajorans. If we had a game with them in it, I would not be kind to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A group of fanatic, enhanced, tribalistic imperialistic humans with chainsaw swords at war with the Alliance over what they believe is heresy by interacting with aliens. That sounds amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They sound like an awesome enemy to encounter/negotiate with in an Andromeda set game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know about soloing the Reapers. Keep in mind the Reapers numbered in the thousands maybe more, and they've brought down species that probably had tech similar to or equal to what the Covenant are packing. Also take indoctrination into consideration. I could see the reapers indoctrinating one of the prophets in order to worsen the dissent that already exists within the ranks (if we're talking about the pre Halo 4 Covenant) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could see them as an ancient rival of either the Protheans or the Jardaan who went into hiding  and are planning on returning to reclaim the galaxy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are they the first victims of the Reaper invasion? They should be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be the Rachini on steroids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could see some tension between the two, as the Klingons could see the Krogan, who like you said fight for pure pleasure and need rather than for a higher ideal like them, with contempt. I could also see some kind of Begrudging respect between the two as well as periodic, almost Sparta vs. Athens-esque, kind of conflicts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fair, but I would think the Borg would find the existence of another AI, especially one that allows for some degree of individuality, curious as we've seen with the Borg queen taking an interest in Data in First Contact. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true, and I would love to see the borg try and assimilate the Geth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK. Thanks for the clarification. 11A is Infantry Officer if I'm not mistaken.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] If you could integrate a species from another Sci-Fi franchise into the ME universe, who would it be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, it would be the Predators. I can see them hanging around the Milky Way, stalking merc groups, criminals (maybe even taking a shot at Aria) and eventually Shepard and Garrus when they show up.

And to clarify, it could be in the Milky Way or Andromeda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could interegrate a species from another Sci-Fi franchise into the ME universe, who would it be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right now, I'm a college student whose interested in earning a commission as an officer with the ultimate goal of going into SF. I've been reading up on SF history and mission sets and I'm really interested in the idea of not only teaching but also helping others to free themselves from a hostile gov. 

With that being said, can anyone help me out in regards to what MOS would best lend itself into to a future career with SF(would Civil Affairs be a good starting point since they work closely with SF),what is looked for in a SF officer,and where else I can find info on being an SF O, as I've had some trouble finding anything online.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SEALS and FID </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this question has been asked before year ago, but I'm not sure if the info given has changed in recent years. Recently, I've been reading up on the efforts of Army SF in regards to FID(Foreign Internal Defense), and its piqued my interest. Now, I know that the SEALS aren't diplomats and they don't conduct FID to the same degree as SF, but can anyone speak to what degree SEALs conduct FID in recent years and how it differs from SF? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree in regards to having stories that solidify Superman as the gold standard for heroes, especially in the wake of what's been going on with Cap at Marvel(that's another post for another time). 

I think giving Conner the Jason Todd treatment is one way to handle him, but I honestly want to see Jon have someone he can identify with as well as expand the family dynamic with Clark having to deal with an older son.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Conner was Dick's age, would he still be called Superboy or would he share the title of Superman with Clark like Wally and Barry are doing with the Flash title? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying Conner should come back right away, and you're right that the Jon and Clark dynamic should explored more before a new cast member comes in, but eventually, maybe in phase 2 of Rebirth, I would like to see Conner make a Wally West-esque return.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If that's the case, then it would be him, Jon, Kara, and Conner (eventually). At this point, Clark would have close to as many young partners as Bruce.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i don't think they would. I hope they mature him like Wally, though I don't know if he would share the Superman mantle with Clark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah, I forgot about Chris. Given all that's happened with the N52 and Rebirth, would Chris still even exist?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For fans of what Rebirth era Superman, what would you like to see going forward </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, Rebirth Superman and Action Comics are my favorite books coming out of the big two right now. Superman has always been a character I've always been into but have had trouble getting into both pre-N52 and during N-52. With Rebirth, they've managed to boil Superman's origins down to something mostly streamlined, got Supes back to his roots in regards to his character, added some of the best character relationships I've seen recently with Lois, Jon, and  SuperLex and have given readers a consistent bright, fun, and optimistic tone. 

Going forward, what would you like to see happen with the two books? For me, my biggest desire is to see the reintroduction of Connor Kent's Superboy and have something similar to what's going on with the Flash where he's acting in a sort of big brother role to Jon while acting as a partner to Clark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could see young Justice get a treatment similar to what they did with Titans where its a reunion of the older, original characters, though to be honest, I would like to see Conner get reintroduced in Superman and have him move in with Clark and Lois and become a big brother figure to Jon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wholeheartedly agree with the inclusion of the Milestone characters. Icon and Static were the standouts for me, and would love to see them get introduced in books like Superman(Icon) and Teen Titans or Titans (Static) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What concepts/characters would you like to see get a book or more focus later on in Rebirth? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To my knowledge, the overall concept of DC Rebirth is broken down into phases, and phase 2 is coming up either later this year or the start of 2018. With that being said, what characters, ideas, or concepts would you like to see either get a book or have more focus put on in rebirth phase 2? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you post some pics of your armor set? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always thought that collapsing helmets were the only explainable way they disappear in cutscenes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For anyone who makes their way down there, make sure to check if anyone who lives nearby is named Shepard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a good entry into a language. It gives you a lot of background info on the language, dialects, pronunciations, etc. I would supplement it with some other research, or cheap books off of Amazon as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mainly Rosetta Stone and books from the "For Dummies" series. 

There is a free language website called DuoLingo that an old friend of mine told me about. I don't know how In depth it goes as I've  only tried it a few times and its content is created by contributors, and last I checked, the Korean section isn't finished yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true, which in my opinion, more likely with a regular network. That's why it should go to HBO. They've shown in the past that they can treat a historical event with accuracy and respect, like with BOB and the Pacific. As a matter of fact they could base it on Steven Ambrose's Undaunted Courage, which was his book on Lewis and Clark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Vlad the Impaler series would best on something like HBO, given how bloody that series would be.

I've never heard of the Lincoln county war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are absolutely right. Thanks for the correction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In response to no. 3, I haven't seen anything relating to Justinian in recent television.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would make sense. I could see Jean Paul Marat's assassination, the ransacking of the Tuileries palace, the "trial" of Marie Antoinette, and the Bastille being destroyed as major events in the style of the Red Wedding or the Battle of the Bastards from GOT.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 03:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree on both. I can see the French revolution show ending with Robespierre's attempted suicide and eventual execution like how season 1 of Rome ending with the assassination of Caesar. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 03:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to see a series on the first heart transplant, especially since it's not well known that performing surgeon was African American, so they could touch on the racial aspect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 03:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just read the Wikipedia description. That would be a heavy show to watch. Actually, I think some networks might be hesitant to pick up the idea given how controversial the riots were and still are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 02:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm surprised the Black Panthers haven't had several miniseries by now. If option for 10 on HBO just because they can show in detail a lot of the darker stuff the Panthers did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 02:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm picturing something along the lines of Silicon Valley or Halt And Catch Fire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the Australia idea. I would also like to see a movie based on the British colonization of South Africa, and the ensuing war with the Zulus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to see a Carthage miniseries. Historically, we've always been so focused on Rome, we never get to see what life was like for their greatest rivals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or the 4th Crudsade where the crusaders were disavowed by the church and became a rogue nomadic army. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would it be a comedy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know much about the Council of Nicaea. 

I like the idea about Gengis Kahn, but I think since Marco Polo wasn't received very well, not a lot of studios would want to touch it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds awesome. Is there a book about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately no. The Pacific was from the perspectives of the Marines and went from Guadalcanal to Okinawa.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK. much appreciated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Netflix or HBO would be a good home for it. I could also see it being something along the lines of Marco Polo from Netflix. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you know if its online? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
