<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2746</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors who have moved from tiny towns to huge cities, what is the one thing you miss the most? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 05:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 12:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds to me like the same corporate line: We're going to do the next great thing in mobile.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 03:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I get an ELI5 on why this is a big deal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 03:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh, like I'm five? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow.  This is a fantastic list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My new favorite sub-genre is the slow-burning spy thriller. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 15:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Examples: Bill Nighy's *Worricker Trilogy*, the 2016 mini-series *The Night Manager*, Gary Oldman's *Tinker Tailor Soldier Spy*, BBC's *The Game*, and FX's *The Americans*.

These stories are evidence that a spy thriller can be gripping and tense without the need for car chases and gunfights.  If you have more suggestions along these lines, let me know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 15:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks.  It worked! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 19:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you explaining like I'm five? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My 950 won't let me edit Word docs because it says I need an Office 365 subscription. I DO have a subscription. How do I convince my phone of this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 04:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MS Office came pre-installed on my 950, of course.  It's great.  Yet when I open an existing document on my phone, I see this message:  To edit and save, an Office 365 subscription is required.

I am already an Office 365 subscriber.  How do I convince my phone of my existing subscription, so that I can edit documents?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 04:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would give you gold for this if I could. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three tips on writing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 17:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 14:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're in the wrong sub.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 16:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm.  From what I've observed, feeding is standard operating procedure.  But I'm certainly interested in alternative viewpoints.  What have you seen that indicates feeding has been detrimental? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 02:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 20:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great info. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 18:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for this reply! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does Ecuador gain politically by giving asylum to Assange? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 16:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand Russia's political stake in harboring Ed Snowden, but I am unfamiliar with Ecuador's place in world politics.  What gains are they making on the world stage, or what important message are they trying to send (and to whom?) by offering succor to Assange?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 22:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A question about veneer edging </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 21:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never used veneer edging before.  If my edge is 3/4 inch, should I purchase 7/8-inch edging and trim to fit, or is the strip of edging sized perfectly to 3/4 inch?  Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 23:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I can't imagine having an heirloom surge protector fifty years from now. OP may not understand the nature of this sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 00:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, that's funny:  about a minute after typing the above post, I used the knife to open a pack of dried cranberries.  True story.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 00:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I could recall all the odd tasks I've asked of this knife over the years.  But the last couple of days are a good example of both conventional and unconventional uses:  opening Amazon boxes that contain gifts for my daughter's birthday; fixing a toaster; cutting a pear; and removing a screw from the back of a small jewelry box.  Also this week, I used this knife to scrape the old registration sticker from my truck window and to strip wires for a ceiling fan installation.

All of this is light-duty stuff, to be sure.  I'm not endorsing this knife if you're headed into the bush for two weeks and living off what you kill.  But for real-life things?  The day-to-day things that make your wife and daughter happy and make your routine tasks easy?  Well, I am no expert, but this is the knife for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Bucklite 444 is nothing fancy, but this will be my 20th year carrying it and using it almost every day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 20:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 01:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's much better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 23:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is very original and wonderful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 23:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Retarded" is not an appropriate word in this instance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 22:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 21:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which of the many apps for transparent tiles can render one for Facebook Messenger and Skype? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 13:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 15:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the Charge 2 the latest model? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 01:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean about the notifications not working? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 01:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. That's the model I'll probably purchase. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 01:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad to hear that it syncs well! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 01:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. I want to make sure it syncs well with Windows Phone before dropping $150 on the Charge 2.  Thanks again for your insight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 00:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you own a Fitbit? How well does the app work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 23:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking about buying my wife a Fitbit Charge 2 for her birthday.  We both own 950s.  I'm glad to see the app in the store, but how well does it function?  Any syncing issues? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 23:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Materials other than leather for a custom sheath? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 22:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My office mate inherited an old Mora knife that he adores, and I'd like to give him a custom sheath for this year's holiday gift exchange. Plot twist: he's vegan. Finding someone to make a leather sheath would be easy, but where do I begin looking for a custom-fit, non-leather version? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 13:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I've always hated the 1000-song limit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 15:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where can I find the Microsoft metro ("modern") font or a similar typeface to install on my PC? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 15:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just started reading EGG's recent biography. It includes a map of Lake Geneva in the style of a map from an adventure module, so I'm hooked. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 03:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Victor Strand is already a more well-developed, complex character than anyone in TWD. I am so pleased that FTWD has taken the time to craft at least one character whose motivations are complicated and even at times contradictory--as real motivations can be. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 23:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 23:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have realized that "The Walking Dead" is like "Seinfeld."  It is a show about nothing.  

There is conflict, yes.  But other than "Just survive somehow," the characters have no goal.  There is no city they're trying to reach, person they're trying to find, or quest they're trying to complete.  Every episode is just showing how they strive or fail to survive.

So it's a show about nothing.

Of course, I'll continue to watch it and enjoy it.  But I'm just watching to see who dies next, and how the horror of their death affects their loved ones.  Wow . . . that's depressing . . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
