<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2797</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but im certainly not here for some white knight bullshit from yet another person who refuses to accept the ugliest of ugly truths </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no... not in my entire life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no but being born female gets you into whatever bar club or party you want with 0 to minimal effort. it also gets you endless free dinners and jewelry and sex anytime you could possibly ever want it (of course you usually don't because you're a woman)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> women's rights  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 21:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> additionally I am finding it very difficult to assimilate myself with the University. at orientation they made the point that you don't want to be the type of student who just goes to class and then goes straight home, but that is exactly what I have become. I have not met even a single person.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> why the fuck does everything suck. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 07:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> all girls do is cheat and hurt, all jobs do is shit on you, all friends do is ask for constant favors but are never there when you need them. who the fuck wants to live in this world. I hate interacting with people. I don't think about suicide because I hate myself. I love myself. I hate this world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> having trouble finding research on Singmaster's conjecture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 03:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to do a little bit of independent research on the conjecture, but I am having a really difficult time finding more than just two or three papers on it. anyone know of a good source for more? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 04:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks for the help. I plan on taking ODE this summer so by fall I suppose I should be more ready. that being said I have seen how to solve very basic ODEs like separable and what not. I will look into this book  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> book recommendations for fluid mechanics/dynamics ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 00:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm an undergrad with linear algebra and calc 2 under my belt (currently learning multi-variable) with the goal of going into research in fluid dynamics. however, I currently only have 1 calc-based physics course done. do you have any book recommendations for someone around my level? or maybe one that's above my level that I should think about getting in the near future? thanks ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 00:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Calculus 2] integrating cot, csc, and sec. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 21:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the procedure for evaluating these does not at all seem intuitive or obvious. I watched a video on evaluating the integral of csc which involved multiplying by csc-cot/csc-cot. how exactly is it supposed to occur to someone to do that? am I supposed to just memorize the whole process? this is ridiculous and now I am completely terrified of my next exam  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 21:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok this is pretty much the approach I thought  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> linear algebra proof: if AB=BA=I, then (AB)^3=(AB) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 17:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can I get a hint on how to attack this proof. I feel like I might be overthinking it. I think maybe I should show it using the associative property of matrix multiplication  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 17:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh I see. thank you for the clarity  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 01:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ohhhhh I didnt know that  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> well I kinda hate to be this guy but... how do you all feel about "common core" math ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 03:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> seems like bullshit to me. last I checked mathematicians try to make a hard problem easier, not an easy problem harder  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 03:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "only the mediocre are supremely confident in their ability". false! counter-example: John Nash  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 04:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> uh sorry advice for something means being redirected to another thread  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 04:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats funny if I posted this myself I would be sent this ... If you are asking for advice on choosing classes or career prospects, please post in the stickied Career   Education Questions thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 03:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> um apparently career and class advice isnt welcome here  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 03:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "If you are asking for advice on choosing classes or career prospects, please post in the stickied Career   Education Questions thread." apparently this is what we do on r/math we act like a little bitch and direct people to other threads where you can then be directed to other threads have fun  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 03:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pussy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 03:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fuck off you fucking egotistical piece of shit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 03:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're an elitist who supports all the bullshit that is dumbing down society. people like you wonder why most people hate math. ironically people like you are why.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 19:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> o look at yooouuuu looks like you tend to spend entirely too much of your time being the police judging by your profile. how about you leave it to the moderators and get a life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 19:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you think youre so cute with your little down vote and copy and paste. what genius things have you posted then? fucking cock  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so exactly what the fuck can you post on this thread? considering how many people I see asking for help with calculations which seems more blatantly against the incredibly strict rules  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> question about calc 3 and analysis this summer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> grab my gun and shoot em, probably with a huge boner swinging around.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 17:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well sometimes people try to come up with proofs using different methods and find new results. Im just wondering if it is still being researched  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 04:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cool thanks I didn't know that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 04:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah another thing is I know basics graph theory, I took one semester of discrete math and have done some reading. but im not sure where to go from here. Id love to see some work on the problem people have done </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> so... whats going on with the four color theorem? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 03:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it over? Have mathematicians more or less stopped searching for a proof besides the computer aided one? Are there applications to other fields being researched? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Why are numbers beautiful? It's like asking why is Beethoven's Ninth Symphony beautiful. If you don't see why, someone can't tell you. I know numbers are beautiful. If they aren't beautiful, nothing is". -Paul Erdos  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm having a really hard time understanding the uses for group theory tho. It's frustrating it's just not really clicking. I can do some proofs and understand the axioms but I don't know where to go from there  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 04:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well put lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yea that's what I was thinking. a as an element of the integers right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> soft question: why is real analysis considered one of the most difficult classes (if not the most) you will take? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> some people even say it is more true for your first semester of analysis than the following. is this from the shock value of having a class that is almost completely proof based? I am in linear algebra now and will probably take analysis this fall. When should I start preparing ? thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 06:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well "perfect" doesn't have a very rigid definition now does it? it's pretty arbitrary. that being so... assume you're perfect because the axioms to be satisfied for the sufficient conditions of "perfect" vary from person to person. see? isn't logic the tits ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
