<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject354</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 15:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't get into a portrait competition with this. I still think it's pretty good :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The New Normal, Oil on Board, 40"x37" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 15:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 22:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Magic mushrooms </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best "No way!" Anecdote you have? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 21:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 22:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad and uncle never really knew their dad. They just knew of him and that he was a Dutch sailor. Jump ahead 30 years, my dad and uncle have completely given up on ever meeting the man. My uncle is on holiday in Greece sharing a villa with a Dutch family. They get talking and my uncle mentions that his dad was Dutch and tells them his name. The holiday continues, the Dutch family go home. A few days later my uncle gets a phone call from the villa. (The Dutch family have gone home and told my uncles story to a friend. The friend knows who this man is). My uncle picks up the phone. "Hello, I believe I am your father". What are the odds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 22:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to get depressed in a sad way several times a year since forever. Now I don't get sad I just got bored and numb. But this last year has been the first time it's been like this and this stint started about 2 months ago. It's kinda worse than being sad. Atleast being sad feels like it has a cure. Being bored in fun situations feels like a dead end. But I'm sure you're right. The sun will rise.... Eventually </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 21:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks man. I do remember the existence of good days  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 21:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there are a few things in my life that I'm angry about. Maybe those things do underpin my being disenfranchised. I'll look into it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 21:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 24 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 14:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much. That's been bugging me for over a year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] comedy film with black detectives? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 14:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's this film with a scene in which a group of black men sit around trying to work out clues or something. Then one of them makes a connection between to completely unrelated things and then it goes on and on until they reach a conclusion. Eg. So chairs have fours legs, four is the number of walls in a room, rooms are where people go, therefore all people are chairs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 13:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh..just looked up Anhedonia, sounds like me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 13:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I'm just getting on with life. Each day has enough challenges and tasks that need to be completed to keep me preoccupied until the evening. Then I just browse reddit, feel numbness then go to bed early to escape the feeling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm bored to death </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 13:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've travelled. I didn't care for it. I keep fit. It doesn't improve my mood. I have hobbies and a creatively fulfilling job. They feel pointless. I don't like sex. I don't like food. I'm tired of drink and drugs. The idea of starting a conversation with a stranger at a party makes me yawn.
I'm bored of life. I don't know what to do. I guess I'm sad but it feels more like an overwhelming numbness to everything. I'd wish I was dead but I'm scared of dying and I don't want to hurt those around me. I wish I'd never been born. This life is dull </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 20:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a lot. I'm already on top of everything on that list. So all should be fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 13:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome. Thanks guys :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
