<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3944</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 08:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lmao, you know you're going to get absolutely shot down by new wave feminists. people only believe what they want to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 08:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> gotten every summer game skin except for nihon genji... lmfao... not even slightly exaggerating.. also have gotten duplicates of every summer game legendary at least twice... what are the odds..? lmfao... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 04:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> getting the health pack while still unable to heal is my favorite part </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feel like Overwatch needs a token pyro character </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 19:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could be another junker, or something? Shift would throw a molotov, has a flamethrower, secondary could be like, spray napalm on the targeted surface (a la Mei's snowblower thing), lasts for 20 seconds, then you would be able to ignite the trail. E could spray napalm in a decent sized AOE around you.

This would allow you to be a brawler type hero, he'd need a decent sized health pool, or some kind of damage mitigation mechanic. Maybe 300 health, and takes 50% reduced damage from AOE attacks, 40% reduced damage from direct attacks, and 150% damage from headshots? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 06:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FIVE GOLDEN RIIIINNNNGS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I just want to whittle birds' nests" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 22:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/BY2Sswp.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not today, Junkrat! TODAY, YOU GET YOURS! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 18:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 07:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Winston will basically always force a Genji to change. Jump is lower CD than dash if he doesn't reset. Can't block your attacks. Squishy. Tracer... McCree is apparently a counter to her, provided you land your stun. It's not a hard counter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 20:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if i had let her fall, it would've taken maybe another second for her to die... always be 100% sure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 20:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he did the lord's work, allowing me to vanquish diablo, the lord of terror </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just di- no stop- don't- fu- OUCH- STOP MOVIN- TO HELL WITH THIS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 16:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 22:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you figured it all out buddy, in fact, you're so good, i'll link you the raw video.

https://vid.me/1Ugz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 19:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> some pleb using a controller on pc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 18:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/EUdJE0Y.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 16:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> when the synergy is on point </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 16:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 03:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2200 something dragonite... steel wing so... you know... *cough* trash *cough* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 15:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> funny story, this isn't me. my friend came over and logged into her account on my computer, she's still new to the game. like level 12 or something? and so i had my recording software on. i was watching her play, saw this happen, and was just kind of laughing quietly to myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> And Bastion still gets POTG </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 07:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> gtfover here </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 23:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 17:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much, me and my friend have been trying to find out what this bird is for about two weeks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 03:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> extra details: it went on the ground and was wading through the marsh. it's kind of brownish, this is also southern Louisiana. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's this bird in a Louisiana Swamp? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 02:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
