<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3750</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Serbian power forward 

Do you want to start another war?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats what you get for waiving NBA D-League champion DeAndre Liggins smh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I switch to pokerstars? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 01:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 12:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn I thought Rondo was gonna bring us closer together...
If I said I was not hurt I would be lying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 20:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think cause of Nadals top spin, it gives him a better point of view and more time to adjust and react to a strange bounce.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 20:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like Roger decided to give him his todger today </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a fucking shot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except for one type of animal... A silent killer if you please </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your input </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HE THINKS HE'S PEOPLE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Techically, a conversation still happened </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 16:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gambling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is actually a fair point, and im finding it hard to argue against it since I want Harden to win, but all of my counter arguments come down to "flair bias lol".
I dont think many people will remember this Harden season even if 29/8/12 is amazing, and he had multiple 50/15 triple doubles if im not mistaken, so definitely an amazing season but not as historic as Brodies, and I dont like Brodie one bit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah i figured that, but since I am a pessimist I keep thinking about the worst case scenario. I havent eaten for a day and a half now, and all i can think about is this little moron that is sleeping on my chest right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [HELP] My beagle is sick </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 23:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today has begun awfully since both me and my mom got sick. My Mom all of a sudden notices that our dog hasnt been himself the whole day. He didnt eat and all he did was lay down. We took him to the vet and he said that he got some diseases that you get from ticks. He said that the thing we put on his skin that the vendor told us was gonna last six months was a complete lie and only lasted a month or two. He had two shots, he is getting his blood taken tommorow. He had fever for the majority of the day, his ears are swollen but now he finally ate and started to get his activity up a bit. I am incredibly worried but do I have reason to be, or is it all just gonna be fine, has someone else had simmilar experiences? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 14:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The question is "Would you really give IT the max", and the answer is no. Under no circumstances would i pay a 30+ year old short guard that doesnt have literally any defense 25+ million . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 22:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A deserved win for Poland, although this does leave a bitter taste in our mouths.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh okay then, but seems like a bit of an overprotective rule, atleast it prevents injuries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Studs up, but he managed to block the ball without touching him, come on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never a foul, but what and amazing free kick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 03:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jared Sullinger disagrees </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 16:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gathered my history of playing cash tables on bet365, and after 2900 hands played I have a net loss of 3.08 euros. Durrr dont @ me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 12:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously, I felt the /s wasnt needed. I dont like the idea of paying 30+ year old short guard with the worst defense in the league 25+ million a year. I want Bradley/Smart and Fultz in the backcourt, with a defensive specialist and a true scorer. 

I get you, I just dont like Lonzo, his game isnt for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 11:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really want Fultz then. We need a successor for IT, and havent had a first scoring option that was amazing since Pierce beside Isaiah and MarShon Brooks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 23:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breaking: A professional tennis player has a decent chance of beating a redditor!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really tho, I always thought of Roger as the more likeable and interesting person, but I am extremely biased so my stance is invalid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 00:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did I say anywhere that you wouldnt get more chances? Its just that its easier to score when there isnt 10 players in the sixteen yard box, but yeah, an insult should be and excellent argument. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 09:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, cause less defence = less goals, amirite? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah Im not even mad, who deserved is a coin flip, you guys are amazing, and one of my favourite teams since the times of Juninho and the Snake(Pjanic), just that we could have gone trough if we had finished infront of the goal a bit better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you wouldnt put 9 men behind the ball so we would probably score even more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, he is a system QB. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dominated is the key word. But a disallowed goal, and fucking Jesus at the goal helped you a lot. And remember, if Lacazette didnt have a stroke of genius at the end of the last game we would be going trough right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Completely unbiased opinion there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 21:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But nowhere does it say that a dog cant play basketball </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mobile reddit, sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that makes sense, I read about premium hands somewhere, is that what you mean? 
And about Dnegs, I get your point, but if he can do it i am pretty sure I can too. After all he only has 6 bracelets and my aunt gave me my ninth one for christmass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but I put him on AQ, cause of the preflop raise. KQ came to mind aswell, figured he would bet the pocket Queens on the flop and/or turn if he had them, and QJ/Q10 and any less he would fold on the bet on the flop. However now that I think about it a queen plus a flopped pair seems really plausible, but luck was on my side. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah sure, what literature do you recommend? 
And in reference to turn and river bets, I dont really know, its just that min bettin will sometimes earn my weak hand a fold, or if they are a nit, my mediocre hand atleast two or three big blinds, so I can atleast pickup something without scaring them off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since Dnegs is the player I watch the most, he said somewhere that every flop is worth seeing, and sometimes lines like that stay in my head and shape my actions subconsciously. Same goes for "Suited trash is still trash" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Hand Analysis] How would you play this hand? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im a relatively new poker player so I dont know how to properly write this so I will do my best. I play micro stakes, and while not big money it gives me a start and an intro into the world of poker. 
Anyway .02/.04 stakes
Hero has 3.83 
Villain 5.23 
Hero is UTG +1
Villain is UTG +2
Hero has 8dKs
BB, SB and hero limp in, Villain raises 5BB, everyone folds, Hero calls
Flop is 2d 8c 5h
Hero bets .23, Villain calls 
Turn 7h 
Hero bets the min, V calls
River Qd,
Hero bets the min, V raises to .88, Hero????
I ended up calling cause I couldnt put him on AQ dont know why, since he did raise pre but I had a hunch , and ended up winning the pot, he had AhJs, so I won the pot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 13:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No he is not. He has been really good for like a third of a normal NBA season, and if anything the numbers should be his strong suit, since his defence is pretty bad, so no defensive presence that is overlooked by stats such as Gobert. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
