<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3386</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They say men think with their penises. Well, I want you to blow my mind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. Plus there is a "rapist" one already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It is sad that good news go to r/upliftingnews but bad news simply go to r/news </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 01:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is coconuts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Argentine congress approves use of medical marijuana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 06:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 06:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Argentine congress too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For Damon: is it true that you weren't allowed to ride your bike on a certain park, but did it anyways cause you were from Gorillaz?
For everyone: How did you come up with "Gorillaz" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To whom it may concern: You must be VERY careful when discussing topics like this. Argentina is portrayed as dark, enslaved and hopeless in those years, and all the blame is put in the military. I am just going to present the other perspective of history, simply to make people comprehend a more "accurate" truth overall. Just to demonstrate not everything is black and white.

From the years 1976 to 1983, Argentina went through a military dictatorship, and that is true. It went through a "terrorism of state" phase, and that is also technically true, given that the definition of that is vaguely saying that a non political group took the state's faculties by force. The military made the wrong decisions when in power? Definitely. Were they wrong in taking the government by force? Probably also true. For now, I'm going to explain WHY this happened, given that is quite important and most people omit this part.
Before the government was taken by the military, there was a clandestine war. A war started by the communist/socialist/populist or whatever you want call it groups. They were terrorists. People may admit it or not, but they were. They would kill people, impose their beliefs and cause terror. The people of Argentina were scared and the government was totally inefficient against these clandestine groups, so the people asked the military for help. They were already fighting these groups, but thought that as the government was inefficient, they should govern. Obviously they had the United State's support for obvious Cold War reasons. They had learnt torture methods and all type of stuff to extract information from suspects. 
As they took power, many mistakes were made, but the people weren't opposing it at first. Considering that the fear of Argentina becoming communist was also in the air. Of course, an as history has shown, the military lost the Falkland war and that was the final blow for them. The clandestine terrorist groups became what are now many (and by many, I mean MANY) argentine politicians. As they have had the upper hand for many years, they tried and have succeeded in stripping the military of all dignity, bending the truth completely and making everyone believe "the BAD military came one day all of the sudden, took the government and started causing terrorism of state".
Then people like Hebe de Bonafini (leader of the mothers of plaza de mayo), would use this excuse to do as they pleased (her "missing" son is living perfectly safe and sound in Germany and she is filthy rich thanks to corruption).
The war between A and B was won by A, and now B has all the fault. Simple idiocracy.
The mothers of plaza de mayo, as families of the soldiers who died in the Falkland war, have grown from 300 in 1985 to 27000 in 2016. Go figure (for those who didn't understand, it has grown because more and more people say that their son died in the war, or went missing by the military, to get benefits from the government or money from corruption).
I just want to say that history and the truth is molded on facts. The more we get the better. I just needed to show, once again, that not everything is so black and white.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EXPLOSIVE DUCKS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 12:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I'm 90% sure they would be happier if they had. You could be happy and have no money, but most probably, having money would solve many problems which make you unhappy. Maybe it should be "Money reduces unhappiness in most cases" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Money doesn't buy happiness" is a phrase mostly used by people who have it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That has been the debate for ages </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literal hunger games  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are a noice person  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What motivates you to wake up every morning? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you think "down-load" stands for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 12:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I HAVE SUCCEDED EXCEPTIONALY. IM HUMAN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 12:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm a prison system? Cells altogether </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
