<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3318</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there Grade "B" or "C" eggs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 01:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are there Grade "B" or "C" eggs? If so, what happens to them?  How do you Grade an egg?
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks, somebody is making some money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 03:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at Yongnuo flashes.  They have worked very well for me and are often compared to canon speed lights.  They are not canon speedlights but do a darn good job and have not failed me yet.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does a flea collar work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 03:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does a flea collar work?  How does it work, and is it as powerful on the other end of the pet when it is attached to the neck?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you tell me more, what is the application?  I take a picture of them to see if they are clipping when I process?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Grey card I am buying comes with a black and white card. Where/when/why would I use the black and white cards?  I have a 100% understanding of the Grey card.  Where in my workflow would I use the black and white cards? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a quote from Wayne Gretzky about hockey, I think it is applicable to photography too!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Spray and Pray" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 11:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alcohol a diuretic. A diuretic is any substance that promotes diuresis, that is, the increased production of urine. You drink alcohol (diuretic) because you are thirsty, it makes you pee more. So you drink more alcohol (diuretic) because you are thirsty from peeing. Now you are thirsty because you are peeing more so you drink another one, now your judgment is blued and you keep drinking to quench your thirst and pee more. (vicious cycle) Eventually, your body is running out of fluids, so you get dry mouth and drink more. A hangover occurs (head hurts) because you have no fluids in your body (dehydrated). Dizzy? No fluids = dehydrated. Not to mention the effects of alcohol on a body without liquids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was figuring it was nothing I would ever need. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what do people do with those lasers?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5:How does an engineer decide which end of a ventilation system a fan should be on? (suck or blow) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 13:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 23:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scares me how they are all jumping around with that blade spinning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is there a US versions, UK versions etc....of a Album/CD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is there a US version, UK version and Japan version etc.. of an album.   Why are they different? 

*edit - spelling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 13:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The job of pee is to eliminate waste.  It is colored and stinks from the waste your body produces.  Your pee is clear because you are pumping out liquid which has not had time to absorb waste products. 
Alcohol a diuretic. A diuretic is any substance that promotes diuresis, that is, the increased production of urine.
You drink alcohol (diuretic) because you are thirsty, it makes you pee more.  So you drink more alcohol (diuretic) because you are thirsty from peeing.  Now you are thirsty because you are peeing more so you drink another one, now your judgment is blued and you keep drinking to quench your thirst and pee more. (vicious cycle)   Eventually your body is running out of fluids, so you get dry mouth and drink more. A hang over occurs (head hurts) because you have no fluids in your body (dehydrated).  Dizzy?  No fluids = dehydrated.  Not to mention the effects of alcohol on a body without liquids.

On a side note, when you take all those vitamins and protein drinks and your pee is dark and stinks, those are your vitamins and protein that you paid so much for going down the drain.   You put more in your body then it can process at one time so you pee it out.
Flushing money down the drain

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buy anything to protect your lens!  Rather damage a polarizing filter then the entire lens.  It's like lens insurance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 01:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, you answered my question.  Had no idea there was a Parliamentarian's office.  Sure know their stuff!  Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
