<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3428</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's achieve a power greater than any meme on r/Place. For the Senate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 08:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 23:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are very hard to kill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 08:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have one less then a mile away and I see more movies there than at regular theatres. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is what I meant by fluke, it hit at the right time.  If you look at the sales, each Nintendo console sells less than the last one, except for maybe the virtual boy and Wii.  I think the Switch will handily beat the Wii U, and its success is not based around being a home console but rather an extremely good handheld.  They probably wont get Triple A console games, but if it gets a price drop and gets sequels to games that were on the 3ds, it should do fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These people fail to realise that most people buy dvds which are only 480p. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 09:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some people may see the Switch as releasing a few years after everything else, I see it as releasing a few years before Playstation 5 and Xbox 2, kinda like Dreamcast and Wii U. I also see the Wii as mainly a fluke, it appealed to a casual market that has been greatly diminished by phones and tablets in the last few years.  There are going to be many huge games that Switch will be missing such as Elder Scrolls 6, Red Dead 2, Prey, Shadow of War, Battlefront, Assassins Creed, and Call of Duty  which could definitly hurt perception and sales. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 08:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But, it still had enough power to play games that Gamecube and Xbox had, and also was an inexpensive DVD player. For example, Prince of Persia the Sands of Time came out on all three consoles, while I doubt Battlefront 2 will be released for the Switch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 08:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This actually is a misconception, even though ps2 was less powerfull is still got basically every triple A 3rd party game.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 08:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /uj when did this hatred for 720p even start, 720p still looks really good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or you could just hide her on a different earth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok thanks for the info </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /uj For some reason everyone expects Avatar 2 to make no money, even though this is the guy that made Titanic and Avatar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> God of War Collection on Vita has strange title with Asian symbols. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just purchased God of War Collection and recieved the Vita version for free, but in the title it is called "God of War Collection(and then some Asian symbols)".  Does anyone know why this is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't believe they're making more Pirates of the Caribbean movies.  Can I have a solo Logan Obi-Wan movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 06:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever contacted Sony about it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 06:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you tried downloading it on PS3 and transfering? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 06:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When did you purchase yours? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 06:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was this recently? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 02:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can you download it now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 01:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does it appear in your download list, or is it something you have to access on the PS3? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 00:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was on the physical version of the game, which they discontinued. But currently if you go the to cross buy list in the PSstore it has the Vita version on it, even though it doesn't list it in the desctription of the game like on other cross buy games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know if Playstation All Stars' cross buy is still available if I buy the PS3 version? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 00:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know at one point Playstation All Stars had a cross buy on the PS3 version, just asking if anyone knows if it is still available? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 16:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [r/WhoWouldWin](https://www.reddit.com/r/whowouldwin/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /uj I am a pretty big cod fan but this name could have been way better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 00:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> QUOTABILITY! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /uj but it was basically Star Wars in the Marvel universe

/j Stop making Avatar sequels </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone think a Playstation TV is worth getting if I have a PS4 and PS3? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thinking about getting one for $30 and then puting my 8gb memory card in it when I upgrade my Vita? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Share thier videos wherever you can. Help spread the Love   Respect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MOVEMENT DOESN'T EXIST IN SPACE!!!!!!!!!!!i!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /uj from what I understand he went a anti "sjw" podcast and stated some of his political opinions, listened to some of it and I wouldn't say he is a nazi.  He was wore a nazi uniform in a Star Wars sketch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no
/uj yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did this with a bunch of movies last night
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Artist isn't quotable=sucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /uj Either google or Rotten Tomatoes has a glitch that when you look up unreleased movies it will show a score. Idk why </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 10:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you sure, because Wonder Women's score just dropped to 58%, but no other movies I am looking at have dropped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CULTURAL IMPACT!!I!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 10:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 09:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think they have trailer ratings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know why google shows the Rotten Tomatoes Score for Films that haven't actually been released/reviewed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 09:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 08:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> T H E M A N W H O C A N C L I M B A N Y T H I N G  climbs all over Batgod's chances of winning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
