<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2577</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If it wasn't for today's Google doodle, I wouldn't have know it was Saint George's day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 02:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it's legal in the UK.

In London it's illegal to drink on public transport, perhaps you're thinking of that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would just reply: I'm 38, not that it matters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, is it normally illegal to drink alcohol as a passenger in the USA?
Completely normal in Europe!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I studied History in school all the way up to 17,i.e. just before I went to uni and I was never taught about the zulus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So will I receive actual gold if someone gives me reddit gold

Edit: Wow, thanks for the gold. I feel all fancy being able to access the lounge now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one's I always hate is when I open up and write about an old traumatic experience and despite English not being my first language, I'll make a typo and a few people will just write, learn to type dumbass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 13:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to work for the bank of England, holding a 100 million note I've never been tempted to tear a note in half in my life. (It's A4 sized so the tear would have been sweet).

The fine (technically) for doing so was only 200; would have totally been worth it right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is annoying that it doesn't cover Hounslow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a student who lived in shared accomodation with 50 people in close proximity with paper thin walls it was impossible to gets a minutes peace. Coffee shops were a piece of heaven. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he hadn't have made it I would have been furious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to do a safeguarding children course for work, which said that 99% of teenagers in the UK use the internet. So 13% of the US not using it blows my mind! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the event doesn't end at midnight? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHO IS YOUR MUMMY AND WHAT DOES SHE DO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know thousands of free parking places in central london now. A few in Soho suprised me, was not expecting any there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take a look at any show's overall rating and the flashback one's are always rated massively lower. I wish they never made them, no-one wants them. I'd rather 1 episode less that season than a flashback one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Night man, fighting of the day man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never heard to learn any numbers. I had to learn my father's number my heart in case of emergencies (plus he always picks up).

Apart from that I don't know any numbers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 11:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL arm pit hair is considered disgusting. :S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Withnail and I turned 30 this week. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 23:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That you're a child? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 23:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were all teenagers when they started tbf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They 100% knew, English isn't even my first language and I know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 12:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did anyone else not know that Charlie Murphy was dead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I did this i got all Pinsir's, never been soo angry in my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 12:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A friend of mine was expelled because she created a facebook group called 'does anyone else hate our library's security guard?, which got to 10,000 members in under a week, with thousands of comments of incidents of the security guard being an arsehole. This then made the local news.

Our security guard was an absolute dick tbf.

A month later they told my friend she could come back but that she was banned from all social media.

The one good thing about it though was that the dick security guard actually lightened up and became ok after that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came in to say this, amazed it's on the front page as 99% of people won't get the reference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He starts new life plus where the bullies are that much tougher. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I been to Picasso's house and honestly at lot of his stuff is just pure crap. But he knew that but instead of throwing it away his family would hoarde it because they knew it would be valuable nonetheless.

Honestly some of the sketches were laugh out loud bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 03:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Freedom. If all laws were cancelled tomorrow the murder/theft etc. rates would go through the roof. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone explain the joke please? Why does the op link to 'Breast Implants and Lymphoma: Wheres the Connection?'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's your funky accent messing it up. All the e's in Mercedes sound the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's got to be loads of crimes of real painting being swapped for fake ones.

Did Mr Bean complete the perfect crime? :O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what you're saying is, you love the bitches? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 04:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't have survived my teen years if we share one mind :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 04:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not quite sure how to. How much of the day is your internal voice on for? Is it on for every thought that you have? I think it would drive me mad to have a voice running in my head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 04:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically I just write straight away, there's no internal voice before I type. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 03:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do not, no. I accept that most people do but honestly I feel like it would be a bit of a waste of time as rather than just doing something right away, most people have a lil' talk first and then do the action.

That's how I see it anyhow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 03:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do actually visualise numbers as shapes. I've always struggled to get people to understand this. The larger the equation the larger the landscape I can see. The landscape just sought of forms and I know what the answer is when it's complete. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 02:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What blew my mind on here, was when I learnt that most people have an internal voice.

When my mum mentioned having one at Christmas dinner we all laughed at her because no one else in the family has one and we thought she was crazy. Wasn't till a few months later on here that I saw a thread discussing internal voices and it seems that having one in normal. I still don't quite understand why people are talking in their heads though.

I might get my mum to read a fast text gif, if that seems to removed your internal voice and then she'll be able to understand how the rest of my family think without having a voice in their head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 02:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbf I'm sure Dr Frankenstein was afraid of fire as much as all humans should be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 02:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are literally opposite games.
1 point if he does it vs. 1 point if he doesn't.:-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 02:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is grandma afraid of glasses :S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 00:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He only conquered Britain; at least Grindelwald made a decent attempt at world domination.

Really Voldemort should have released Grindelwald and then they would have been unstoppable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 01:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lil' trick I learnt years ago; if I wasn't actually paying attention I reply, 'of course I'm listening, what did your sister say. (She always gossips with her sister straight away).

From there I say, and do you agree with her advice.

From the replies I get here, I get caught up on the topic I missed and she's none the wiser. Been doing this for over a decade and she still hasn't noticed :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 04:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And now the Russians are looking into all of our post histories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it crazy that americans use pounds and not stones and pounds. That be like talking in cents rather than dollars and cents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We prefer to call it Burma and ourselves Burmese. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 02:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this the 1960s, how is 'spaz' an acceptable word to use :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 00:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WSJ are just gonna say he acted alone and of his own accord and nothing else is going to happen.

Its a disgrace but that's what's going to happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 00:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much of a telling off did you get for typing 'were' instead of where :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about 'no black students' :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's soul destroying food. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 02:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent, now to just wait for the schedules so I can work out who I can go see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 02:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really wish that there had been a native American in the queue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 00:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long does this data joke last? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Colombia landslides kill at least 92 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 18:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello mods, hope you're having fun renaming everything to 'Data'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gilbert Baker, LGBT+ rainbow flag creator, dies aged 65 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 02:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 02:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As everyone is asleep, quickly touch and my family members to ensure their safety. All other family live abroad so they are ok.

About 80% of my friends will be dead though, not to mention 16 million other people :(

Id touch our safe as it has all our family keepsakes and I keep a copy of all our family photos/video on an external hardrive in their, the rest the insurance will cover/has no sentimental value.

They I'd go outside and touch our cars, as it'll be a good hour's drive to exit London with all the debris that will be on the ground. Thankfully my dad drives a 4x4 so that'll come in handy. Filled up the car today so plenty of fuel.

Oh and of course, I'd touch a couple of towels.

If just touching the house saves everyone in it, my oldest friend is a literally 4 minute drive away but if I smash the speed limit (and with the roads being empty at 1am) I could probably just about make it to his house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Spaniard I've never heard of those sweet/drinks but if I saw the pics on the right in my local shop, I'd give them a go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the officer didn't introduce himself as Bond, James Bond. I'm going to be furious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish they'd kept Firth's return a secret and not mention him in the poster.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why everyone hates HR. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pizza place in my town does buy one get **two** free. Large pizza is $7, so that's three large pizza's from $7. Been open almost a decade now. Has to be a money laundering place, as surely they can't be making money.

It also always closes much earlier than the advertised time, on the store front. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My town still has a Blockbuster's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 02:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> La La Land. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 02:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL you can't be black, Mexican and Muslim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No shiny for me either :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 02:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have hypermobility too, whilst sometimes it can hurt (especially when I run too much) it's a massive bonus in the bedroom knowing. Especially with my fingers :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 01:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was interviewed live on a national news channel a few times but the first time I was really nervous, but when I was on I completely forgot the cameras were there and it was just like having a normal conversation. It was quite nice actually, so when they kept calling me back I was thrilled. Not to mention the pay was great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being a latino but living in London my skin is always a lot pastier than my families skin, as I'm not getting the sunlight that my skin requires but when I got back I tan quickly to their level.

My English girlfriend, however burns easily because she isn't pasty in England, that's her natural colouring, whereas mine isn't.

People tend to forget their ethnic origins will determine how tanned they go become. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 14:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to work in a primary school in a poor area of East London. The kids were 10/11 years old and 26/32 kids had never seen the sea/beach. 

The nearest one was less than a hour away, so I organised a school trip to the seaside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 06:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I used to work in a drug store and people buying pregnancy tests would 9/10 say to each other 'which one do I get' 'I dunno just get the expensive one, that has to be the best'.

Our manager increased the price of our cheapest brand to $5 more expensive than the most expensive one and it then became our best seller. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 00:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spaniard here, we kiss all of our women but also the men in our family (including close family friends who are considered family).

We carried this trait over when we invaded the americas, hence why they still do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 14:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dust mites; my only allergy but my god are they lil' bitches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 10:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't see any in my part of west london :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 10:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only found 1 king's rock in 3k spins :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 17:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to work for the government and we were banned from using facebook at work (this was when it was all the rage). Now obviously the ban just applied to on our work computers, at lunch I would have a quick read of my messages on my phone.

The big boss saw me looking at facebook on my phone, whilst I was in the canteen and on my lunch break. She actually started shouting and me and completely lost it when I politely said the ban was for computers and not private phones during lunch. She carried on shouting at me in front of everyone regardless.

When I got back from my lunch break our servers were down, initial reports was a virus, it took 3 days to fix and when it came back what had happened, my boss had gone onto her facebook. on her work computer, just after shouting at me. click on something someone had sent her and it then infected her computer which quickly spread. They not only fired her but they fined her $100,000 (the fine was in our contracts so she couldn't argue against it). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could do with this, 2500 pokstops and only 1 king's rock :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Level 28, I have 3.

Butterfree, got this in the first week on the game coming out.
Tentacool, about two weeks later.
Dragonite, just before the big CP shift.

All eggs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Map doesn't identify that they're shiny, it's not until you click on the normal looking magikarp that they reveal themselves. Bit of a bugger really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bit annoyed, was planning to go to hyde park on tuesday but the weather was terrible, so was gonna go tomorrow, now they're not there. Just loads of vulpix and drowzees (like we don't have enough of those!)

Loads of cyndaquils now, in nearby regents park though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 03:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try being the only white family in an Asian rural area literally everyone for miles knows my name and my life story before I've even met them. It's quite bizarre meeting someone and them saying didn't you play Moses in a school play; um yeah like 10 years ago, how did you know :S

I had one woman today (who I just met) ask me why I now longer have long hair (had long hair about 7 years ago). Who is gossiping about my hair! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never trust tammy two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The girl is mine, motherfucker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any other white people also think 'Maybe I could do this then'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 04:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a guy says his "bro" he could be talking about a friend or his legit brother. If a girl says 'sis' she's almost definitely talking abouther her legit sister. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Free entry for women.

Just try having a place that's free entry for men and women have to pay 20+ to get in. Feminists would have that place closed down within 24 hours.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope you're doing the power rangers marathon. Only 17 days long! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In England a lot of people say non-plussed to mean indifferent.
I've even seen it used this way my a few journalists, who should know better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First thing would be to see what I look like i.e. look in a mirror.

Go get a haircut that I like and take a picture so I can request the same haircut forever.

Go clothes shopping and pick out a few outfits that I like, then my friends who help me shop will now know my clothing style next time I need clothes.

I would also see what my friends and family look like and finally understand some of the jokes that have been said about each others appearance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 15:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got 7 pinsirs in a row back when they were in 10k eggs. What were the chances of that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 14:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't believe there are american parents out there who are anti vaccination :S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I told a friend (older that me but quite naive about sex) about using a certain mint on my girlfriend and that she loves it because of the tingling sensation and that he should try doing that.

He calls me up that same night in hysterics, telling me that the tingle sensation idea didn't work as his girlfriend is in agony as she says she's on fire and what should she do.

I asked him what mint he used (to gauge how 'on fire' she was) and he told me he didn't have any mints so he tried out wasabi!!!!
This was without warning her it was wasabi as she would obviously had said no, you're an idiot.

So I told him that milk would help, so then they poured all the milk they had into a small bowl and she spent the next few hours with the milk bowl held over her clit.

She told me it took her 4 days to recover from that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should have taken a photo where all the wives are nagging the husband and you are just looking like a boss with your young, free and single lifestyle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 02:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I pass the same pok stops at exactly the same time every morning and I have only ever gotten 1 item. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 18:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know soo many sporting events that betting money would be easy.

Couldn't invest in Apple as that is before my time but I could just about make some serious money from bets and invest in facebook. Obviously have to use my dad to do the buying/betting and buy 51% of facebook when it is just starting out.

Then continue to invest in all the major smart phone apps.
So that's unlimited money for my family.

The hard part, really is my friends. I made soo made great friends at school but it be a complete waste of time from an educational point of view up until sixth form. And even if I joined then, the friendship bonds would never be as strong as meeting much younger.

Could go to the same uni but do a different course, so I could still become great friends with my uni mates but then I'd be middle aged mentally, dunno if I'd fancy going wild and partying like an animal.

People saying they date/make out with the missed opportunities. Think about it though you have an adult mind (possible middle aged mind), you wouldn't fancy the teenage girls that you used to anymore (you'd feel downright creepy about doing anything sexual with them).

I'd most likely just focus on learning a few languages, travelling and mastered things that are just hobbies atm. I'm a pretty decent tennis player at the moment, could have gone pro if I didn't need to get a job but if I went back with my experience but a good 15 years of solid practice, I could become the goat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 17:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really wonder what goes through the minds of redditors who re-post front page gifs within 24 hours :S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> European here, you say 120 year old age like that's old :D, tis but a mere boy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know I'm odd but when I lie down in bed I literally fall asleep in the small gap from lying down to my head hitting the pillow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 01:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Two weeks of intensive outdoor exercise simulated the strenuous wartime physical work Britons would likely have to perform.

So you're telling me that a healthy diet and exercise means you live longer! No wonder the Brits kept this a secret... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 01:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are people making pi jokes on 14/03 :S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got my item (kings rock) at 16:25 today (GMT) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happened to reddits clock as I wrote my comment yesterday and not 4 hous ago!

Anyway, I finally found my first item today, king's rock. Probably not see my next item till Christmas! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 13:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great map for when I'm in central London but I live 3 miles west of the western cut off point :(

Would love it if it expanded to cover zone 4 of West London. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
