<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1499</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 09:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the best one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 09:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Knowing this occurred on bike trails I on occasion bike on, it puts some fear in my heart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 08:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Off the top of my head:

1 I think there is a a thread for that on "about this community l" not sure. Either way I won't know too much about that.

2 https://jobs.ca.gov my sister got a job through that.

3 I've grew up here and I am still young so I can't say with an outsiders perspective but: BUS I-80 don't go on it during rush-hour. Summers go into triple digits for a few days, but winters can get cold (not enough to snow though). Bikes are great here. 

Welcome to Sacramento </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 08:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marking this to check it out later  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 08:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understood approximately 30% of that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 08:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Rolls eyes* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 08:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBH Benedict Arnold was getting quite fed up by being screwed by the continental congress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 08:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About #2 SHE CLAIMED FAULT? Wow that's not recommended. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 08:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man I'm clueless I responded seriously before encountering your comment and /u/biondina 's comment  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love to say you won't need it but the divorce rates bring a tear to my eye </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CA doesn't have fees for Public HS, is that... not normal for other states? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I heard the Wehrmacht at times committed atrocities hand in hand with the SS so I don't think that they had qualms working with the SS. Though it kinda depended on the Wehrmacht commanders as some commanders had a more "do what you want to do just don't get in my way" approach but none had serious conflicts with the SS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 10:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> at worst you still get the ticket so you don't have much to lose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 10:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From experiences my close relatives have unfortunately endured, they can persuade people who have been arrested for drug charges  to stand in stings in exchange for lesser charges. But honestly when it happened to my relatives the cops didn't seem trustworthy so maybe a gray area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 10:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also if by chance damages are not completely covered by insurance and you couldn't get damages from the guys who crashed, you can write off some damages in your mother's taxes. At least that was recommended to me when I was in a similar situation but the driver was not hostile. (Also CA) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 10:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thinking would the data on the save file be treated as software? Because if one deletes software a company invested thousands in that would seem like a case. (But yeah the damages of deleting a save file? Minuscule.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 10:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What... the bot what? Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 10:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aye </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same I am full of medica, though now I have mage BSB finally  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 08:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My instructor stored code in word and pasted it into IDLE, he had to replace every " mark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 08:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But don't look at it as "good" or "evil". It's really your perspective and morals that matter, otherwise you will become biased over time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 10:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh even though I agree nazi Germany did horrible things, that does not make their enemies good people. US servicemen executed SS officers. US took few Jap POW (there is jap code of honor involved), due to world politics US dropped A-bombs, Russia, shoot where do I start, just look up rape of Berlin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 10:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 10:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 10:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While it's not a bad idea to plan for worst scenario it feels bad to jump to worst scenario. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 10:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are all accounts with flairs lawyers? Because if it is that's cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 10:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy wow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 10:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are the perks of British citizenship? (Other than what US citizenship will give) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 09:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amtrack the train company? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 09:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In strange situations many otherwise normal events are made terrifying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 07:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rome total war </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 07:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And it would have probably still wouldn't have prevented war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 07:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno about good vs evil, on the eastern and pacific front (especially the eastern) it just looked like vengeful massacres. Screw it most of WW2 was inexcusable and just screwed up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 07:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your work good sir </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 07:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it wasn't like WW2 rape of Berlin when there was a nasty vengeance and hatred streak going on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 07:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marking this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 07:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is this the only question answered  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 07:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rome could do more but maybe that's because it was warlike and organized  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 09:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1 second the boss deals 800 dmg, the next second 2800 dmg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried to be vague  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Even our own blood... just not my sisters blood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think so, death threats were posted by fringe alt-rights too many times. Such as death threats against victims and family of sandy hook, and in one case murder. Why? Something along the lines of sandy hook is a conspiracy back Obama and democrats to enact gun control laws. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 10:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is one hell of a post I'll get back to you later either tomorrow or more likely the weekend with my verdict.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 10:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best way to individually combat this is cite your sources and call into question other sources that appear to be untrustworthy. Some sources you won't need to state as untrustworthy or not such as a CDC (center for disease control) article on the flu as they have a reputation to uphold, direct accountability, and low to non-existent motive to mislead. 

Others such as a CNN report on republicans or a Fox report on democrats will need to be independently researched, before sharing or accepting as truth.

Edit: minor grammar: democratic changed to democrats; non-motive changed to non-existent motive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 10:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey it works on both sides of an election some that appear blatant lies to me are accepted as canon to others. One particular one I heard was "Hillary absolutely enjoyed ordering killings and that she had the most evil smirk" and that was said to me by my father, he believes it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 10:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And my point is it shouldn't come as a surprise that a man running for office be covered in controversy, a spotless man would cause me to worry more. (Just rereading some of the past elections and why do people want tabloid magazines when such things were printed in national newspapers in the past. They could just read a history book on the past elections) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 10:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That these articles that wrote ill of Trump, only surfaced during the election, my response is once someone runs for office a lot more people have a lot more incentive to find and Air the dirty laundry of the person running, look on Hillary and emails, Libya; this is not just today's Trump and Hillary. Obama and birth certificates and speculation and him being Muslim. JFK and being catholic. (Really the earlier you go the more outrageous the claims are, Jackson the 'bride stealer' comes to mind) Anyone running for office, especially running for a high office like POTUS, will have a dreadful amount of scrutiny on them.

Edit: removed the first sentence as it was no longer needed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 09:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is one hell of a ship, I can see a comedy out of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 09:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i am sorry if I am coming across as rude but could you rephrase or edit your first paragraph? I am having trouble understanding it clearly and I hope to avoid misunderstandings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 09:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't stretch figures, it's a trait of Trump, don't be Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 09:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only tried to find information about the donations to aids charities but I couldn't find anything viable after a 8 min search, could you maybe link your claims? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 09:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is evidence to you? i understand there is the 5th amendment that renders confessions obtained under duress void, but I don't think when they said/wrote/published/endorsed/ect those things that anyone had a gun to their head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 09:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I posted my address and went on a vegan subreddit to say eating meat is much better than veggies I wouldn't have to fear for my safety. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 09:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude chill that racism, this isn't the 18th century. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 09:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Impersonation spot on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 08:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well while in the end he was a traitor, I heard Benedict was one fine general before he had enough of the continental congress screwing him and not recognizing his achievements.

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Benedict_Arnold

He even tried to resign his commission to the continental congress a few times in disgust but was refused even that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 08:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do note that due to Finland the USSR reorganized its military to be much more effective  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 07:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I thought it was ok overall, minus the pot smokers but I never really heard anything too violent minus an incident where a mentally unstable person blew it a year or 2 ago and wound up killing a relative. But do you think I'm too deep in rose colored glasses or bc I live near the border with the north. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do these things work? Some programmer codes in an Easter egg? Or a logic error turns into a feature? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah I meant quality of neighborhood. Sorry. Thanks in advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's pretty sweet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tapioca express is somewhat better than jamba, has its own unique-ish thing, and is 3-4 bucks for a smoothie  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would you consider south natomas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I couldn't do avoidance once and now I'm dealing with the aftermath of a 10 car accident. (Some guy 4-6 cars behind me started the dominos of cars) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not like the car behind you is going to bail you at freeway speeds, he will move you but perhaps not much more than 6 ft? (This is under the assumption that he hits you while he is going 35 and he is not driving a substantially bigger car, I.e. Smart car hit by hummer) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> II they killed the emperor of the largest empire that if let be would have developed the world at a faster pace.

X resolved the problem of a huge ball of destruction so capital could be centralized easier, and not randomly destroyed, I think that is a bigger plus than the murderof a few prominent figures (sucide in the case of Mika) and downfall of the most influential organization known as yevon.

XII prevents a total war so I think they did well in preventing a whole lot of loss, and cleared a few hunts.

Tactics (WotL) other then preventing luvici, they indirectly enabled a machiavellian-like man become king (perhaps good for the economy?) but on the other hand they did increase the length of a major war by flooding a battlefield. And destroyed a revolution that would have redistribute wealth to reduce inequality thus bettering the economy (caused the leader to become a demon later on).
And caused chaos by killing quite a few influential figures, but that I think was for the better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hard to choose </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It immersed you from the get-go </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It did its function as an exposition so well, it covered the world and made it much more immersive. (And the battles between airships? That was pretty amazing) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have it on IOS (WotL) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The main boss (not the super boss) isn't exactly evil, though at first you will be inclined to think so, and at the end you agree with him somewhat and feel bad for fighting him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The world was fleshed out and really immersive  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 10:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always hear about certified mail, how expensive is it? (In case I wish to sell an IPhone via internet and want proof the purchaser received it) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 10:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly from what I hear 'the wheels of justice grind finely' at least in the US. Some of the maximum sentences are pretty ridiculous, and most of the US prison system is focused much more on the punishment side rather than rehabilitation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 09:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well even with acceleration and deceleration, using the mean value theorem (MVT) they could theoretically bag you for speeding if you were.

(IE speed limit is 60, you drive 60 miles in 50 minutes. MVT states you were above 60 at least twice,) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 09:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine has been colonized and dominated by Bermuda grass, very drought resistant. Pity I am likely mildly allergic to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 09:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Evergreens can be a pain in their own way though, they constantly shed branches and twigs, not a large amount, but large enough for you to have to clean every week. Also if you or a neighbor have allergies you may have a problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 09:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone tell me the resolution? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 07:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly I thought there was a 50% chance a picture of a cannon would be posted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the actual cannon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can get jntrouble with the law and PETA, and this guys are like the church of Scientology when they put you into their scopes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A bundle of needles will be your loot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did it but it takes a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of curiosity why didn't he instead mothball the fleet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 10:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did they ever state the name of Yuna's mother, or Tidus's mother? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 10:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet, when is it out again? Also will the bosses and mobs (I hope) get buffed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 10:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't john snow ignored for a good while? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 09:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guilty of that in MP, but is worked out in the end after a 15+ min clown feista of confused characters. (160 difficulty and all lv 99 characters) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 03:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that guy who started it is screwed (on the bright side 1 driver pulled out so now only 8 drivers involved) also if I had full coverage I would not have to deal with this as my insurance would be dealing with this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love smugly saying 'I got OK gauntlets off banner, no worries maybe it will happen to you' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 10:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Confusion everywhere  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 09:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got the OK BSB as an off-banner draw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 09:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh dam, doing it with a physical team was hell, affliction break probably kept us afloat. Brought lenna BSB just to see how it was in MP and by chance the reraise helped. But yeah don't do physical it takes way too long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 08:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dam yeah... I just might try it, it can't be worse then Tactics DK grinding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 08:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glaudios (sp) dagger, Dustia, katana from werewoofs, ZODIAC SPEAR (if done right and with zone out exploit) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 08:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will it work on IOS? And if it does tell me how </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 08:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shame that guy one hits bosses (To be fair I like to grind to lv60-70 chapter 1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 08:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, you couldn't level up to 99 over a night, on an emulator running at 3x speed for ~6 hours I only got them to ~70. (3x but in occasionally became slower if PC was taxed

A better grind spot would be Dustia (btw will that be in the zodiac age?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 08:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly a while back I did not know that until I saw the prequel(?) because I was confused on what people meant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 07:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FF tactics war of the lions will keep you entertained for months. It's story is sweet, and it's quite customizable giving it high replay value. Only thing you might not like is it's tactics, much more emphasis on strategy rather than mashing attack. (Though if you go nuts and grind like I do and have triple the level than your opponent...) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 07:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man and I just beat the game. It's has great dialogue, great music, and in my opinion great gameplay (though I wish the bosses were higher level, my lv 70 characters just pubstomped the final 4 battles like nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
