<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3191</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If things were as bad as you are saying defaults would be skyrocketing and/or the housing market would be like it was before 2008 where prices were skyrocketing everywhere. Yes I know california real estate is crazy. I live in northern virginia in the 2nd wealthiest county in the country. My house is worth less than it did at the height of the bubble. The bubble burst 9 years ago. If we were in a bubble my house value would be skyrocketing again not getting back to previous highs 10 years earlier and in a very wealthy location. 

Sub prime loans were valuable because the banks can sell them as mortgage backed securities. They didnt want to hold on to those shit mortgages. Dodd-Frank added regulation on this. Its not as bad as it was. 

Its not fixed with underwriting, its constrained with regulation. Its not perfect, but its better. As long as trump cant deregulate the shit out of it. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Banks are less likely to give loans to people who cant repay them. That is what caused the 2008 financial crises. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a kids movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AMA with a cop who wrks for a speed trap town. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They need to pass a law where you cant give multiple speeding tickets due to speed changes. I didnt even know this was legal. If someone ticketed me for that, I would hire a PI to tail the mayor 24x7 and put all his whereabouts on the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a competitor to google pay backed by verizon and ATT. They named their prodct ISIS. Googlw bought them out, shut it down, fired everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its why he threw a tantrum and threatened to shut down the government.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There isnt. If there was voter turnout would go up. People who are interested just yap more online.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop being a wimp. This isnt chilling. This is trump being a huckster and a dumbass. Start calling trump a fool and can the stupid, i need my teddy bear routine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So can I put a civil war plaque in my yard to increase property values? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont know how they will change how you handle your taxes. For a small llc you do your txes on your regular tax form and profit is treated like 1099 income. 

If you have an S Corporation or an LlC that you opt to be taxed like an S Corporation, you also fill out a corporate tax form and send that in. You dont pay taxes against this. Its just where you put your revenues and expenses. I use turbo tax business to do this. It gives you a profit or loss. You put that number on your regular returns. I again do this with the turbo tax personal. So I need 2 versions of turbotax. Fir an S corp you also pay yourself a regular w-2 salary. That income is put on your tax form as regular taxes just like if you had a regular employer. The profit/loss after that is put on the form differently. The tax difference being that any profit above w-2 income does not have social security or medicare tax. 

I dont know how they would change the tax forms. The simplest is you keep the pass through entity the same and the money that goes on your regular tax form as profit is taxed at 15%. 

You will see executives in every corporation create business to lower their taxes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Election is over. Russian trolls are gone. So less downvotes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is an official cataclysm dda site. Google it or it might be on the side bar. Im using an ipad app so I cant see the sidebar. There is a forum button. There is a set of forums. One is for releases. There is a long post i. There called whats new new or something like that.

Im on an ipad. Im not gonna go get the links, but you can find it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Fox, breitbart wont challenge him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dickerson will never get another interview. Every reporter who does this will be cut off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The president isnt nuts. He is an idiot who doesnt know what he is doing. He acts like alot of us do when we talk about politics. One day he wants to bomb north korea, the next day a voice in his head tells him to be diplomatic and say nice things about Kim Jong Un. He thinks this makes him clever. He is an idiot. 

There is a reason why president temper what the fuck they say and have teams review speeches. Its cause if the president farts, its news. You cant wing it. 

I say lots of shit to people I know about politics. No one is listening. Presidents know enough to temper what they say. 

He is also fucking lazy. This dumbshit should be reading foreign policies briefings every night and have a set a questions the next day. They can be tough questions and should, but instead dumbshit watches cable news. Hell he should require staff to have briefings for him while he eats dinner to help him come up to speed. 

The moron doesnt even know what is in the healthcare legislstion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is blowing off his mouth. Republicans have to be crazy to want a shut down. They were blamed last time and now they control everything.

We should respond by organizing protests of trumps business and say the Trump organization needs a good shutdown.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a huge new features thread on the main forums.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he retires there will be a push to overturn roe v. Wade that will likely succeed unless John Roberts switches sides like he did with Obamacare. I dont know if they will take up gay marriage since the court usually waits atleast 20 years to reverse a decision. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He averaged less than 4 yardsa carry. Its not like this is a huge signing. Is he a good pass blocker? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone have context on what they are doing wirh a big cat at what looks like a public pool. Instead of posting a gif, I wish people would post the source.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sarah Palin implied she was harrassed at Fox, but wouldnt come out and say it. She has a big mouth, if she is so ingrained in right wing culture that she wont say it, they are screwed. I am on an ipad, so pasting a link to her recent CNN interview is a pain. Google it. She clearly implies she got harassed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone explain the difference between a spread offense and what they do in the pros? Pro teams frequently go 4 and 5 wide receivers and spread it out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My companies policy for layoffs is 1 week per year with the company. Minimum 2 weeks, maximum 10 weeks. I dont feel sorry for Wade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I expect DJ fluker to take Harts stsrting job. Fluker though not very good at tackle was graded in the 70s 2 years ago which is much better than Harts 40 something ( you dont belong in the league at that). Fluker is far inferior to John Jerry at guard who is also mediocre. 

Of course he will say they will improve. Who says my guys suck. Even if Hart does improve alot, that improvement would likely mean he still sucks.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At 234 lbs isnt that small to block as a TE? He would have to put on 10-15 pounds to be an effective blocker. If he does that he will slow. The other issue at 234 lbs is getting off the line from a down position. At his size linebackers can bump him and that is all it takes to disrupt a pattern. NFL LBs and DEs are alot bigger than in college.

I think one of two things will happen.

1. If he turns out to be a really good receiver they will transition him more to a big WR and he will move to the outside. Not this year as long as Brandon Marshall is healthy. They will stand him up more and spread him out more to get him a free release. If he does this they might have him lose a little wait to improve his speed. 

2. They will have him bulk up some so he can block. He will lose some speed, but to be a full time TE you gotta block and you gotta be able to get off the line from a down position. He could still be a good receiver matching up on LBs and safeties, but he would lose a step if he added bulk. 


This assumes he is good and not yet another tweener who doesnt have a pro position. I hope the scouting is good on him. This year expect them to have him stay the same size and have him focus on the pro game and see how he does.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The conservatives are from rock solid republican districts. They will not face a serious democratic challenge. The moderates tend to be from swing districts and will face a serious democratic challenge. From a keep republicans in the majority standpoint, conservatives compromising have less risk then moderates. Now some conservatives may face a primary challenge, but that isnt as dangerous as someone in a swing district facing a tough democrat. Incumbents rarely lose primary challenges. There was one in 2014 in virginia, but we remember it because it was rare. I live near there. He lost more because he was an asshole who didnt go back to his district enough than because he wasnt conservative enough even though the challenge was from the right. He seriously blew off the district and didnt see constituents. Guy was an idiot. 

Conservatives should be able to sell, if I dont compromise we are stuck with Obamacare permanently and we will likely lose the house. They have to hold out fir a while. Maybe later in the year they can compromise?

If they dont they wont get anything. I wonder if Trump would work with democrats after that to reform Obamacare instead? Two issues with that. Trump is a lying prick. So democrats have no incentive to work with him and compromise other than Obamacare needs reform. I want it to stay, but it needs to be changed. Its a good first step. Trump would have to go pretty far left to get enough democrats and republicans on board to do this. 

He could then take credit for being a good compromiser. I think his base rural poor supporters are not conservatives. They need the healthcare. Alot dont get the medicaid benefits from Obamacare because they are in red states so they dint know what they are missing. 

I am really curious how Trump will respond if he cant get conservatives to compromise by early next year. If Trump cant reform healthcare there will be a massive democratic pickup in 2018. If he compromises, democrats will still pick up seats, but republicans in swing districts can say they voted to fix Obamacare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> U of Virginia has no problem getting applicants. Its considered one of, if not, the best state university in the country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump style response </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kim dong long </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And one next to russia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was a college level math class? You went in debt for this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They will send him to Guantanamo Bay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giants have had consistent QB for 30 of the last 35 years. Not worried </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cowboys.

3 f their 4 starting DBs gone. Starting DT gone. RG and RT gone. Ok they can run left, but can they pass block on the right? The nfc east is playing the afc west this year and they have the giants twice. If they can block can they score enough points to win with that secondary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If JJ Watts is the old jj watts, They have a better shot. Big if. Bigger if is if the houston coaches are smart enough to not put him out there until they are absolutely sure he is healthy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They traded for Marshall Faulk with a second round pick. Drafted Tory Holt in the first round. Isaac Bruce was injured in 1998. Kurt Warner became the starting QB when Trent Green went down. 4 future HoFers join your offense in one year. Orlando Pace was the best tackle in football.

Holt, Bruce, and Pace will all make the HoF.

It was the perfect storm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What percentage of southerners owned slaves? I remember always hearing its a small percentage. How come poor whites who didnt own slaves were not resentful? You dont have to hire them if you have slaves.

Also, the plantations still existed after slavery right? The plantation owners used former slaves as sharecroppers. How profitable was that relative to slavery? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ron Howard convincing women to put out for science </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is the sky blue? I dont get it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the oil refinery rate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it said 1 coal to 4 oil, but it doesnt show after you build it. Asking because if you get 4x oil from coal i should use oil  in my refineries </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do bears sleep the entire time they are hybernating or are they partially awake? I can understanding fattening up for hybernation, but how do they go without water? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically he is a cuck for taking the cash. Guy got a huge contract. I dont feel sorry for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was a server when I was younger. Taxes for servers are based on how much they sell. The restaurants report it to the government. I think its 8% of sales is considered taxable income.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These plans cost a fortune. We have a huge deficit and poor people need healthcare.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 05:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends how long ago you read the books </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 04:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bible. Has magic, creation mythos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 04:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sanderson nerfed the One Power in a Memory of Light. It was annoying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 04:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wear reading glasses, so I need good lighting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 04:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you post her sub? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 03:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Orcas hunt those things </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Page numbers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alternative uber payment method? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Whaley was the coffee boy for the draft? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An Orangutang just got elected president of the US. Bill Mahr show Trumps geneology gits back to Bozo at the Bronx zoo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Urban Meyer wins so much. people are going Mr Urban please stop winning Not so much for Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously not a Kentucky game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Former giants pro bowl guard Chris Snee is the son in law f Tom Coughlin. When Coughlin would fine him for not being early enough for a meeting he would go home and hate fuck his wife. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a record for most picks modulus 7.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hardly the first </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you like Mel Kiper? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 09:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 09:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roger Goodell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 09:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Victor Cruz 2.0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 09:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giants need cheerleaders. Never had them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 09:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trubisky will be a bust. Karma doesnt allow the bears to have good qb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 09:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> F for all mock drafts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 08:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of them are filler </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 08:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its ok Jay, I wanted to play QB for the Giants. I was told if I didnt leave the premises I would get arrested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 08:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is an asteroid coming in a few years. We cant stop it. The human race will go extinct.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 05:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With trumps coming tax cut he cam get off food stamps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 05:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just like people commuting to work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 05:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you have state run media and no free press that tends to happen. When the internet in censored it tends to happen. Russia doesnt have a history of democracy or a free press. Before the Soviet Union, they had an absolute monarch. Russia disnt even free the serfs until the late 1800s. Serfdom was essentially a replacement for slavery in europe. Google what serfdom is if you dont know.

This is why Trump has a gay butt crush on Putin. Its why Trump wants Putins cock in his mouth so bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He will sit for 3 years. If the giants think he can play, looks like they wont resign Eli after 2019 even if Eli doesnt want to retire. They will want to see him in year 4 before picking up his 5th year option. So if eli stays healthy... At his age you never know, we have 48 more rrgular season games with Eli.

If he sucks, then if Eli is still healthy and wants to play he will be back for 2020. Assuming trump doesnt surrender to Russia and we become a Russian overseas colony. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rotary phone too grandpa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 01:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did he tear it? Did he do a leaping high five when he got drafted? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apparently the giants still think shit tackles = win? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Starting DEs play too many snaps. Giants need a rotation. More snaps means more beat up and more chance for injury. I hope the backups step this year and we can get a rotation. The lack of rotation was likely also due to an inability to score. So the defense had to play lights out to win. Hopefully they can score more points. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cowboys cheerleaders </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to the legislators houses </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Browns fans are the scientologists of he nfl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With all the smog its safer to stay inside and watch tv </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 03:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Easy nfl is most money </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> JonesGate. Some brave patriot needs to show up locked and loaded at his house to break up his child molestation ring </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see no new features. Clickie zoo appears to be a straight up rip off of incremental zoo that adds pay to win elements. Everyone of this guys posts on all forums are about clickie zoo. This is onviously the developer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 06:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The shitty ones yes. The good ones are the most valuable players in the league </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many first round picks do you think will be busts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 06:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its typically about half.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 05:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have no idea if this pick s a good weapon until we see him on the field. Half of all first round picks are busts. The over reaction to draft picks before they get on the field... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These guys should just shut up. They have not done anything in the league yet. These kids sound like idiots. Im confident the veterans are their nee teams will agree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Teams try to trade for guys all the time im willing to bet 95% of trade discussions fall through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its only a little over a year old. He has a subreddit too, but not real active </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clinton tried this and the supreme court said presidents dont get immunity. The precedent is set. He has no chance with this. Its just a delaying tactic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The dust they inhale living in their parents basements </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do they have to replace the 2 linemen they lost? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coughlin got his qb first when he was in jacksonville last time and in New York. Its how he roles. Bortles is shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He s coming off 2 straight back surgeries. Lets see if he can still play. Lets see if the Houston front office are not dumbshits and bring him back too soon like last year. If I was in Houston, I would have him spend 6 weeks on PUP just to be safe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mark Sanchez </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok poll. How wrong will this be? I say 70% wrong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giants passed on reggie white and won 2 superbowls in the next 6 years with 4, 10 win seasons </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are any of jacksonvilles picks good? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If i worked for cleveland, id make a wager through a 3rd party when i knew the selection </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cleopatra lived closer in time to us than she did to the building of the pyramids </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He finds it hard to negotiate with people who know what the fuck they are talking about. He doesnt fucking know anything and he is a lazy prick. He doesnt read anything. Obama and Bush were voracious readers. They read vast numbers of books. They also read fucking briefing material.

If you are an entry level president, this dipshit should be getting extra briefings and reading in the evening to ramp the fuck up. World leaders think he is a dumbass. Too lazy to learn the details.

This fool should be getting briefings on technical details every night with reviews. The man is a lazy sack of shit.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the penalty on a former US military person who accepts payments from a foreign government? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The reporting on the Michael Flynn foreign payments has been choppy and not very detailed. The best I found is the Washington Post article I am linking below. This is a combination question/commentary for discussion.

The implication of the article is that this is a civil and not criminal issue. The article mentions that a debt collector may come after him for the money he was paid by Russia.This isn't clear, but a debt collector cannot impose fines. Only a court can. So it sounds like the worst that can happen is that Flynn will lose the money he was paid. Anyone else know more? Seriously really weak reporting. They should lay out the penalties better.

This is a totally separate issue from Flynn lying on his security clearance form. I have filled security clearance applications before. That is a felony and that would involve the Justice department. This question is strictly about the defense department restricting payments from foreign powers to former US military. 

If the only penalty for this is we seize your money, there is no reason to comply. Ignore it. Try to get away with it. Worst case government makes you give them the money. Take the cash, put it in a bond. At worst you get some interest. Given that this only came out because he was National Security Advisor, it makes me wonder whether many other former military take these payments.

Mods: please keep the discussion on the topic of the military going after someones momey. The penalties for lying on a security clearance form can be easily googled. 

https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/checkpoint/wp/2017/04/27/top-pentagon-watchdog-launches-investigation-into-money-that-mike-flynn-received-from-foreign-groups/?hpid=hp_rhp-top-table-main_flynn-1105a%3Ahomepage%2Fstory utm_term=.f613946d18b5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never saw it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 90% of the native americans died of disease brought by europeans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He didnt do it himself. It was the army his father Phillip created. The greeks had radically superior technology, training and tactics. Persians had soldiers armed with shields made of Wicker. What should amaze you is that 150 years earlier Persia invaded greece and got their ass whooped by a much smaller, but much better trained, and technologically superior Greeks.

The army Alexander had crushed the rest of Greece because it was technologically and tactcally superior. The persians had the same shit inferior army 150 years later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 50 million people died of the flu in 1919 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was this due to the ice age? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You dont die immediately from beheading. There is still blood flowing to the brain. There are stories of eyes moving when they hold up the head. Death by firing squad is more humane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did so many people die? Was it famine and disease? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get Ajit Pais home address and send them to his house </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The movie was shit and butchered the book. The book was a really cool spin on the zombie genre. Nothing like the shitty movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isaac Arthur youtube channel. Great hard SF channel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is a big fat slab. Put up pictures of what he would look like with his shirt off and pierce his nipples. Put a tattoo that says Vlads Whore on his chest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pictures of you shitting yourself in a diaper </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are in seattle, you can get one of those umpteen fired Amaholes to jerk you off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He forgot his name too and how to pee standing up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a crime. If he really did this, i expect him to be charged </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder what Joe Thomas would get now that his memory is going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good time to borrow momey from joe. Then tell him you already paid him back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who cares? The TV show is going to give us the ending. GRRM will do it( if he actually writes it) differently, but the major plot points like Tower of Joy, Hodor, etc... Are put out by the TV show. I do t care anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He will tell us when its totally done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a link to a blog post about going to a con. The title is lying or has the wrong link </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What us his youtube channel. I cant get to it from an embedded youtube video </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are youtube videos about this. It was the only reason he massacred the templars.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump winning so much we beg him to stop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happiness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Phil simms is the elvis grbac of broadcasting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The nfl analysts get turned over all the time. Its not like Dilfer is going to be giving handjobs on the subway for rent money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I worked on a defense department travel application. I was told that DoD has this contract with all airlines they use. They never get bumped. Its not a one time fee, the ticket prices are a little higher.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are lying. Its never as many as they say </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trumps a scientologist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have too many. Its better when there are less with more time to speak </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With republicans controlling everything they could change the laws on how money is distributed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They will last until the Russia investigation blows over. They hope it will blow over. No coincidence this comes out the day after the Michael Flynn is going to prison.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stockpile lots of power runes, gold runes, invulnerability runes, and dungeon keys. These way you can get your power up faster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The easiest way to beat the doomstone is to save e 2 dungeon keys. Use the dungeons to get your power way up, then hit him again. I still needed invulnerability runes, but the fight is over in 2 minutes. I also saved alot of bonus power runes for these dungeons and just before I kill the boss I restart repeatedly. 40 minute grind leads too 100x higher power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do mods work with .15? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or do they all have to be redone to work with them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So e youtubers who do science shows should jump on this for free publicity and bait these idiots into fining them. Easy way to get views. I wouldnt pay it if they fined me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We should troll people and make a stickied thread. Martin and Rothfuss latest updates </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tiki too... Oh yeah dumb shit retired a year to soon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giants have more superbowl wins in the last 20 years than the cowboys have playoff wins. Draft away </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how many mementos Matt Millen has </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 02:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found the paid russian troll </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 02:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never, ever invest in a pass through entity. You gotta b crazy to do that. You write check. Owner doesnt spend any momwy. Money flows to owners pocket.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 02:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no official entity called a partnership. I listed 2 entities. S Corporation and an LLC. I think those are the only 2 pass through entities. Any type of company can be a partnership.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
