<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2159</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MLG pro captain builds for pub stomping (totally legit, most people pay money to see these) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 03:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 21:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. The way I see it, if you're willing to quit the game because T6 isn't as fun as it once was, you're just looking for an excuse to stop playing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 16:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's just mean </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 15:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They didn't ruin the perfect sweet spot, they just moved it to T7. Sometimes you have to adapt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 23:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does that person go deaf after 3 salvos? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 23:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Getting 3k+ base XP with the current ecosystem is insane. Well done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 23:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thatt Izyaslav is probably on maximum tilt now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Beauty of Permanent Death - BoukenJima </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 20:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 23:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn what am i supposed to do with all this knowledge  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 20:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well pretty much. It's all about playing to the strengths as I've been saying. Hindenburgs 8.8 second reload is insane at mid range. Zao has a long reload and low HP so it can't fight where Hindenburg can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 20:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree with him so I dislike him? This mindset is dangerous. He's a great commentator and I watch most of his videos. Doesn't mean he can't be wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 18:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, zao is good at HE spam but the HP pool and maneuverability don't serve it well in the constant back and forth of mid range engagements. Zao stays at range and pops in and out when safe. Hindenburg gets in there and doesn't stop firing.

And of course the hydro is way better than zao hydro.

You say it cannot rely on a single player but wouldn't my 78% solo winrate lead you to believe otherwise?

All I see is people trying to play Hindenburg a certain way and that way not being successful. I find a new way to play it and it's very successful but flamu gets the final word, of course. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hindenburg punishing broadsides is a single strength, not the only one. I have over 100 games in Hindenburg and fired probably 90% HE, using the powerful AP situationally as it was intended. It's one of my best ships with like 78% winrate and 130k average damage (solo stats) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 15:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the AP is reliable from all angles then why would you even need "situational" HE?

No, balance works the opposite and you have claimed to like this on other ships before. Where balance is polarizing and something is really good at times and then countered at times. 

Hindenburg AP on a good broadside is fucking insane dps and then this drops significantly when they angle because that's balanced. The HE is still plenty effective on an 8.8 second reload. 

You keep running the range mod and then having 95% of your engagements (sometimes more) within the standard range. It's completely silly. The range mod is worth it over the reload because you can hope to land a couple shells on a BB at the start of a match? 

Hindenburg has excellent reload, steering (with mod 3), turret traverse and the turtleback makes you hard to citadel especially through the nose or aft. Play to the strengths and you will get results.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 00:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grounded doesn't get shivs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 23:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The issue with ocean is a only get to play it once a month :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 00:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but their puny guns don't hurt your armor and your guns do 20k damage every time guaranteed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 20:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *everything except yamato* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 18:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In his defense, from that distance you should have enough time to do some WASD if you're paying attention.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 18:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Getv used to it. Montana one shots everything  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 07:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not really the game or the price's fault though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 15:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You still fully control where you aim with camera lock though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 17:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Why am I so cold?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 05:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RPF is kind of a buff and a nerf to DDs as I imagine more DDs will run it than anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 21:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With this new tree though, every cruiser will easily have CE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 02:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use expert loader on every T7+ CA that I have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 02:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of that and DDs are still hugely influential.

I'm not saying they need to be further nerfed or anything, but it's just worth pointing out that DDs are still not objectively shit after a dozen counters get put into the game. IJN DDs are in a weird place, some of them are good though, but overall DDs are still functionally carrying games as ever. 

The word is still out on whether the German DDs are good though. High tier ones look solid on first impression.

It's also worth pointing out that cruisers get some better tools at dealing with BBs with these skills so that'll also help keep the BB pop down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 23:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - Developer makes post asking people to wait and see and stop raging at theorized results.
- People fill the comment section raging about theoretical results.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 16:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know about taking everything. I remember looking at the leaked skill tree before and theorizing several different builds for many ships. There didn't seem to be a one size fits all anymore.

Surr, some builds will probably still be standard for some ships, but I never saw a situation where it was clear 100% what build to take. There's plenty of combinations now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 23:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I am incredibly unhappy with my Saipan purchase. There should be a system in place where you can't buy a CV premium until you have matches played in CV, that way drunk idiots like myself don't lose $40 to the thought process "how hard can it be, tho?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 23:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That generally only lasts until their superstructure gets saturated, but HE is still going to be more consistent at doing superstructure damage. At least vs BBs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 22:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The AP is very good, but still more situational than HE.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 22:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe one day I'll get a beard for christmas... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 21:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should be using HE all the time in Moskva.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 21:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Montana and Moskva.

Moskva is the best at playing like a BB and Montana is the best at playing like a cruiser. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 16:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, 1790 is real close to super unicum as well. 

You gonna share some of that magic juice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 19:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is still an extremely healthy amount of players for an NA game. The EU server also pulls from so many different places. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 19:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No idea, but the NA numbers have been steadily increasing since release. Previously highest I've seen was 17k </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 17:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gives me conniptions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 16:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell, I'm pretty sure this is more players still than both COD and Titanfall on NA put together.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 16:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realize I may not have used the word "suck" appropriately. I don't mean that low tier ships are supposed to be terrible and that's okay, I mean they more have limitations to their playstyles. The Japanese cruisers, for instance don't come into their own until their stealth starts being good. 

I haven't played the KM DDs yet, so I am speaking out of my ass a bit, but they seem more opportunistic than most DDs. They are a jack of all trades, master of none. Drive around more cautiously and when you need your guns, you have a good choice. When you need your torps, you have a good option. Playing them like straight up gunboats may not be fair until the guns get better at higher tiers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 16:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Low tier ships usually don't have their playstyles fully realized yet, which is why most people enjoy higher tiers for the better balance.

So all this complaining about the low tier German DDs being terrible is just silly imo. Not only do most low tier ships suck, that doesn't mean the rest of the line is bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 15:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I play this game very well imo.

https://na.warships.today/player/1001953699/subject2159 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 14:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One day I'm going to have a 50k captain XP game. Maybe it is now my time... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 12:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blowing smoke again, I see.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WoWs NA has almost 18k players online right now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 03:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/Tra2GoR.jpg

This is the most players I've ever seen online and it's not even the weekend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 02:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I can't speak for the Yorck as I wasn't around for the German cruisers when they dropped. But I don't see how that compares, tbh. All I'm saying here is based off my knowledge of this game and this community. 

Mostly being: 

- It's barely been a day

- People are whining about low tiers

- Most people are potatoes


These 3 facts are leading me to believe we should all take a fuckin chill pill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 02:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There's plenty of things you can do about it

Oh boy you sure elaborated on that one.

You've got me floored with all this factual support. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 02:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wat.

If it's late game and it's you vs a stealth firing DD, what do you do? There's literally zero counter to it which is why people have always wanted it removed.

Now all of a sudden things change.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 22:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they transfer you to NA they don't retain you as a customer at all. They have no reason to transfer you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 21:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he's asking why it's not, to which the answer is because the game is meant to be fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 20:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have shit smoke because of hydro so they can't sit in smoke all day with hydro up. And the plan is to remove stealth firing from all ships. Calm yourself of overreaction and learn to see things in a different light. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 20:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well don't fire if you risk so many ships giving return fire.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 20:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It should go down by 1.9km and stealth firing needed nerfed anyway. Shouldn't be a valid mechanic and wargaming are pushing it out of the meta. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 19:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 19:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to invest in the pitchfork business please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 18:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man I wish I was as good at learning the ins and outs of a new ship line as fast as the pitchfork weilders in this thread.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 18:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it isn't just as bad, it's going to be significantly less.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 18:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh, don't know what you're on about m8. Nothing about being a competent BB driver can do against stealth firing and it's also something cruisers cannot effectively counter either. The only REAL counter is planes and even that isn't guaranteed because some DDS can good AA and CVs aren't in every match.

Stealth firing is a non interactive mechanic and needs to go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 18:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are people always so polarizing?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 18:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah dude these guys have been playing these new ships a whole day on 4 point captains, they know exactly what they're talking about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 17:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it's not supposed to be a long range harass ship because we already have ships that do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 17:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was my thought as well. That people were not playing them correctly and jumping to conclusions based off literal first impressioms. 


That would never happen though right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 17:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> .... no its not. Look at the base detection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 17:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make up your minds people.

Stealth firing has been a LONG complained about mechanic and now everyone wants it back for the German DDs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 17:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Montana has significantly better dispersion and pen than the GK. As someone who has played all the T10 BBS, the Montana is the best at killing cruisers. If not only because of the aforementioned, but also because of the playstyle getting you into positions to use all 12 guns without being seriously vulnerable (GK). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 12:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tighter dispersion and US AP *do* mean the Montana kills things faster. You say forced into the kiting playstyle, well that's like saying old IJN DDDs are *forced* into a stealth torping playstyle. It's just what they do best, which is what this thread is all about: identity. Yamato burns to death bow on and can't escape without smoke, Grosser Kurfurst barely even fits in the smoke.

Montana is fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 04:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How I play Montana: 

Kill everything that's not a T10 BB insanely quickly 

Win

The dispersion and AP pen is just too good for the ship to be bad. Everything gets deleted by it.

I generally just ignore other T10 BBs unless they are going potato. From kiting range of 13km+ I rarely take big damage from anything.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 20:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on how the value of the box compares to the lowest value of item you can win, but it's just for fun.

They're also giving us a free T6 premium.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 20:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks like it is without the module and CE, right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 18:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much /thread.

Too many games these days try and be open world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 14:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The premium feature is being able to backlight the stuff whatever color you want. The flashing here is just for fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 13:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I imagine you can turn off the effects...

And/or change them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 13:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got me back to playing Montana. The dispersion is so good it's almost sensual.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 20:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't see much art of Essi, this is great! Love Geralts posture and eyes. Very mutant like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 20:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That song still gives me the shivers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 19:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's got to be more than this 15 second clip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 15:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could've gone to college but instead I own every premium in the game. College is overrated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 14:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not the picture I was thinking of.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 14:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh more DDs in the game? Yay another buff to my RU cruisers. 

dealwithit.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 14:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey bud just want to say I'm a new subscriber since your ownage video was posted a few days back. Keep up the quality content! Top notch stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 21:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are big and slow though which is super not okay for a DD against BB shells.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 16:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And at the right time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 16:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 ships of the same type are usually pretty trash divs. You need diversity since you all spawn in the same spot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 21:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not /r/comrade? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moskva is best T10 BB, comrade. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 21:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 22:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a MP focused titled and what campaign it does have was basically just the MP with bots.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 21:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All battleships take big damage against other battleships while broadside. Some take more vs other stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 15:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's good thing HE exists.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 15:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a good thing HE exists.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 06:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry flamu, you've gone off the deep end here. Why does the highest AP damage cruisrr need better pen angles? Sounds op as fuck and one dimensional. The same thing you didn't like about the RN cruisers. If they start angling against your AP you have 12 shells of HE every 8.8 seconds. Why does everyone act like German HE isn't even worth shooting? Hindenburg is fine in the meta. 

Source - 126k avg damage Hindenburg player in current meta. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 00:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your HE shells can kill it and you still get arsonist. Arsonist only requires % damage done with fires, not that they have to die to fire like it once did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 16:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think your best bet if one pops up at 9km from you is to tank the broadside momentarily to start kiting away or if your hydro is up rush him and dodge torps. Either play is risky depending on HP levels and stuff. If you have a lot of HP I would try and kite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 15:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you shouldn't be in a situation where you're super close to a Minotaur. Try and stay like 12km and it should be no contest. If they're smoked up just sail straight away. If you do get close, we'll it'll be tough I think it could go either way depending on the player and if you have hydro. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 13:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Angle slightly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 13:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you expect out of someone named Autism Speaks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 05:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go 1/4 speed at first. Most things shouldn't really be hitting you from that range but yeah, that's why some stealth is good generally.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 01:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hipper plays similarly to the Roon and Hindenburger, but with significantly less firepower. Less shells pet salvo and way longer reload. It's mediocre imo. Imagine the Hipper firing 9 shells every 8.8 seconds and that's basically Roon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 22:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hindenburg has much better turning radius than chapy too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 22:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but I carry more than other good ships because of the versatility. Des Moines is not very versatile. Neither is Moskva.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 21:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I carry so many games in my Hindenburg it's not even funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 21:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been playing Moskva a lot lately and seeing this would make me so excited I'd probably miss all my shots.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 21:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My reasoning is that I'm so often detected anyway with the amount of firing I do, and even with the full stealth build its still not that stealthy anyway so... I've even considered taking off concealment expert and stacking on like SE or AFT with the demo expert. Your rudder is so good with steering gears mod 3 it doesn't matter if you're spotted generally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 19:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people commenting in this thread are mistaken or are not playing these ships correctly. Roon and Hindenburger are much more versatile than the other high tier cruisers. Their high HP and turtleback armor will keep them alive the whole match assuming no broadsides getting punished. I regularly tank 80k-85k damage in Hindenburg. 

You need to be firing HE most of the time. Their HE is not the greatest, but their accuracy and rate of fire is. Slap on demo expert and your salvos every 8.8 seconds will start plenty of fires. Be a good shot.

AP is situational and needs to be used as such. When the situation does arrive, I use expert loader to quick swap to AP and then your DPS is insane. 

Run steering gears mod 3 because stealth play is overrated with 8 second reload and turtleback armor. I try and play around 13km from the enemy BB fleet and do a lot of kiting. You can move closer once the fleet thins out.

Running down DDs with your hydro is literally unlosable.

Source - 76% winrate and 126k avg damage in Hindenburg.  

Edit - basically, there's no situation I felt I couldn't handle. Every 1v1 I felt I could win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 16:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out the company GECCO. They make some of the highest quality statues you can buy (~$300 each) and have a Dark Souls line coming out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 13:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Became a member of the 300k club. 

https://i.imgur.com/pZbZOFnh.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teaching the Missouri about Russian Bias </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 02:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 22:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> useful 

*OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 19:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I'd rather just have a full $60 campaign experience than a multiplayer game at all. A frostbite star wars campaign sounds incredible if they can do it right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 18:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hindenburgers are an exception </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 17:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe at low tier, but having planes in the air moves matches along at high tier and gives useful Intel about enemy movements.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 16:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I think the 1% estimate is a big of an exaggeration, but I agree. I've always wanted CVs to be support role.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 16:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The good ones do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 15:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get 75% winrate on everything else and they're far more encouraging to play. 

The other classes, I mean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 15:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CVs are required for game balance. They limit the use of stealth and stealth firing (the two most uncounterable mechanics) and they act as an equalizer between classes. For instance, a BB vs CA 1v1 will be in the BBs favor, but throw in planes and that could change. 

Not to mention keeping CVs in matches keeps AA ships and AA builds in the meta, leading to more diversity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 14:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The CV economy is wrecked right now and USN CVs are almost universally outperformed by IJN.

Fix the economy and give USN CVs a *small* bit of love and we're golden.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
