<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1239</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am alcoholic, can confirm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 11:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I can't defend my argument because it has no real substance so I'm gonna wuss out and claim it's a form of protest" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 18:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Political science majors are the most clueless people, I swear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 17:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Destroyed? He threw a temper tantrum and wouldn't let him speak. This is just Harris and Affleck 2.0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 04:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "911 what's your emergency?"

"I've fallen and I cant get up!"

"That's a shame sir, but there are pills for that" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 04:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. Closest thing is to get it on PS3 or use steam and plug in your ps4 controller to your PC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drove an ambulance all day in this. It was not as enjoyable as this picture makes it seem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 11:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's pretty common knowledge that most people aren't big on sharing their partners. If you believe that your SO is still in existence and waiting for you in an afterlife, I'm curious how people holding that belief view remarriage in that case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 10:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The idea that you see your loved ones again in an afterlife. How does this work if you have multiple spouses?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Religious widow(er)s of Reddit who have remarried, how do you reconcile remarriage with your belief in an afterlife? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 09:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 00:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had this almost happen to me. Group of kids that liked to pick on me drew some threats/graffiti on a desk and then said it was me. Had the cops show up to interrogate me for planning a shooting. Fortunately didn't go anywhere. A lot of my teachers started treating me like I was bound to be the next Klebold or Harris. I had never hurt anyone or done anything markedly antisocial, I was just a quiet kid because I had a bad home life. I spent time outside of school hiking and helping at a soup kitchen so I didn't have to go home. I didn't really do much of anything that year and had to redo some classes.


People fucking suck, teachers are no different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 09:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can find an actual Nazi, absolutely, go nuts. In fact, he probably deserves worse. He's a mass murdering psychopath after all.

Here's the dirty little secret though:

The people who are going around justifying "punching Nazis" actually just want to label anyone they want an excuse to punch a Nazi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 08:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Firefly

Because God is dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 07:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is my doggo eating your catto? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 06:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in so much of a haze in the morning given I don't reliably sleep 8 hours in my profession that I'm certain I'd use the wrong paste in the morning and fall asleep at the wheel on my way to work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 06:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone got all the obvious ones, so I'll just say the Everybody's Gone to the Rapture is insanely under-appreciated . Not really much of a game so much as a story that you explore in first person. The soundtrack alone is pure art, and you can find it on YouTube easily. The stories of all the main characters aren't like most emotional games since they're all just regular people living in a simple village in England, but that makes the tragedies they face all the more real. Rather than the typical "military hero bro gets killed by bad guy to sad piano theme" it's real world, existential tragedies you're probably all too familiar with yourself. Lizzie's phone call in her chapter conclusion in particular was a huge gut punch, especially because of the soundtrack. I think the track is titled "I hope you find peace" in the official track list that's on YouTube. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 21:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1: the series relies on artificial difficulty way more than it pretends to not

2: the community is almost as bad as the LoL community. The amount of false sense of accomplishment among the elitists is depressing. 

3: PvP has always been an unbalanced mess and you know it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 09:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American Hustle.
Holy shit do I have an irrational hatred for this boring-ass pointless movie about people doing absolutely fucking nothing but yell at each other. Nobody accomplishes or achieves anything, and the entire time there is this contrived plot about the FBI forcing them to help expose some corrupt politicians but like I said, it's really just A list actors screaming at a each other. How did this thing win an Oscar? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 04:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I mean there's tons of *speculation* by the community, but nothing really concrete. It just reminds me of the Mass Effect 3 controversy and how they lacked epilogues or any explanation of what happened beyond vague hints. I prefer to know what happens, even if it's a bit shrouded, rather than have nothing but fan theories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 04:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they could explain anything at all if be happy. Like, what the fuck happens in each ending? I still have zero idea what the consequence of anything is. This series explains nothing at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 00:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Nameless Dancer. That's all I'll say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 10:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I myself only really made improvements in my life when I embraced humility and was honest about how insignificant and boring I was. I plan on maintaining that mindset, which I feel is mainly just me being honest about my circumstances so I never forget about doing better than I have so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 01:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This entire thread:
"I don't have a clue about what you're asking for but I still want to look brainy so here's a barely relevant factoid you didn't ask for instead" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At a complete loss. Laptop touchpad and external mouse randomly stopped working, cursor disappeared. Nothing I do fixes it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 11:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in the middle of playing a game on my laptop when my mouse suddenly stopped working. I initially thought the battery may have died but the mouse was powered on. I tried unplugging the usb receiver for it but it did not fix the problem. I then minimized my program to look at the control panel only to find my touchpad is also not working. I've sometimes had problems where my keyboard will either partially or entirely stop responding and I'll need to reboot. However, rebooting has not fixed my cursor disappearing. I've tried checking drivers but my PC insists everything is up to date. Troubleshooting turned up no errors. Laptop is a Dell Inspiron 5555 Signature Edition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 09:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good question, she was a rescue so I'm not 100% sure. I think she's a German shepherd/lab mix going by the fur and the ears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
