<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3278</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you picture Korver in the finals? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worst case scenario. I'm worried about that too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And some of those fouls they didn't agree with shook em </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cavs spanking that ass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw that LeFuck You three from a mile away </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't remember a more frustrating game to watch on both ends </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here comes the Lebron lockdown D on Derozan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Korver melted Hubie's cold heart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did not know Lebron was a natural lefty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, Cavs are hungover </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what Canada does to people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yanked him by the arm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a hell of a lot more like it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are you watching it?

Edit: Not a cop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean he's not a big dude so if they're determined to double him its tough. I didn't see as much of that last year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Irving 4 of 13 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last year all through the playoffs I think Kyrie was under the radar slightly more. That Game 7 shot put him on the map and its hurting him this year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The switch must be stuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cavs sucking and still up 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most everything I've posted on reddit has sucked so if people want to repost this and take credit I won't even be mad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Figures. I wouldn't be surprised if the hit boxes were extra large as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smart bounce? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Throwing one is taking a risk. Yeah its a smart set up. Online makes it worth risking not just at the finish line. The race is pretty much won at the start whoever comes out of the first few turns in first gets unentangled and leaves everyone else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously this shit bounced back diagonally </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I've noticed even the blue shell doesn't delay you that much, it just opens the door to people hitting you with red/green shells.

Edit: I needed to hit with both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Murphy's law </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For long stretches its been working beautifully for me. Earlier today I got kicked and then it kept happening for an hour or so after that, but so far that's the anomaly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 06:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it must be a hidden stat because the same bike and wheels don't turn as well depending on the character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turn radius wins me matches, except in this case </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turning radius </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 00:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't seen it discussed anywhere else. I've been mostly using light characters because of how sharply they turn. I'd love to get used to the speedier characters but they can't turn as sharply. What stat governs this? All the discussion about the weight classes only mentions speed vs. acceleration as if they all turn just as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Played myself (Mario Kart 8 Deluxe) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 00:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Played myself </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 00:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell yeah it's awesome. Looks so good on the Switch screen too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The Godfather" reunion at the Tribeca Film Festival </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a reward for beating the 200 cc Time Trials? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 00:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title. I'll probably try to beat them either way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Moo Moo Meadows is essentially what happens when you rely on depression era structures to accommodate the rigors of modern-day transit." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 07:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way I see it they must make a Wii Sports Resort sequel. I honestly can't believe it's not announced already. To this day, I still play it regularly with my casual gaming friends. Nintendo has such a wealth of IPs that I guess they have forgotten about Wii Sports for now, but it would sell massively and move Switches without a doubt. Wikipedia says the original sold 80 million copies... I know at least half of those were pack ins, but people bought the Wii specifically to play it, so I'd say that counts as a sale. Third all time and bigger seller than Mario. I know it's popular around here to trash it, but it is a masterpiece in my opinion. Wii Sports Resort improved upon it and still sells for $60 as it is hard to find. Wii Sports Club had potential but they got too cute with the marketing when they split each game into a separate purchase. Also, the relative failure of the Wii U meant it was nearly impossible to find an online game. Switch Sports would be at least as big as Mario Kart 8 Deluxe and Splatoon 2 are about to be. It's a slam dunk if you're Nintendo.
Side note: Do we have confirmation that the Joycons will work as a pointer like the Wiimote? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 10:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So there's no way to give him the 2 counter except breaking down a Hector, which aint happening. Bummer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 10:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, well shit. I knew there had to be a catch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just made a +1 Marth - Is there any reason I shouldn't give him Ryoma's weapon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 10:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what the security guard showed me when I walked up. I already knew they weren't going to let me in, I just wanted to see what he would say. Fun walk over through south Kyoto from the Fushimi-Inari Shrine. And by the way that place, Mt. Inari, was the most fun I've had on this Japan trip. We walked all up in the woods for hours finding all these ancient shrines. Was a very BOTW experience and it clearly makes sense that Nintendo is from there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The newer white building. There's the old building too I read, is that where R D still is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nintendo HQ in Kyoto wouldn't let me in </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nintendo headquarters crushed my dreams </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 03:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 11:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I second this. Worst 3 months of my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 13:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Switch is a must buy and I'm going to savor every minute of this game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 09:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there any way to have multiple accounts on a non-jailbroken iPhone? Actually I wouldn't be opposed to jailbreaking it if the end result with the two apps wasn't crazy janky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 09:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the analysis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 08:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My arena team is made out of the 5 stars that I have - Marth, Robin M, Lilina, and Nowi. Also I have 5* Roy and Jakob. Don't know exactly what I need to improve this team, other than wishing I had a Takumi, Hector, Azura, and Linde. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 08:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could do one roll right now or wait for the next banner 24 hrs from now. I don't have any of the 4 family bonds already. Should I spend the orbs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 14:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Skyward Sword might have the best crafted dungeons in any Zelda. The overworld *was* limited, and you had to revisit the same areas, but I put those shortcomings on the hardware. I still really enjoyed it for what it was. Great music and story too. Also the motion controls always worked well for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 12:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man I was hungover once and a Lime-Cucumber Gatorade brought me back from the brink of death. Been in love ever since. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 09:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I knew. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grigor played out of his mind and showed that he belongs in the top 10 if not top 5. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All time shit we're seeing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HOLY SHIT!!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 12:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The tie breaker was the whole match. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 12:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are the odds that either Federer or Nadal will win the title? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 12:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rafa in straight sets. And people were talking about how scary Raonic was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
