<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3297</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep! It's actually pretty darn good. And they really do seem influenced by great shows such as "Spaced".

[Incidental music]  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Settling does not equate to an admission of guilt. They literally could've settled out of court to avoid legal fees and public image is being dragged through the media. 

Also, it's intellectually dishonest to equate words with actions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Accusations are not proof. I'm not saying he didn't do it, but to assume that he and the other accused did is just presumptuous </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> E...A....SPORTS....IT'S IN THE NECK! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, to be fair, it is right to give *him* thanks and praise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As much as I don't like the guy, let's wait until he actually gets his day in court.

Post-edit: am I seriously getting downvoted for the fact I pointed out that he hasn't actually been CONVICTED of a crime? Jeez, some Redditors are sensitive. I guess to these Redditors if it's someone they don't like, then any accusation is immediately proven. You're no better than the worst of FOXNEWS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like FOXNEWS, but wouldn't it be more intellectually honest to actually let these accusations have their day in court rather than jump to conclusions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, that's absolutely ridiculous. If you think no critical thinking goes into mainstream movies, I think you're absolutely wrong. Read "Narration in the Fiction Film" by David Bordwell. 

And just because Star Wars is about spirituality doesn't make it against critical thinking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it stinks that it doesn't look like we'll be getting Imperial Commandos anytime soon, but I am happy that we at least got to experience a great adventure with Delta squad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is an odd attraction to seeing a new episode of a show "live" with everyone else who's watching it at the same time (a sense of community, I suppose). I still prefer to watch at my own leisure without commercials, and without having to worry about missing out on an episode should my schedule for the night change up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, I have to go with Nicholas D. Wolfwood (Trigun) or Matt Murdock (Daredevil).

They're characters that are torn between their religious dedications, the complicated real world, and the points of views of their friends.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jericho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, this is the episode that really seems to focus on wrapping up her personal arc with her family. Jack's been the big dog in terms of narrative drive since the first episode. 

But I respect your opinion on the matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus is my boy when it comes to good morals, but I don't think he'd be all in for a fight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it because it's a show that is a character drama but it's sensibilities and artistic style have one foot firmly planted in the realm of reality, and the other in surrealist fantasy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smart Guys - it's an online mini-seres. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on what you like:

Daredevil, The Expanse, Cowboy Bebop, Legion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jericho, Cowboy Bebop, Dark Matter, Daredevil, Riverdale </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The West Wing, Cowboy Bebop, Jericho, Smart Guys, Prison Break, Dark Matter, The Expanse, Daredevil, Legion, Samurai Jack (especially this new season) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arrested Development, Archer, Smart Guys, Chozen, Police Squad! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd recommend (based on your criteria):

Band of Brothers, Cowboy Bebop, Jericho, Dollhouse, Samurai Jack, Arrested Development, Smart Guys, Twin Peaks, Babylon 5, Star Trek: The Next Generation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ideas for a motivating TV show?

I don't know about motivating TV shows, but I do like the general concept of family unity in "Arrested Development" even in the worst of times and I would consider it a more-or-less upbeat show. It's also a great show.

Bob's Burgers is a great animated series that's more family-friendly and upbeat. It's all about a family going through the oddness of everyday life and trying to run their restaurant as best they can. 

There's also an online mini-series called "Smart Guys" where three buddies are trying to make their own video game without any background education in the subject matter. Pretty funny and a bit exaggerated surrealism.

I hope your depression goes away! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it red-red-green, or red-green-red? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Narration in the Fiction Film" David Bordwell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 06:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Careful with that joke, it's an antique. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 06:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoah, there, Tumblr. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 00:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tradition, mostly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd suggest not telling the children this story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you use protection? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More like "Fuckruckers", amirite? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not? Don't fuel the standard that priests can't get lucky in the confessionals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I keep telling your wife, too. :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  No, it said a 4" tongue, not a 4' boy.

He's a priest, not a public school teacher </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's one of my favorite shows, but even I got to admit that if you're not willing to go with the show in terms of tonal and narrative shifts out of nowhere, you're probably not going to like the remainder of the series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "A sphincter....says....'what.'" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Batman Beyond](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sMXjtvMAFlI)

[Megas XLR](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=poV2mZuVOjI)

[Cowboy Bebop](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Aw3fN3OPk3A)

[Samurai Jack](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VYm1igKY9Ys) (Sorry for the french subtitles and the weird repeating)

[Men in Black: The Series](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TwP4vSfjygY)

[Family Guy](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uThx9lO8u0k) (I really haven't liked the show ever since it came back from cancellation, but I still hold that the first three seasons are among the best American comedy ever produced)

[Band of Brothers](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=r1DosMJafGk)

[Twin Peaks](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=i7d0Lm_31BE)

Recent ones:

[Daredevil](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KFYFh8w4758)

[Game of Thrones](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s7L2PVdrb_8)

[The Expanse](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=krqqqgixNq8)

[Stranger Things](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-RcPZdihrp4) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 01:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Not yet.

It's treason then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 00:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  George Michael!

"....15 minutes to Legoland!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay. Well, then I'll give it a look. I'm not judging the show (as I haven't seen it yet), but instead the writer and how poor this article argues it's points.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Except of course historically religions don't keep to themselves and play well with others.

Which ones? I personally think it's a bit intellectually dishonest to lump all religions under one group. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Throughout the season, we see the sneering Pastiche writers cry free speech as well-meaning allies trip over themselves to atone. But the show isnt as interested in the white students perspective  and thats as it should be. 

Yep. In a show about decrying "institutional racism" (read: white people), it's important to NOT get white peoples' perspective on the matter because their opinion doesn't count because of their race and not who they are as people. Fuck this writer and fuck Vox for publishing such nonsense.

Also notice how the writer's limp attempts to deride "Freedom of Speech" as secondary to what skin color you have. Seriously, this is someone who got paid to write. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jessica Jones - I felt like it had three very solid beginning episodes, then lost its mind completely. Things like not actually knowing how the legal system works on a basic level, the annoyance of side-stories that go nowhere, the whole thing with "Nuke" (seriously, that's stretching the level of coincidence I'm willing to accept), side stories that have no actual relevance to the rest of the series (like Luke's wife and the flash drive), questions that aren't at all answered or touched upon (like why Jessica was able to break free of Kilgrave's control or how she even got her powers).

The actings all over the place, the characters are too broadly written, side steps interesting issues they could have taken the story down, and has a main protagonist who actively discourages liking or siding with her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually think it's a solid show, but I LOATHED season/series 8. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Forgive me if these are repeats)

Cowboy Bebop, Stargate SG-1, Trigun, Dark Matter, Daredevil, The Expanse, Space Dandy, Star Trek: The Next Generation, Babylon 5, Farscape, Dollhouse, Almost Human, Fullmetal Alchemist, Samurai Jack (hard to define), Legion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stick and Matt on "Daredevil" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arrested Development, Fraiser, The West Wing, Archer, Police Squad!, Downton Abbey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jake and Eric Green with their father Johnston Green on Jericho. They had so many moments that reminded me of my Dad and I. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Maybe he meant the singer-songwriter?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "What?! That's highway robbery, you son of a bitch!"

"Yes, I am. Thank you for noticing." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Kristanna!

What was the hardest character for you to get into the mindset of? 

Best of luck with Black Rose! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Why does everyone laugh when I say that?! They ARE after me lucky charms!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do they call him the Bullet Dodger? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So we're ignoring the scene where Brad Pitt cuts the girls hand off causing blood to squirt everywhere?

In the theatrical cut, it was out-of-frame, and we don't actually see the gore of that moment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Honestly it's the best property in the MCU at the moment.

I strongly disagree with this sentiment. Between the films, Luke Cage, and Daredevil (maybe my favorite thing in the entire MCU), AoS is a very good show, but I wouldn't consider it the best thing going on right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Cowboy Bebop](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nQXtsFFgr3w). It's wordless and not even a minute long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know Kung-fu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THIS IS SPARTA! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Sometimes you gotta shake the tree to see what falls out." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 07:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Aaaaand....."Woof"

[well...](http://i0.kym-cdn.com/photos/images/newsfeed/000/617/851/56d.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 07:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She has HUGE....bowls of Kibble!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I yam what I yam." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We've already established that Atheism is "a lack of belief in gods or god"

There's a difference between "disbelief in God(s)" and "belief that there are no Gods". The first would be closer to agnosticism, whereas the second is a held belief there aren't any God(s) which would be atheism. 

 which is not a belief system because the definition of Atheism is explicitly a lack of belief nothing more. 

No, because even if atheism was defined as a "non-belief in a God", it's still presupposing other philosophical assumptions, which have already been mentioned in the "Scandinavian Skeptic" above. Even if you change the definition of "belief that there are no Gods" to "non-belief in God(s)", it's STILL a belief. 

 So calling Atheism a belief system would be like calling lacking a hobby a type of hobby.

No, calling atheism a belief system would be like calling abstinence a position on sexual activity, as in, one knows about it, and one chooses not to engage in it. 

Allow me to pull up another argument from "the Scandinavian Skeptic":

 A further drastic problem arises if the atheist wishes to claim that his statement there is no God is not a claim or a beliefif it isnt, then it cannot be true or false. The problem is that only claims can be true or false. It makes perfect sense to ask whether a claim like It is raining today or The Maple Leafs lost again is true or false. On the other hand, it is meaningless to ask whether the colour blue, a small off-duty Czechoslovakian traffic warden, or the word Wibble are truethey are not claims and thus cannot possess a truth value. So heres the problem for the atheist. If atheism is not a claim of any kind, then it is simply meaningless. On the other hand, if the atheist wishes to claim that his atheism is true, then that must mean that atheism is a claim, and claims need to be defended, evidence provided and reasons given. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Regardless your claim that Atheism is an ideology that started this conservation is absolutely and entirely false.

I do concede that I shouldn't have placed that word in association with atheism itself, but I should have made it more clear that it was used in context of the Soviet Union's political doctrines and ethics utilizing atheism. 

 It's not a belief system because Atheism is simply a lack of belief in god(s) thus you don't believe in anything. 

You put forth positive claims by the very argument "atheism is a non-belief", which you've STILL yet to argue against.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  No. It is not a belief system, Atheists refuse to admit that because unlike you they understand their lack of belief is not a belief system.

Basically, your argument is boiled down to "it isn't a belief system, because I don't want it to be" rather than arguing WHY it isn't.

I also noticed you failed to actually address the criticisms brought forth by the "Scandinavian Skeptic" article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which game is this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Atheism is the concept of not believing in God and is not intrinsically tied to communism as many Americans STILL think decades after the fall of the Soviets.

Yes, it is. Especially since it has been the governmental doctrine that has been violently enforced across many communist countries. The Soviet Union, Mao's China, and Pot's Cambodia violently oppressed religious peoples and institutions. Marxism-Lenism, Maoism, and Stalinism all employed actively oppressing the religious (to the point of active genocide), justified their oppression through their dedication to atheism/state-secuarlism, and promoted atheism/state-secularism.

The Soviets DID subscribe to atheism as a defining part of their ideology, and used it to be [hostile towards the religious](http://www.country-data.com/cgi-bin/query/r-12521.html). No, that doesn't mean that being atheistic makes you a violent oppressor. My point is that they used that belief as apart of their ideology, and twisted it for their own ends.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  it's a lack of belief in god(s) that's it.

Okay. I sincerely believe that atheism is a belief system (which doesn't inherently make it a weaker argument, and I think that atheists are strangely afraid of acknowledging the idea that it's a belief system out of some irrational fear that it somehow undermines their argument to understand that their position is an abstract notion based on their own arguments and evidence). 

 Communists =/= Atheists,

I understand that sentiment; I know they're not the same thing. That's not my argument. My point is that Communism utilized atheism in their political doctrines and programs and used the belief of atheism to justify their prejudice against the religious. No, it doesn't mean that being atheist makes you prejudiced against those who are religious/spiritual to the point of violent action. What I'm saying is that they warped an ideology to allow themselves to persecute others. It could have been any other ideology, and in this case, it was atheism, like it was nationalism with the Nazis or religion with the Muslims during the crusades. 

 all communists may be atheists but not all atheists

I agree. I was merely pointing out that communist countries like the Soviet Union, Mao's China, or Cambodia under Pot used demanded that atheism be the state "religion", and that all other religions were to be violently oppressed in favor of making the people subscribe to that ideology. 

 Just because atheism is a part of communist ideology does not mean that it's an ideology, 

Atheism is an ideology, because it's an active belief. If someone says "I don't know if there are any Gods" that's agnostic. Maybe if they say "I'm leaning towards there not being any Gods, but I'm certain enough to say I don't believe in any Gods" that's agnostic atheist (at best). If you know what God's are, and you say you don't believe in them, that's not a passive belief. That is an active claim. It's the belief that there are no Gods. 

I really would suggest you read the article "[The Scandinavian Skeptic](http://www.rzim.eu/the-scandanavian-sceptic-or-why-atheism-is-a-belief-system)" (as I had linked above) to why it is a belief and how it's intellectually dishonest to not consider it one (which is, to say, that atheism as a belief does not lessen it's arguments as a belief). As "The Scandanavian Skeptic" points out, just by claiming that "atheism is just non-belief in God(s)":

 The atheist is now claiming to believe that the external world really exists (thus she is rejecting metaphysical idealism), that other minds exist, that the human mind can form beliefs, and that our cognitive faculties are broadly reliable. Each of those is a hotly debated area in philosophy.

Even claiming it's a "non-belief" (which I wouldn't classify atheism as) brings positive claims to the table.

 Their ideology (which wasn't Atheism) is what was used to justify their violence against religion/religious people.

Their ideology was based on militant atheism, and active government-sponsored programs to re-educate the masses to distrust and vilify religion; they actively imprisoned the religious in gulags and utilized executions for those holding religious beliefs. Yes, it's only part of their ideology, and throwing in atheism doesn't make something inherently worse or holding to the idea that atheism will immediately make you a bad person, but they used atheism as apart of their governmental doctrine, and used that militant form of the ideology as justification for their persecution of the religious (specifically the Christians in their country).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  come to philippines, feels like 38C right now

Yeah, well, you're going to die in a hurricane. 

(By the way, I don't actually mean this. That was a reference to "Continue? Show" [in this episode](https://youtu.be/dgI6YOUF6NM)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Have a pepsi and let's hash this out.

The HELL did you say to me? (Throws Pepsi) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true. Sometimes, we need the low bar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Atheism is not an ideology,

Yes it is. By it's basic foundational principles that there are no Gods, and downplays spiritual elements and institutions. It is [a belief system](http://www.rzim.eu/the-scandanavian-sceptic-or-why-atheism-is-a-belief-system), even if some might not want to see it that way, and contributed to the ideology and culture of the many communistic countries by being incorporated into their governmental doctrines and programs.

  They did not commit those acts because they were Atheists but because they were Totalitarian Dictatorships, next time do your research.

Man, that's just wrong. Atheism was used in justification to persecute the religious, and the state [actively encouraged it](http://www.country-data.com/cgi-bin/query/r-12521.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well actually, they believe in the same core values concerning representation, the economic doctrines placed down by Lenin, and the focus on the state being the central figure of authority over religion (among many others).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  No one's denying that, just that he wasn't truly making a religion free country.

Well, that was certainly the intent of the State, which Stalin had vigorously supported when he took power.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. But it doesn't change the fact that the state had used it's belief in atheism to justify those actions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Out of desperation to find a rallying cause for the people. 

It was when he had taken power that the government began implementing wide-spread religious persecution and funding anti-religious education.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You're talking about totalitarian Communist regimes not atheistic ones.

What ideology do you think that Communism employs? Atheism was apart of the Soviet Union, of Communist China, and of a great number of communistic countries. 

When you try to defend something, at least do your research. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You mean under dictatorships?

Uh, no. I mean "Communism" under Marxism-Leninism/Maoism/Stalinism ideologies. What great straw man arguments you have there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing you actually don't know what ideologies the [Communists actually employed](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Marxist%E2%80%93Leninist_atheism) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. The world would be better without jerks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it's mostly concerned with charitable contributions across all spectrums. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  His point is that while Stalin did force atheisim on his people it was in service of creating his own cult of personality and not allowing the population's belief in god undermine that.

That doesn't change the fact that the State still used it's atheistic/secular stances to make itself the "worship icon" in the culture, and to use that ideology to persecute and kill the Religious. 

He DID force atheism onto others and openly mocked, criticized, and persecuted the religious. This is basic history: [link](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Persecution_of_Christians_in_the_Soviet_Union#Resumption_of_the_anti-religious_campaign) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries! Thanks for responding. The world could definitely use more tolerance, especially with some aggressive people who take any ideology as a call to action to belittle and berate others.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  That doesn't change what your actual income is though.

That also doesn't change the amount of money people donated through these charitable institutions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Those people weren't atheists, 

Isn't that the "no true scotsman" argument? Also, those people were forced to be "practicing atheists" as it was the national doctrine, so I consider them to be atheist, especially with a lack of evidence to suggest that they secretly kept their religious beliefs (due to shoddy record keeping of the Soviet Union).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 08:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Donations wouldn't factor into overall yearly income though.

Not if they're given to a charity, which Churches are usually considered to be charitable institutions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 08:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If you're going to do a study that purports to show religious people are more charitable than non-religious people, it's disingenuous to just blanketly categorize all tithing as charitable.

Well, it seems like [these reports](http://connectedtogive.org/) go into more detail concerning how the research measures the charitable actions of the sample size they took of religious vs. not-religious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So.... that's kind of bullshit if you'll excuse my lack of finer words.

I think that's bullshit. 

 Your churches coffers that will pay your pastors salary and for a new "prayer chapel" is not a charity.

They have direct donations whenever they need repairs or go towards supplying our Church. My church is open and honest about their spending. They've even been kind enough to sit us down and go over our finances concerning where donations go and which organizations we contribute to when my family friends and I were curious (as their had been rumblings about misallocation of funds). 

I feel like you might be projecting anger here instead of actually considering the good Churches and Christians provide in terms of charity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh....so the poor atheists in the Soviet Union, Mao's China, and Pol Pot's Cambodia were...what, outliers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yet, more people died under atheistic regimes like the Soviet Union, Mao's China, and Pol Pot's Cambodian atrocities than any other war in human history in the 20th century alone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regardless of whether or not Stalin himself was an atheist (I think his compliance with persecution Christians indiscriminately and burning down churches speaks volumes towards a militant atheism), he and the higher ups of the soviet union advocated for forced State atheism/secularism which did affect how the government ran, and how they justified persecuting, torturing, and killing the religious.

I don't think atheism causes that action. Only some individuals cause that action and twist their ideologies to suit evil acts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Why do you need the promise of a reward to do the right thing? I know the delivery is crude but the point remains.

I'm a Christian, and I do charity because I like helping others where I can.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really. I mean, people have differences of ideologies and opinions. In comparison to countries going through civil wars, political upheaval, ACTUAL genocides, and the government committing violent oppression, I'd say we're pretty good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't that usually because Christian groups DO give more money to charities?

(https://www.philanthropy.com/article/Religious-Americans-Give-More/153973)

I'm not saying one group is better than the other. I'm just pointing out that using statistics to prove which ideology is better is a little silly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   People behave as if everyone is a Christian, and if you aren't a Christan, you are expected to live in silence and utter shame. 

I kinda feel that way being a Christian on Reddit. 

I have an old buddy of mine who won't stop talking about his atheist beliefs whenever we're together and constantly tries to steer conversations towards making cutting jabs at religion, even unprovoked. 

There's jerks on both sides of the aisle, and it's just sad that normal people who just have to suffer through that lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Atheist, Christian, Jewish, Buddhist, Zoroastrian. I think we can all agree that she's just being dumb without actually showcasing evidence.

Disclosure: I am Christian, and I think she's making a weird grand assumption of an ideology with little to no evidence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd argue that the Soviet Union's state forced atheism/secularism influenced their ideology as a culture (especially in terms of their mental justifications for persecuting Christians), but atheism doesn't inherently make anyone more susceptible to being poor (or being religious). 

She's just being dumb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree that poverty is not always symptomatic of one particular ideology or another. However, fuck Marxism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it's just a symptom of her being an idiot, and education and religion are just unfortunately associated with her own idiocy.

After all, she chose to say something as stupid as a religious belief (or lack thereof) is the cause of something she can't actually prove.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heath Ledger as The Joker. Jeez, he was intimidating. The "Why So Serious?" scene was one of the most tense scenes I've ever watched.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Splinter Cell: Conviction, to co-op stories end with the story pitting the co-op protagonists against each other. 

Or, Dead Space 2 when first encountering the chargers. Those things terrified the crap out of me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least his face is at that point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AWESOME! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be keeping both you and him in my thoughts and prayers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know I wouldn't trust me if I saw myself in a mirror walking to the bathroom at night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Healing.....what exactly?

[This kind](https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=eA4_O3oeJCw) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  She stays as vague as possible in everything she says to the public and lets people draw their own conclusions

Soo.....a politician? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adam Sandler movies. It teaches kids you can have zero talent, use productions to justify vacations, and just never listen to anyone's constructive criticism to better your craft. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Dango! You delicious son of a bitch!"

"The D's not silent, Hillbilly." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hush up, little girl. Lotta cats got that name." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It's over Ashi! You have the low ground." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6 seasons and a movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GOIN' UPSTATE TO THE FARM! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
