<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1417</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sophisticated Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 19:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 02:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a huge extrovert but what you said perfectly describes my girlfriend. My friends don't understand it but when it's just me and her she's really relaxed and funny, she can be herself. However around 20 people she only slightly knows she goes quiet and they think she's rude or boring. The really good friends have taken the time to wait and chat to her, which means she can relax and be funny but sadly the majority don't get it and judge her for being quiet. I find it really annoying but if anything it separated my good friends from my  acquaintances. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 18:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my opinion one of the funniest (if not THE funniest) line from the Star Wars Specials. Cracked me up first time I heard it. That and Admiral Akbar saying "Big mistakey?"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best of the droids from Robot Chicken: Star Wars specials. I don't care what Disney says, Dr. Ball is canon to me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 17:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hide Your Presence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 12:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How The USA Created The Taliban (2003) - "An extract from the documentary 'Breaking The Silence: Truth And Lies In The War On Terror' about the US and British Government's involvement in creating the Islamic Extremism we see today." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 11:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 20:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't wait to check this out when I get home.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 12:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love he expects them to pay despite them not eating anything. Fucking nuts! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amy's Baking Company - Kitchen Nightmares </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 11:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 18:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how much fun he's having with it, the way he laughs before insulting them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Captain America v Iron Man | Robot Chicken | Adult Swim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 15:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Captain America   Iron Man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 15:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 10:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help me identify a game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 15:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played an online game a few weeks back that I found on here and I can't remember the name of it and it's driving me up the wall. It was a game you play in your web browser, you control a small ball and move it around the map trying to swallow up smaller balls, making your ball larger as you do. It's an online multiplayer as others are trying to do the same on the map. If someone bigger than you swallowed you up then you died. 

It was really addictive but as you can imagine that's a difficult thing to google without it sounding like you're looking for some kind of porn.

Please help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cristiano Ronaldo Thinks Lionel Messi Will Win The Ballon dOr </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 18:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Never seen anyone so happy about solar panel power. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 17:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 21:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fucking love this show. Might need to give it another viewing soon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best of Darth Vader from Robot Chicken Star Wars. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 15:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best Kickstarter I've seen in ages. Make the Censors Watch 'Paint Drying' by Charlie Lyne. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 13:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 15:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [There are few more from this series on this channel.](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCu4XcDBdnZkV6-5z2f16M0g/search?query=the+private+life) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Super Hans Bloody Loves Crack - Peep Show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 18:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Little Big Dreams (2008) - "The young children at the infamous Li Xiaoshuang Gymnastic School in China go through the most rigorous training for at least five years in search of their Olympic dream. A ruthless factory of child abuse and ambition." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 18:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Never gets old, Happy Friday everyone! 'I Remember You' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 18:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guy cuts his ears off to look more like a parrot. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 13:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 360 Video: Incredible Beijing Race Start Onboard Formula E </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 16:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 20:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even though you know how it's going to end it still ripped me apart when I got there. Such a lovely but sad book.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bradley Cooper and Sienna Miller Learn About Nutscaping - The Graham Norton Show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 19:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Possibly one of the funniest moments in British TV. Peep Show - burying a dog corpse. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 15:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grown Up Halloween </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 15:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 00:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is great stuff mate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey it's a Wednesday so why not just kill yourself? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 18:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thunderbirds Are Go - Special Delivery At Twickenham </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 17:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This guy is better at Bowling with his arse than I am with my hands. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 15:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 15:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well now I'm addicted to this game! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 19:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where's it blocking? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 17:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is amazing mate, well done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Adult Swim UK just uploaded this masterpiece to their Facebook page </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 14:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Adult Swim UK just posted this masterpiece on their Facebook page. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 10:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 11:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You gave the punchline away in the title... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found this gem in a documentary, I call it 'The annoying little brother dance.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 11:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cake on the Desk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 17:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> George Osborne Loves N.W.A. - Have I Got News For You </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 18:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 17:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this may not be a popular opinion but I just don't get it with Halo anymore. I absolutely loved the first one and played it endlessly, Halo 2 was great and I felt improved on the franchise. Halo 3 never lived up to the hype for me, the 'Believe' diorama looked like it would end with an all out war with loads of NPC's battling it out but it never felt like I got the end the adverts promised. I completed 4 but I honestly couldn't tell you a thing about it, it just never drew me in and the now 5 just doesn't hold anything for me. I tried re-visiting 4 and even the gameplay didn't feel that great anymore. Then again I never played Reach, or ODST or any of the spin offs so maybe I'm missing the greater lore but to be honest I don't think I care enough anymore to learn about it.

Then again maybe I'm just a moaning old man letting nostalgia weigh my decision and I'm talking shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-10 23:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just what I was thinking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Testing The Kia Optima On The Nurburgring - Fifth Gear </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 12:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 11:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your mortgage is $750 per month?! Where do you live? I live in London and my rent is 380 a week, which works out at roughly $2518 a month and that's for a small one bed flat. I share the burden with my SO, meaning it's $1259 each, making it a little easier but it's still a lot. I'm not trying to brag or show off, I'm just amazed/jealous that mortgages are so low in the US.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ian Hislop's Pig-Gate Rant - Have I Got News For You </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 11:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 19:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's funny and entertaining but I learnt fuck all about RV electrics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Worst RV electrical tutorial on the Internet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 18:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your favourite 'Jerry is pathetic' moments? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 08:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best opening to a TV show ever - Trigger Happy TV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 18:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sri Lanka's Killing Fields (2011) - "A hard-hitting investigation into the final weeks of the Sri Lankan civil war, featuring devastating video evidence of horrific war crimes." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 13:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Emotional Tracy Morgan interview at the Emmys and talking about his rehabilitation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 19:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 10:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always preferred the Bubble Bath Boys myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ice Bear Makes Me Laugh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 10:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best Ice Bear Moments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 10:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In 2003 Derren Brown played Russian Roulette 'live' on British TV. Obviously there is some trickery at play here but as a teenager this was the most nerve wracking TV I'd ever seen. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 12:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 13:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, it's so easy to focus on the global implications of that day and forget the smaller human element. Such a sad story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trapped in the South Tower, the story of 9/11 victim Alayne Gentul. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 13:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 9/11: The Falling Man - A chilling documentary about the people who had no resort but to jump from the burning World Trade Centre towers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 13:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 00:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That guy (the audience member) is a fucking douche. I'm a Brit and embarrassed by it all. Great work by Luke though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 21:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's American, I'm English. He just moved from London back to Ohio. I'm sad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 18:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it is, dude is a great comic. Average mate but great comic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 18:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, that was the most disarming reply I've ever seen. I'm not American but I can get behind that. Corbyn 2019 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 18:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet took the time to write a comment on it? I don't quite understand how you value your time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My best mate has sold virtually everything and bought a crap motor home. This is his tour of it before he does it up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 16:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This song goes from funny to fucking mental pretty quickly. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 14:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeremy Hunt   Michael Gove Rant - The Last Leg </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-28 15:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Hear You're A Racist Now, Father! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 19:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Candiru  The Fish That Can Swim Up Inside The Penis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 10:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 14:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He hits the nail on the head with this one. Great video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Candiru  A Vampire Dick Fish, the stuff of nightmares. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 11:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> July 19th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 11:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 08:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least give credit to Bec Hill, the comedian who made the comic. This version of the comic someone deleted her surname. Sadly this is the version the gets shared the most. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 08:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah this needs to be higher, this version of the comic is always posted where someone cropped out her surname. It sucks as it means she doesn't get credit for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 20:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for posting. More are coming, we're going to release an episode every Saturday until they're all up. Happy to hear you're enjoying it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mrs Doyle Best Bits - Father Ted Compilation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 10:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Malcolm - A true Cagenist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 14:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 14:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny how the sound with these 'strangers' was all so perfect and not one person reference the cameras; the ones that had somehow established perfect lighting and focus on them.

I call bullshit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
