<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject350</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 05:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brought them with me from Sydney. Just for handing out with tips and stuff..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Look what the koalas brought - I'm in the USA right now, and since I'm new to the whole tipping for services business, I'm trying to have some fun while at it. Hope the housekeeping like the koalas and the tip </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 03:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 00:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't think so man, but I'd now like to check this one out. Might try and get the Spanish version for lulz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 14:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a movie my brother and I watched years ago. It's a horror film with 3-4 stories. The only two bits I can remember us #1 this one story about Crows and an old house, a bit like that Adams family house and this housekeeper guard guy. Anyway ends with a lot of Crows everywhere. NFI what the exact story was. 
#2 the second story I remember was about some people (a couple?)  getting lost and ending up in a village. They go to this one house and are fed rabbit stew. I especially remember this part. The village people help them but are quite sinister and when they try to escape they can't. 

It'd be amazing if anyone can find me the name of this movie. It's prob early 90s or late 80s.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone give us some tips for baseball in NYC in June? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 09:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what's the biggest fluke you've pulled and how has it impacted your life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 06:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 07:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also seem to have a gag reflex when it comes to vodka, there's gotta be something in it my body hates. Been reading up online about this and like us mentioned - grew up drinking whiskey so that's that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 07:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Too much Bro " Best.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Alcohol effects : why can I drink half a bottle of whisky and have no hangover but can barely digest two shots of vodka or tequila. Also, why can I drink a 6-8 beers and be very normal while some of my friends can barely hold it together after 4 beers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 13:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alcohol effects : why can I drink half a bottle of whisky and have no hangover but can barely digest two shots of vodka or tequila. Also, why can I drink a 6-8 beers and be very normal while some of my friends can barely hold it together after 4 beers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 12:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what drink should I drink in your city? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 02:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good morning from Sydney! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 23:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that there is a colony of Welsh speakers in Patagonia. The Welsh people first arrived in Patagonia in 1865. The reason for their migration was to protect their native Welsh culture and language, which they believed was threatened in their native Wales. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 00:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what's a random act of kindness you received that completely blew you away and how? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 13:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did this change your perspective on humanity and/ or life?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
