<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1563</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah...lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes it was! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you get the thunder helm you're immune to lightning damage. Just wear that and you don't have to worry! /s  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Way to be insensitive to gay mass murderers... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Season 7 cannot come soon enough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad you're not writing the show  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will try that. If it doesn't work, I will see if steam can give me a refund because I only have a half hour played, and that was mainly trying to make it run decent. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 12:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had to watch this like 20 times because I was convinced Luigi crossed first  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah either a stroke or ALS or something like that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I couldn't disagree more. I love the shift in tone this season. It's really starting to set things on the path of BB. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jonathan Banks looks so much more badass now. The glasses, lack of facial hair and the balding head make him look kind of like a dweeb. Now he looks like someone I would not fuck with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doom won't launch after switching to vulkan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've searched a bunch of forums and here are the things I tried:

*   updated drivers
*   typed +r_renderAPI-1 into launch options on steam
*  typed +r_renderAPI-0 into launch options
*   tried launching DOOMx64.exe manually
* tried launching DOOMx64vk.exe manually

When I tried launching DOOMx64vk.exe manually, it says I'm missing vulkan-1.dll

I've seen suggestions on forums to make changes to doomconfig.local, but that file isn't there.

It worked when I was running on openGL but since I changed it, I can't get it to run at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't played Fo4 in probably 4-5 months, but I might just start up a new game to make some of my own! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then basically everyone would be a woman.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I guess that's true, DC hates Jones way more. But what's to hate when you're the GOAT? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know DC fans wanna believe DC will beat Jones because they hate him, but the reality is he won't. Any way you put it, Jones is better. Can DC beat Jones? Yeah it's possible but i'll put my money on Jones every time. He hasn't been beat by anyone.

edit: a word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that, but it wasn't really funny so i thought maybe it meant something else </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah his best chance is obviously when Jones is rusty, but I still think Jones will beat his ass. He absolutely despises Cormier and will be ready. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cormier is a great fighter, obviously being the current champ who just defended his title, but there's no way he beats Jon Jones. Can't wait to see the GOAT back in action. Been too long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's so fucking dumb. Sjws can have their own little academic circles, but stay the fuck away from STEM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm really glad I don't see them anymore. Joe Biden always creeped me out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I find it disgusting. What I find even worse though is when new parents post stuff like a picture of their kid sitting on the "potty" and saying how proud they are. Nobody cares and nobody wants to see that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont get it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lore =\= story. Dark Souls has rich lore. Compelling story, it does not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly, what you need to do is silently fantasize about killing the person.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listen to shit music. We all listen to some pop music, and we all have guilty pleasures, but if you don't have any good music I judge you hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More specifically as a straight white man, I have nothing to blame if i'm not successful, and if I am successful it was expected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice title </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pinwheel needs a massive health boost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't get better at dark souls, you git gud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right before Gwyndolin: "Amazing trap ahead" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speed/challenge runs or move on to a new game until DLCs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's really cool! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much you wanna bet the person posting this was a fat black woman? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't look into statistics, but if thats true that it does prevent smoking, I'd still be cautious about the precedent it sets to increase taxes on certain products in the name of "good." It seems dangerous to me for governments to decide which products should have higher taxes based on what is deemed "bad" for society. I don't wanna pay a high tax on video games even though it might be shown that they can be addictive and have a detrimental effect on mental or physical health. I like video games, it's my choice to play them. The free market should decide what I pay and I shouldn't be burdened with added cost because the government wants to deter me from playing them (Protip: they actually wouldn't want me to stop, because they'd be collecting a lot of money). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the real issue. It's that the way healthcare in America works, we end up paying for other people's medical expenses. It should be the person who chooses to smoke that pays the extra healthcare costs, not everyone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely despise smoking. My parents smoke and as a kid I always despised it. But raising taxes on them doesn't prevent smoking. If people were logical about it they wouldn't smoke because it's horrible for you and because it costs a lot of money to have that habit. People will make their own choices.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's implied in the username  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everybody's a hypocrite  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no God confirmed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think puppy outdated at all. It's basically just what you call a baby dog. It's like the word baby going out of style for humans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, my definition is correct </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Black people can't be racist. Racism=power+prejudice  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow this faggot didn't even specify whether the teacher or the kid broke the arm and two ribs. Reeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of faggot says full stop instead of period? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can make a tumblr account that doesn't have your name but it's still social media. People have accounts here, there's an entire system of karma that is linked to each account, and the entire point of Reddit is socialization. People post images of themselves, of their pets, of things they created, they post memes and comment on eachothers posts. Reddit in essence is just interaction between users. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "I don't like social media"

 posted on a social media site </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but who was phone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ITT: 99.99% of posts saying its a chinchilla and not a mouse. and .01% of posts calling it a mouse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's okay I already did it on my laptop. Thanks though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 14:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do I pay the fee? I have my credit card information right here  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 14:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh okay that must be why. I'm on mobile. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 14:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm actually serious tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I get my team name next to my username? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 14:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well god damn that was sad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll concede to that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not the same thing at all. I'm not saying you need to put in every single assumption, I'm saying to write down what's mathematically correct because it's correct and because it's good practice. I'm arguing that in math, these simple mistakes matter a lot more than they do in grammar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> integral[(dy/dx)ds]

has a completely different meaning than

integral[dy/dx]


Say there's a relationship between s, x and y. You can't do anything with the second one but the first one you can. 

Edit: actually this would be a better example 

integral[xy^3]

where x and y have a relationship. How do you know how to integrate this without the dx or dy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was stressing that it does make a difference to not put the dx, because the integral doesn't make mathematical sense. It's like putting a square root symbol with nothing inside it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't put the dx on an integral it doesn't make sense though. Yeah you can still compute things with mistakes like that but it's bad practice to not write things correctly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is nothing trivial in math though. A simple mistake means the whole thing is wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could be, but the fact that it's Caesar makes me think Chuck. Chuck is much more tyrannical than Jimmy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He didn't make it up. So many times we see him alone and still acting this way. He couldn't handle these traumatic experiences and his intense anxiety manifests in these delusions. His ego doesn't allow him to see that he's suffering from a mental condition so he has to believe it's a physical condition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean it's not really that offensive but its also not that funny tbh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's shamelessly advocating for thought policing. Wow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 03:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A good few minutes. Start up a stopwatch and wait 3 minutes. Yeah, that's a really fucking long time to stare at someone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 00:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That could be the case, but knowing how much Jimmy cares about those around him and how cold and spiteful Chuck is, I truly think their mother loved Jimmy more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 00:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chuck is meant to be hated. Is he more than a one dimensional caricature? Yes absolutely. Does he have reasons for being how he is? Yes. Is he still a piece of shit? Yeah, definitely. It does take good acting to make viewers truly hate a fictional character. I absolutely despised Joffrey in GoT because Jack Gleeson did a phenomenal job at playing a massive cunt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I still don't recognize those songs, only the Jackson 5 one. But yeah, I agree it sucks. I hate forced "quirkiness." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes absolutely I hate this trend too. I hate breathy singing in general. It's so cringey.

Could you post the original songs so we can compare? I only recognize the last one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should have done that with this post, because it's been reposted a million times </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean I think Aaron Hernandez would be up there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He fought a wight though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mounted archery camp by far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. The screen always recenters just as I'm about release my arrow. Got the bridle but idk if I can get 23 for the saddle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're expecting a good reward, you'll be disappointed. It's still a fun challenge though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really find that an issue. You can keep playing after you beat it, it's just that Ganon is still there. I'd love a true crafting and repair system though. And more armors/weapons/dyes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I want is the climbers set upgrade to let you climb in the rain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah me too, I love the option to dye armors in this game but I don't always like how certain sets dye. I hope the dye system will be expanded upon. Something as simple as a primary and secondary color for a set and improving the way certain sets dye like the Ancient armor set...it barely changes when you dye it, only the clothing underneath actually dyes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I guess they would ha. I dyed the set blue to look like the blue tunic from OoT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Banhammer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only one who doesn't mind the shorts? It's classic, and it sets it apart from the amiibo sets. Plus, you can actually dye this set which I love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 05:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might wanna go see a gastroenterologist. Seems like you have a giant stick up your ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 05:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're ready, you just need to git gud. This lynel is the best way for you to learn the combat so you should definitely fight him until you can beat him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 04:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't mean they don't take it seriously. It probably makes them really uncomfortable saying they love someone that they don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 04:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DAE breathe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, I'm looking forward to them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Oh you mean for switch."

 /r/nintendoswitch


could you be more cancerous? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MK8, Yooka Laylee, Mario Odyssey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what do you mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 14:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah what? All of the best Mexican places i've been to are owned and operated by Mexicans. Americanized Mexican places are not even close to as good anyways so it's not like a white people Mexican place could ever compete in an area that has authentic mexican food. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 14:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure Mexicans who own restaurants in the U.S. are happy with us "appropriating" their culture by spending our money in their restaurants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 17:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd believe Glenn was still alive before I believed this relationship. Horribly forced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Link might have the Master Sword, but Pikango has the Master Brush </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 05:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 02:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What color Rito gear? I did orange because it looks like Luke Skywalker when he's in his orange jumpsuit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 02:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All Barbarian gear fully upgraded. Weapon: savage lynel crusher. Shield: savage lynel shield. Bow: Savage lynel bow. If I break my lynel crusher i switch to a royal greatsword and if my shield breaks, royal shield. I never run out of lynel bows but sometimes I'll use a falcon bow or my great eagle bow when i'm firing from mid air. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It took me a while to realize it, but yeah. At first I was wondering how the hell Im supposed to collect rupees when they never drop, but then I realized how much can be made from selling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you can't explain that  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
