<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1137</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 10:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont think i can buy Crush cream soda in Norway though, Maybe I'll find something similar! :) Thanks for the tips! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 10:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the tip! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 08:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah i feel like the others just cant get onto the same level as the Truck stop. There is simply just not necessary to take other bases unless you have a special plan? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 08:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The STW is such a nice base though, hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 08:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yes thats right i have a Workshop too, maybe i should remove it?

I really think i should make a munitions shop cause i just cant scavenge enough ammo. No matter what i keep running out :(

Thanks for the reply ! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] What goes well in a Jgermeister mix? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 08:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello,

Im going to a party on friday and could use some tips for some simple Jgermeister mixes :)

It's not a fancy party at all so i dont need proper drink. Just whats the best way of mixing Jgermeister or what goes best with Jgermeister.

Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 12:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also:
I use a Nvidia 970 4 GB Card and I have 16 GB RAM. 

Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need Some Advice on a New Monitor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 11:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys,

Im going to swirch out my 5 year old Benq moniyor with something much more nice.

My budget is around 300 USD (Im from Norway so monitors you suggest to that price might be alot more expensive for me, but i'll look into all suggestions).

I'd like a screen with really nice colors, something i belive IPS Monitors will give me? A high refreshrate would alsp be nice. I've only had 60hz until now, so something higher would be nice.

I bet this question has been posted here millions of times, so im sorry about that but im just seeking some quick tips.

Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trend OfficeScan Server, update from 10.6 to 11. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 11:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys,

I have a Test Environment with a Main Server (Domain controller and all that), and a Trend Officescan server.
I also have 2 Clients for testing the Officescan server.

My next task is to update the Trend Officescan server from 10.6 to 11, and it's really hard!
I cant find any proper tutorial or documentation on how to do this online.
And also im just an IT-apprentice so im not the best guy on this area.

The officescan 10.6 server, is setup and integrated with AD, and I've setup a logon script that automatically installs the Client software.
This logon script works beside that it always asks me to logon as an admin in order to install it. I dont know where the right permission has to be put
in order to make this go away.

But anyways the main problem is the update, so if anyone here knows how to do this or if someone could point me in the right direction that would be great.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 19:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have not been on this reddit for this long so i didnt see it :P  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Favorite base location? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 15:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys,

I was wondering whats your favorite base location and why?

Im using the Truck stop, because its really big and close to the town where i can put up tons of outposts and svavenge! :)

I have the following in my base:
- Kitchen
- Extra tent with bunk beds
- Machine workshop
- Library 
- Infirmary 
- Shooting platform.

All of my stuff is highly upgraded.
But is this a good setup? I cant have all of the stuff set up so im missing for example the dining area. Should i switch something out?

Thanks guys! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it German? Someone once said to me it could be a Yugo build or something else. Im not the best on rifles :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 10:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So i recently bought this Rifle. I had a post about it, and someone mentioned it could be a Yugo build or something else.
So here is some photos of the markings on the rifle, hopefully it can tell more about it. Hope someone knows! :) Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 10:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh woops, sorry i forgot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here is some proper photos of the Mauser i just got. Anyone have some info on it, beside that its bubba'd Mauser? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 09:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 08:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u/R_Shackleford </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guys here is some proper photos i took:
https://imgur.com/gallery/IPyCz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 14:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty cool dude :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 12:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks guys! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does State of Decay YOSE include all the DLCs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 02:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just need help with this, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 02:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im hung up in why you're hung up in something so not important </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol why get hung up in that, is it that important?
Just wanted to express myself bro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 15:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what the fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 14:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im not so into guns as you Muricans, so its not too important. 
The gun works, it has a sight, im okey with it. 

If you're not thats your problem, i dont mind it. 
If the gun didint work or was totally fucked i would ofc not buy it, but this gun is fine.

My standards are not sky high nigga </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
