<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3183</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 08:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arguably that sentence never needed, intended, or started out to be good prose. 

Thats journalism not prose, in many ways.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 08:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So glad I saw this. If he had any shot to win them over it wasn't to jerk yourself off in front of the memorial wall. What's wrong with that kind of person? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 08:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, of course, sorry for not being clear enough. I can still see the ten feet down though whether I'm over the hole or sand. It might decrease a bit over the hole, less light reflecting off the whiter sand bottom 

Like look at the edge closely there's some plant life past the edge you can see from here and we're a few hundred feet up.

When I meant bottom the implication was to the only bottom you could see since the hole is so deep.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 07:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but be realistic. Of they only gun I got I can't hide I'd probably try to hide it.

Plus the first thing I said was I disagree with a lot of the current regulation. I just talked through the point, partially kind of got where someone who doesn't know jack shit about it would, and how they look at it. Also, claiming today's bans are an inheritance of a 1930 law is a bit bold at best. 

And ask yourself why ban handguns? Cause they're easily concealed? Maaaaaybe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 05:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know a couple girls who told me that too. Oh it's just words he gets like that when he's mad. 
   
usually they were getting the shit beat of them too. 
   
If the person is willing to say that publicly he's probably willing to act or does act on it in a more private manner or criminally. Because that's pretty private shit unless you get caught. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 05:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah i heard they jsut keep pushing back the handgun sweep so they can get all the guns at once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 04:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The assault registration designations are dumb and give a bad name to actual legislation that might stop harm. 
  
I could see, criminals being dumb and all, that if you felt the need to reduce the length of the barrel to help conceal your weapon I don't need to wait for you to shoot anyone to arrest you for it. 
  
So while the criticism is fair, that particular point, in regards to someone trying to conceal kind of made sense to me. 
   
Part of it is hard to designate an assault weapon period. If both guns fire semi automatic how do you distinguish a hunting rifle with a 5 round mag and long distance optic vs something that could hold a ten round mag with a close/medium range optic? Unless one is bolt action you can't. Even doing it by caliber or bullet size would be difficult. And really both would hold a ten round magazine anyway. If we all ask ourselves what gun we would use to commit certain acts though that would go without saying.
   
So I think that's part of where it comes from. And the two major shootings we had that were terrorism related in this country very well would have had a hell of a better chance of being stopped with a Brady Bill kind of background check on them. I'm referring to Orlando and San Bernardino. The guys who bought those guns, legally, in both instances were found in hindsight to be have been investigated for terrorism, travel to Pakistan (not on our genius president's list), have connections to people arrested for terrorism, and immigration issues. The first one point in regard to the former and the last 2 regarding SB. 
   
Bitch at me all you want and make your points, I'm all for fair ownership, robust ownership even. Good gun owners biggest risk to anyone is to themselves. But the facts of these two shootings so thoroughly changed my mind it hurts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 04:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get a little frustrated with the don't register thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 04:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not to bust your imagination but i do think you'd still be able to see as far down as you would over the sandy part. or at least immediately under you. this looks so pronounced in the picture because it's from a bit further away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 04:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying there aren't real effects about long term loss of sleep. A lot of those studies, that I've read, especially the ones that equate your ability to drive to that of a drunk driver are often after 2 or 3 days of reduced sleep compared to true long term sleep study. 
   
So don't put words in my mouth. There's a stark difference between sleep deprivation and insufficient sleep. Consequently often those long term effect studies are *directly* conducted with conditions that effect sleep like sleep apnea.  
   
I was actually saying that you don't recuperate your sleep that way. That you'll maintain a sleep debt and won't actually help yourself. 
   
Don't be a dick if you want to make a point. But more than that your arrogance and generalizations just make you look, well, arrogant. And arrogance looks stupid.  
  
edit: The implication of what I was saying very much was that if he's getting by on 6 hours and feels fine, for him, it's probably okay. The other point is from my own experience of doing shift work and recognizing my own body adapted pretty damn well. Especially in a field with a decent amount of oversight, constant driving, and solid QA/QI.  
  
Also, as a generalization, if people couldn't get used to it a lot more med students would be killing people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 23:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont think a guy who's dropped IV's a few tubes, while mostly treating blasts, gsw's, and penetrating trauma should be handed a medic certification.  
  
Medics aren't there to be trauma all stars and the interventions they are good at, in a trauma or critical situation, are also in a place the golden hour actually applies to.   
  
Come stateside with real medical calls you can't jump the gun on, reading EKG's, 12 leads, and uber reduced transport times? EMT is fine not sure they should be handeda Medic card though. 
  
And that's a fine job to start at too. That is giving vets jobs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 23:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This makes a good point toward why it transfers nationally to EMT. I think a better point is that it's one of few things outside of mechanics and computers that'll transfer out of the military.  
   
That said it's also anecdotal. Most people I know who were special ops kind of shit usually weren't idiots either.  
  
CA eh, lotta buddies went out there from NYC.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 23:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my understanding is that everyone is different but falls into a 6/7-8/9 area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 23:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eh i think like anything we adapt and get used to shit. and get better at sleeping less even if our ideal time is a couple hours more than what we get a night. 
   
for the first few weeks yeah, you'll do the sleep debt thing and is u sleep 2 hours less than what you eprsonally should be doing after 4 or 5 days it'll show. but after a month? you're probably fine. 
   
that said, if you're doing 5-6 hours a night and knocking out for 10-12 on the weekends that's just your body resetting that debt you earned. if that makes sense. like u get 25 hours sleep instead of the 40 you might need or 25.  
   
you put 20 in on the weekends you're body is trying to compensate/make up for some hours you lost last week and prep u for the coming week.  
  
sleep's pretty interesting shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 22:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Need someone to tell you that, catch it on camera, or see it happen. Need a warrant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 19:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not even you're thinking too much like a non criminal. As long as they're not driving when the APB/bolo goes out they're good. So a garage to put it on a car trailer or place to strip it for part or change plates/paint job are enough. Could be taking it a couple miles away to a garage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 19:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also curious where I could see one of these? Museum? To be fair to my eye when I did see pics online I was a bit skeptical silver still looks like silver with a patina. Not even sure if coins patina honestly.

Edit: I like learning about old stuff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 19:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow and I get it too. Like I flirted in antiques for a bit. It became 1, 2, 3 kind of thing. This though? You google 1804 or 1870 you get values before fake pages. Always why I never bought shit I didn't know or had someone I could call about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 17:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ketamine would be more appropriate for prehospital care. Milky solution is just so commonly associated with porpofol and I've heard of some doctors doing some crazy stuff in Europe.  
   
Yeah I guess my point is those civilians who made that assumption don't need to know better about whether he was on drugs. Shame on them for judging and presuming. That said, you're in the field you at least know better to judge a presume, let alone what an actual person on cocaine looks like (nothing like that scene) and it wouldn't matter if he was. So leave it to people who don't know better.  
   
On one hadn I want to tell you this would have happened at some point. Something would make you think, I can't believe I saw that. On the other it might not ever get worst than this. It could but probably not. Might see some alternatively just as bad things though.  
   
Just kind of comes with the territory. Do your job, do your best. See someone about it if it really eats at you. You learn to deal with it though and it's not all that bad. If it really didn't bother you that much then maybe reconsider what you do no reason to keep traumatizing yourself with traumatic event. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 16:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lolol
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 06:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how'd you make it sound so satisfying? 
  
lol i'm kidding. sometimes i watch this and think man that's cool. sometimes i think damn, they're crazy. and sometimes i think it's both cool and a bit crazy, in a respectable paying attention to detail (the baby dovetails) kind of way. 
    
super cool tho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 06:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How often do people see real ones of these though? I'd at least go get them checked out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 06:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that's some shit to witness. I'm curious where you're from that they give, probably propofol, on scene of an accident? 
  
Not that the guy didn't need it. That's some shit man. I'm a paramedic and saw a few things while I was working every once in a while some shit really happens that's like that, just traumatizing on a whole nother level.  
  
In NYC every so often we get someone who gets caught between a subway car and the platform at the waist. You'd think, they have to pass out, but much of the blood gets trapped in the torso and they stay conscious as the heart pumps, the lungs breathe, and the brain gets oxygen.
  
To be fair calling them a 'druggy' or something really isn't fair. There's not evidence to that. Burn victims often are conscious after they've been burned. What kills them is the lungs being burned from hot air and filling up with liquid. Or the smoke. This is just something terrible that happens to somebody. No stigma should be attached or tragedy excused on the grounds of something that is speculation. Even for that matter if it were true, no one deserves to go through that. Absolutely not, and cocaine certainly wouldn't keep you alive through that at all.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 05:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol right? like it's some nuanced for of the gif and a a real treat blossoming with all the possibilities it could take you to. 
  
teetering on the edge of your seat, establishes a good central character you care about, possible a solid supporting role as well, real stakes, options for the conflict and then, just then, finally delivers on the one you didn't quite see coming but is just, absolutely, just as fulfilling as anything you could imagine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 09:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> totally get that. 
   
and totally lost on the contextual knowledge of even beginning to understand it.  
  
that said, it is slightly ironic you used such a well written sentence to explain that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 04:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so are these shared with a sense of irony?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 04:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah for sure. A big part of it to me...I almost feel like it very much falls on *how* we intervene rather than why or the actual 'what' persay (intervening at all). 
   
On one hand I want to say, yeah isolationism! But in reality globalism is here. Now do we need to wield our expansionist (might be more appropriate term for the 21st reality of the situation)  military and maybe just do it with our economy? I don't know you get one without the other. Or at least one with on such favorable terms. Now on the other hand, ethically and morally there's a whole ton of shit that comes with jsut the economy too. Hell, arguably more so than popping a few bases in a few countries. We're not exporting materials we're often manufacturing and importing our own.  
  
But they certainly work amicably hand in hand. And I guess, I absolutely hate the war hawk kind of "we need to do it to keep x in check!' but there's an element of truth to it. Part of me though doesn't quite get why we don't, in a sense, turn the other cheek and win over people more through friendship rather than aggressive posturing. Particularly when it comes to Iran or Cuba. Cuba is probably the best example of how hard it is to change an ideology. The country is absolutely ravaged by the embargo. And in today's world you don't get everyone cooperating all the time either.   
  
I do feel a more 'give em a chance' way of looking at it would be better overall. Now with things like someone like Saddam or North Korea obviously that's not going to work. But a place like Iran, specifically at the moment? I don't see why not.  
  
And then you have the very real points of, why weren't we on the ground in SUdan or Rawanda? Like *what the fuck?* You want to play good cop, fucking be the good cop. Hell, in rawanda if we flew a few f-16's overhead they would have shit their bed they committed the massacre with machetes. It's also not like that happened over the course of a week it was a few months. 
   
So I guess my biggest complaint is the "biggest dick in the room approach" and the hypocritical nature of it all. With all that said, being on the ground in Rwanda or Sudan, or today in Syria or Libya wouldn't particularly be a good thing either. So it's very, tough and makes it all that much easier to lean toward isolationist tendencies and arguably, we were in those cases.  
  
Lol so yeah, nuanced perhaps starts to describe it. Lol. I don't expect a response to this either, I know it's long. I often don't get to have such an amicable exchange and get my views off my chest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, in regard to Latin America we're acting a regional power. But global/regional yeah interchagne em. 
   
That said, it just feels like it's a part of politics. Like it's always been a role someone will take, so why not us? I'm not saying I entirely agree with it. Like most issues though it's a hell of a lot more complex than people allow it to be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright to be clear if you really want to get into it pointing out the covert operations we've tried to pull off I think is way different. Sure people hear and find out about some of that eventually. But it's not like immediately clear that it was 'America'. 
   
Afghanistan got arms that we bought but all that training took place in Pakistan by Pakistanis. Sure we paid for the guns but it was largely Pakistan and their own militarily run camps by their ISI. Sure CIA support? Of course. But it was really Pakistan doing it on our behalf with us picking up the tab for the guns.  
   
Pakistan get out of it? A big spot as a regional player, arms, and proxy groups to use for its own uses.   
  
I'm not going to act like there wasn't bad choices made. 100% Iraq was a cluster fuck that didn't need to happen. And then when it did didn't need to happen as poorly as it did. The execution was just shit. 
  
On the grand scale of things is that bad? I don't know. Sure ISIS popped up but that was in the making for almost as long as the invasion and jihadists were coming out of the Syrian Revolution anyway. There would ahve been someone to step up and take an al-Qaeda role.   
  
I'm not saying we're not at fault. And when Bush did go to war it was clearly the operation of a few bad actors believing they were acting on a good reason. The intel on the chemical weapons wasn't entirely sold to the CIA but the U.N. did believe he was producing weapons since he barred their inspectors. Not sure enough or reason to go to war but there was sort of enough there to sell it. And that's what he did.  
  
When you compare what is a few truly in the wrong kind of moves Iraq, Iran, Cuba with all the shit people usually clump with it as our 'imperialism' it doesn't seem like a fair accusation. ANd I'm not sure the other option isn't without risk either. Inaction is dangerous too. We know how the world turned out from our acting but we don't know what might have happened not acting. So it's easy to say 'oh, this is what's wrong with it because you did x' but if we didn't is it better Pakistan rises on its own with the help of Iran? Is it better we don't have the help of Jordanian intelligence or cooperation from the Egyptian government. 
   
I also think it's important to look at it from the perspective of people from those regions. The biggest criticism of America after our arms support of Afghanistan in the 80's was that we *didn't* stay, or that our money didn't at least.   
   
I don't know it just seems like a cheap stone to throw especially when you tie a string around the stone with a list of complaints like "all the bases we have around the world" or some shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'm not going to disagree with that. It's not that much different for me as a citizen as it is for the other country. They don't see much more of our aid or any of that other shit than i do. I guess it's kind of a perception/reality thing. In the sense that the perception of it very much is its reality. 
   
That said, everyone has been a part of middle eastern politics for a long time either because of colonialism or oil. They sort of bombed us first. Or rather had been bombing shit for a long time before anyone did anything about it.  
   
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 07:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For sure, historically we got involved in governments we arguably had no business getting involved in.  
   
That said, it was always because we picked a side though. For forever bigger powers have always played a role in regional politics by influencing the states around them, either covertly or overtly.   
  
Of course it won't always be a good thing. I'm not saying were free from all fuck ups or have a totally clear conscious.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 06:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well technically it's two different versions of the same word. So it's a cheap shot grammar wise. populace is the noun, populous is the adjective. While you're right and when using American people would probably be most fitting, it's sort of a cheap shot to take from a grammar perspective. 
   
Ironic af tho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 06:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, I get frustrated when people point the finger at American "imperialism" when we export as much culture and influence as we do military products to many of these countries, as well as hard cash and aid in order to set up out 'imperialistic' bases. 
  
You act like we sail out ship in, fly a plane off it, land, plant a flag, whip our dick and piss on the ground and go "Merica!! bitches..." 
   
Let's stop exporting any products too. Limit our exposure on youtube and the internet. Sure as hell don't let em see our movies or listen to our music. 
   
I'm sorry I am being condescending. Deep down I would love an isolationist or a limited foreign policy approach. The reality is globalization is the way the world works today. A major part of that is able to have influence and bargaining chips. One of ours, and it's one no one else has, is our military. So while I'm not 'for' it in an expansionist sense I don't think backtracking is the right path. I also think think it's a cheap stone to throw. Especially considering we only got to where we were through billions of dollars in aid. It wasn't free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 06:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GDP is representative of that to an extent though, is it not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 06:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't as % of GDP most representative though? 
  
I understand why someone might want to see it as a % of budget but that's not nearly as comparative as a % of GDP. Def would appreciate a better understanding here though.   
   
I imagine the budget one would look closer to the population one than any of em. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone seen the new Verizon on-demand menu? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 06:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's horrible. And a great example of what might have been a good idea in a meeting but the actual implementation is really bad. Especially compared to the straightforward text list and 4 or 5 wide movie images they had previously. You could scroll through it quickly, find what you wanted easily.  
   
Now it's this clunky, image driven mess. It's two columns and they run for a while. Slow to get through and sometimes hard to identify what you're highlighting at times. 
   
I think part of it is inspired to get sponsored content up front and recommended. It may be a driving factor in the change. I'm going to see if I can get some images of it for a before/after. Think I may be stuck taking photos with my phone and emailing them to myself though. Just a really good example of something that isn't practical and ultimately detrimental to the user. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ChineseEnglish] Written at the right of a painting of a tree (plum I think) but still a part of the overall 'picture'. Is it just the artist's signature? Small chance it's Korean. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 05:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 04:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could be respect. And the bot's translation, brotherly really isn't that different. So I'm going to say that it's a pretty accurate description. 
    
Def could be wrong. But I imagine if someone translated that or saw brotherhood as a translation it might stand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was only wikipedia that referred to her possibly not being with CNN when she sent the emails.  
  
As for her actual removal from CNN she was already suspended in October. 
   
The timeline is something like this. And really man, we've both spent more time talking about something a lady did, for her party, in regards to a *primary* debate.   
  
She was with or a 'contributor' to CNN when she sends the emails. I saw one thing that kind of made that a little fuzzy but it seems she didn't head the DNC till June or July. I think it's also important to clarify this a bit, her role at CNN. It wasn't as a journalist.   
  
The nature of people today they want conflict in their shows, even their 'news' shows and shit like that. So she was a talking head at CNN that would always err to take the liberal view. She really, absolutely, was not a journalist. 
  
And some people, as the WaPo article claimed, a few others too, that it's the name of the game in politics. And that there's a level of expectation that people would behave like this. Part of me believes it too. No one on the Trump team would think twice of doing this nor would they out it/turn it down if it happened.   
  
But whenever the debate was she emails the questions that she gets. Then when Wikileaks leaks the documents in October she still heads the DNC but is forced to resign. When she headed the DNC she was suspended from CNN as a contributor. It's pretty much in every major news source.
   
https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/the-fix/wp/2016/11/07/donna-brazile-is-totally-not-sorry-for-leaking-cnn-debate-questions-to-hillary-clinton/?utm_term=.6d3ac5590833  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 10:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair resignations are often done instead of being fired. 
   
That said she wasn't even technically working for them at the time though. So it's not really like they could fire her from a job she was suspended from because she took the head of the DNC position. 
  
So I'd say she had a lot of pressure on her from CNN. To publicly give in a resignation from a job she technically wasn't holding? So they  could show they condemned her individual actions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 06:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you lack a fundamental understanding of how the news works though. Almost all news stations subscribe to the AP and Reuters and all participate with one another to be able to report on news the other one does. It's often missed but at the very beginning or end of a snippet they'll say reported by the AP or reported by WaPo. 
   
So the facts are the facts and they're gathered and shared by everyone. You're right in the sense that an individual station might have some bias in determining how those facts should be perceived, particularly in their impact.  But ultimately that's your job as a viewer. 
  
I don't disagree with you because you have an opposing view. I can only disagree and respect an opposing view when it isn't outlandish. Claiming that the media is a creation to control the public's thinking is outlandish. Especially when a good chunk of the media that reports on this stuff has no skin in 'controlling' anyone's point of view and still reports on the same topics. Because while profit isn't a defining factor in what they do you can't let a story go by and and lose your regular viewers/readers to another news source because you didnt' cover it.  
   
See what you're claiming with the misrepresentation or omissions just doesn't happen. What you deem to be someone omitting facts probably isn't. It more likely is something that wasn't relevant to the story despite how you feel about it.  
   
And this is my issue. See your flat out denying that quotes are something to be taken at vace value. I don't take it as the truth, because anyone can say something for any reason. But I judge the person they are interviewing, I take the quote in context, and I arrive at my own conclusion. That's the whole point of thew news. Is to provide you facts so you can reach your own decisions.  
   
Once in a while a quote is taken out of context but rarely is it openly reported that way unless there was clear wrongdoing on the part of the initial reporter. And when that happens people offer corrections and admit wrongdoing. They admit they took journalist x from the Wall Street Journal at face value and reported the story like many other people did. But this or that part of it wasn't factually correct. 
   
The most recent thing I can see taken out of context recently was the Obama video when he's talking with a Russian diplomat or Putin. THe recording is of him saying "Ill have more flexibility after the election." Everyone presumed he was talking about sanctions. The clip was from like 2012 I think and there's 0 indication of what he's talking about.  
   
That clip wasn't reported on regular news sources. Because that clip was truly out of context.   
  
The best news outlets set the standard though. I think to a degree the point you're making shouldnt so much fault the news outlets but fault the people viewing them. The only reason that there would be any narrative to feed to them is because they aren't willing to think for themselves. I'm not sure what else a news outlet could do besides give you a quote, a situation, and let you decide if it was right or wrong. Liek the Flynn thing, the guy was clearly in the wrong. And the intelligence community feared he could be blackmailed. So they leaked it to the Press. But everyone else is defending the guy because it came from a 'leak.' And it's like, thats kind of missing the point. We had someone who was going to compromise himself and his position to act in the good interest of America. He needed to be held accountable.  
  
I think to a large degree the fault does lie on the people. The largest threat to democracy is an uninformed electorate. It's true. Unfortunately I think more than the media right now we have a President and an Administration who feeds a narrative that the people eat up without fact checking a single thing the guy says. That's infinitely more dangerous than the media. At least the media has these 10 or 12 places you can go to to look for an answer or get a different side to it. The White House is just one source with one version of a story. And if they're willing to lie they're going to feed a story to epople who have no where else to turn. And aren't willing to trust the news when they call him out on it.  
   
There is one thing you're missing though. That's in today's world, and this very much goes along with your point, the way we use surf engines and use the web creates this world where eveything is agreeable to our views and our points. It, essentially, gerrymanders our news. The search engines will continually feed us back to places we like and have views that are similar to ours.    
  
So while there's some validity to your point I don't think the fault lies to the media. Not entirely at least. I think much more of it is cast on the people consuming it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 06:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it makes it pretty clear that cnn wasn't happy with how she behaved. I wouldn't for a second imply it was condoned when the owner/ceo used words like disgusted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 22:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did fire her. And she had stepped away as a CNN and ABC contributor when she become Interim Head of the DNC.  
   
As for timelines for all that some places say she stepped away in the Spring, when she sent the emails. 
   
Either way she was fired for it. Zucker, the head of CNN, in a leaked document is quoted as calling her behavior 'disgusting.' 
  
And from a media perspective, I have to agree entirely. It's frustrating she'd risk such backlash when people already view the media so poorly.  
   
My biggest recommendation is to not watch your news. Read it. Or if you want to watch it go with the BBC or Al-Jazeera. Very thorough, super thorough and fair reporting.   
  
Also Reuters and the Associated Press. Neither of them is defined by profits or has a network to answer to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 21:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not really anecdotal though. If you have questions about something a journalists says or does, you can check who or what its source was. It's why they use quotes so much (and laws protecting their sources). Because it shows the facts directly from the mouth of someone who is involved with the issue they are reporting. 
   
Sure is there a slant when it comes to MSNBC or Fox? yeah a little bit but it's not anything that can't be seen through. And further, I'd argue don't get your news from watching the television. Read the Wall Street Journal and the Washington Post. 
   
If you would rather watch something watch the BBC or Al-Jazeera. It's thorough, fact based reporting.  
   
But it's also not anecdotal that it's for profit when news companies make up such a small amount of the profit of their larger corporations. That's facts. CNN is 3% of Time Warner's revenue. ABC is 1% of Disney. Fox and NBC are similarly low % of their corporations total revenue. Being sustainable and profitable is a benefit but it isn't a compromising factor in their reporting.  
   
Jesus man, I can't take an opinion seriously that is actually anecdotal and potentially flat out delusional.    
  
Reporting facts isn't information control. They're facts man. Do some stories get bumped out because of page space and stuff? Of course. But I'd love to know what should bump out what our President is doing or the ethics of our National Security Adviser?  
   
I'd bet you prefer infowars over the 'mainstream' news. And again, I wouldn't watch your news. Read it. If you do want to watch it go to the BBC, they don't have skin in the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 21:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stand corrected I was under the impression it was the debate regulator who did it, especially in the context of the conversation that I was having. The other guy was putting the blame on CNN. Obviously the DNC isn't going to fire her for that though. I mean, it's a bold move for their candidate. Unethical af, sure, but politics isn't exactly a beaming beacon of ethics. 
  
And to be fair, it wasn't a presidential debate it was a primary debate. So something that would even more so be handled in house by the DNC.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 21:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i do man. I love watching it. I love cracking my window to listen to it. Sometimes with classical music too. I love listening to it land and pitter-patter. Or even drive and slam.  
  
Thunderstorms are great ofc 3 Thunder Lightning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 21:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright the way the press works is that there's a close knit group of reporters called the 'pool'. Often briefings are done with just the pool. When the White House opens up the briefing to media outlets outside that pool it's often open to everyone. Especially, and this is the point, when media outlets request to be allowed in. That's the difference. 
  
Trump denied access to outlets the requested it even when he was opening the briefing up past the pool. 
  
There's a stark difference there. Every public official plays favorites with specific reporters but when it comes to something like press briefing picking and choosing what outlets should be allowed into one and denying others is dangerous territory.   
   
Here's the thing, they don't have to blindly attack him. The guy isn't presidential and he doesn't execute things well. You don't need to blindly attack someone who wrote an executive order that wasn't constitutional. The fact that the ban could even be called a 'muslim ban' isn't the media's fault. It was a poorly written document that was rushed and ultimately failed. 
   
His national security adviser was a fail. the phone call with teh australian prime minister was a fail. 
   
The other executive orders he did? Standard conservative first 100 day stuff. And a continuation of policies that people aren't in line with. Like doubling down on the war on drugs. An executive order on the AHA that didn't have any results or impact.   
   
The reality is that leading up to the primaries Trump got a ton of air time without repercussions. People didn't take him seriously but they still aired him like *look at this!*.  
   
After the primaries they took him a bit more seriously but the media is in campaign mode and it's, at best, a 50% focus between the two candidates. 
  
Now he's in the driver seat and everyone is paying attention. Everyone is going to be watching every move, especially with the means he took to get where he is at. Which, on the campaign trail, were arguably in poor taste. Now that he's there and in control people are expecting you to meet the expectations of that role. 
  
One of those expectations is for the American people to trust their President. When he lies to us. Blatantly lies to us or tries to answer questions by talking about how much of a electoral college win he had in the election and claiming it was the 'greatest ever' people don't see a President. 
   
And a big part of that is on the campaign trail everyone said 'don't take him literally' or he doesn't mean everything he says. It's clear that he does though. Now we need him to be called to task when he lies or makes something up or claims something outlandish. It's because he's proven he does mean what he says and now he's the one in charge. He's in the seat and that's part of the job, is being held accountable, clarifying what you say, and delivering ot the American people an understanding of what's going on. A big part of that is trust and he's losing it quickly. I had high hopes for him. After the election he gave those interviews and his first press conference and I said, man this guy is good. All that campaign shit and now look at this *a president*.  
  
Then he actually got into office and went back to campaign Donald. 
   
And I'm not here to argue the merits of his travel ban. It's not a bad idea to review policy that's 4 years old. It's the execution of it. The fact that it was done in a way that could be perceived as a 'Muslim ban'. There's no reason to do this either through executive order or publicly for that matter. Let alone in a way that the constitution could hold it up. If he really believed there were threats trying to get in through the refugee program and then it gets held up in the courts, you have literally defeated your own purpose in creating the ban in the first palce. It's laughable at best and desperately sad and confused at worst.
   
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 20:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her? It was a guy...lol wtf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 20:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah man, I really can't have a legitimate conversation with someone who truly believe the media exists to control the public's beliefs. You clearly have never met journalists or know any.  
   
The kind of people who control beliefs are the Alex Jones types. When he gives you a scenario, without evidence, and tells you what you should think about. He brings his own conclusions to a situation and expects you to agree with it.  
   
The current media actually doesn't do things without evidence. And they abide by journalistic standards. Often it's done for you to come up with your own conclusions on the situation. That's the beauty of the free press. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You get a patch, you get a patch! We're all getting patches! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I passed on LoE. Going to make sure i complete BRM now though. Or i still have it I guess after it gets out of rotation. but anyway I already have it.  
  
Hmm LoE...eh guess I'll just have to make due. Not going to buy it, didn't really like it. I do understand that limits me though. Not with a new expac coming out. 
  
Thanks again. it's funny I just sort of gave the same advice to someone else. Like BRM, LOE and Granc Championship are all out of rotation in April. I'd consider waiting for the expac but I'm sure someone else might fill you in better.  
  
lol thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but I think to be honest, compared to 2015, 2016 was a lot more difficult. Things got competitive around rank 15 and was pretty tough. Before then, in 2015 it was much more casual to rank up. A grind and challenging but didn't feel unobtainable.  
   
After WooTG it got pretty tough, it felt like. I'm a super casual player but around rank 15-13 it got really challenging. It almost felt like I need more than one deck to rotate just to rank up efficiently.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I'd spread it out over relevant expacs. I'm definitely out of the meta for a bit right now. I'd consider if what expansions are close to being moved out of rotation for regulation. And possible consider saving some money for this new expansion. It's releasing in April.  
  
With its release the Grand Tournament will get bumped out of standard format. Along with Blackrock Mountain and The League of Explorers.   
  
So, I'm not sure what exactly it should be spent on, other than advising maybe to spread it around, but def consider at least that. Cards from those three sets will only be good in Standard, for the next month and some change, month and a half.  
  
Someone else please help him out a bit? Got a paying customer here!  
  
edit: after reading some other posts, I'd def wait for the expansion, besides maybe some classic cards if you feel the need you could buy a few packs. But wait till someone else answer for a clearer picture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone catch me up a bit? It's been a while. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I briefly played at the start of WotOG. I disenchanted a class or two and basically built a mage deck. Mage has always been kind of what I fell in love with (mage in wow, yes i'm guilty). It worked out well since it's always been meta/pseudo meta and manageable. 
  
Anyway, I hit rank 13 or 14 that season after a week or so and then just never came back. I was happy the mage deck I built actually turned out to be close to the meta one in general and sort of stands up on its own as is anyway.   
  
I'm curious where the meta is out. What decks I might look into. Do I need to drop any money on it to catch up at all? If I do what should I put the money into? 
   
Anything at all to kind of bring me up to speed would be cool. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah for sure I hear that. It's a fair point.   
  
That said, personally I liked earning gold and then picking who I'd get next. So many of the heroes are low gold amounts too I was able to amass a pretty big collection quickly. Then when you earn enough for a newer hero it's pretty cool.   
  
Again, my biggest point I think is you get what you pay for. So totally F2P is not going to have the same level of engagement as something you pay for. I mean really I would recommend him buy something like Civ 6 or Wildlands or whatever and then have it for good with one initial purchase. If he can't afford that I wouldn't limit myself to things that don't have advancement structures in them. That's a natural part of gaming. A game that I don't need to spend money on though but still has one of those is absolutely still F2P, despite him not feeling like it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woha, negligence? The employee showed negligence, not even negligence. It's flat out wrongdoing. But he was chosen among a lot of people who wanted that spot. I think you'd be hard pressed to prove they lacked due diligence in selecting him.  
  
So, with that said, the network takes some heat for that for sure. No denying that. And of course the apologized for it and the guy was fired. lol come on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 05:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you guys now how much of a % CNN is of TIme Warner's total revenue?   
  
3%  
  
ABC of disneys? 1% 
  
NBC 1% 
   
So, it isn't really to make money but to make enough to keep operating. The truth is most journalist do care about the truth and do care about reporting facts.   
  
But even if the media isn't the best what Trump is doing is dangerous. It isn't his place to demonize the media. Especially with the implication that people get their facts from him.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 05:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd argue that he might be attempting to censor it. The other day he picked the normal 'pool' of reporters to a press briefing and then hand picked a few other media places. Then when a few more places asked to be allowed since they were bringing in more reporters than the normal 'pool' they were denied. 
   
It might not be a big deal and it happens sometimes anyway. In the context of his contentious relationship with the press it very well could be the start of something that's a dangerous road. 
  
It very well could be sending the message that the news organizations should be reporting more positively of the president too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 05:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I think it's a fair criticism to claim that clicks and revenue have effected what the media leans toward posting on the web it doesn't diminish when they do more serious work as well. It's not really the President's place though. Especially since our President lies. A lot. Doesn't fact check what he says nor does he try to.  
   
And to a degree it is the media job to hold people accountable when normal systems don't, can't or won't. I think we saw that precisely with Michael Flynn. That was some pretty messed up shit he did particularly by undermining the current administration the day they announced the sanctions and retaliation. 
  
The concern among members of the intelligence community was that Russia could use it to blackmail Flynn. The most telling bit was that he lied to the vice president about it. So he knew it was wrong and not something he should have done and that he possibly could have gotten in trouble. So the individuals in the intelligence community concerned about the potential blackmail told the President. The President didn't act on it, despite knowing it compromised Flynn and potentially could be used to compromise his decision making down the line.  
 
So they tell the press. Which is exactly what Russia would have threatened to do in order to blackmail him. The pressure of it going public got his resignation. It also got us a public official who wasn't at risk of making decisions based on his fear of a scandal, public humiliation and losing his position. 
   
Trump's lambasting the media is really not good. Trust in the media is already low. That's okay to a degree. But when the President calls them an 'enemy of the people' with the intention of filling that role they did you essentially lose the free press. We don't ahve a government sponsored news station in America. Nor is it a role the government should have. Your press should remain separate from the administration and the official government channels.Which is also why when he cherry picks certain news outlets for press opportunities he's exerting jsut a little bit too much influence on who and how the news will be reported. It's one thing for there to be a bias from a news channel if all the channels report on it. Then you can at least hear everyone's bias and make a decision for yourself. It's another thing to only allow a certain group of places to report it and allow for a single bias or similar bias to come out on the story. That's dangerous.  
   
Really it comes down to the press should be free. Even if it sucks it shouldnt be held accountable to the president. THe president is held accountable to us. One of the ways that happens is through the Press. Public pressure gets shit done often. The press is free and should be able to be so. Does it deserve to be criticized? Sure. But with valid criticisms. The President doesn't even make valid criticisms. Nor is it his place really to criticize it. Especially when he comes at it from the angle of taking the facts directly from him is a valid replacement. Especially since he lies. 
   
   
Trump bashing the media and eroding the trust of people in it more so than it already is while also presenting himself as the only source of the 'truth' you should be tuning into is beyond dangerous.The media is run by corporations and is accountable to shareholders. That said, your average journalist and average editor do believe in trying to do good meaningful work. They're not out there to corrupt the truth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 05:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eh it was the actions of the one dude not so much the network. He had the questions. The reality is, contrary to what people think, journalists do tend have standards and ethics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 05:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol no one is disagreeing with that. haha, that's for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 05:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's just not true. No one said the Russian influence delegitimized the President. They said the Russian influence was present in the election. But measuring that to what degree was impossible. The Dossier released by Buzzfeed was clearly stated as being unverified. Although currently the intelligence community seems to have verified a bunch of the less salacious points. 
   
No one is claiming the president isn't legitimate. In fact when reports of Russian influence did surface while Obama was still in office they didn't want to have too big of a retaliation. By acting on too big a scale they feared it would lead to delegitimizing the election by making people think the influence was more than it was. 
   
Man it's so frustrating when people don't properly read what these new institutions actually said. Even Fox defended CNN's reporting as sound. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mentioned HotS too. I think OP is a bit confused between the nature of MOBA's not having a story attached to them and since that's the case a game including an advancement mechanic. 
   
With no story MOBA's have nothing for you to work toward. People enjoy earning gold from their games and being able to utilize it toward something. Especially with different game modes that don't all have an experience or ranking element to them.  
   
And I can see why he kind of shuns them because a lot of 'freemium' models include an advancement mechanic that is insanely slow but offer payment to skip it or skip ahead.  
  
That's different than an advancement model that is setup with the context of you playing the game over the course of a month, three months, 6 months or a year. One with regular gains and loot, prizes or using your gold to purchase things. Which is seperate from using cash to buy things that are purely cosmetic. 
   
heroes does let you purchase heroes of buy bundles of them. And the bundles are good deals. I only purchased it when I felt the game had earned my money by then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HotS too. You earn gold through playing to unlock characters. And there's giveaways a few times a year to gain heroes. 
  
You can pay money to buy heroes but you really, truly, don't have to. I didn't for at least 6 months and that's only when  I wanted to put some money into the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he's really limiting himself if it is the gold structure of League or HotS that he feels isn't F2P.  
  
IMO you get what you pay for. And having to earn something from a game, like gold to unlock heroes, gives you something to work toward a little bit. Otherwise a MOBA wouldn't really have anything to work toward. Lol and it would be a lot easier not to log in for a day. 
  
Truly and solely F2P there's really only a few games that offer you depth and are great games at the same time in that model. 
   
I think what's awesome, in today's world, is that people have figured out how to not make their games Freemium but still have an element of afvancement that isn't P2W or behind a paywall at all. Like the games are truly F2P mechanically and in context. You pay for cosmetics or because you're impatient. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heroes of the storm. It's a MOBA from blizzard. I didn't spend a dollar on it for the first 6 months or so? Or until  i wanted to. They have free heroes on rotation through the hero pool. You can also try out any hero to get a feel for them before spending the gold you earn. In that sense it does have an advancement mechanic. But that isn't P2W or freemium by any stretch. It's a part of the game so you can actually work toward earning something, being that it is a MOBA that element is lost since there's no 'story'.  
  
  

Edit: I see you mention LoL, HotS is the same category of game. And while skins cost money and you can buy heroes with money, you don't have to. So, in that sense,you could argue it isn't entirely F2P but you really only pay for cosmetic skins. The gameplay itself has no P2W element to it.   
  
The games are 20 minutes long instead of the 40min-1 hour that DotA and LoL usually have. It's fast paced, a lot of maps, and a lot of Blizzard characters. So if like their games you'll love this one.  
  
I think you pay for what you get. And F2P while it's awesome isn't going to offer you nearly the experience as a game that costs a little bit of money. Heroes of the Storm I think found a great balance between what is truly a F2P model and one where you can choose to invest some money into it. I think after playing it the decision becomes easy because it's well made and a lot of fun. But this general idea applies to all games. 
  
Like I said, I didn't put a dollar into the game because I like to feel out if the game earned my money. Since they are offering it without charge or by choice, I opt to feel it out first. When I did choose to spend money it was like $15-$20 bucks on a bundle that got me tons of value for what I paid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why donate somewhere with any doubt? https://www.charitynavigator.org/index.cfm?bay=search.summary orgid=4770  
  
also, you're presuming all this stuff. what about the other questions you could be asking? 
  
what about all the male tigers?  
  
Why didn't I donate to the charities helping to care for the tigers now? Especially since I'm concerned about their conditions currently?
   
why breed so many? 
   
could they care for them past having space? 
   
Why did I presume they had open space? They only allowed them in open space in 2011, on a rotating basis, is what I read wrong?   
   
How did the corruption in Thailand effect them?  
   
Are the claims of trafficking true? Or are the accusations warranted enough to proceed with caution?  
  
How many sources did I check? Why didn't I just share those with these people to make my point? 
   
Why am I presuming stuff to make a point beside just trying to argue against overwhelming evidence?  
  
The U.N. and international community made statements condemning them after reviewing the evidence, is there more to this? 
   
Am I really looking at this from the Tigers perspective? Really?  
   
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely not. Lol...wasn't the case at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no, because it sounds a bit ridiculous in hindsight. I'm not going to say it's fake or real. It is a bit outlandish and I won't fault someone for a slightly overly cynical approach to anything on the internet that isn't sourced first hand with proof. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except it's a shitty cause. The evidence against the sanctuary was overwhelming and the account from volunteers are all over the place.  
  
There's donating and then there's altruistic donating. That's kind of like selfish donating. It's done to make themselves feel better without thinking about the consuquences. Let's theoretically say, given there's two sides to this, that there's a 50/50 shot they're good vs bad. 
  
And they claim he or she is arguing for concern from the tigers point of view. Right now those tigers are in the gov't hands and Four Paws and a couple other groups stepped up to help care for those tigers. If they really believed in helping the tigers, no matter who held them now, they'd donate to a charity helping the government care for the tigers. That'd make sense.  
  
Or alternatively, the ten bucks could go to another charity that doesn't have a 50/50 shot of being a bad or dangerous group. It's called effective altruism. 
   
That's the 17 min version [here](https://www.ted.com/talks/peter_singer_the_why_and_how_of_effective_altruism). 
   
This is part one of the longer version, it's [1 hour](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F-PGmHeYzlI) 
    
What he or she is missing here is that people aren't arguing to be part of the hivemind and about being right. He is presuming I care less about these tigers than I do about being right. That's not the case at all. Actually the contrary. So it's important not to be misled and put your faith in something that very well, with a large body of evidence, isn't helping anyone but themselves. And for people to put the resources to stopping things like trafficking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, and this is kind of killing me now. Please don't presume things when making a point. And yes, you are presuming. Saying something like "would colunteers be there if they were abusing tigers?" doesn't account for the fact the volunteers weren't allowed into certain areas for the monks. And shit that you clearly didn't read or hear about before jumping to your own conclusions. That was my problem with your initial claims. And now you're doing it again. "Could be" is the entire issue. And that's really the problem. You're claiming an alternative scenario without any basis for it. Without understanding a thing about Thailand too. It's a country that is described has having *endemic* corruption. To suggest the gov't wasn't getting a piece of the pie...It's probably why the center wasn't shut down in 2005 to be honest. It's also why suspicion of trafficking carries a bit more weight there. Sure it wasn't proven or prosecuted. That's the kind of thing that never would in Thailand because of who was involved. But it certainly may have been wrong enough for them to put an end to it. How that for an alternate could be? And if that is the case, compared to what's happening to the tigers now, it's a relief no more cubs are being sent away as pets or to private zoos or for pelts or rugs or using the teeth or fur or bones for medicine. Hell that region of the world uses all sorts of shit for medicine and they may not have even trafficked live tigers but their remains and remains of cubs and shit. And that's fucking wrong too. So that's my problem with your point. It's conjecture at best. And you clearly lack an understanding both of what it was like on the ground and the region as a whole. The tigers point of view. Really? Get a fucking grip. Anyone who knows shit about big cats knows having 100 of them together was a mistake from the start. To continue expanding that number? Those people had no care int heir heart. Have you even considered what they did with all the males? How the territory was worked out?  And from what I read it was only in 2011 that they were able to allow the tigers to experience open space, on a rotating schedule. There's concern for how they're being cared for now but they found skins, pelts and all sorts of shit. Fucking read something beside the Wikipedia page. 
   
Christ how old are you? I'm praying you're under 18 and an idealistic kid. Because if you're an adult who's lacking the critical thinking to actually come to conclusions about this, well, I guess it should be expected today. I think you read the wikipedia page, followed the cited sources there and didn't consider contrasting views because you took that *as the contrasting view*. Now that I'm actually looking into the accounts of the volunteers there and the large body of evidence present, including in the off limit areas from the volunteers, it's painfully clear this wasn't a good place. Especially with reports of the trafficking and tigers 'going missing.' 
   
Okay, even if they were breeding tigers illegally, do you suggest they wait until the problem gets larger? Think about what your saying. Anyone who knows anything about big animals, period, knows 100+ of them probably shouldn't be kept together like that. 
   
The problem had already grown large. And let's go with the illegal breeding. If that's why they were investigated initially in 2005, warned, and then continued to do it. Yes it would be appropriate to step in at that point. 
   
It also created a large amount of suspicion. Mostly due to the rate at which they were breeding them. Was 100 or 150 not enough for the tourist exhibition? Or maybe there was trafficking. If one fucking tiger was trafficked for its pelt shame on you. Really fucking shame on you. 
   
Besides that all the arguments for reason still stand. It's not appropriate. They absolutely should not have been breeding them. And you can't deny that with that many tigers it certainly raises some interesting questions as to why they would continue it. 
   
 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, thanks a lot. I guess, and normally I'm pretty good at googling, I jsut got a lot on the invasion. And the attempt to avoid it. This def paints a better picture and will certainly help me pursue the topic more thoroughly.  
   
Also, in context, the way people talk of how there was almost a 'coup' to by the Japanese to not surrender seemed sensationalized. Obviously invading Japan would be horrible but it presents almost like the U.S. was naive and had all their hope on the initial two bombs. 
   
Thanks again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 12:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pfft you're trusting the media nowadays to teach some smarty pants stuff like that? Hard enough trusting the science itself, but getting it through the media? A public funded one no less! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 12:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to ask you so many questions. lol.  
  
Man, I like to think I stay up on things that are myths and avoid common traps like that but that was one I didn't really question.   
   
I guess my biggest curiosities are what 'defines' and atmosphere then and what contributes to a palnet keeping one vs 'losing' it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 11:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah really, my first google search brought me to a times article. It doesn't alleviate the inadequacies of the gov't but any place that had tigers so that you could pet and feed them was a place not meant for tigers. 
   
The very notion of that is fucking absurd. They called it a zoo in the first paragraph and the owner disappeared?  Come on man. Really?  
   
Yes, seriously get a grip. Either actually learn about how these big cats are supposed to live or get some common sense before you point the finger at the person who tried to do something about the problem someone else created. 
   
Sorry I don't mean to shit on the fond memories of your backpack through Thailand and the time you fed a bowl of rice to a tiger. But at the time it had to occur to you that "this doesn't seem right" or maybe it didn't. Because in your ignorance you probably jsut thought "Oh different cultural, these wise buddhist monks trianed the tigers!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 11:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cats self harming could easily have been from just being relocated on its own. 
   
And I don't have to just read a headline. They dodged this once ten years ago, and I doubt that's the first time anyone said anything either. The government finally stepped in probably when it felt it didn't have a choice.  
   
I mean the fact they took 100+ cats alone seems irresponsible. "wasn't perfect?" Keeping a few tigers anywhere but a rehab or because they can't return to the wild is irresponsible. Let alone 100+ 
   
Oh come on. Anyone who knows anything about these animals knows it's irresponsible to keep them in a collection like that. Unless it's an animal sanctuary that's protected. But you know what the difference there is? It's actually a wild area that's protected. Not a 'sanctuary.' Whatever the fuck that is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 11:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're presuming it's less-adequate. You don't know they weren't kept in cages.  
  
You keep passing the buck. If they didn't amass 100+ tigers in the first place, tiger care and how difficult it is to maintain adequate care for that many big cats is never an issue. 
   
This isn't about bucking the hivemind. I love playing devil's advocate all day. What you're doing is giving a 3rd world country shit for trying to maintain some semblance of animal rights.  
   
If it were America I'd be right on with you. Really get a grip. In some semblance of a classroom you could debate well, were the tigers better off? Why didn't the gov't just take over the palce? Or whatever the ideal solution was. 
   
That's just not reality. They were continuing to have poor practices there. Risked being shut down once and when they finally do it it's like but wait! Look at how the tigers have it *now?*  
   
Come on, really? 
   
Yes it's condescending. Everyone has a right to an opinion. Not facts. And your presuming a whole lot to pass judgment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 11:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry man, totally thought the pretext was about him. 
  
I guess the point still stands. Really sorry about that though. Really don't bring politics into shit it has no place being.  
   
Anytime you use the phrase "I don't mean to be racist" you're probably actually being racist.  
  
The situation you described is different. That's someone doing something and someone claiming that it was racist. And then person denying it. What the person did could or couldn't have been racist.   
  
If you feel the need to defend something, as you're doing it, you're probably guilt of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 10:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck. 
  
And I love the psychologists reaction. You can grow out of it.  
  
I'm not against people expressing and dealing with things in extrordinary ways. Life can be fucked up. And weird and difficult.     
   
But I'd seriously consider before i publicly made a stance on something. Then again between 12-24 you really don't have any clue how long life is. You only begin to appreciate it in the years after that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 09:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah seriously. might have a shot like talking me into it and seeing where it goes. 
   
what made her think blindfolding you and just being like "okay now open!" 
   
"Surprise you're a cat and we're gonna fuck now" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 09:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if it's gone that far sometimes you just gotta say, fuck it. 
   
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 09:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dude i'm hysterically laughing right now. and probably about to read this out loud to my girlfriend. that's fucking too much.  
   
i mean, why not just fuck her at that point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 09:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol i'd be lying if i said i wouldn't be into that shit. all bout that showmanship.   
  
calling out to him for feedback. like how am i doing? do i stack up to the last one? what's she like? 
   
nah i'm kidding. i'm all about exhibitionism just not sure i'd be into a dude right there wanking it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 09:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that sucks because ime most chick who are taking off knee high boots tend to be on the sexier side. 
   
and i always try to give some consideration for outfit choices, especially if there's a touch of fashion sense there, ya know, but sometimes things are just too much to forgive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 09:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha, absolutely would do this too. like welp, dog's here. guess that's it because, ah she's just so cute. nah i can't do this. i'm not corrupting her and putting on a show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 09:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whaaaaaaat the fuck is wrong with people?  
  
jesus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 08:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing like having Uncle Ted fondle your nuts while he's in town for Thanksgiving.  
  
And then while you're eating Turkey you look around and think, damn, at least 4 adults here know about my freak out over the bumps on my dick.   
   
#jussayen might just be worth suffering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 08:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For sure. I'm all for that in the heat of the moment exerting control thing. 
  
But it's my fucking mom calling. Like come on? Nothing like Mom's voice to put me over the edge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 08:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol more than once? let's be honest she's into some kinky shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 08:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i dont know if it's inappropriate at that point though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 08:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i want to be all like fuck that! 
   
but if i'm being honest, ya know. easy enough to brush off, pretend you didn't hear it. 
   
weird enough that road might be worth taking once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 08:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's kinda... 
   
eh, who i am kidding? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 08:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's a great fucking story though eh? haha that's awesome. 
   
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 04:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, to be fair, I don't know how accurate that depiction is. 
   
The place was investigated and cleared in 2005 after years of allegations. So this probably wasn't a one time thing. Then when the government does get proof and does something they're the assholes because the people amassed 100+ tigers?  
  
Hell, that was probably a big reason why the gov't hadn't done anything sooner. I can't imagine that's good for any population, particularly of wild big cats, to be kept like that. I mean really, this place had the 2000lbs/day on average a 100 tigers would need? I don't know it sounds like a lot of big cats who would need a lot of space and a lot of food. It just sounds like a recipe for abuses, whether intended or not.   
   
All I'm saying is being a google detective without acknowledging the lack of actually being there and the context/history of the place seems to be just as much of jumping to conclusions. 
   
Nor do you know that they're worse off now, for that matter. That's firmly an assumption but what isn't is everyone else for condemning someplace for charges that they were found guilty of. What we do know is that they were closed for rights violations and then the government fucked up for not being able to care for 100+ tigers? The more I think about it, get a fucking grip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 04:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> damn right i would. i think it's awesome. besides you should never be ashamed of you are or what it is you like. particularly for video games ya know? 
   
things that are truly taboo don't get shirts made of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 04:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> like a boss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 01:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not what happened. Anytime you say "I'm not racist but" Or "No offense" what you're about to say is probably offensive or racist because you feel the need to defend it from the accusation beforehand. Did you watch the same press conference I did? It was 77 minutes long. Just the length of it alone you have to ask what the fuck was going for all that time.   
  
If I feel the need that to defend what I'm doing against an accusation *that hasn't happened yet* then you're admitting that you feel that you may be worthy of that accusation. Does that make sense?
    
The reality is that anyone who likes Trump because 'he isn't a politician' and 'tells it like it is' didn't see anything wrong with that press conference. The difference now is it wasn't one of his rallies. He was talking to a room of reporters who are writing for the reading Americans. Not the Americans who are attending his rallies and supporting him no matter what. People respect their President to be Presidential.    

He was ranting and going on and on about different topics form one question. Like he normally does. Like you ask him about increased reports of anti Semitic attacks since his inauguration. To which he responds by denying the fact, saying how great america is, how he'll have to look it up himself, and the says something like 'You know, we won with 306 electoral votes the most ever. You know how great that is, the largest margin ever for a republican president 306. That's just wonderful and these are great people, not divided.'  Is that answering the question? Or is that more like a rant?
  
I'm paraphrasing here. But that's not really that off from how he answers any given question. He'll address the question, and then talk about other stuff that he feels might be related to it but isn't. And it'll just keep going and going. That's called ranting.   
  
So as he keeps giving these long answers and then says "You'll probably say I'm ranting and raving." And then everyone is like "I was thinking he was ranting, and now he thinks he's ranting too."     
  
As a side note:     
That or we'll be looking a lot more like Russia or China if the people actually turn their back on the media only take their news from the State. Because this is exactly how dictators take over the press. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 00:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what everyone is missing is that...it doesn't even need to 'work' per say. Just having the presence of people being in favor of Forbes will leave some people with a better impression than if it were all negative. I think this has more to do with actually creating a positive impression on something by 1. tarnishing the people who tarnished your client 2. bad mouthing the competition/discrediting them 3. indirect praise of the client's product (making posts that put the type of or lists that include the game out there) 4. posts regarding why the client's innovation or take on teh innovation is a good thing and then maybe links ot the client's actual product through that piece. 5. then finally if needed posts about the client's actual product being good. 
   
but by then the subreddit will probably have gotten to that conclusion on its own.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 00:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> corrected! she got me! oh she got me good! god damn video game industry! I mean one of the few times where I didn't question myself about it and said, nope, Matt, you're good, he is fine here. And bam! 
   
that's what happens when you grow up on wow. to be fair you could be a female paladin but never see em. blame the video games! nah i'm playen. but some truth there.  
  
but, being a woman makes that username from sorta awesomely cringey to full on awesomely cool. so there's that.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 23:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, to be fair, a lot of survivalist take that. When you ask what the pamphlet on carving human meat is about and he says, oh justi n case shit gets real bad... 
   
Nah man, it's for that plump wife he's kept stuck in the same seat on the couch for 25 years. Sometimes, every once in a while, he thinks damn she probably so tender before snapping out of it. Only if the shit hits the fan, he reminds himself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 23:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "uh, Yeah. Thanks. I just...It's just that I'm not you. I get it, you want me here. But that's because you guys *need* me here. Much more than I need to be here. So listen, and I don't mean this - thanks John - I don't mean this the wrong way but I need to think about myself 5, 10, 20 years down the road. I'm just starting out and with a few tricks under my belt I got places I need to go in front of me. I'd hate to pass up the opportunity for a bit more of the same. What I'm saying here is, I appreciate all ya done for me Mr. Johnson, the rest of you, the company. You really got me off to a good start here. You can't expect me to stay though, not just with how *damn* good of a start I had. I need a challenge. I need to move on. It's just the way it is and the way it's gotta be." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 23:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> honestly man, i get mixed bag of replies vs non replies. i'm not the most photogenic but if i make sure the picture isn't complete shit i tend to do alright. also when i'm not wearing my glasses i get a lot of attention. 
   
back when you used to meet girls irl at the bar and shit, i used to do pretty good. better than jsut online messagin/swiping right. and the glasses thing. and i don't have that casual good lookingness. Like my t-shirt and sweatpants photo's never are like oh he's ho!. my collared shirt and nice jeans photos get responses (still not hot but cute i guess? i dont know it worked).  
   
i met my current girlfriend though through beating someone who took money out of her purse. now when i tell that story to someone it's like oh you're a tough man who will protect his girl...and you're taken...challenge accepted! 
  
I don't get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 23:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah take /u/cervical_paladin advice. she clearly be slayin' those cervices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is it so hot this year in the Northeast U.S.? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not a bad idea people might be more inclined to watch some thing if it's more like 'content' than it being a 'tutorial' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'll second that too. I've seen multiple instances and studies showing that digitally reading something isn't nearly as effective as holding a book in your hand. My gut reaction is the interaction with the book or lack there of in the digital version. I'm a highlighter on my kindle, non fiction fiction, I'll highlight great passages. But I think that's also because I'm a writer (read: editor) lol. So it is very second nature to me. But when it comes to referencing a page or flipping back to something it isn't nearly as intuitive on a kindle as it is a textbook. It's probably the sharpest criticism right now, imo. 
   
Besides that, and the issue of children not having internet at home, I find it a weak stance to not be transitioning toward it. 
  
As for the school funding, we have, by me, a 3% tax cap on school budgets. And they've passed for nine years in a row the increases at a rate of 98%. When people talk about government bloat and reducing the size of gov't, look toward the schools.  
  
Sorry, had to put that in there. The reality is what might cost us more now will absolutely pay us out in the long run. If we find out how to teach digitally right. It's actually some interesting points. There's definitely work arounds for the 'fairness' issue though. And the schools have money. 
   
It's bureaucracy and a me, me, me attitude. For all the finger pointing everyone does at liberals for being 'victim' this or 'me' that, look at any school district, its PTA, and its School Board. It's a 'what about *my* student mentality. Not a what about us thing. And it's kind why we can't get anything fucking done in this country. 
    
And so this doesn't just end as a rant. You couldn't even **try** to do this at a school because people would say, "well it should be one class it should be all the 3rd grade classes get the tablet." And then "well what about when they go to fourth grade, do they keep it? or stop using it? well then the 4th grade should have it!" Then "You'll trust 3rd and 4th graders with a tablet but not the 5th and 6th graders?" Then "We had to scrap the pilot program it's costs got too out of hand."  
   
And the whole time you're wondering whether or not it was jsut a fuck up or if the teachers union was actually against it and spurred the resistance on. 
  
look what happened with common core too. It's not even whether something is good in education. You can't even take the time to try it out or find out if it's good because of how fucktarded it is.  
 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I never really had that issue, well sort of while working in a restaurant it's kind of an industry with the unwritten rule of you don't call in sick. It's gotten better recently from what I hear though, to an extent.   
  
And every once in a while on reddit you see a thread that compares European employees with American ones in regard to attitudes and work cultures surrounding time off/sick days/vacation. The difference are startling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> called in sick yesterday /u/steamboxer4 and i just wanted to talk to you to make sure this position is a good fit for you and you want to be here. 
  
*sneezing, still runny nose* uh yeah boss, i'm sick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 08:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eh, to be honest i can't imagine your standard ocean wave really messing up the landing if the pilot skills it. 
   
for a few reasons but mostly because the plane will displace the water. not like the top of a wave will tilt the plane. besides that the plane will land on more than one wave too, if they were that strong.  
   
the plane is already coming however many thousand feet in the air i can't imagine a 3-6 foot, maybe even a ten foot wave.                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                           </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 08:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to be fair this is kind of like that argument, and i hate to bring it up here but it's the most recent public example, trump saying "i'm not ranting and raving" lol. 
   
anytime you have to say, making me look like, i'm not this or that, i don't want to be [insert rude, offensive, racist]. 
   
it's a good rule of thumb that you probably are being that thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 05:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey it's jsut my 2 cents. i can be the same way and loved to play devil's advocate. now i have a habit of doing it, at least with certain people. while i appreciate healthy conversation and debate, even the good ol' fashion argument every once in a while, be careful. 
  
In hindsight, while being analytical is good, it isn't a healthy way to think. Or in that regard, it can be but it needs the proper channels to be expressed. It's best kept with the mindset of using it to challenge yourself and arrive at your own conclusion regarding the topic.  
  
That said, not a criticism, you're oviously in the right channel for it. Just a, from my experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 05:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this is something I've been thinking about a bit myself. And part of me would like to see more decisions left to the states. The reality is though that the federal government steps in not because it wants to but usually because it feels it has to or because it was asked to. 
   
It has to in cases like deploying Guardsmen to implement desegregation. It's asked to usually in the form of the supreme court.  
  
One thing that I find frustrating is that why are we even talking about rights anymore? Why are we even opposing people about rights they feel are deserved? I think we're at a point where we can be sensible about it and fair. I don't see us offering protections to people who don't have legitimate complaints. In that regard it's important we ask the question whether this or that person is someone who should be granted protection. Once we ask the question we also ahve to ask are we denying them that equality just because it makes us uncomfortable? 
   
You know it's really only people who make us uncomfortable that end up really needing those protections. And that tends to be the point. It isn't like a 'oh everyone will want to do whatever they want.' Because everyone else already can.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 02:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> shotcaller ha! --bronze 
   
but you're right. a good part of it is giving people jsut a bit of direction. to be fair the game knowledge down here is atrocious at times.  
   
but i can also relate to when i jumped into rank without knowing a thing about the game. i think to a degree the shared xp and team nature of the game though does translate into winning without knowing why to an extent and people just continuing their behaviors. 
   
really need a tutorial that like lays that shit out. i know they updated it but i'm not sure if it includes that stuff now. there's a good chance a lot of people who are already in the game wouldn't do the tutorial anyway. 
  
i almost wonder like if there was a way to 'refresh' people with the tutorial or like force them to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 22:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The really dialed in on a certain ebb and flow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 22:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what i don't get is why we even still have textbooks. Besides the practicality of not reprinting books, purchasing books, printing new editions, all of that aside. The increased avenues for learning with each student receiving an ipad or access to one while at school or in class, even a chromebook, are immense. Infographics, interactive videos and images, pronunciations, definitions, games, at the tap of a finger. Live updates and news bulletins that are relevant to the topic at hand! Classrooms that go beyond the classroom by having the tudents all sign in to watch election stuff live or any other big stories that effect us all nationally or regionally. 
   
And you don't even need to give them the tablets. Each desk in each class gets a tablet. Each student has an account they sign into. Like a combination of Kindle Reader and Google Drive, essentially.   
  
Instead they get issued books, even if they're 'up-to-date' they can be dated for what our current standard for what up-to-date information is. College kids are still buying textbooks and everyone else borrows them but physical copies. While the collegiate level is letting you borrow some books now it's still is no where near the same. 
   
And come junior year you get your own tablet.  
   
School is one place where we could really be living in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know Dr. Huang from Law and Order was an artist on that [game?](https://www.google.com/url?sa=i rct=j q= esrc=s source=imgres cd= ved=0ahUKEwjezq6_iqfSAhVl2IMKHX5JDM0QjRwIBw url=https%3A%2F%2Flawandordersvufans.wordpress.com%2Fgeorge-huang%2F psig=AFQjCNERPa04cSEo9vC2aUyxDRBozjlFjw ust=1487968966511970) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Were there more atomic bombs? What was the actual plan in dropping them? I searched and couldn't find an answer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 06:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was the expectation that they'll surrender? If the fear in invading Japan was that they'd fiercely defend it why was the presumption that two bombs would end it? Were they bluffing that was had more bombs and that we'll just bomb everything?   
 
I searched a bit for this and didn't really see it clearly answered or asked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 00:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in my experience it's probably best to just get a group of us together and see what happens.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 22:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> isn't it a wild idea that if there is life there, advanced life, they could have been looking at us looking at them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 22:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's a religious thing really. or a religious/cultural thing. Muslims follow a few texts that they turn to. One of them is the Hadith. In the Koran itself dogs aren't considered bad or dirty. It's the hadith that some leaders get the idea that dogs are dirty. It seeps into their lives culturally probably from that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 22:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i wouldn't have. there's a good chance this gets turned into something for an anti muslim piece about how they hate dogs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
