<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3232</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 21:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, he is implying that women are constantly avoiding responsibility, which is pretty uncool.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 21:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking maybe she worked for Ringling Brothers or something. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 20:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Wouldnt an advanced civilization have a better way to adjust appearance other than ground up pigments temporarily applied to the face? 

What on earth is your issue with pigments? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 20:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> please do what makes you smile

This is disingenuous. You're labeling people as inferior for engaging in a custom and then you turn around and say "but do whatever makes you happy." You say it makes no difference to you, but it obviously does--so why say that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 20:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Rememver when our backwards social systems made it okay to kill rape and destroy entire civilizations but combinations of certain words were not okay because a magical man in a castle with a funny hat said he was talking to an omniscient presence that controls all things?

Yep, that's totally the equivalent of wearing makeup. 

Also, there's an undercurrent of prejudice to your dismissal of body art as "primitive." That was logic used by people like Melville to depict Pacific islanders with tribal tattoos as less-than savages.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 19:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, why can't we all just live in vacuum-sealed pods filled with nutrient gel and communicate with each other only through telepathy? Surely then we would finally be elevated about our primitive physical selves and social customs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 18:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, that is 100% true. And it's really easy to point out others' problems, too, than it is to examine our own. However, I'm sure it's much more difficult to actually be that guy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 18:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, IME people with interpersonal problems often have that issue. They don't see the pattern of how their behavior affects their ability to form and maintain relationships. 

My money is on this: he's severely anxious, has difficulty functioning socially, and vacillates between being super nervous about people judging him and then super aggressive when he feels judged. He pushes people away and then resents people for not wanting to be with them. That's my 5 cent take on the situation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 17:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It comes down to a classic internal conflict--they desire women but resent that they desire them. They want to do sexual things with them but then hate themselves for having those thoughts--and project that hatred onto the objects of their desire.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 17:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or how about I say whatever I want and you deal with the consequences of painting your face constantly. 

This guy sounds like a really nice guy. I can imagine he has *no* interpersonal problems whatsoever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 17:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure is--my dad used to make me butter and sugar sandwiches on tea bread as a special treat--for dessert or afternoon tea sometimes. They kick ass.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are those cinnamon pop tarts? Those are the only flavor I like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Microwaves use some kind of waves

Yes, they use microwave radiation. Microwaves are perfectly safe. Cooking food in the microwave does not affect the nutrient content of food any more than a conventional oven. And if you want to stay away from microwaves, don't eat out ever--they're widely used in commercial kitchens.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it was cooked in one pot... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you should consider reviewing other recipe sources if you think this is a "typical American recipe."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just not sold on this cooking pasta in milk thing. For me it's just as easy to boil the pasta separately and toss it with the sauce and a little pasta water at the last minute. That said, I think I might be making some bowtie pasta and broccoli for my baby this week, he might enjoy that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just for a second remove your hatred of the president and imagine you're him. You know you're not guilty of this ridiculous conspiracy theory that you're a Russian collaborator. Why in the fuck isnt Comey telling everyone you're innocent?

Because that's not how these things work? At all?

It doesn't matter how many times he writes in a letter that he is not under investigation--just saying something numerous times doesn't change reality.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not only that, but the reprints of his work just do not do the colors justice. It's like trying to recreate Matisse colors, it just doesn't work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there are some amazing contemporary artists out there--the umbrella of contemporary art is so huge it's impossible to discount all of it IMO. Check out some of these people:

[Zhou Chunya](https://media.mutualart.com/Images/2011_06/22/09/095452551/b5268d73-72f3-4109-b0db-548fb8701d46_570.Jpeg)

[Miguel Barcelo](https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/originals/b2/45/b5/b245b5c18400dc71db4eb6a131f1ab36.jpg)

[El Anatsui](http://images.huffingtonpost.com/2013-02-25-El_AnatsuiEarth_sSkin.jpg)

[Robert Fry](http://www2.hm.com/content/dam/HM%20Magazine%202017/Interview/MARB2-17-AL-2-Interview-Robert-Fry.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it happens, it will take a while. Watergate took a couple of years. My bet would be 2019.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure thing. A common "grounding" technique for people who are overwhelmed is to concentrate on the five senses. For someone who is experiencing flashbacks or severe emotion dysregulation (which you see in PTSD, and Borderline Personality Disorder, for example) it's best to help them return to the present and practice mindful relaxation. So we make little kits aimed at that goal. We take small boxes and include specific sensory items: essential oil on cotton ball that they pick out to smell, a sour candy or menthol cough drop for taste, squares of textured fabric to rub in their hands, polished stones to hold/rub (the weight is helpful), putty or playdoh, items to encourage deep breathing (I've started using bubbles--gives kids a way to concentrate on how they're breathing by watching the bubbles as they exhale) and then additional items they come up with themselves. For sound I have a list of links to free guided meditation exercises, and I encourage them to make playlists of songs they find comforting. So the kits can include a wide variety of things. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's just priming + coincidence. You suddenly became aware of them through the video and this thread, so you noticed the kid at the bus stop.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you need a fidget cube? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's drama for drama's sake in /r/pics when numerous children argue what "art" really means </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's called a pastitsio. It's tasty! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You see? Music videos help me predict the future.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Layered pasta nationalism in /r/FoodPorn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No therapy via Reddit--no malpractice policy in the world is high enough to cover that potential ethical minefield.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Neurotypical" refers to people not on the autism spectrum and not with any developmental disorders.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a mystic who uses music videos for divination

So do I. For example, I predict you're going to [open this link](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dQw4w9WgXcQ). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the deal with Babish? That's what one commenter in /r/videos wants to know--but his question is not well received </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now *that* is a lard pastry dough. Very nice! Looks amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure why they've seen a sudden surge in popularity. Just in the past two years they've gone from being something I occasionally recommended to parents to something that parents are recommending to *me*. Were they Oprah's favorite thing or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, during the Elizabethan period food was [heavily spiced and/or sweetened](http://www.history.com/news/hungry-history/shakespeares-suppers).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anything other than rare? Fuck you. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is how I got ink all over my hands on more than one occasion. And once I even got ink in my goddamn mouth. Not my proudest moment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although it's uncommon, it [can happen](http://www.aaaai.org/ask-the-expert/peanut-air-travel) according to The American Academy of Allergy, Asthma   Immunology.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the correct answer. *Or* you use a combo of the two. I made my son his first grilled cheese last week and he approved.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PTSD is a syndrome of reexperiencing, hyperarousal, avoidance, and trauma-related alteration in cognition and mood. What's not clear at this point is whether or not children on the spectrum experience this syndrome in the same way that neurotypical kids do. Part of the problem is that there aren't good trauma assessments that are normed for ASD kids. 

Often traumatized neurotypical kids have difficulty talking about things that have happened to them--they experience flashbacks and anxiety and need to go through gradual exposure to help them cope. Some of the kids on the spectrum I've worked with are just the opposite--they are emotionally detached and can report trauma they have experienced with no affect whatsoever. That doesn't mean they aren't traumatized. Also you're more likely to see tics, repetitive behaviors, and rocking when they discuss things that make them anxious--that's what you see in lieu of emotional expression. They sometimes have communication deficits that make therapy difficult--and because they don't present in the "traditional" way some clinicians might miss the trauma symptoms and assume they won't benefit from therapy. Finally, these kids are often *very* concrete. Abstract concepts don't work well. It helps to find something solid you can link to, preferably something that they love. For example, one teenager I work with only responds if I can link back to dinosaurs or trains. Or 5 Nights at Freddy's. You have to get creative.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's an example](https://www.ebay.com/p/?iid=262880624989 lpid=82   ul_noapp=true chn=ps). They give your hands something to do. There's research that supports that fidgeting helps people with ADHD focus in school.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can definitely see that being confusing. My current setting is working with traumatized kids. Interestingly enough, PTSD presents very differently in kids on the spectrum than it does in neurotypical kids. I think of "neurotypical" as meaning "not having a neurodevelopmental disorder." I can see it being used in cases of ADHD as well, though, as people with ADHD process sensory information differently as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember they stopped making those because the metal slipped out and cut some kids' arms.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use the term "neurotypical" and "not neurotypical" in my work because that language has utility. I've got a few clients on the spectrum. What do you dislike about the lingo?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it should be like medication in school--get it preapproved by the school, and use it appropriately. I know they're called "fidget toys" but I approach it as "this is a tool, not a toy" because it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a total fucking moron if you don't think those are implants.


9/10 when there's an "are they implants?" argument on Reddit, the answer is "Yes, of course they are." But Christina Hendricks is the perfect example of real, huge boobs. She's had them for as long as I can remember her (earliest things I can think of are *Firefly* and *Hunger Point*) and they have gotten bigger and smaller over the years when she loses and gains weight. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an odd thing to argue about, too--I can't say I've ever seen an argument about fidget toys. But then, I can imagine that because it can be a highly personal thing, people's emotions get involved.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boy, these special people's clubs are getting more and more specific...

BTW, I always thought eating ice was bad for your teeth. I associate it with being in labor and nurses handing me cups of ice chips, so the idea of eating ice brings back bad memories.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just speaking from my own experience with kids who use these toys, they can be super helpful. In fact, if we could find a cheap source for them, I'd suggest putting them in the coping kits we make for kids with PTSD--it's not just for kids with anxiety and attention deficits, it can be a helpful grounding tool for kids who are overwhelmed by flashbacks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Argument over fidget toys and who should have them in /r/gatekeeping </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You saucy troll. You think I don't know what you're doing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/theyhaveplates </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't taste the vodka, but it helps get more flavor out of the tomatoes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But Pittsburgh is awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gingerbread was popular in the Elizabethan era (but remember that vanilla was not used at that time). Another popular option is the pasty--you could little ones with roasted root vegetables for example. Remember the potato was not common there at that time, but they loved their turnips and parsnips. 

Also, as a note, if the party is on a Friday or a Saturday, they did not eat meat on those days during the Elizabethan period--only fish. This was actually written into law.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 12:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was a green chutney? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 12:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the tuna is already cooked. Ceviche is *raw* seafood that is then cured in acid to "cook" it. What you're describing sounds more like tuna salad to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's it 

What about cream cheese frosting, or as an addition to mashed potatoes, or in crab rangoon? Yes, I know crab rangoon is ridiculous and not good for you but I still like them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the sauce? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might want to get the grill a little hotter, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really works, IMO. I particularly like it if the syrup/honey has some chili pepper added to make it spicy. 

This is going to sound strange, but my favorite food at the Texas State Fair is called the "Buffalo chicken flapjack." It's Buffalo chicken dipped in pancake batter, rolled in jalapeno breadcrumbs and fried, served with a little cup of spicy syrup to dip it in. Yes, it's overkill, yes it's terrible for you, but it's really delicious. [This is what it looks like](http://bigtex.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/08/11buffchknflap.jpg).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a big fan of bean salads and grain salads. You can mix black beans, halved grape tomatoes, corn, cilantro, peppers, avocado (that you can cut up and add at work if you don't want to risk browning) and a nice citrus dressing--delicious. You take grilled vegetables and toss with quinoa and some nice fresh tomatoes and parsley, a little olive oil and some lemon juice--it's killer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love that Mr. T is wearing a shirt with his name *and* a button that reads "I heart Mr. T."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm...I'm not sure! I wonder if you could use virgin coconut oil? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What makes it "ceviche?"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been doing prep for weekday meals every Sunday, and this week on the menu is pot roast. I did the meat, onions, and mushrooms in the pressure cooker and it could not have turned out better--I cooked the potatoes, celery, and carrots separately in the drippings from browning the meat. Then I combined everything together. I ended up with a meal in which all components are cooked perfectly!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't write it down while I was experimenting because I'm a big dummy, but it was approximately as follows:

1/2 cup flour, 1/4 cup protein powder, 4 tbs butter, 1 egg,  tsp baking powder,  tsp baking soda,  tsp salt, 1/2 cup slenda brown sugar baking blend, a cup of cooked white beans, vanilla. Puree the beans. Melt the butter and splenda on the stove top and cool a bit. Whisk in the egg and the bean puree, fold in the dry ingredients, and bake for 20 minutes at 350. 

Edit: it's also good to add yogurt chips, or walnuts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Cookie marker things

I've never had good luck with these. Do use royal icing and then let it dry and then apply the marker? Do you use the Wilton brand? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oooh, of course. I knew I had seen it, but I couldn't place it. Very cool.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> U of C is a pretty conservative business school, though--not a lot of liberal academics involved. What makes you say they're liberal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dead Kennedys - Live in San Francisco (1984) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that from the X Files? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It most definitely is not. It's pot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's hilarious--she was only 18 then. Fun fact, he lost that tooth running into a stage divider pole at the Reggae Lounge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Jackson and Mr. T, 1985 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 02:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before the cream sets up too long... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Duplicate it but use ham instead of salmon. Problem solved!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can season it as you see fit! Don't add anything that needs to cook, though. Pepper, light cheese, salt, etc. is fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, but I don't engage in conversations with "trolls" who use the term "homey" seriously. 

You're an anxious, socially awkward person who is now trying to pretend he was "trolling." Good luck with that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look, I'm not sure what you think there has to be a "rebuttal" to, but I would argue that the success of a joke hinges on whether or not it is well-received--and your comment, if indeed it was intended as a joke, was clearly not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I knew what that JPEG was the moment I saw the link.

Because you know that what you're doing is dumb as a bag of hammers?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're too generous! I was told this morning that it went for $40, which is pretty good considering it was a small town auction, not really a big money affair. So a little extra money for a good cause! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Oh I see](http://i.imgur.com/n8umjWj.png).

Honestly, that just makes you more of a doofus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Argument n /r/AskReddit over who deserves gold and what the appropriate response to gilding should be </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's Charo, you doofus. And Shakira is from Colombia, she's not Spanish.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lox.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I seal mine in plastic containers. I have [some like this](https://www.amazon.com/Containers-Airtight-Microwave-Dishwasher-Stackable/dp/B01LC7UIWO/ref=sr_1_1?s=home-garden ie=UTF8 qid=1494175871 sr=1-1 keywords=plastic+pint+containers+with+lids+32+oz) that I use to store leftovers of all kinds. They work great for tomatoes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely this. I chipped my medium Shun chef's knife and it made me SO sad. Don't put them through any unnecessary punishment. Fortunately, I learned my lesson and my large chef's knife and paring knife are still going strong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's adorable! She should try using 7-Up or ginger ale, those both work really well too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I got the color by combining Americolor peach with Americolor electric orange. The leaves use a combination of avocado green and leaf green. For the buttercream color I used a few drops of lemon yellow and one drop of peach. Gives it a soft, buttery color.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could make that work--I've made [eggs in a cloud](http://www.cookinglight.com/food/recipe-finder/how-to-make-eggs-in-a-cloud-video) before, and you do that in an oven. I'm not sure about your timing, though--you might have to experiment. I would think maybe 4-5 minutes at 450F, but you might need more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I miswrote, I meant to write private.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not particularly invested in defending that sub. I'm a socially liberal centrist, and I don't believe that all private property should be abolished. I just think you're reading too much into what they wrote.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, if you want to stick with the reading that makes you the most outraged and offended possible, you can choose that one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lemon layer cake with sugar flowers I made for a charity auction [OC] [1728x1639] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're being too literal here. They're saying it's important to have resolve and stand by your convictions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like unsweet meringue, kind of. I love the texture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a [Hollandaise sauce](http://www.food.com/recipe/julia-childs-hollandaise-sauce-251332) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That...doesn't really say what you said it said.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't beat a babka! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lemon layer cake with sugar flowers I made for a charity auction [OC] [1728x1639] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've made these at home, and the most efficient way is to do 4 at a time and use an electric mixer. 

EDIT: BTW, for anyone curious, in the gif the egg is sitting on an English muffin with lox and hollandaise sauce and paprika on top.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I wanted it to look a little "rough" but still polished, if that makes sense. Also, funny note--I realized a bit too late that I don't currently own a [decorating comb](https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/61BO46NIRjL._SL1315_.jpg) so I had to use a [grilling spatula](http://blogs.solidworks.com/tech/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/Grill_Spatula_moderate_image.jpg). It worked surprisingly well. However, I've since ordered one--they're cheap, and I decorate enough cakes to make it worth it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look man, he just asked how to get it to set more. I told him. Not everyone loves runny egg, and that's okay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an English muffin with lox.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recipe:       
1 cup butter, softened     

 4 eggs      

2 1/3 cups cake flour      

1 1/2 teaspoons baking powder      

1/2 teaspoon baking soda     

 1/4 teaspoon salt   

   2 cups sugar      

1 tbs lemon zest      

2 tablespoons lemon juice      

1 cup sour cream

Allow butter and eggs to get to room temp. Meanwhile, grease and line with parchment two 9 inch round cake pans. Combine flour, baking powder, soda, and salt. Set aside.

 In a large mixing bowl beat butter with an electric mixer on medium to high speed for 30 seconds. Add sugar, lemon peel, and lemon juice; beat until well combined. Add eggs, 1 at a time, beating well after each. Add flour mixture and sour cream alternately to beaten mixture, beating on low speed after each addition just until combined. Pour into prepared pans.

Bake in a 350 degree F oven for 25 to 30 minutes or until a wooden toothpick comes out clean. Cool cakes in pans on wire racks for 10 minutes. Remove cakes from pans. Cool thoroughly on wire racks.

I wrapped them in plastic and refrigerated them overnight--cold cake layers are easier to work with when you're frosting them. 

For the buttercream, I kept it simple. 

1 lb butter

2 lb bag powdered sugar
 
2 tsp good vanilla

1/4 cup whipping cream

The flowers and leaves were done with gum paste, two sizes of rose petal cutters, leaf cutter, ball tool, and Americolor gel colors. If this post garners interest, I will write out instructions for the flowers.  

EDIT: and for anyone curious, this is not a hard thing to do--in fact, I would say you just need about three hours to make all the sugar flowers and leaves without interruption. It took me longer because I have a one-year-old who constantly ran at me while I was trying to make petals, but you can do this without too much work if you get the right stuff and have a few hours free!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Lemon layer cake with sugar flowers I made for a charity auction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recipe:       
1 cup butter, softened     

 4 eggs      

2 1/3 cups cake flour      

1 1/2 teaspoons baking powder      

1/2 teaspoon baking soda     

 1/4 teaspoon salt   

   2 cups sugar      

1 tbs lemon zest      

2 tablespoons lemon juice      

1 cup sour cream

Allow butter and eggs to get to room temp. Meanwhile, grease and line with parchment two 9 inch round cake pans. Combine flour, baking powder, soda, and salt. Set aside.

 In a large mixing bowl beat butter with an electric mixer on medium to high speed for 30 seconds. Add sugar, lemon peel, and lemon juice; beat until well combined. Add eggs, 1 at a time, beating well after each. Add flour mixture and buttermilk or sour milk alternately to beaten mixture, beating on low speed after each addition just until combined. Pour into prepared pans.

Bake in a 350 degree F oven for 25 to 30 minutes or until a wooden toothpick comes out clean. Cool cakes in pans on wire racks for 10 minutes. Remove cakes from pans. Cool thoroughly on wire racks.

I wrapped them in plastic and refrigerated them overnight--cold cake layers are easier to work with when you're frosting them. 

For the buttercream, I kept it simple. 

1 lb butter

2 lb bag powdered sugar
 
2 tsp good vanilla

1/4 cup whipping cream

The flowers and leaves were done with gum paste, two sizes of rose petal cutters, leaf cutter, ball tool, and Americolor gel colors. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lemon layer cake with sugar flowers I made for a charity auction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say use lower heat and cook it a little longer, it will help the yolk set more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like it would be all sweet with no balance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've been assaulted by bouncers? Where was this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun fact: in my state, Medicaid cannot be used to cover serves for autistic children--and the wait list for the program that *does* covers services is two years long at present. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like arugula tossed in with my pasta. I've never had a bean-based pasta sauce, but I like bean sauces--it's interesting and I will give it a try. Might add a little vegetable stock or a splash of white wine in place of that water, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just tradition to put a cork in the water. It's supposed to tenderize it, but it doesn't really--the only thing that can tenderize an octopus is how you cook it (either short enough or long enough).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it just active dry yeast? It should be just fine, I use the same yeast for my bread, bagels, pizza dough, coffee cake, etc. (unless I'm using a starter, but it doesn't sound like you're working with that).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, I'm not sure what the issue is--it plays fine for me. Did you try the mp4 link in the comments?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's not working for you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep kneading until the dough becomes more elastic and comes together more. Your ratio seems okay--I've used 2 cups flour to 3/4 cup water and that works well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Egg Devaux </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks good--I've never been a fan of dipping them in ketchup, though. For me it's grainy mustard or nothing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. And I think that was inevitable, as technology chances so fast. I loved that he vapes--so perfect. Of *course* he does.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I finally saw the pilot last night and I loved it. I was wondering how they were going to do that part with the Queen of Sheba, and I thought it was handled very well. As much as I love Ian McShane, I had been on the fence about him playing Mr. Wednesday, but not anymore. I also really enjoyed Pablo Schreiber as Mad Sweeney. I can imagine that if you haven't read the book, it's probably pretty confusing--my husband said "we don't know anything about what this is about"--but I don't think that's a bad thing necessarily.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey gr8tfurme! Thank you for your submission, unfortunately it has been removed from /r/SubredditDrama because:

* You linked to the full comments. Please link directly to the comment tree containing the drama. If the comment you're linking to requires some context, add "?context=x" to the URL, where "x" is the number of parent comments you want displayed. If there are multiple drama threads create a self-post containing the relevant links.

"The whole thread is drama" doesn't count.

If you're unsure how to use context or to submit a write up, please check out our [wiki](/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules#wiki_using_.3Fcontext)



For more on our rules, please check out our [detailed rules wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules).  If you have any questions or concerns about this removal feel free to [message the moderators](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FSubredditDrama). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is fun to say, though. 

In seriousness, though, if I had said "freeze your green beans and make a salad" you would have thought I was nuts. Hence the term and the link to explain. It actually works really well. There's no need to be rude.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually pretty good if you ever get a chance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> La Methode and La Technique by Jacques Ppin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm intrigued... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I salt the meat but I do not compress it much when I form the patties. I also get my hands very cold before touching the meat--helps keep the fat solid!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You probably wouldn't want to eat all that excess mirror glaze. It's pretty, but it's not particularly tasty--it's kind of like super sweet vanilla gummy candy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wrote out detailed instructions [back when I made one of these a few months ago](https://www.reddit.com/r/Baking/comments/5tlqaj/lemon_1234_cake_with_blackberry_jam_filling_and/?st=j2dzbsbr sh=f5acbd39). These steps will help you make a good mirror glaze--the most important point is temperature! Get the cake cold and the glaze just the right temp. You can use any colors you want! Next time I plan on doing a darker color so that the shininess of the glaze comes through more. You can also use dark chocolate instead of white chocolate and do a straight chocolate glaze, or chocolate swirled with a color.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the flow of the mirror glaze. Mirror glaze is made with white chocolate and gelatin mainly, and you get it to just the right temp and then pour it over. [Here's one I made a few months ago](https://i.redd.it/09ih3norvffy.jpg). You pour the different colors over each other to create a marbling effect. As long as you get the temp just right on the glaze, it's actually quite easy to do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since pickling has already been suggested, I say you [cryoblanche](https://www.splendidtable.org/story/3-techniques-to-improve-your-home-cooking) some of them and use them in a salad with a nice vinaigrette.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a little...done for my taste. Like, Bill Paxton in *Near Dark* done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey OrangeFarmx! Thank you for your submission, unfortunately it has been removed from /r/SubredditDrama because:

* You linked to the full comments. Please link directly to the comment tree containing the drama. If the comment you're linking to requires some context, add "?context=x" to the URL, where "x" is the number of parent comments you want displayed. If there are multiple drama threads create a self-post containing the relevant links.

"The whole thread is drama" doesn't count.

If you're unsure how to use context or to submit a write up, please check out our [wiki](/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules#wiki_using_.3Fcontext)

* There is not enough drama to merit an SRD submission.  Please wait and see if things develop further, or look for a subthread with more drama. Make sure you're linking with the proper context.

Events such as "X sub was hacked" or "Y sub was made private" are not drama in and of themselves - do not just link to a subreddit that was taken over. If there are dramatic happenings around the takeover, please make a self post and include links to drama that users can read.



For more on our rules, please check out our [detailed rules wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules).  If you have any questions or concerns about this removal feel free to [message the moderators](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FSubredditDrama). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of all the people to so staunchly defend, it seems really weird to defend Terry Richardson.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh heck no, I was just making a note of my mistake. I'm leaving the post up, I think it's amusing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *weigh in, dammit, spelling mistake.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should you take photos on the railroad tracks? Experts in /r/itookapicture/ weight in. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I look t it as a mindfulness exercise, which helps me relax and focus. I concentrate on the smells, the way the food and the knives feel in my hand, etc. I really enjoy the process of going from prepped ingredients to a final product. 

If you're trying to learn to love it, set yourself up for success by making simpler recipes with fewer ingredients, and learn to clean as you go--it will be less work that way, but you can still enjoy the end results.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The butter in the crust is key. This looks like the real deal. I'd like to get some pepperoni, black olives and mushrooms in there instead of that sausage, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another day, another cheesesteak purist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OP in /r/ProRevenge likes to help the less fortunate, but one commenter doesn't approve. "You're proud of this? You're bottom-feeding scum, you stupid cunt." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, sorry, I didn't realize that--I thought it had to be stuff served on non-plates, my mistake.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooh, I wish I had a picture of that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never had these, but I will say that I've been to the Whiskey Cake up in the DFW area and I really enjoyed it. They have a pretty good menu. Their brunch is killer. I thought this looked a little silly, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god, I'm trying to imagine how overpowering each bite would be. 

These people clearly love bread, so I'm surprised it's not in a vessel made of crouton.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sent to me by my father-in-law from Whiskey Cake in Katy. Deviled egg delivery board. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it's long and skinny? Who the hell knows? I mean, I would dip a cold blanched asparagus spear in Caesar dressing, I bet it would be good, but it's still very weird to see it in a Caesar salad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found this on Pinterest. Someone really thought this was a great idea for entertaining! "Welcome to the party, here's a glass of salad to get you started. There's dressing at the bottom so it will all kind of turn into a lukewarm mushy paste as it heats up in your hand!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I simply refuse to believe that's possible.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure how you phrased things, but you may have done that person a favor. Sometimes you just have to level with an annoying person and say "when you act like ________ and do things like _______, it hurts my feelings and it makes me not want to be around you." He needs to hear that or he'll never change. So no, I do not think you're the asshole--he's the asshole.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You both sound like immature assholes to me. Him breaking shit, you calling him a "faggot," him attacking you, and you punching him in the face.

But yes, you are responsible for breaking his nose, because you punched him in the face. And he shouldn't have attacked you. And you're both assholes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not the asshole. It's not like she was having surgery, or was getting scary test results or something. Now if that had been the case, sure, I think you should go in with her, but it's routine and she's fine with you waiting in the car, so who cares? I agree with you, waiting rooms are germ factories.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, see I thought that was a bread stick, on top of the crouton you already have...now I'm even more confused.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You make a slurry, making sure to dry your meat off completely before you coat it. [Here's a helpful guide to "velveting" as it's called](http://www.seriouseats.com/recipes/2014/07/stir-fried-cod-yellow-squash-asparagus-recipe.html). It keeps the meat moist and tender throughout the cooking process.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found that for me, it helped to feed my baby football style every few feedings to minimize the air he swallowed. At first it felt awkward, but it worked for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I adore yakisoba. The noodles are a nice cross between soft and crispy, the veggies are delicious, the whole dish is just so comforting. 

Also, I love lard na. The texture of the soft, flat rice noodles is addictive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you try it? Did you make a slurry, or apply it directly, or what? How much did you use? Because it always works for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This just makes me angry. How are you supposed to eat this? Also, the greens to bread ratio is absurd.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it is rare for babies to develop sensitivities to foods mothers eat via breast milk. Some babies are just fussy and have digestive issues, regardless of what you're eating. Also, babies swallow air when they cry, so if they're crying a lot they're going to be more gassy anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shot Glass Caesar Salad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The trick to mirror glaze is to do it on a narrow pedestal, over wax paper. It's perfectly even, doesn't stick, and clean up is easy. I learned this the hard way by trying to do it on a rack the first time around.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They taste a little like all-sorts--gummy and sweet. They don't taste great, though--I made one for my son's birthday this year and while he ate it it wasn't his favorite part.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds like she's generalizing her personal experiences to everyone. It is possible for babies to be intolerant to cow's milk proteins that pass through the breast milk. If that's the case, the doctor will tell you to eliminate cow's milk from your diet and see if the baby gets better. But you shouldn't avoid dairy if you normally eat it just because you're afraid of it making your baby gassy. There's not reason to eliminate a food from your breastfeeding diet until a doctor advises you to do so, and foods should be eliminated systematically in order to identify specific sensitivities. It shouldn't be a general rule to avoid garlic, onions, cabbage, etc. Babies have gas, and sometimes they get fussy, and you can't ever avoid that 100% by avoiding certain foods. Not only that, but you should eat a wide range of foods when you're nursing--including garlic because it helps with your milk production. There's no research that says beans and broccoli and cabbage make your baby gassy via breastmilk. If you like beans, enjoy your beans! Protein and calories are vital when you're nursing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have a 1-year-old, so there's always work when I get home, but not having to wash up and sweep up after feeding the kid, bathing the kid, and putting the kid to bed is a real treat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 16:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, what you eat goes through to your breastmilk--all the fenugreek I took while breastfeeding is a prime example. But babies are generally cool with the food you normally ate while you were pregnant. They've had time to get used to it. 

I'm lucky to have a particularly hearty kid--my biggest problem was the volume of milk production, as he was too big and grew so fast I just couldn't keep up and had to supplement. If I had restricted my diet a lot it might have made milk production even harder. 

On a side note, I read a study while pregnant about third trimester exposure to certain flavors--and how it can influence the infant's preference for those flavors later. And interestingly enough, two of the foods I craved incessantly towards the end of my pregnancy (oranges and tomatoes) are both foods my baby can't seem to get enough of. Especially oranges--I have to cut him off after a while like the town drunk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 16:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, that's interesting--I knew my conception date, which I know is rare, but they still used it to confirm. Maybe it's because I have endo and I hadn't had a period in *years* when I started trying to get pregnant, so my cycle was nuts the month before I tested positive. I told them I knew my conception date and they looked suspicious, so I'm wondering if maybe they thought I was farther along than I actually was.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe I misinterpreted, but I got the impression that the police officer knew the driver? Or at least knew his wife? Because they seemed familiar, and obvious the cop must be friends with the family to be in on the announcement. In which case he wouldn't be nervous, I would think--he knows the guy.

If it was just a random cop, I think that would be a really bad idea on her part, lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least it has a plastic cap that goes over the end so you don't get the pee on your hands... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got an ultrasound to confirm pregnancy when I was 6 weeks. It's pretty standard these days.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it depends--if you know for certain that your partner wants to get married then I think it's okay. My husband asked me in public and it was a blast, but he knew I would say yes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is the cutest, most creative way to tell your husband about a pregnancy. That's hilarious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For humor: How Did This Get Made, Doug Loves Movies, The Dana Gould Hours, Wait Wait Don't Tell Me, Ask Me Another

For science: This Week In Science, Freakonomics, Radiolab

History: Stuff You Missed in History Class, Sawbones

Politics: 538 Politics podcast

Arts and Misc cool stuff: The Splendid Table, Maltin on Movies, The Dinner Party Download, This American Life

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 14:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My husband did the dishes and vacuumed while I was at work. It was nice to come home to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 14:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about you not get so unbelievably defensive and then say rude things to the OP like "I think that its less about you understanding people and more about making yourself better understood." That's why people are giving you such a hard time. Take your lumps, say you were mistaken, stop arguing about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still don't know what you're talking about. I ate eggs, and chili, and onion, and milk and tons of parsley because it's *good* for nursing babies. And fenugreek, and lots of it! It helped me make more milk, which was an issue for me. You're just reporting what *you* experienced and then lecturing other people that they just don't know, but you don't have any research or medical opinions backing it up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Find me some actual evidence besides your experience. 

[Food sensitivities to things that nursing mothers eat are very rare](http://www.parents.com/baby/breastfeeding/basics/avoid-foods-while-breastfeeding/). It's not good to limit your diet unnecessarily when nursing!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're stalking this guy's comments for some reason, then I care.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is 100% BS. If you eat spicy food when you're pregnant, and keep eating spicy food while nursing, baby doesn't care. In fact, garlic, in particular, boosts milk production and makes [babies nurse longer](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/8108198). So the whole "avoid pungent and spicy foods when nursing" thing is really an old wives' tale. Unless your doctor tells you to start food elimination, do not limit your breastfeeding diet (well, obviously don't chow down on oxycontin or anything like that).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god, you're arguing about this in here, too?

Lady, I just had a baby last year. I just went through *all* of this. And read all the research, and observed my own son. People had told me "don't eat broccoli, don't eat onions, don't eat spicy food, don't eat garlic!" Guess what, I ate everything, and he did just fine. But that's just anecdotal. I haven't seen any peer-reviewed research that supports the avoidance of so many foods while breastfeeding. If you have a new source, I'd love to see it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, well babies scream--garlic actually helps boost milk supply, and there's evidence that [garlic enhances nursing behavior as well](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/8108198). 

Now if their stool is abnormal, there could be an issue with the breast milk and you may need to talk to your doctor about changing your diet. But most babies, by the time they're born, they're used to what you've been eating. If you eat a lot of spicy food and then keep eating it, they'll be just fine with it. Too many mothers feel like they have to give up a million things when they stop breastfeeding, and it's just not true.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you find this particular post? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 05:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a reason you selected a two-month-old thread to start an argument in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 05:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No insults, please. Follow our sidebar rules. Thank you in advance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh, the oil separating from the cheese is too gross. Looked better before the cheese IMO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You see a lot of those, do you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Knock it off, please. No insults, play nice and be respectful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you could make a post for /r/MetaSubredditDrama  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey EducationalSoftware! Thank you for your submission, unfortunately it has been removed from /r/SubredditDrama because:

This post is not appropriate for SRD. Please read our rules before posting here again.



For more on our rules, please check out our [detailed rules wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules).  If you have any questions or concerns about this removal feel free to [message the moderators](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FSubredditDrama). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is just not true. There are lots of Black Hispanics. Just ask some of the people who live in Cuba and the Dominican Republic. Also, that's not what Latino means.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their Arnold looks like Steve Doocy from Fox   Friends, and Ellen looks like Jane Lynch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's actually a bit of an old wive's tale and not backed up by science.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mexican Independence Day is September 16, anyway. This is some Ken M level stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IMO, a good strategy is to quickly blanch it in boiling water and then either saute or quickly stir fry it with a little fat, salt, pepper, and any other flavors I might want (garlic, lemon zest, ginger, etc.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The shrimp looks a bit overcooked, but that still looks like a very tasty combo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would try mincing your garlic and using lots of it. However, you can also try granulated garlic, which I think is better than garlic powder. Garlic paste isn't shabby, either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Penzey's for most of it, although my sister got my a subscription to Ghost Spice company's spice of the month club and their mixes are pretty good, too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love that makok are also called "hog plums."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this a Bezoar? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
