<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2423</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a really ugly looking import figure of Spider-Man that has a ton of articulation for incredible poses. It's not a Marvel Legend, but it is about the same size, give or take. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Caitlyn Snow- her change from good to bad is so complex the reasons can't possibly be stated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm surprised Disney Channel is airing this since the movies are from Sony, I think.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *sharp exhale :D*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 02:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God, I hope not. Their resources would be wasted on that grimdark garbage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 02:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope the strike goes through so there's a chance the show loses more viewers, thereby prompting Gimple to start planning a god damn end game. No show can go on forever, otherwise we'd still be watching the 90s Spider-Man on episode 739, just because "there's still too much source material bro!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 01:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Said every prison inmate upon their release. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 00:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that feel. I do freelance proofreading online and I can't get a part time proofreading gig, because my experience isn't professional. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 00:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If her feet are a little stiff, run some hot water over them to loosen them up! I had that issue with mine, but she articulates just fine now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm assuming it's got to be one of Hot Toys various Iron Men. They have a lot of moving parts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope you got her. Ms. Marvel is great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just looked at the pictures! 

The review explained what the deal is with the suit, it's the latest Spider-Man armored suit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marvel Legends Series Toys'R'Us Exclusive Spider-Man   Mary Jane Watson 2-Pack Review </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 04:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes it's the only way to get certain things out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just looking at buying the BAF itself last night, because I really want a Rhino, but I'm just not comfortable buying used stuff, so seeing Rhino is potentially being released on his own is great. It's about time they realized they could make more money by selling BAF (assuming it's the BAF) a few years after the wave is out of production. I'm sure the exclusive Groot Evolutions was the catalyst for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They shipped him off to Belize. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently this list came down from a trusted source over at the Fwoosh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you guys think? 

I'm hoping this is true, because it's got a few figures I want, like Rhino, Ghost Rider with Bike, maybe a comic Iron Man (hopefully the ANAD suit) The Ant-Men, Tony Stark, X-23, and a potential Stan Lee figure! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rumored Marvel Legends list for 2018 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Due March 1st 2018:-

* Spiderman 6" ML
* Spiderpunk
* Spiderman Noir
* Spiderwoman
* Gwenpool
* Prowler
* Demogoblin
* Mysterio
* BAF Lizard

Jan 1st(so maybe end of year, movie based wave)

* Black Panther x 2
* Siberian Toger
* Leopard
* Black Bolt
* Iron Man x 2
* Namor
* BAF not confirmed

Deadpool ML Asst
1st Jan

* Deadpool 90's x 2
* Cable x 1
* Dominoe x 1
* Xforce Deadpool x 1
* X-23 x 1
* Palidin x 1
* Deathlock x 1
* BAF musclur guy in pants

Avengers 6" Asst
1st March

* Movie Iron Man x 2
* Movie Captain America x 1
* Taskmaster x 1
* Songbird x 1
* King Cobra x 1
* Spiderman x 1
* Vision x 1
* BAF Thanos

Marvel Legends 6" 
1st March


* Ghost Rider with Hell Cycle x 2
* Black Widow with Motorcycle x 1

Store exclusives (stores to be determined)

* Leopard   Everett BAF lower body of Stan Lee
* Winter Soldier   Falcon With Stan Lee Upper Body
* Dr Strange   Tony Stark (2nd haf 2018) with Stan Lee Head
* Stan Lee Target Exclusive (March 1st) Captain America version
* Walmart Exclusive Rhino 6"
* Walmart Exclusive 2 pack 6" Ant Man   Hank Pym

* Walmart Infinity Gauntlet sdcc 2014 repack

* Walgreen Exclusive Mr Fantastic

* Walgreen Exclusive Silver Surfer

6" thor

* executioner x 1
* young thor x 1
* female thor x 1
* Villain Ruler xela x 1
* villain loki x 2
* thor x 2
* baf hulk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might have to buy it if you get caught defacing store property. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, yeah, but it took the X-Men wave a while to actually start hitting here after it hit over there. I'm hoping the wait is a lot shorter! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hoping this means the US release isn't far behind! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not weird at all, though. Most people are familiar with Spider-Man and MJ being together, so it's a natural pairing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, take that you do nothing bitch! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard that putting a small amount of super glue on the joint and constantly turning it does the trick. Research that though, because I don't want to be the reason you fuck up your custom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they'll probably just delay it, but I think it might have wrapped already. I think the Punisher did, and I think that comes after JJ2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was just a joke, and I should have been more clear about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 06:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Compare him to what we've got now. If you're a Trump supporter, you may have difficulty doing this, though. Simple things are a daunting task for those folks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 06:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get it, cuz she got exploded in the Kingsman base. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They only had about 8 episodes worth of story this past season and they stretched it out to 16-19 hours of television with all the extended episodes they had. It was downright soulless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt the strike would be the reason it gets cancelled. If it gets cancelled it's probably because of the time slot ABC put it in. Nothings made it past a season in that time slot. I'm hoping it gets a final wrap up season to address things that I'm sure won't be brought up this season (Gravitron) and give the characters a proper farewell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #**BECAUSE HE LED US WITH GRACE *AND* ELOQUENCE!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I remember reading that a lot of Iron Man wound up being improvised by the cast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is just gonna mean later start dates for the following seasons of the DC CW shows. I doubt they'd be dumb enough to try to do the shows without writers that know how to write a good "Can we talk?" segue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marvel Studios pretty much only has Captain Marvel in danger at the moment, but last time there was a Writer's Strike we wound up with Iron Man, and that was pretty cool, cuz it was built in a cave **WITH A BUNCH OF SCRAPS!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh shit, the Writer's Strike might be able to fuck over TWD in the ratings, and they'll finally be forced to start planning an endgame for the series! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 01:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I should actually get around to slogging through the second half of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just stick with the normal versions. No snow, flame, shore, crack, or biker scout troopers for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe SHF Grievous will be the September release? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He still looks repulsive as fuck though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're getting ripped off. The seller just launched and offering a huge discount on products is a well known scam. You may have gotten a phony tracking number. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yikes, my AOTC Obi-Wan and a Geonosis Battle Droid have that squeaky plastic on plastic thing going on too. I guess they're gonna be taking a hot shower tomorrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't stop people from doing it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, that the combat is better, but stuff like clearing an outpost only for it to be full of kett the next time you drive past it is meaningless. An easy way to have avoided this was to populate it with Nexus colonists. 

I experienced the freezing a lot on every Nomadable planet, and I know I didn't play as much as you did. 

The character issue isn't one that sticks in my craw too much, because I expect them to be developed more in potential sequels, though I would have liked to like them more by the end of the game.

I played the OT, and I think that over all the game just did not stack up to it, and I tried my best to like the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are mass market toys, you probably are just winding up with some duds. There are methods of improving friction between the joints though. I think I've read that using Pledge on the joint will do the trick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disagreed 100% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd rather you just down vote me than have you light up my inbox with such a half assed rebuttal that doesn't benefit OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But those calves'll stiffen up on you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait until it's $20 bucks. The game isn't worth anything above $30. It feels like a game from last gen, and it's more frustrating than ME2 and ME3. 

So many hidden loading screens, even with the patch cutting down some of it.

 The Nomad fucking blows... Lots of empty terrain, meaningless combat. You take an outpost down, drive back later, everyones back. There was also a lot of temporary freezing while piloting the nomad to the next waypoint. It was annoying. Fuck the Nomad.

PB is annoying... Squad mates are kinda dull. Some decent non squad mate characters though, like Reyes on Kadara.

Damn alien sudoku. The game is very repetitive. TONS of pointless side missions. TONS. Take those out, and the game is short too.

I regret paying $60 bucks for this. I went straight back to finishing the Platinum for Horizon after I beat the main story+epilogue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That just kinda seems like cheating if you ask me. I mean, I did that, but I didn't feel good about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna have to disagree with you there. OML looks small in the box, where as this guy is bulkier, taller, and comes with that stand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you seen the Mattel version? While I may rag on Mafex for their build quality, the figures are still way above what you'd find from Mattel, King of Garbage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much is that in doubloons? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not just order online to fill in the gaps? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 06:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #**"YOU WANNA GET NUTS?! LET'S GET NUTS!"** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 06:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Power Rangers could make a big, juicy, comeback if we add sex scenes to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Annie, are you okay? Will you tell us that you're okay? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Annie, are you okay? Are you okay, Annie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just don't like their sound. Also, I can only take *so* many white dudes doing their best attempts at reggae... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't Smooth Criminal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been waiting to buy the first Green Arrow trade for kindle, but the price just won't budge! The artwork looks absolutely gorgeous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm doing stuff, Lori. Things, isn't that enough?"

-The Walking Dead

I really think this is the perfect quote for what the show has become.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CHEATER! 


OP said *a* quote! 

"A" as in one, not "A" as in *ANARCHY!!!*

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he's coming for that booty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it's an Oscar caliber period piece featuring tour de force performances from Will Ferrel and Amy Poehler. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> somebody spilled some salt in your cheerios, mate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I derived a different meaning from FPP's comment, than what was intended.

I'd be down with checking out some Marvel Comics, provided they do their rebirth right and get new creative teams and hook us up with that $2.99 price point. Otherwise, I'll just keep waiting for cheap Kindle trades of Ms. Marvel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 02:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing DC Rebirth totally fell apart after the initial arcs concluded? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dorkside is salty.

Still, it must suck for them having two recent ML waves pop up before they can offer them to collectors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 23:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IT'S ON THE BLU-RAY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bandai: S.H. Figuarts GotG2 Star-Lord, Rocket, and Dark Knight Joker Magazine Scans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just stopped caring about where exactly each movie takes place in the timeline. It's clear that the folks in charge don't really care, so why should I? It makes it easier to just enjoy the movie that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> never were </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought this was the Hamburgler. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These go up on the 28th? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the official Mafex figures are already QC nightmares considering how often they break, the bootlegs must be even worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That hair piece isn't placed correctly on the figure. It should come down to his eyebrows. That's the normal hair piece, the other is the helmet hair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bootleg Mafex figures? If you're considering buying one, you might as well throw your cash in the trash and cut out the middleman.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not nearly as lame as the used condoms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just watch New Girl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 03:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gov. Brown is trying to kill the MCS, Senator Nguyen is trying to save it. Get informed, and sign the petition linked in the article, if you can (there might be something funky going on with the zip code field.)


The Middle Class Scholarship was what got me through school, I'd hate to see it cut.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senator Janet Nguyen's bill to save the Middle Class Scholarship clears Senate Education Committee </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 03:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's actually only *slightly* over 10 inches. I'd imagine he'd still be a little bigger in terms of proportions in relation to 1/6 figures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the info, I can now gladly pass on this wave with no regrets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only slightly intereseted in the cosmic Spider-Man, simply because of the bearded Parker head, but I can wait until it's on sale.

Hopefully someone can say whether it fits on the Pizza mold or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're all gonna wind up in Trump's gulag, along with Alec Baldwin's severed head if Trump isn't stopped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's on Hulu. I caught up on two seasons last summer before the third started with a free trial.

Anyone looking to do the same should wait until they put up the third season like a week before the fourth season starts, whenever that is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's [*dirty*.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fBVhfdduwfo) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell your wife that's a fucking amazing coat hanger she's holding there. I've got a couple of those things myself, and let me tell ya, when they break, they make excellent back scratchers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 03:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [RIP](http://www.fleurette.co.nz/wp-content/uploads/2015/11/single-red-rose.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He should try again when he's 18. They're probably not even considering him because he's a minor, and there are rules about when and how long they can work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is fucking incredible dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll probably wind up getting it, even though it doesn't look like Figuarts is really trying with this release. The only Ledger Joker I have is the Movie Master I got when I was 12, and that came with nothing except a stupid zip lock bag for a 1:1 scale joker card. fucking mattel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's right. People need to learn to read closely. 

Besides, if they revealed accessories now, it would surely eat into the sales of the Rebirth Set. I'd expect to see something at Comic Con. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just found out the Zelda BoTW is available for Wii U... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 05:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 05:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started jogging about a month ago, and each time without fail, my knees start to ache at about the 2 mile, so I feel very apprehensive when I start running, cuz I feel like they'll give way. What am I doing wrong that's causing my knees to ache? I'm only 23 and I weigh about 235 lbs, and I'm trying to lose my fat  belly, so I'm wondering what the deal is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Star-Lord, man. Legendary outlaw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate to be *that* guy, but if the photo is taken from above, and  Wolverine is crouching and hunched over, we don't really don't get an accurate sense of scale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny enough, I've been waiting to fight a Thunderjaw to the sweet sounds of Connor 4Real's "I'm So Humble." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wasn't thinking straight, cuz the wampa funked up his face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This game is basically what the Telltale games should aspire to be. If it had come in at $25, like those games do, you better believe people would have raved about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dog treat, am I right!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He plays the dog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thing was in an episode of Netflix's Santa Clarita Diet. I only noticed it because I see it posted here all the live long day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thereby ensuring that he will be impossible to find, as is the norm for post December Star Wars merch, it seems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From those of us that didn't or couldn't buy the Rebirth set: Thank you. You probably made this possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> too much blood

not seeing any cuts or bruises, so is Batman just casually wearing somebody else's blood? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 07:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been applying to different writing jobs. One I'm really hoping I hear from was a job at DC comics that sounds like I'd be reading scripts from their TV stuff and comics and providing notes on it. 

No job experience in the traditional sense, though I do do some work in transcription online. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (NOT MINE) ML Homecoming Wave about to hit, I guess. Rumored 4/28 street date. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theory and Practice of Film w/ a focus in Screenwriting

I have no idea what I'm doing. I was not prepared for job hunting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Job hunting cuz I graduated 5 months ago and I still don't have a real job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 05:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent post dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 05:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right here. http://news.toyark.com/2017/02/18/toy-fair-2017-dc-collectibles-action-figures-241059 

http://news.toyark.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2017/02/Toy-Fair-2017-DC-Collectibles-064.jpg

That's a pretty good shot, by most people's estimations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 04:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's Caitlyn Jenner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 04:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not true, they showed the final production figures at Toy Fair, and they did a pre release video on the DCC facebook for the set. They also gave Jay C from TNI a set to review, all before the set was released. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 04:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not even close dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 02:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lookin thicc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 02:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With Frank Gladstone? I took it under the FEA number, but the name sounds very familiar.

The class was dreadfully boring. You're stuck looking at animation from the 20s and 30s for weeks before you get into anything remotely familiar. Almost all of the modern stuff is glossed over in the final class. The middle chunk of the class mostly revolves around stuff from the 40s-80s with a heavy emphasis on the earlier stuff from that period. Attendance is mandatory, he passes a sheet around during class. 

I believe there are only three assignments. A midterm, extra credit essay, and a final essay. Each essay is 2 pages each. I got an F on the midterm, but he curves the grade, so including both essays I wound up with a B in the class.

If you're just taking the class as a requirement, I guess I'd recommend it, you could always just arrive sometime during the last hour and sign the attendance sheet at the end if you decide you're not up to sticking around for the full 3 hours.

I took it because I thought it'd be fun and interesting part of my major, and it really wasn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They probably already had these figures planned, they just wanted fans to feel like they had a say in it. I'm sure it was 100% rigged from the start. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jadis doesn't bode well for the quality of the upcoming season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
