<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3788</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look into PSLF, I'm sure you qualify for forgiveness. If you plan on continuing to work with the govt. you should continue to go to school and get the degree and have the cost forgiven if it will secure a higher position.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There really isn't a way to notice unless you have the actual .Docx and your looking at everyones margins/font. Otherwise, you literally can't fucking tell...plus, most undergrad Profs DON'T CARE!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FUCK NO! 

Dude, the point of no return in puss'n out and not taking it. You took it, ok, now learn from your mistakes. This test is aimed at testing how you react under pressure. Take it as many times as you have to in order to pass it, BUT every time you take it, remember your mistakes from the previous test. 

This test's mission is to mind fuck you. You CAN beat this test because other do every time it's administered. All you have to do is get in that mindset and just embrace the suck and get shit done. Get out of your own way and focus on whats at hand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He/She asked...step into the depths we law students have to tread as we are ill prepared for actual legal practice. 

I dare them to even consider writing about something like that. I bet they will go with the immigration issues in connection with current events. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The third one is a triangle. 

(Yes, sarcasm, I know it's a defendant symbol people...) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took it. Loved it. I put the time in and passed the first time with plenty of room to spare.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use to do the opposite of this in undergrad to meet length requirements.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should do it on Adverse Possession and how that ties into the Criminal Justice System when looking at it from a Rules Against Perpetuities standpoint. 

Your going to narrow down a point of law to write about, haha, and then have to expand beyond what you want to in order to write about it. 

I dare you to take a 1L Property class.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jeez. 

Ok, so he has to be some what smart. Give him the numbers, and be as honest as you can with him. Just lay it all on the table. Show him how you'll make payments, how he will have to take loans out, how you will be on the hook if you co-sign...literally everything. 

College is an adult decision. You could bargain with him too I suppose. If he goes to a community college closer, maybe you could buy him a car or something. 

Tell him to do his research on the prices of college. Tell him I went to law school and have $184,000 of student loans. I am dreading having kids because of this talk; screw the birds and the bees talk, this one is going to suck worse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow...$2K BEFORE taxes...don't spend it all in one place; you'll be lucky to net $1,200! Run...any place like that has little to *NO* respect for what you've gone through; they just want to take advantage of the current market. 

FUCK THAT! 

I suppose they will have you write your own contract as well...smh!

Edit: I would rather pretend to act dumb and ignorant to get a factory job then work somewhere like this. You should email them this thread so they can wake up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 23:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, first, you should have taken the Sub-S Election with your current LLC for the Web Development. The Sub-S Election is for Federal Taxes only and allows you to minimize your tax burden significantly.  Most small businesses are eligible, but you may want to double check. If you don't elect to be an S-LLC your going to have to pay Self Employment Taxes. 

Now, your Accountant was correct *IF* they were talking about the Airbnb rentals. The article you read was kind of misleading, because regardless of how long they stay, so long as you make $0.01 (yes, a penny) the IRS wants you to claim that as "gross income." Airbnb may only send you a tax form if they stay longer than 14 days or whatnot, that's something you have to read in their "Terms and Services" when you use them as a broker. 

I'm not a tax expert, and I'm not going to represent that I am. I suggest that you should go a schedule a free consultation with one to lay everything on the table so you can minimize your tax burden over everything you have going on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should *NOT* form an LLC for your random Airbnb stays. Your going to go through the hassle of paying the fees with your state, opening up a bank account, getting everything else in line...for what benefits? 

Oh that's right, there is none in this scenario; you didn't even take a Sub-S election on your other LLC. 

You should set up an business when you want to separate your business liability from your personal liability. 

*You are not going to incur any liabilities, unless you turn your home into a bed and breakfast and you fail to pay your outstanding order for the complementary nightly Rocky Road ice cream bowl.*

Your homeowners insurance is or will usually cover guests, which these individuals are your guests...they just happen to be paying you. 

Plus, your more than likely:

* (a) Not going to receive a tax form from Airbnb; and
* (b) Not going to be audited by the IRS.

Everyone is so "LLC Crazy" now days, and they forget the fundamental purpose of such entity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 13:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to update the blog and it must be original content. If you use someone's canned content Google's algorithm views that as a negative and effects you negatively in SEO sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 12:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go ask the members of r/lawfirm they may be able to give you some better advice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 02:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, same! I yell at them...

"My shits paid!" 

...and give them the super finger.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 01:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same. I will amplify my voice to "out-side voices" level just as if we were in preschool *where you learn NOT to cut lines.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 01:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you being intentionally vague? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's all about perception.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 01:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fixed my post, but it was capitalized interest. 

I would have done a few things: 

* Taken the LSAT over to get a higher score
* Attempt to get some type of scholarship
* Lived with my parents
* Try to minimize life expenses/ lifestyle change
* Made payments before to minimize capitalization
* Work more through law school to save/pay down the loan

...just to name a few...

I made the choices I did thinking I had to, brain washed almost by how I was raised, but in reality I didn't. Law school  opened my eyes to a lot about life, and I'm thankful; I wouldn't trade the experience for anything. This is my reality, my life, and I'm thankful to be in the position I am; even if it means sacrificing for a little while longer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * $155,000
* $197,000 w/ capitalized interest
* $188,000 currently (just made $8,700 payment)

Shit is expensive if you go it alone. Looking back I would have made a few different choices, but I learned from what I borrowed; it is what it is. I have a good job and I'm aggressively paying it down. It's not going anywhere and the interest will kill me, so I've *embraced the suck and I'm going HAM!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Consider that stolen, sir.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the feeling. You'd literally have to explain everything, without making them feel like a complete fucking idiot, which is impossible at that point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmfao. Smh...

Like, what is your response to that? My jaw would just drop.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 12:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poseidon   Zeus. 

73% of the brain/heart is comprised of water. [Google It!](https://www.google.com/webhp?sourceid=chrome-instant rlz=1C1CHZL_enUS687US687 ion=1 espv=2 ie=UTF-8#q=water+in+human+body *)

Does this mean I could potentially control someone's mind/actions? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 12:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that response every time I tell someone I went to law school. Never fails.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 12:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand where your coming from, it's a good place, and shows a lot about your character. You have to look out for you and your family though. It's a tough decision, but if they truly care for you they should reasonably understand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heed his advise. No sense in turning down 50% more money and a easier commute. Shame on them for not binding you contractually, that's their error, not yours. If an offer comes you have to take it. With the 50% increase in salary just pay for the remaining classes out of pocket.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 02:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usual Conversation:

* "Defense or prosecution?"
* "If it were only that easy...see what I'd really like to do is practice Commercial Banking and Article 4 of the Uniform Commercial Code..."
* "...oh..." *glazed over look, instantly regretting entering this conversation* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 02:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely. I have $184,000 of student loan debt, but I'm working diligently to pay that down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahahahahahah! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would second this, or Commercial Paper/Sale (whatever your school calls it). Sales is a great re-cap of contracts right before you take the Bar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great article. However, SOFI is not eligible to make mortgage loans in my state (MI); that's probably why I've had a few big named banks offer essentially the same thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha. 

I'm in the legal field, language is very important to my life. I suppose I could have been more clear when differentiating the two portions of the student loan. 

I'm not completely sold on the HELOC itself, for a few reasons:

* Usually they have a higher interest rate. I figured if I could refi the house while utilizing the HELOC cash to pay off my loans it would save us money over time in the form of less interest paid; 
* HELOC usually have Call Provisions in them, Google them, they suck; and 
* The loan right now on the house is not in my name so we would be adding me to the mortgage, maybe. I don't know the effect that will have on the overall math. 

I looking for the ideal position for my family. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your correct. 

I'm securing and attaching my home to the amount I will be paying off, essentially rolling it over into the equity I've established. If I die, this amount will *not* be extinguished and my wife *will* be responsible for the reaming balance of our mortgage; hence the life insurance inquiry. 

The remaining student loan account will have roughly $100,000 and has interest rates ranging from 4.9% to 5.6%, respectfully. If I die, this amount *will be* extinguished and my wife *will not* be responsible for the outstanding balance. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect! Yea, CH 13 is pain and the plans suck; that was a smart move on your part. Keep up the good work, bud! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean by:

 You are not securing your student loan debt.

Now, your on the right track with the rate deferential talk. My student loans range in interest rates so the difference with vary, but overall this will lower the overall amount I will pay. Also, refi my grad debt later on may be an option if this does not work out; that's the primary reason I'm seeking advice here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is true, Hawaii is dope though. Fuck your stuck there because flights are SUPER^super expensive usually. 

Seriously though, whats your end goal? 

If you suddenly had to pay rent, what would you do?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, so your upside down by roughly $4,000 *ish*. 

What is your end goal? You just want to get out of the loan?

If you want to just get out of the loan your going to have to think about parting with the vehicle. There are a few options, but its going to vary on a few variables as u/chocolate_soymilk outline in their comment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Understandable. Must be California or New York. Haha

Cost of living makes things very difficult to live, because well, you have to survive. 

What do you eat? Do you make your own food, or do you eat out 7 days a week? 

You can check out r/Frugal some people on there eat for as little as $1.00 a meal. I'm not saying you have to in order to survive, just giving you some insight and avenues you may pursue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Completely agree; for example, MI SOL for contract claims is 6 years. 

I was just responding in a metaphorical sense just to educate and expound on your comment; hair splitting, yes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No offense, but it sounds like you have a little self-worth issue. Reality is you owe this money, and it will continue to grow by paying nothing towards it. 

You have to proactively pay on this loan until its gone. Maybe the first step is changing your attitude here. We are all, probably, in some similar situation; I myself have $184,000 of student loan debt. I'm working 60 hours a week to pay it off as much as I can. I wanted to take advantage of the PSLF program, but I don't trust it will be around in 10 years, so I'm doing it on my own. 

What's your budget like? What are your job hours life, could you get another job? Do you have the opportunity to get a higher paying job?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What type of car? Year, make, model, condition...essentially, what is the KBB value? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clearly they are not a priority to you now. You should change your mindset on the loans IMO; $60,000 can easily pile up fast and like you said your not paying on them at all. If you sacrifice for 3-5 years you can easily pay off $60,000 of debt. What is your income now? What type of working field?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In your closing documents you should have a break down of who was paid what. Once, you get the original agreement I'd error on the side of caution, you may want to go speak with an Attorney. Communicate with the realtor in writing only and keep track of all correspondences.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I ask you why you *didn't* file bankruptcy? It looks like to me all of this debt was eligible for discharge.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Bullshit Alarms*

Plus, it may be illegal as a form of insider trading.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's in my nature to disagree with this comment. If the Statute of Limitations has rung, it's a moot point, they sat on their right. 

Realistically, you need to read the contract you signed with them and determine if they were paid by the closing costs. You could have paid the fees, but somehow they were shafted on their share of the commission.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read what you just wrote. 

 HELOC...It's just more cash you can use as you want to.

I want to use the HELOC to pay off my student loan account. You don't have to re-invest the HELOC money into your house. I know a HELOC isn't associated with my student loans, nothing is, hence my hesitation on attaching them to anything I hold jointly with my spouse. 

 Student loans don't have security associated with them; they don't need to, because they have other ways to get the money from you. 

Again, the exact reason why I'm hesitant on attaching them. As of now, if I die, the loans are extinguished because they are Federally backed loans. If I attach them to ANYTHING, the lender will be able to seek repayment...even after my death. I'm not stupid. Thus, the primary reason I will only attach my debt to my house if I get life insurance which will allow my surviving spouse to pay off the secured debt upon my death.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I have read and discussed in length with multiple lenders, no. 

When I was tire-kicking a few lenders they offered me an opportunity to finance the loans, but required me to pledge my house as collateral.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, but you can. I've been offered this refi/HELOC hybrid by two different lenders. 

I wasn't paying on the student loans because:

* I wasn't married and the home loan was not mine (still isn't technically);
* My wife was working at the home loan before we were married...now we are refocusing our efforts on my student loans; and
*  I was wasn't paying on the student loans because I had to live and could only work part time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roll Student Debt/Mortgage Refi Question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 13:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the title suggests, I'd like to roll some of my student loan debt into my residence by utilizing some of the equity I've established. 

* Property FMV: $180,000.00
* Mortgage Balance: $87,000.00
* Mortgage Type: 30 YR Fixed Rate
* Interest Rate: 4.25%

I have two accounts with X Student Loan Service for a total student debt amount of $184,000.00 currently. I just processed a principal payment of $8,700 towards knocking out the highest interest loan disbursement which was at 7.65%. I'm sure I will get a lot of comments about why it's so high and asking what I do; I've attended law school and I'm in the licensing process to become an Attorney. That being said, my one accounts of "Direct Grad Plus" loans has $84,000.00 of debt and is ranging from 7.65% to 6.59% with interest rates. 

My main reason why I was hesitant on attaching the student debt to the property was the fact that it wouldn't terminate upon my death. I will only attach it to the property if I can get life insurance to cover the payoff amount to safe guard my wife. We currently have around $22,000.00 in our savings account as an emergency fund. I'm a contracted consultant for a law firm on a very prominent case which can, but most likely won't, be discontinued at any time and my wife works two jobs both of which are very secure. We have a very minimal lifestyle, we only have the usual household utilities and our mortgage to pay on monthly; we've paid off our cars. 

We live in a rural mid-western portion of the USA if that matters. We purchased our home in 2014 for $145,000 and put $30,000 down when we purchased; the surrounding area has appreciated significantly. I don't want to make a poor decision with regard to the two biggest investments I've made in my life so far, any help is greatly appreciated. 

My questions are simple:

* Has anyone done this?
* Where would I go for life insurance? What should I consider? (28 years old; non-smoker; very light drinker)
* What would be a good rate for life insurance? 
* Should I consider doing 15 yr vs. 30 yr? 
* Rates are rising, what should I consider a favorable refi rate? 
* Is there anyway I can get away from closing costs? 
* (Insert question I can't think of right now...)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 12:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you want to go to law school? One class should not be the basis of such a monumental decision.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 01:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I consider myself healthy. I would like to play basketball more often, but I'm always on the go and I eat relatively healthy. I don't drink soda or munch on snacks. I have the occasional beer, but don't over indulged; most people don't live the lifestyle I do though. You have to be smart about what you put in, and since you have not attended law school, you haven't learned that most people don't know how to keep a healthy balance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 01:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, your not in law school? 

I'd argue that before law school I couldn't work more than 45-50 hours per week. 

Law school easily conditioned me to put in 50+ hours of "work," but you have to remember this is significantly different work than your thinking. The work you will be doing is purely mental and over the three years your brain is conditioned to put out for prolonged periods at a higher than normal intellectual level.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 01:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the same with my firm. I only have to bill 40, but I'm a hustler by nature, and agree with your comment about earning your keep.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 01:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm making money, that's all I care about; I just threw down $8,700 on my student loans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 01:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work 60 hours a week currently. I can peak out at 75 before I start to feel like a zombie; I'm sure I could easily push more, though. 

Edit: Only reason why I'm at the firm I am is because I outlasted and out performed 5 other individuals. So, as long as they don't have a problem paying me for 60hrs a week, I'm going to continue to put in the time. You get what you put in! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends if its Al Capone's missing tax returns...those are highly valuable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [NBA Shoe Size...unusual ones]
(https://solecollector.com/news/2014/01/the-nba-s-most-interesting-shoe-sizes)

Yao Ming is in a size 18 dude... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are so many video game posts on here; search video games just in r/Flipping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 12:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can start by making an outline that includes everything. As you go along an review the outline continuously you will narrow it down in size. By the time you get 1-2 weeks out from the final exam you should have a great underlying understanding of the main issues and just focus on the main issues/what you don't know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 22:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it does!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome!!! I'm going to sit down and read it ALL! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 17:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, congrats dude!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 16:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the best thing to do in your circumstances. 

It's very normal for LLCs to be set up this way so it shouldn't be anything that will cost you more money. In my state, it's literally a "check the box" to select manager-managed entity and explicitly laying out the managers powers in the operating agreement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is so specific...is this a problem for class? If so, don't get caught it will go down *on your permanent record.*
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your going to get addicted...welcome, welcome to the club. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His math in the beginning of his video IS NOT CORRECT! I cringe every time I hear him talk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it's a promise to repay the lender. It's a contract for repayment; contracts are just promises to do something in exchange for consideration. 

You signed a "master promissory note" when you took your loans out.

It is paramount you, yourself, get an Attorney involved to protect your interests. You don't want any balloon payments and you want the 0% interest explicit; all this needs to be in the contract.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 03:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought an S-Video one and it works AWESOME!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 03:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your attorney friend doesn't practice business law. 

You can set the LLC up 50/50 revenue wise, that's fine. You should look into a manager-managed system of control. 

That way you elect someone to make the business decisions, which takes out the possibility of voting into a deadlock. 

Your going to want a very precise operating agreement written out that explicitly outlines who has what power, etc. I would suggest NOT going with a DIY boilerplate legal document from legalzoom; if you do problems WILL arise in the future. Plus in most states, LLCs are set up by default as member-managed entities; manager-managed is an election, much like your Sub-S election you SHOULD look into as well. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 03:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You neeeeeeeeeed to have a lawyer draft a promissory note. I'd suggest seeking a free consultation from a local contract/business attorney. 

I can't stress this enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I HATE his advertisements! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Federal Student loans give you a lot of options for repayment. If you REFI you loans with a private lender your going to paint yourself into a narrow corner of repayment. I would suggest against it until you graduate, are out of the deferment period, and have payed down the loans for a while. IT is a growing field and you will get a good job somewhere when your done, so don't stress now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So annoying. I had the same thing happen to me with a VERY RARE book I bought for $45.00 at auction; the book is easily worth $200+ in any condition, and this book was flawless. 

The Seller told me she was not going to sell it to me because there was conditional issues she did not disclose in the auction description. I told her I didn't care and would take it regardless if it was in a tub of water. She wouldn't budge and was an asshole about the whole thing, so I Neg'd her. I didn't want to, but that is just wrong. 

I wanted to file a suit in small claims court to force her to sell the book to me, but she lived in Texas and it would have cost me more than the books worth to do so. Had I known someone in Texas...I'd have that book.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Planned on going to an Estate Sale near me which had a TON of items I could flip. Was late getting there and found upon my arrival a line of 120+ people. When I finally got in the house, everything I wanted was GONE, and it was uncomfortably tight; house was from 1844. I still ended up purchasing eight items for $40.00 and plan to flip them soon. 

* (1) Tin Type photo of a woman sitting on a chair (great condition, no frame, but she is attractive and will sell); 
* (1) Personal/Pocket *Holy Bible* in excellent condition from 1864;
* (1) Texas Rangers Vintage "Rangers" Large Patch;
* (1) *My Father, Mark Twain* by Clara Clemens (Mark Twain's Daughter) 1st Ed. 2nd Printing and it is SIGNED by Clara...could be the best item of the lot;
* (1) *Manual on the Constitution* by Marietta College President Andrews in 1874 (I will keep this one; I'm a law school graduate and collect anything "law related.")
* (2) U.S Army Remembrance Pillow Shams from Camp Phillips, Kansas   Camp Forrest, Tennessee; 
* (1) Malta, Montana Wild West Pillow Sham (Great graphics; Man riding a bucking bronco).

I bought the pillow shams out of fear of passing them up; I thought they were flags. I couldn't do my normal eBay search because there was SO MANY people around me. The house easily had 50-100 people in it. In the upstairs bedroom I found a floorboard that looked to be intentionally cut to be removable. I popped it up and there WAS a space for hiding items, but there wasn't any items in the space; super glad I found it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 16:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had an internship with a law firm that specialized in construction law, and like another comment said here, it is *VERY* broad topic. 

I did a lot of Condo Construction and general land splitting for personal development. With the splitting we drafted a lot of documents associated with transferring of ownership and easements. With the Condo Construction, we drafted a lot of the Master Deeds in accordance with our state's [Condominium Act](http://www.legislature.mi.gov/documents/mcl/pdf/mcl-act-59-of-1978.pdf)...your state may have similar legislation. 

Since your in CA, I'd be knowledgeable about commercial leaseholds. We had a few clients that were developers, but whom also had commercial property we did the lease work on and had to evict a few tenants. 

You should really know contract and property law rather well. I love this shit, if you come to a cross-road feel free to PM me and I will do my best to help you in your quest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 16:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd second this. You can easily jump right in and search with the lexis/west engines, but your going to have a narrow view of your issue. 

I would suggest Google first to see if there are any connecting issues that tug at your overall issue. Then once you have a good understanding, go into Lexis/West and use the Secondary sources to get a great overview of the law associated with your issue. Once you have that done, you will know what your NOT looking for, and in turn you're going to be a lot better off. 

It's a stylistic thing, your going to search the way your comfortable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why I do this in spurts. I will list a lot of stuff for three months, and then it's like I don't even know I have an eBay account. It will come in waves and you just have to ride it or get off the boat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh goody, another DIY Legal Website!

Are you fishing for comments, reactions, free advertisement?

*Disclaimer: This message contains sarcasm.*

Edit: The sample will has got me laughing out loud. Your distributing 3 outdated vehicles, probably with high mileage, but yet your also distributing a $30,000 piano and a $25,000 clock; there is no consistency in your gold and Cartier laden example. I don't think you know who your target customers are. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super noob here. 

Is it possible to find a website you like, copy the code they use, and then in a way reverse engineer it using your information to personalize it? 

Is that a thing?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Christmas ornaments are pretty hard to move actually. The Christmas train depends on what number, I'd say the first 15 cars are pretty common. It's when you get into the later train cars that will run upwards of $85-$100+; people just got sick of paying $25 with shipping. If you do the math there were 40 cars at $25 each, that's $1000 total! The Halloween train is a little bit more hard to find and does fetch around $35-$40 per car, but same thing with the Christmas Train, later cars are worth much much more. The Christmas Village and Halloween Villages will fetch you quite a haul as well; same concept as with the trains, the later pieces are worth more. The Halloween Village is especially hard to come by and is highly sought by collectors. I was fortunate as to how bad this collector wanted everything; she paid full price and shipping.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Random bricks can be fun to buy if you can find them cheap enough. I mostly look for retired sets I can easily flip. Sometimes I will take a stab at open sets, complete them to know what is missing/there, and then either buy the missing bricks/grab one I have or just sell it incomplete depending on the set; really depends on what I find and for what price. The booklets and boxes are super important to have, condition is everything. I'm not a huge mini figure guy, unless it's the super rare ones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was their Hamilton figures. It was a few complete sets and a lot of the rare figures. Since she was in was in Australia and wanted every item I had, I sold them all at a premium price; she didn't mind because she couldn't get them otherwise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They look like cats trying to climb out of a tub filled with water.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's harder to do both portions on eBay. It really takes an ignorant Seller to find an item significantly lower and worth your time, but it can be done. If a Seller takes 5min to research before listing they can prevent listing at a low price; some people just don't care though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have quite a lot I watch. Old books, Legos, vintage fishing lures, The Simpsons stuff, Old tin type photos, video games...I do a lot of antique things...a lot of smalls because they are easier to ship. What ever I can make a buck on. I'm constantly looking up stuff I find.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are right! I found one in the trash and looked it up on eBay real quick and saw one comparable sell at $150...instantly snatched it up and found five more rummaging through the rest of the trash. 

They were store over sized displays of their men's and women's perfumes, epically rare from what the gentlemen I sold them to said; he had a perfume business himself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If free trash counts...I obtained some Louis Vuitton Store perfume displays and sold them to a gentleman in Chicago for $750 each; I had 6 for a total of $4,500 profit.  

If your counting item(s) I purchased: I bought some sets of The Simpsons Figures off craigslist and sold them all to one individual in Australia for $3,550 for a $3,250 profit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did this two weeks ago. The Seller had a Buy-it-Now for $75.00 and I offered $50.00...they accepted. When I received the item I sold it three days later for $135.00 on the same site. I do this quite often for the category of goods I watch;it's call arbitrage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My comment was slightly sarcastic in nature. Your right though. I don't know how the law school can justify it, maybe it's just aimed at obtaining publicity for sticking up for the little guy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would this affect C+F? I'm sure he will be alright as long as he discloses it. 

Edit: This is a sarcastic comment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People do this all the time. As long as there isn't anything in the small print about length requirements. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an issue with the MBE statistics. In my state, MI, they removed the ability to test out of the state writing portion. Additionally, Civil Procedure was added to the mix as well. They expect us to know more law, but then complain about the drop in scores? If I could have tested out of the writing portion I would have dedicated all my time on the 8 subjects, instead of the 20+ subjects if you count state distinctions and MBE topics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need this in my life...where can I find one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least! It is really going to depend on the quality of studying your going to do. Quality is paramount to quantity; your going to want to know this stuff and it just spill out when you talk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I treated it like a full-time gig. I graduated in middle of May 16' and started slowly studying the Themis work. I ramped up my studying June 1 and did Monday-Friday,sometimes weekends, up until I took the exam in July. I did mostly 6/7:00am-5:00pm and would work past that most days when my wife worked late. Biggest thing is routine; establish one and maintain it. 

Edit: Not to be a dick, but you get what you put in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would strongly suggest against this; unless, you want to be a science project for all of us. 

I quit my job to study. I was a middle of the pack A-/B+/B student in law school. It's not worth risking it. Your going to need a lot more than two weeks to focus on everything, practice, and hone your skills. I did 8-9 hours a day with Themis and passed by a fair margin on my first time last July.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a good suggestion. Even if your introverted, most people now days can appreciate a sarcastic dry humor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bingo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Copy that. Is there a department that would be better over another. For example, Shoes/Footwear vs. Purses vs. Designer Names... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha! I have done this before. I was helping a friend move out of their dorm and snagged 4 books in the bins; sold them for $25-30/each. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 14:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is an awesome website for [VALUE GUIDE](http://oldcurrencyvalues.com/collectible_currency/)

After reading this article I went and looked at the small amount of paper money I have in my house. I was pleased to find a 1977 US $100 note with serial number: A0005535*...should be worth a little more than $100 on eBay. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
