<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3132</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 20:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nicky because she is just downright a good person who I think I'd get along with. Great character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 15:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Named my first electric, an Ibanez, Alex as is seemed suiting to the sound.
My Fender acoustic is named Tom because why not.
My new Black and Gold Epiphone Custom Pro LP is named Jesus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-09 14:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for finally putting what, in my opinion, a lot of people wanted to say but didn't exactly know how, I included. 

I guess we'll never know if we see him again, after all- he did get a clone phone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-05 22:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't seen S1 in so long but all I can remember is her saying that one day she's gonna get Delphine "so baked".. If only we knew everything would end up happily ever after and this had any chance at all of being fulfilled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 20:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> C, Am, G, D 

or

The pre-chorus to Up All Night by Blink-182.
It just happens, it is great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-01 20:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could be a new clone. It looked slightly like S (possibly because of the clothes). It probably isn't though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-26 20:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm pretty sure Felix was actually just sleeping there and heard Sarah break in, so he went to investigate.

I just re-watched the scene and Fee did seem to have a 'Fee-Style' investigation look going on with his beanie, coat and flashlight. After all, he does have his own apartment to stay in. 

Thanks for the comments though, greatly appreciated.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thoughts regarding Felix. (spoilers?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-26 19:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I have never exactly "trusted" Felix and some events recently have lead to that feeling growing even bigger. A few reasons why are as follows (I am not sure whether anyone else has already mentioned these):

* He left Cal's cabin just before Daniel Rosen arrived. Did he tell DYAD or Daniel where Sarah and Kira were located?
* In episode 2x04, Fee was for some reason also snooping around Mrs. S' house when Sarah was.
* Why does he want Alison to stay in rehab? Does he want to cut her off from the other clones?

To elaborate on the second point. As I was thinking about the baby-tooth stem cell match scene with Delphine and Scott in 2x06, I thought about how DYAD could have possibly gotten a hold of (Kira's?) tooth. Maybe Fee was snooping in S' house to find an old tooth? There is always a possibility for anything in this brilliant show.

I am not sure if my suspicions are valid or not. Maybe the writers and producers wanted the element of suspicion surrounding Fee so us viewers are not so sure of what we suspect we will see in the coming episodes. 

Any thoughts or additions?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 23:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thoroughly enjoyed this one. It is written superbly! ["Of Microscopes and Bloody Hopes"](https://www.fanfiction.net/s/9958328/1/Of-Microscopes-and-Bloody-Hopes) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-18 16:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is not British though he has never said that he isn't gay. If I recall correctly, there was an interview where he didn't want to reveal that aspect of him as it would "change the whole dynamic of Felix as a character". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Foo Fighters - Everlong (Cover by Legs) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-17 13:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 07:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Welcome to the trip, man." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 20:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was meiosis, not mitosis. Sorry to pick that out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 11:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That could be a possibility. No one knows who the original is, or if there even is an original. I just assumed Rachel was more closely related to the scientists [Spoiler](#s "considering her last name being the same as them. She could possibly be the first clone, a sort of test to see if the procedure would work. They might have decided to keep Rachel.") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 20:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, I agree. At least we get to meet Carlton in the next episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 14:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice theories. I have a whole bunch written down and will try to add later, but for now I just wanted to clarify something you said. In the first 'Project LEDA' part, you mentioned something at the end regarding Mrs.S wanting to protect Kira to such an extent because she is Sarah's offspring and exhibits all the characteristics they wanted from the beginning. 
This makes it seem as though you think Mrs.S is one of the scientists in the LEDA photo. I am not 100% sure of myself here but I don't think Mrs.S was one of them as she was too young (possibly, judging from Maria's age). 
The other day I was watching the trailer for 2x04 and noticed the newspaper clipping shot. I paused it and zoomed it (as many others have) and tried to read the caption of the photo with the same two scientists. [Spoiler of what the caption was](#s "Two scientists were incinerated in laboratory explosion, Project ?LEDA? spearheaded by Professors Susan and Ethan Duncan")
After reading that a whole flood of theories came to mind. Especially regarding Mrs.S' involvement. In 2x02 her and Brenda were talking of Mrs.S being part of 'Guns for Funs' -  most likely to do with The Troubles in Ireland back in the 1960's. This leads me to thinking she somehow could have been involved in [Spoiler](#s "what happened with the explosion at the lab")
It isn't the most clear theory but oh well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-06 19:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regarding the brief discussion of Mrs.S' past in 2x02 (dinner at BirdWatcher's), she mentioned that something about being part of "Guns for Funs". This immediately stuck me with the hint that she may have been involved in the "The Troubles" in Ireland back in the late 1960's. After this, she somehow must have migrated to England. [Spoiler](#s "If you refer to the most recent preview, a newspaper clipping can be seen which states something regarding two scientists, Ethan and Susan Duncan, being incinerated in a lab explosion"). This in association with Mrs.S' past hints to her possibly being in the act of [Spoiler](#s "the lab incident. Maybe she was hired with others to collect all research in the lab before it was blown up, or maybe she was hired to blow it up herself/with others. I don't think the explosion was entirely accidental").
With all this in mind, I still have no idea as to how Mrs.S became involved with Carlton. This thought was not received well on tumblr, but anything can happen on this show right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 12:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nail gun? I assume if you could get one powerful enough, it could move through most of the skull/brain then slightly pierce its potential exit point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 11:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None of the clones had nay idea they were being monitored until Sarah found the electrode that one morning and Felix, after being filled in, suggested that if he were part of an illegal cloning case with subjects that needed to be monitored, would he place someone on the inside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 11:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We know that Donnie is in the dark regarding the other clones as when he was told to look out for a woman named Sarah, he had no idea of what physical characteristics he was looking for. 
It does make sense for Donnie to keep an eye on Alison because she slept with chad, though the mysterious funeral texts and quirkiness during the phone call in which Alison purposely mentioned Sarah. 
Donnie is trying to do his 'job', though not necessarily that well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 20:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for this. Definitely something to think about. Now I guess we will just have to wait, look more more clues and then see. Thanks everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 20:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the input. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 02:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh shoot. I have just been thinking about what I said and thought "No one ever confirmed that the other clones were not orphans." Sorry for just assuming that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Original? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 00:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am thinking about Orphan Black a heap these days in preparation of the arrival of the new season. There is one question I just can't seem to have a possible "answer" to...: Is there an original clone?
In one of the earlier episodes, when Felix was going through the Birth Certificates Sarah found in Beth's Safe Deposit Box, he mentioned that all the women's births were within a month from one another. So we know that if the clones' DNA would be derivatives of a baby who has been selected to be cloned (meaning they would be older?). Anyone think that maybe one of the clones who were killed in Europe (or a clone/s we don't know about) could be the original. IS THERE EVEN AN ORIGINAL? 

Thanks 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 00:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, I think that several women around the world were selected to become sort of surrogates/mothers for the same group of scientists that asked Amelia to carry a baby. Amelia had twins from the clone egg as it must have split. I also think that if Amelia would not have run away from the scientists, she would have raised the babies as planned and they would have grown up in a family, similarly to the other clones. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
