<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6681</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 18:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am still bothered from yesterday, when I had to eat supper (and snacks) without knowing any of the calorie content. I don't know why but little things like that bother me. I am going to make up for it by restricting today. Should be easy because I will be at work.

**Breakfast** : Skipped

**Lunch** : 1/2 block of Tofu (315 calories)

**Dinner** :  Skipped

**Snacks** : Skipped

**Total**: 315 Calories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 21:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn. Hits close to home.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 21:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can relate to this post a lot. I haven't ate anything today and I'm debating between continuing the fast or just throwing away all fucks and eating. I hate myself too, and want to embrace Ana because I feel like it might make me happier, but I don't even know anymore. Ugh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 21:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My goal for August is mainly to maintain weight and to not seem suspicious around friends / parents / therapists. After August, I am moving far away - where no one can tell me what to eat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 20:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shitty Day. I've been able to avoid food so far. I'm not sure what dinner will bring... I may have to eat so I don't look suspicious. 

EDIT: My prediction was right. I couldn't avoid the food any longer without my parents knowing. I had to eat a larger portion at supper, along with some snacks. I am just going to write today off at 2000 calories and pray to god it doesn't affect my weight that much. We will see what the scale says tomorrow. 

Breakfast : Skipped (0 calories)

Lunch : Skipped (0 calories) 

Dinner : Chili and fries and vegetables (??? calories)

Snacks :  Banana (105), crackers and hummus (???) 

Total: ~2000 Calories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 00:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello there! It seems this sub doesn't have too many guys on it, from what I can tell. But we're growing in numbers!(: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 00:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So far I have walked over 10,000 steps thanks to pokemon GO and hanging out with friends. I plan to walk even farther this evening! 

Breakfast : Skipped

Lunch : Tofu and Spinach (315)

Dinner : Potato and Beans ( 400) 

Snacks : One slice Pizza (260) , Banana (105) 

Total: 1080 Calories  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 21:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Skipped

Lunch: Oatmeal (360)

Dinner: Vegan Burgers and Fries (820) 

Snacks: Banana (105) 

Total: 1285 Calories

Bonus points- I was able to fast for 20 hours inbetween last night's early supper and lunch today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 20:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> -Breakfast: Skipped (0)

-Lunch: Tofu and Veggies (338) 

-Supper: Pita (476 )

-Snack: Orange ( 62)

-Total:  876 Calories


I know I'm posting this a day late, but not bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Longtime Lurker- Intro </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 20:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello everyone,

I've been lurking this subreddit for a long time. Now, Im hoping to join this wonderful community!3 Here is a little bit of backstory ,while still trying to maintain my anonymity : 

- Shitty Go at Life (rather not go into details)

- Mental Health Worsened: Depression + Anorexia (Hence the username) 

- Was recently hospitalized in inpatient for two weeks, at a LW of 104lbs (forced to go by therapist and parents - hated every second)

- Currently in "recovery" (lol)

I only have a couple sessions left before I am moving far away. When I move, I plan to break all ties to therapy and embrace the soothing voice of Ana once again. Until then, I can't restrict too much, but I am going to try my best...


I'm looking forward to meeting wonderful people here in this community 3.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
