<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8657</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: What are some steps that I can take to control my compulsion to B P? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 18:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am currently overweight, and I have been most of my life, but I've made a lot of progress this year, coming from being well into morbidly obese. I do a good job of eating   exercising, and I lose at a healthy rate. I get a little overwhelmed by restricting calories, but I don't think I need help for that.

When I have cheat days, I easily eat back that entire week's deficit. I purge it all by vomiting, but I know that doesn't really get rid of it. I figure I can continue eating. I have been feeling for so long that this is fine, because it's only once a month, as opposed to more than ten times a day like I was doing before I got on track. But yesterday I genuinely set out to eat moderately for a cheat day, but I found myself compulsively buying more junk food than I actually even wanted, and purging all of it. I felt like I didn't even have a choice.

I have a therapist, and I know she's not the most productive one around, but I'm currently in crisis with depression and anxiety and it's really not a good time to go shopping. I might go on Prozac soon, and I need to at least have someone familiar to see every week while I'm adjusting. I think I'll look for someone new if I get through all of this without a hospitalization. 

But for now, I'd like to know if anyone has any advice for how to talk to her, and what I could expect in return. I don't think I'll ever fully recover, but I want to take steps to feeling more in control and more capable of making the decision not to B P. Has anyone successfully come back from a very compulsive habit? What were the first things you did to break the cycle?

I am motivated to push myself, but that's offset by my low expectations that I'll ever be normative with food. I really want to just focus on not doing what I'm doing anymore. I want to be able to eat off-program every few weeks without binging. And I hate, hate, hate purging so much. It feels like death. How do I do this, with my therapist's help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to stop the nosedive that my relapse is taking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 05:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey,

I've (19/m) been diagnosed with Anorexia for 4.5 years now, and it's been about two years since I sort of recovered-but-didn't-really from when I was at my worst, so to speak. Came out of hospital, vowed to never let it happen again (.. sort of) and maintained a not really super high weight. I mean all I really felt like I did was maintain my weight enough so I would lose all attention from doctors and such, which worked, but it didn't really solve anything, just stick it in the background.

So now, two years later I've started at a new college and completely relapsed. I've had bouts where I have relapsed but it's never been this bad/lasted this long so far. I think what kind of sparked it is: being surrounded by all these new people and struggling to make friends in the first two weeks by feeling like a complete outsider confirmed my feeling of a lack of identity. So I went back to something I knew, and that could stand in for it - except this time the mentality is not as clear cut and it just makes everything feel so much awful as I'm objectively aware of what's at risk now compared to the last time.

So now I'm here (if any of that even made sense), right on the verge of wrecking everything I worked for in the past two years and I just.. don't care. I should, but I don't, and I'm at a loss (so is my therapist..)

It's like I faked my way through the past two years without actually solving anything at all (something that my therapist can't seem to understand when I try to be honest)

Erm, to finish (wow this seems long) - does anyone have any.. I don't know, advice? I guess, on where to go from here (where I'm pretty much alone support wise. Well, I have my therapist but he's .. well, he can shove it sometimes).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: help with an out of town friend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 16:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are a small group of friends and one girl moved away a couple of years ago to a city 5+ hours away. Independently, three of us have noticed signals pointing to an eating disorder, ranging from downy body hair a period of time ago, an obsession with food, and recently, very restricted eating on the few occasions we have eaten together, but because we only see her occasionally, it is hard to tell if she has an eating disorder. 

Three of us are going to visit in a few weeks, and would like some advice on how to proceed if we keep noticing signs, or what else we should look for. We will be staying at her place. We don't know her friends in the new city, and have only briefly met her new boyfriend. We are comfortable speaking to her parents or brother   wife, who live in the same city as us and we know them well. They see her more often than we do.

Tldr; friend lives in another city and we suspect an eating disorder. What should we do on an upcoming visit to either find out more or what should we do if we get enough confirmation to be very concerned? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Does anyone work in the health field? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 05:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
I'm not sure of the demographics of our subreddit but I was curious to see if anyone works in the health field? Nursing? Community Health? Nutrition? Mental Health?

I am about to graduate with a Bachelor's of Science in Nutrition degree with a concentration in Dietetics. My route would be to become a Registered Dietician.

To sum up a lifetime of information in a short sentence, the decision to be a RD (registered dietician) was made at a different time in my life. I thought I was....better.

I feel deflated. I wanted to become a RD when I was more "recovered". I thought I WANT TO HELP PEOPLE FEEL BETTER! OMG FOOD IS AWESOME AND EVERYONE SHOULD FEEL THIS HEALTHY! OMG RAINBOWS AND SUNSHINE AND UNICORNS AND AVOCADOS!

Now I have a dark cloud over me. I think I eat pretty well? I still restrict...but I don't know. My mind is all over the place. I'm burnt out from school and everything that has to do with food. I have thought about food for the past decade because of my eating disorder. Now I have academically studied food/nutrition/health/physiology day in and day out for the past 3 years. Straight A's. Study study study.

Now I feel like my restricting patterns are covered and intertwined with piles of justifications and reasons I feed myself. The worst part is, I don't feel like helping people anymore in that way. Mostly because no one really cares WHY they should eat healthy. They just want me to tell them the easiest way to lose weight.

I'm rambling. Does anyone work in the health field? Do you feel like a hypocrite? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 15:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please consider the recommended diet in [Not about will power](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2f0p7y/anorexia_to_binging_its_not_about_will_power_its/) that includes low glycemic foods.

Also, [Weight Loss after an ED](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2lyta0/navigating_weight_loss_after_an_eating_disorder/).

And, other posts on bulimia:

[Relapse](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2j7kf8/request_crazy_bingepurge_relapse_after_8_years_of/)

[Bulimia recovery sharing](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2dc4rb/recovery_sharing_ziploc_bags_and_other_things/)

[AMA on bulimia recovery](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1uob3k/ama_on_recovery_2_years_ago_i_recovered_from/)

[Addressing Bulimia](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/24g5vt/request_how_to_begin_addressing_bulimia/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Navigating Weight Loss After an Eating Disorder. -Not a perfect article, but a beginning. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 15:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: It's Getting Worse, thoughts of purging </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 22:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like I'm slipping further into the eating disorder abyss these days. I posted on this subreddit over the summer, and didn't get much feedback, but I'm hoping for more guidance this time.

My boyfriend gave me an ultimatum this summer to see a doctor about my bad body image and eating thoughts. I went to the doctor and got told I had BDD, and "disordered eating" leaning on the side of EDNOS. They told me to take a day off of work each week (I work 7 days a week) but I can't afford that and they prescribed me meds. I took them for a while but really didn't think they were helping.

Lately the thoughts are worse than ever before. This all started while I was on a weight loss journey, which kind of became an obsession. I injured myself overdoing it with the exercise (I ran a half marathon, then went back to work, worked out during the week and then ran a 5k in the rain that weekend) and I was just on a work trip - which means largely unhealthy eating - and I've not only stalled in my weight loss, but I've gained.

It's the gain and the fear of gain that's impacting me. I'm petrified to wake up and see that my double chin's come back. I'm tired of being overweight.

But now...on to why I'm posting. While I had thought about throwing up and starving, I had never acted upon it until now. It happened during my work trip. I was eating with a group at a Mexican restaurant there, and I overdid it. I basically binged. And had a margarita - a strong one. During my tipsy state I made myself throw up, but didn't push it too much. 

I told my boyfriend and he's terrified. I've thought about doing it again, but haven't acted upon it. I've even considering exercising with my injury against doctors orders, so I don't gain weight. Work's been a million times stressful lately and I've been stress eating and binging as well.

What do I do? 

How do I get back on track? 

How do I keep myself from wanting to throw up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Anxiety, depression, bulimia, and saying the wrong thing to my ex, nipping BN before it gets worse. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 04:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
I have anxiety, depression, and bulimia. I'm a guy. Four years ago I met my (now ex) gf and she had bulimia. I loved her so much, I still do. She said I helped her get better just by loving her. We broke up after three years  and the last thing I said to her was the nastiest thing I ever said to anyone, and about her bulimia. That comment was not me, and it sent me spiraling down into a sea of anxiety of depression. I want to tell her I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. She is happy now and that's great. 

I've always been underweight and I would eat and eat to gain weight but it is hard gaining weight for me. One day a few weeks ago I found myself sick to the stomach and needed to get rid of the feeling. So I did. Ever since I've been binging and purging. I'm not sure if it's karma or what. I think about that comment all the time. We had such a good relationship and her last memory of me is an evil one. 

I have suicidal thoughts and daydream about dying. I love her so much and I wish she would know how much she means to me. It's been like a month and I need to stop this before it get's worse. I don't know what to do, where to start. I'm alone and hide all day. I want to drop out of school. Idk what to do.

How do I tell her I'm sorry?

How do I get out of bulimia? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Vyvanse for BED/Binge Purge: Anyone With Experience? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 00:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've struggled with B/P and BED for several years, tried lots of therapists, meditation, hypnotherapy, anti depressants, clonazepam for anxiety. etc. and have done better or worse depending on whats going on in my life but have never really been able to complete recover. I started researching drugs for Bulimia and BED and other than anti-depressants there is nothing FDA approved. Since I've tried those and they didn't work, and they can make you gain weight, I didn't want to try those again. I considered Topimax, but I have a girl friend on it and she told me of horrible side effects and having a hard time focusing. Not really an option for me since I need to be on point for work. Anyways, I came across a few studies on Vyvanse, an ADHD drug, that is trying to get FDA approval right now for BED. I talked to my doctor about it, she had never heard of it being used for ED so she researched it and agreed to try it on one condition. She said I had to promise no purging (vomit type not exercise) as vomiting could give me seizures, which is why it was tested on BED and not bulimics. Well seizures are pretty scary... enough to get me on-board with no purging and knowing if I don't binge then I don't purge. She started me on 20 mg/day for the first week and then moved me to 40 mg. Its been 3 weeks and I haven't had one binging episode yet!!!! This is the longest I've gone in...well... forever it seems.

So my question to the group. There isn't a lot of information on how to use Vyvanse... I'm curious if anyone else has tried it? If so, how long did you take it for? Did you try stopping it and if so did your binging come back? Do you take it every day? My hope is Vyvanse will be enough to break the "habit" part of my ED while my therapy works on the emotional part.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Roommate concern, bulimia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 23:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My roommate is a friend from work and we started living together 2 months ago. I have noticed she throws up her food but does things like leave the toilet seat up, almost to be obvious, I dont know. I have been ignoring it. 

Last night I walked into the bathroom and saw her making herself throw up. She did not see me. I dont know what to do. It is upsetting because I do care for her, but I dont know how much to get into her business. 

Do i continue to ignore? Please help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Quitting Calorie Counting/Exchanges/Measuring Food Cold Turkey...good idea? Ways to manage anxiety, intuitive eating, etc? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 20:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Long story short, I've been recovered from AN for some time and am at a healthy weight. However, for the longest time, I still used a food scale religiously and kept a food journal/app (flipped between a few methods). 

As of late due to stress and the fact that I am still at this whole religious tracking, I've had issues binging off an on for the past few months. Last nights basically occurred because I wanted a healthy food item, was hungry for 2, but only had "allowance" for one. I ate one serving...then another...then broke out some other food and went at it. It hit me right after it happened. 

I now binge off and on when anything is off limits. I also binge when I figure out what I'm eating for the next meal (really bad at night trying to figure out what to eat for breakfast).

So...as I'm writing this, I literally just threw out my food scale(...s-yes its sad). I now know that I'm going to be anxious pretty much 24/7 for the next few weeks, but I tried weening off of counting in the past and it never worked. The second I got stressed I'd regress..I'm kind of an all or nothing person, so I'm going to try it this way.

Any tips on how to manage anxiety? Intuitive eating? Making sure I'm still doing okay health wise (I just weigh myself 1x a week)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 14:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Possibly helpful posts:

[Helping gf](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1pl03w/sharing_girlfriend_is_recovering_from_bulimia/)

[What not to say](http://www.anad.org/wp-content/uploads/2010/11/What-Not-To-Say.pdf)

[Helping gf #2](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2ajwpb/sharing_some_of_my_personal_experince_on_how_to/)

[Help gf](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1y5gup/request_how_to_help_my_gf/)


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 14:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful posts:

[Helping gf](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1pl03w/sharing_girlfriend_is_recovering_from_bulimia/)

[What not to say](http://www.anad.org/wp-content/uploads/2010/11/What-Not-To-Say.pdf)

[Helping gf #2](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2ajwpb/sharing_some_of_my_personal_experince_on_how_to/)

[Help gf](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1y5gup/request_how_to_help_my_gf/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Request for advice on how to talk to roommate/best friend about recent habits? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 12:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend, who in recent months has become my roommate, struggles with an ED. Before moving in together, we talked very often but of course I could only know what she told me over the phone. Although she never specifically told me that she has an ED, she has often talked about her food issues and stress surrounding them, and although I am not sure how to describe it, but it is very clear between the two of us that I am aware of it. 

However, despite me knowing about her issues and being highly concerned for her well being all the time, I know it is not my place to comment on her habits or to tell her what to do in anyway. This is mostly due to the fact that I know her mother is not supportive of the notion of her having any kind of issue, and often will stress her out by forcing her into eating, and that she also regularly would see a therapist, although honestly I have my doubts about her mentioning anything food related to her. During this time I knew not to be the person to bring anything related up, as again, she has enough people doing that and I am her friend, not her therapist and I do not want to become another source of stress to her or have her distrust me in anyway. She has made it very clear that she does not wish to talk about it. 

Coming to now, however, I am concerned enough to want to break my silence. As Ive said, we now live together and spend a large percentage of our time together. For a while she was doing great, without her mother there to stress her out and without anything else stressful in her life it was ok. Recently though this has changed, and I have picked up that she had not been eating well for a couple of days, and now I am certain that besides an unnatural amount of water she has not eaten anything in more than a couple of days. 

I am at a loss for what to do, as I know that I cannot make her do anything, but I dont know if it is smarter or safer to her health for me to tell her my observations or not to. On one hand I dont want her to continue this of course, because she is very obviously not feeling well and I am scared for anything more serious happening to her because of this, but on the other I do not want to break her trust or cause her to become anymore stressed out due by me talking to her. Im just at a total loss for what to do or say reddit, I just want her to be ok again ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Think girl I am dating has an ED. If so, ow do I approach her about it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 06:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've recently started dating this girl who I am pretty into, and things seem to be getting serious. Her eating habits do concern me though and I'm looking to find out if she does in fact have an ED, and how I should approach her about my concerns.

For starters, she does have celiac, which she was diagnosed with about a year ago; she also chooses to be vegetarian. Because of these two things she is obviously very limited in what she can eat. She is not visibly underweight to the point where its noticeable in everyday interaction, but from the chart in the side-bar, and judging by what shes told me her height/weight are, she definitely may be underweight. She admits to not eating much at all and says that she is tired of the foods she is able to eat; when I asked her what she enjoys she says she eats marshmallows and chocolate chips and drinks a lot of lattes/Espresso. 

I have hung out with her about 5 times, some of which were for 8+ hours and during that time she has only drank coffee/water. I've had to eat multiple times during these times to keep from getting HANGRY, as I put it. She has also told me that she ate a specific number of calories for a period of time that I know to be well below what is healthy; she says she did this because friend told her it was okay/healthy.

Do you guys think she has an ED judging from this info?

 How do I bring it up without hurting/offending her? 

I take my personal health really seriously, and even though I haven't known her long it is difficult to see someone seem to be so uninterested in/struggle with food. Thanks in advance guys.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Started recovery and noticing pains in my body. What should I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 11:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been bulimic for 8 years and a month into my recovery. After looking through some of the medical effects of bulimia, I've only just started to realise that the pains I've been having are likely to be related to my eating disorder. I get very severe stomach pains I can barely talk through and used to, very naively, blame it on hunger pains or too much food. I've recently started to have chest pains as well which got quite bad last night. I'm not 100% sure this is due to my bulimia but now I'm getting worried. I've read so many stories of the problems people have had because of their disorder and not sure what step I should take now. I'm away from home and not registered which any doctors in my area. I have tried calling the local doctors but they say that they're full. I was considering going to A E (emergency room) but how urgent do you think this is? I feel like I'm overreacting slightly and not sure what tests they can actually do or whether they'd do anything once I'm there.

There is also the choice of calling the NHS helpline but it's expensive and not sure how much they'll be able to help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Survey: Anonymous ED survey, Chance to share your story if you'd like </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 05:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

I would like to collect anonymous feedback from other eating disorder sufferers for a presentation I am doing on EDs in my college Psychology course. I have set up a survey online which keeps all submissions anonymous (to me, and thus to everyone else), in the hope that I can shed light on the individual struggle. I want to keep my presentation from being clinical and impersonal while still respecting the privacy rights of sufferers.

This is a link to the survey https://www.surveymonkey.com/s/CTFS3RP and the password is "roadtorecovery" ... 

I greatly appreciate all your help. Thanks.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Advice on helping girlfriend with EDNOS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 03:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, thank you to anyone for your time and comments on this thread. Secondly, please forgive me if in my attempt to speak knowledgably, I use any wrong wording or misinformation. Im here for help and not to offend anyone.

My girlfriend and I have a fantastic relationship. Theres not a thing about her I would change, except, this one thing. Shes struggled with binge eating and purging for a long time now. This all pre-dates our relationship. Earlier in our relationship, I addressed it. It was obvious that she was sneaking off after meals. Sometimes, Id find the underside of the toilette seat to have stained or still wet vomit.

We had a very open, though hard conversation about her addiction. Shes gone through therapy and has done a 30 day inpatient rehab. Shes explained to me that her addition is not fueled by a body image issue, but rather its a control issue. Also, weve talked about the sugar rushes she experiences from carbs and junk food and enjoying that feeling. Im not certain, but I believe shes bingeing and purging about every 4-5 days.

I know that I cant be her white knight. I cant fix this for her. Ive dated a person with an eating disorder before, and its a hard battle. And its a battle that cant be fought by anyone other than the person suffering.

Im having a hard time with it, because while shes open to talking to me when I have questions, its an incredibly hard conversation to start. I know shes ashamed and embarrassed by it, so having starting a conversation about not wanting to be finding vomit stained toilets anymore is difficult.

I know I cant fix this, but I can support her with every fiber of my body. Im looking for any advice for being in a relationship with a person thats suffering; if there are any communication tips, things to say and not say. I dont want to make her uncomfortable or make her feel bad. Shes stopped going to therapy within the last 3 months, and I feel like maybe she needs to keep trying. How do I suggest that?

Again, thank you all for your comments/advice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 16:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some centers that offer this - we know nothing more than what is on their websites about these programs:

[Indiana](http://selahhouse.com/Programs/AdultTreatment/EquineTherapy)

[Arizona](http://www.remudaranch.com/about/types-of-therapy/eagala-model)

[Arizona](http://rosewoodranch.com/)

[Washington](http://unbridledcounseling.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/04/Equine-Assisted-Therapy-Flyer1.pdf)

[Florida -Christian based](http://www.canopycove.com/equine-therapy)

[California](http://www.anxietytreatmentexperts.com/equine-assisted-therapy/)

Search your area and you should be able to find some sort of equine therapy available near you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Equine Therapy for Eating Disorders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 15:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Remembering that I'm a binge eater.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 12:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know I have BED, and I have had for the past couple of years now. The past few months have been quite good, in that I have discovered a way that works for me in getting over the disorder, and whilst I still have a way to go in overcoming it completely, I've definitely made progress. My question is about reminding myself about it. For example, when I haven't binged in about a month or so, I feel so great and happy and back to my normal self that I forget I have this unhealthy relationship with food, and allow myself to eat something I wouldn't normally. This is the trigger, and it then happens all over again. When I'm feeling so good, and I try to remind myself that I'm a recovering binger, I don't believe myself. I become schizophrenic and talk myself out of the fact that I need to be careful with food. But once I have that bad food which I know I shouldn't, I go on a 2 day binge and make myself completely sick and hate myself for it. only THEN do I remember, and believe the rational me, that I am a recovering food addict.

How do you guys remind yourself after extended periods of time NOT to have that food in case it starts another vicious cycle? When you've come such a long way and it feels like that part of your past never existed, how do you remind yourself that it did, and that it'll never be the same for you as it is with other people who haven't suffered the disorder??
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Do I have an eating disorder, anorexia, or just bad habits? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 05:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do I have an eating disorder

I'm really confused right now about whether I have an eating disorder.

 I'm a 21 year-old, 5-10 male and am severely underweight. When I say that I mean I want to make it clear that severely means really, really, severely. I would only be at the correct weight, according to my doctor, if I would a lot shorter and female. When I used one of those BMI scanners in health class, it just read "error", though at the time I thought that meant I was in really good shape.

Anyway, I eat 1-1.5 meals a day plus a snack or two. My meals are usually small compared to other people since I'm rarely hungry and get full easily. 

I had previously never worried about this, I was always underweight for my height, but it hasn't really affected my life as far as I can tell. I always eat when I'm hungry and eat till I'm full. In fact, sometimes I eat until I'm uncomfortably full. 

What brought on my concern is that I recently spent 5 days at the hospital. I was incredibly sick, and couldn't hold down and food or liquid and had to go to the hospital to avoid dehydrating. At first the doctors thought I had a flu or something, but by the 2nd day 4 out of 5 times I was visited by a doctor it was a psychiatrist, they were weighing my food before and after I ate and on the 4th day they told me they thought I might be anorexic. I told them that I wasn't, that I wanted to gain weight, but had a really hard time doing it. 

They didn't really listen to me and kept asking me over and over about if I skipped meals, and how I personally felt bout my weight, I told them I didn't skip meals and that I wanted to gain weight. At first they didn't believe me, then they said I might have anorexia without realizing it.


I'm out of the hospital now, but they want me to see a psychiatrist and a therapist about whether I have an eating disorder or not. They said my health could be in serious jeopardy. I guess what I'm trying to figure out is whether or not I actually have an eating disorder, and should see the doctors (an important note is that I'm a broke college student with no health insurance and only want to take this route if I'm really in danger) or if I just have bad eating habits and should maybe work to improve my diet. 

Important things I want to reiterate are that I never don't eat on purpose, except sometimes if I'm feeling really depressed, but that doesn't happen too often, and that I feel like my health is fine, in fact I play tennis and teach it to kids over the summer.

I just want someone to tell me whether I have an eating disorder or just bad eating habits? 

I've never really thought about this before, but the doctors at the hospital really scared and confused me. They even told my parents that they think I have an eating disorder and now my parents won't stop bugging me about it.  I really need an answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Need immediate help for GF who is having a breakdown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 19:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Not going to get into a long description of what's going on, but my GF is having a complete breakdown (by her own admission) and says she needs to talk to someone immediately. The phone numbers for NEDA and ANAD are not open on the weekend.

She is self-harming. Her mind is on overdrive with thoughts of self-hate, abuse, body-shaming, "not deserving food/love", etc.

She has been suffering from ED for years, but it has been extremely bad for about a year and half. She went into an outpatient facility about 8 months but broke away from guidelines while there and quickly turned to old habits after leaving. She was seeing a therapist who dropped her a couple months ago and she has stopped seeing her nutritionist.

She says she has no one to talk to about what she is going through, but she is at a breaking point and desperately needs to talk to someone.

We have very little money and she does not have insurance. I know she needs long-term help, but is there any outlet for her to reach out to today? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How do I talk to my husband about my eating disorder - food addiction? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 15:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
I've been struggling with food addiction for several years. I have good years and bad years, good days and bad days. When we started dating I was in a good place, but now, after a couple years of marriage my monster is starting to emerge from its cave. I had been very good about healthy eating and regular exercise, but lately I can't get my shit together.

I tried to tell him a couple weeks ago, "that I'm not just a girl struggling to lose weight, I have a real problem." I'm not sure he really understands the extent of it, or thinks of it as a real disorder. His response was, "ok." 

Last night after dinner with a friend i stopped at two places on the way home for extra treats. I felt like shit about it, obviously, and this morning when he rolled over and put his arm around me I recoiled and said, "please don't touch my stomach." I DO NOT want to push him away, hide things from him, or withdraw into hiding as is bound to happen.

First, what do I say so that he truly understands that food addiction is a real, serious thing? 

Second, what kind of support is helpful from him? I don't know how to lean on someone for something that I've always kept fiercely private. I have no doubt that he will be supportive, but I don't think either of us know what that really means.

I've never sought counseling for this before, but I think it's time to do so. I cannot watch myself repeat cycles of massive weight gain and depression, and I cannot hide from my marriage because of my disorder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Eating Disorder Triggered Due to Ex's Comments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 20:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two weeks ago my boyfriend of almost two years confessed he had been 'living a double life" and was cheating with his ex-girlfriend (which was also his girlfriend - he had two girlfriends - me and her).
He told me he was in love with her and was breaking it off with me to be with her and her two children. He let me know all this via email.

His other girlfriend (she lives in another state) didn't know that he and I were still together - -- he told her that we had broke up in May --- which wasn't the case. I knew there was an problem due to the decrease of sex in our relationship - which I addressed with him and he stated it was due to him going through depression.

As someone who has been through depression off and on all my life - I tried to be understanding and backed off the issue for a while. Offering him advice, support and time.

Well, all that time he had been having sex with her - he was going back to his hometown every month -- which is 6 hrs from where we live to be with her - and do all the relationship/couple things I wanted to do with him - with her.

The issue is - even though I wasn't IN love - I loved him and cared about him a lot and also thought we had a great and supportive friendship aspect of our relationship. So, I feel betrayed and really hurt.

He knew that I have been dealing with eating disorders (anorexia and bulimia) all my life. He also knows/knew that I battled with disordered eating/thoughts daily (hence ED recovery books all over the apartment) and that I am in therapy for it.

He also knew he was my first real relationship in three years -- since I got serious about recovery.

After he let me know he wanted to be with his ex - his ex reached out to me to tell me she didn't know that we were still together and to basically rag on him and compare notes - since he was with us both at the same time.

In our conversation with each other she said that he claimed he broke up with me in May and the reason was I wanted an increase in sex (which I did ask him for - so he shared that with her) --- and that he was not physically attracted to me - so he couldn't have sex with me like that. But, he told her that with her --he could ALL THE TIME.
In the last month or so, we had been having sex more regularly and thought his "depression" was improving.

When she told me that, I felt terrible and broken. All that time, I thought he liked me and was very attracted to me - as that is what he stated when he pursued me hard for three months in the beginning of our relationship and always acted as he was.

I know that I am attractive and I don't have issues with men trying to get to know me - and he knows that. But, it is my own thoughts about myself that keep me from engaging or entertaining men for relationships and/or friendships.

I am currently at a healthy weight. I feel I could stand to lose  some lbs but I overall I think I am ok. His other girl is taller and weighs more than me - but I guess it's packaged better to him. I don't know....

Since this has happen my ED is back in full effect. I have told my therapist and been reading all I can on self compassion and esteem - but I still feel terrible.

What makes it worst is my family and friends think I am already too small at this weight -- and they are worried that my ED is back - and now I have BD symptoms cause I see something totally different than what everyone else is seeing.

What do I do? 

I am trying to let his comments go and not care and continue my recovery but I feel like I am right back where I started. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How much can I lean on my boyfriend for help? Bulimia, binge / purge. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 14:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After a particularly bad week of relapse, I have broken down to my boyfriend a lot. Sometimes I forget how hard it is for that person helping too. 

He struggles to understand why I do it and I can see the frustration when he sees me binge straight after purging. In an attempt to get a better understanding of it all, he tried looking for information online but got too upset and couldn't bring himself to watch the videos on it. 

I've been so blind to how much this is hurting him and feel awful that I'm putting this pressure on him.

How far can I really go? I've started lying to him now and told him I went a whole day without purging just to give him some relief from it all.

I wouldn't be trying to change this part of my life without him because I know that it would be unsuccessful. He allows me to rant about my problems and doesn't judge me when he finds me sneaking food or sneaking off to the toilet. But now I'm worried it's going to get too much for him.

Anybody out there with family or friends with bulimia, how did you cope? 

When is it time for me to stop leaning on him when I feel myself slipping?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Sick of being like this and don't know what to do, binge eating </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 14:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even know where to start with this, there's too much to say for one reddit post. I've realised in the past year that I have a problem with binge eating, and have done for a huge part of my life. But only recently it's become a huge problem. I have reached breaking point. 

Every day I'm fighting the same fucking battle. I hate my body, so I go on a health kick that lasts about two days. I go running, I count calories, the whole shebang. Then I decide it won't make a difference, then go on a huge binge, then feel awful about myself and lock myself away and cry. Rinse and repeat.

And I'm sick of it. I hate feeling this way, I hate my body, I hate this awful unhealthy relationship that I have with food. I really don't know what to do or where to turn, I don't even know if there's any point in attempting to fix this, because every time I try, I just relapse and binge. It's an endless cycle. 

How can I learn to appreciate my body? 

Ways of dealing with stress and other unpleasant emotions?

Where do I start?

Any suggestions would be greatly appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to get help while studying abroad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 13:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a 21yo female in college and have always been on the lower range of a healthy body weight. Last November I realized I had gained some weight after not exercising regularly--as I had been all throughout high school--so I started to count my calories and exercise 5days/wk. My family was thrilled that I had begun to exercise more. They have always been supportive and encouraged sports, healthy eating, and a healthy body. I ended up losing fat and gaining some muscle, which I was really happy about and I felt great! But then I broke up with my long-term SO, changed my college major, and decided to study abroad. I guess that's where the tipping point was. I then started getting almost addicted to the feeling of seeing the numbers on the scale go down and seeing that my clothes were getting looser. I would count calories obsessively and follow a low-carb, vegetarian diet. 7 months after I decided to begin losing weight, I am now very underweight. I can't stop thinking about food and calories and carb content. I am chronically constipated and constantly feel cold despite living abroad in 80-90F weather every day. I avoid going out to dinner with my friends here, and don't go out drinking with them because of the added empty calories. I have begun to get worried about my health and don't know what to do. Like I said, I am currently studying abroad so I don't have family or close friends here to talk to. I also do not have access to a health care provider except for the university health service here... which I am hesitant to go to, as they may not understand me. My question is: What should I do for help? I don't want to worry my parents/family back home by telling them I may have a problem since I'm so far away. Is there a group or provider/counselor I can email or talk to via internet (I only have a Chinese phone)? I don't think I'm so out of control that I necessarily need a counselor, so is there a way I can help myself by myself? Thank you very much. I really appreciate your help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to approach roommate who I believe is bulimic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 13:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there! I have a roommate that I'm pretty positive is bulimic. I just wanted to ask whats the right way to ask or if I should catch him red handed (I easily could). We're pretty close but this is a sensitive subject and I would like some advice.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to help bulimic girlfriend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 13:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend drunkenly admitted to me last friday that she is clinically depressed and not and meds, and bulimic. She told me that her body is used to throwing up at least once a day. I've dealt with depression before for myself, and I know how to help in a way, but I have no idea how to help her with her eating disorder, and I imagine they are very linked. She told me that being bulimic has "kept her grounded" for a long time. I told her that I could not abide it - meaning that I can't allow myself to ignore it, which she asked me to. She said "I get selfish when I get drunk", which I guess means she thinks putting her issues on me is selfish? I told that it isn't at all. The other thing I told her was that anytime she felt the need to make herself throw up, to call me or text me, and I would get there immediately, or talk to her immediately. I've also been asking her at least once every day "how she is doing" meaning if she has made it through the day without forcing herself to throw up. We made it through the weekend without an incident, but today she was feeling nauseous and made herself throw up to get rid of the feeling. She had also been experiencing trouble keeping at least one of her meals down each day, but was able to do it, probably because we were together most of the weekend and she forced herself to keep it down. But she told me today "I messed up" and told me what happened.

She is very scared to stop her habits because she believes they help her stay grounded.

Please help me! Is her case severe? Does she need to be checked into a treatment centre or at least get a treatment program? I am the only she has told, and she didn't even mean to tell me. So if a treatment was to happen she would have to tell at least her mother, which I think she should anyways.

I can use any advice you have! please, thank you
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Just recently acknowledged I binge eat and don't even know where to begin.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 11:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've recently come to terms with the fact I'm a binge eater, and it's been a legitimate issue I've struggled with for as long as I can remember, although I've only just recently acknowledged it's existence in my life. I can't exactly identify why (at least there was no major motivating factor)...it's just simply something I've done.

I first looked into the world of binge eating a couple of months ago...I had never really given serious thought to that subject before. Over the next month or so, I kept an eye on my hunger habits and routines. I realized that I never really reach a point of satisfaction. There's always some sort of hunger burning in my stomach.

I'm a 21 year old guy who used to be a pretty unhealthy individual, but around March I decided to change my diet and exercising habits and ended up losing some weight and getting in better physical shape. Today, I still maintain good exercise habits, and in terms of quality my choices in food are pretty healthy as well. Still, I feel like all of the effort I'm putting into steering myself back on track with exercising and dieting is being nulled by the fact I can never seem to satisfy my hunger and over indulge myself with huge quantities of food.

I struggled in life with severe depression and anxiety, and I sought out help about a year ago. I'm in a far better place than I was around that time, although like everyone else recovering I still have my moments. I don't personally think any of those issues contribute to the binge eating, though I could be wrong.

As someone completely new to this world and as someone finally acknowledging as issue like this in my life, I ask my friends in this community to help a guy just know where to even start. What are some resources I should be looking into? Who should I talk to about it (I can't really afford therapy atm..)? Strategies? Any help would be genuinely appreciated.

Thanks for taking a few seconds out of your day for a guy who feels a little in over his head. Smile today.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I don't know when to stop eating! Help?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 01:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Background: long story short: I spent the last summer eating too little calories and over-exercising. I lost some weight because of it, and am now at an unhealthy BMI.

Issue: Now that I'm trying to recover my lost weight, I don't know when I am supposed to stop eating. I am currently lifting light weights to make sure the mass I gain balanced, but I still don't feel confident with over-eating.

For instance, just today I know that I went over the calories I needed by a reasonable amount. However, I ate some bad food that was high in calories and low in nutrients, so I am still hungry. I really want to eat some more food so I can feel full, but I know I will just be eating an unhealthy high amount.

Should there be a cap for how many calories I eat, or is it more important that I feel full?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 18:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful posts:

[Helping gf](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1pl03w/sharing_girlfriend_is_recovering_from_bulimia/)

[What not to say](http://www.anad.org/wp-content/uploads/2010/11/What-Not-To-Say.pdf)

[Helping gf #2](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2ajwpb/sharing_some_of_my_personal_experince_on_how_to/)

[Help gf](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1y5gup/request_how_to_help_my_gf/)



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 18:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. This is very helpful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Befriended and now falling for girl recovering from Anorexia. Advice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 18:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Met a really cool girl recently. We have a lot in common and had some very intense conversations over a short space of time. Long story short - after a friend of hers passed away from anorexia, she told me she is in recovery from anorexia and currently bulimic. I was pretty rocked to be honest. Especially as I am still getting to know this girl.

We're going to see each other a lot over the next year or two so it's important we maintain a friendly relationship. I really don't know what to do. I find myself avoiding her not because of what she told me, but more so that I don't want to get hurt. I'm still raw from previous relationships and have pretty low self-esteem.

How does one maintain a platonic relationship given the situation?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 15:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful posts:

[Getting my mind back and diagnosis](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2hw3tw/request_i_want_my_mind_back_why_cant_i_remember/)

[Why recover](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2j10j5/request_just_want_to_give_up_why_recover/)


[Therapy](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2gg4v9/request_honesty_in_therapy/)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Resistance to Treatment: Anosognosia and Eating Disorders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 15:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 15:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful post:

[here](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2izjwj/request_talking_to_my_sister_about_her_eating/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Recovery from AN b/p type, it seems like no one understands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 14:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi everyone,

I'm looking for some advice in my recovery from AN b/p subtype. For some background, my ED is basically binging and purging all of the time, I rarely restrict (despite my diagnosis of AN), and that is what I am trying to recover from. I was in IP in August and discharged with an OP team and a meal plan. I stopped seeing my OP dietician, however, at the end of September because my insurance was not covering it, and she wasn't helping at all (I was following my meal plan to a T and didn't restore weight and all she told me was to eat desserts with every meal).

My main problem is this: I can't stop binging and purging, and no one seems to even recognize it as an issue despite my insistence that I need help with it. Especially with all of the doctors I saw in IP, it seems they took one look at me, saw that I'm underweight, and assumed that I am restricting. No matter how many times I said that I hardly restrict, I just binged and purged all day, they won't address it. 

When I go to my dad's house, he'd stock up on junk food and pressure me to eat it all, essentially pressuring me into a relapse. It took me MONTHS to convince him that binging is, in fact, what I'm trying to recover from. And when I go see my OP team and tell them of an episode, they just say "I'm glad you gave yourself permission to eat that! You're doing so well!" as if it were some sort of triumph and not a terrible demon that I feel is controlling my life.

I would understand this attitude if I were recovering from restricting type AN, since binging is a fairly normal part of recovery. But I hardly restrict which is part of what terrifies me. But I feel like I'm going insane from this. 

The urge to binge is constant and I have to fight it every moment of every day. I made it three weeks free, and while I thought it would get easier to resist, it just felt like it got more difficult everyday until I simply couldn't handle it anymore and I turned into a raging monster tearing through half of the refrigerator. It doesn't help that no one seems to understand what the real problem is, and they're practically congratulating me every time I relapse.

I would also understand if this had only started recently. So, I don't really want to do the MinnieMaud approach of letting myself eat whatever I want because I know that binging is mainly just a destructive coping mechanism for me and I don't want to reinforce it. Especially because I don't think that I would be able to stop binging, even when I got back up to a normal weight.

What helped you through recovery? How did you get others to understand that binging and purging is the problem? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 02:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful posts:

[Bulimia recovery](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2dc4rb/recovery_sharing_ziploc_bags_and_other_things/)

[How to include "bad" foods](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2io660/request_what_is_normal_eating_how_do_i_include/)

[Anxious about "bad" foods](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2bga1t/request_recovering_from_ednos_i_feel_so_anxious/). 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Baby steps towards recovery. (Male, 20 yrs old), previously anorexia, now bulimia (non-vomiting) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 02:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, so I am a 20 year old male who struggled with anorexia for around a year, following some drastic changes in my life. It caused severe effects to my body, but I am now at a much healthier weight although I do not quite have the athletic muscles that I used to. 

I am an active guy though. I enjoy running and have been trying to lift some weights recently to gain back some muscle. But currently, I struggle with Bulimia (non-vomiting) and it is something that drives me absolutely nuts because it dictates my life, prevents me from being/feeling normal, and just fuels my overall depression. 

I truly want to make some changes with my eating disorder, but as I'm sure you all know, my mind prevents me from taking the actions that I have began to realize that I need to take. I just really want some help because I am at University now and I have not been enjoying myself, have had no self-esteem, and have yet to make friends. I really believe this eating disorder is preventing me from being myself. 

By the way, this subreddit has been EXTREMELY useful for helping me understand my condition a little bit better. But, I am submitting this because all of our circumstances are unique and the best advice is tailored to our own personal needs. This eating disorder has seriously been the most difficult thing I have ever been though, and it has cost me some really valuable things in life. It has gone on too long and I am becoming desperate for help since I don't have anyone to talk to about it. If you guys need to know anything else, I'd be more than happy to go into more detail.

One of the weird habits that continues to humiliate me is my relationship with restricting carbs. I really want to eliminate that mind block because I feel like gradually introducing carbs back into my diet will allow me to eat a bit more freely, like I used to. The whole "low-carb" trend has really messed with the way my mind views carbs. But, I feel like it will remove a large portion of the the anxiety I have towards food if I can eat them again. So, this is the first tiny step I want to actively take towards being "recovered". It seems so simple, but my mind has convinced me otherwise. 

So, how can I introduce some carbs back into my diet without bingeing on them? For some time now, I haven't been eating any carbs at all and I am aware that it is a problem in my life. I try not to even look at the Nutrition Facts on food any more, as it fuels my anxiety. 

Anyways, I just want to thank you guys in advanced, whether I get any responses or not. Feel free to ask any more questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 06:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful posts:

[Relapse](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2j7kf8/request_crazy_bingepurge_relapse_after_8_years_of/)

[Bulimia recovery sharing](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2dc4rb/recovery_sharing_ziploc_bags_and_other_things/)

[AMA on bulimia recovery](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1uob3k/ama_on_recovery_2_years_ago_i_recovered_from/)

[Addressing Bulimia](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/24g5vt/request_how_to_begin_addressing_bulimia/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My will to not purge is failing. Need advice on how to turn away from bulimia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 06:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had been slipping into my bulimic tendencies the last few months. I really thought I had control. Everything would be intentional and I could squash that inner voice telling me to purge at work.

It didn't work tonight.

I came back from dinner feeling full. The uncomfortable feeling overcame me.

Before I knew it I was purging my dinner. I know the nurse heard it. Played it off that it was something I ate. I wasn't in control though. So I left early.

I feel like such a piece of crap. I had this controlled and now I'm not just spiraling at home. It's happened at work.

What do I do???? How do I not let bulimia into my life?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> rRequest: bulimia caused by poverty, food insecurity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 01:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there, I'm hoping somebody will be able to help, because there's not a lot of info online about what I think is turning into bulimia. Here's the backstory:

Earlier this year, I was laid off from my full-time job and the financial consequences swept me off my feet. I was raised upper-middle-class in Australia (now living in the US), am financially responsible, and went to an expensive private school, so I never thought that I would find myself living on the streets, but that's exactly what happened to me. I lived out of my car for three months, and often ate food from dumpsters (or occasionally stole it from tables in fast food restaurants) because I felt bad accessing resources for the homeless as I felt that I had had a good life so far and didn't deserve the help. (My parents didn't want to help me and I didn't want to burden my friends by asking for help.)

Now, I'm back on my feet with a place to live and a full-time job that pays more than most people my age earn (I'm 23), and life is getting back to normal. 

However, now I feel out of control with binging - not so much out of a low self-esteem, but out of a suffocating awareness of how easily I could topple into poverty. Whenever I see food, I eat it all. I can't keep food in the house because I eat until the pantry is empty and I feel sick. I then feel really bad about myself because like any 23-year-old female, I want to be attractive and healthy. (Plus, I used to work in high fashion, and I never used to eat then like I do now.)

But I know the big problem here is that I can't shake the feeling of food insecurity. I can't stop feeling like I may not be able to buy food for the next week and I might have to dig in rubbish bins in parks at night again. I KNOW I have a job now and everything's ok. But I don't know how to get out of feeling this way and binging like there's no tomorrow as if I don't know when my next meal will come...please help! I feel awful. 

How can I shake the feeling of food insecurity?

Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Recovering bulimic dieting, don't want to slip into old habits. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 15:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been in recovery for about two years and in that time I have become overweight. I am now in the situation where I need to loose a modest amount to return to a healthy weight (Dr.'s advice not mine) and am now dieting and working out to achieve this. 

I've downloaded an app to make sure that I'm eating enough and track my nutrition. I've found that I've been slipping into old habits a lot easier than I like and it scares me. I'm consistently under eating and working out and last week I purged for the first time in over a year. 

Are there other people with this problem and what are coping mechanisms they use to deal with it?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Binging in Recovery, hopelessness, social concerns about gaining weight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 15:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have just binged after been doing pretty well in recovery for awhile. I've been so bored and I think that's what triggered it, or maybe I just don't want to dig deeper. I just really hate that I feel like I am not going to get out of this cycle and I'm just going to keep gaining weight and gaining weight. 

I hadn't binged in over a month around. I mean i guess I've had mini ones but not a real full out binge in a long time. I knew that If i just kept watching tv I would have been fine, or If I wouldn't have gotten that one snack. 

I'm just so pissed. Like why. Why can't I just be normal. Can I please have some advice and how you guys deal with binging in recovery? 

I'm crying as I write this, just feeling hopeless. I can't keep gaining weight, nobody is going to want to be associated with me, I wouldn't want to associate with myself. I just really need someone right now. Much love, XOXO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Is it counter intuitive to count calories in recovery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 04:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
When my ED was in its prime, I would spend the whole day frightened by an arbitrary number such as a calorie. Now that I'm in recovery, I've learned to simply enjoy food and live each day based on what my body wants. 

However, there's a problem. I've been living this way for about a month now and have seen no results in terms of weight gain. Could this mean that I need to eat more than what my body wants? Or that I have lost touch with what my body wants?

Do I need to count calories to make sure I get at least xx amount of calories each day, or would this lead to another eating disorder entirely? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Is there such a thing as a full recovery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-22 17:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was wondering if anyone has real successful recovery stories to share. Or if there's such a thing as a full recovery or if it's something like AA, you have to struggle everyday forever.

I'm asking this because I've struggled with EDNOS for what I thought had been 6 years. In 2007/08 I had gotten out of a relationship, was going through some difficult things in my life and started blaming it all on myself and I despised the way I looked. I started regularly dieting, eating low carbs, lean proteins, etc. I lost weight. I came back to my country after a month traveling and losing weight and plateaued. So I restricted a little more my calorie intake. Next thing I know, I'm obsessed with calories. I memorize whole lists of calories and then start betting against myself to see what was the littlest I could eat everyday. If I ever went over a certain amount I'd purge. (I never binged tho). As it usually goes with this disease, I started withdrawing from my family and friends company because social gatherings would usually involve food. I lied all the time and when I couldn't avoid eating, I'd purge afterwards. That went on without stop for a little more than 3 years. Then in 2012 I had to undergo a procedure, but I needed to gain weight. I forced myself into recovery and gained the necessary weight, and actually kept myself "healthy" for sometime. After that I just started gaining weight uncontrollably and long story short (not really), I'm going through everything again. I can't eat, I cry out of anxiety when I have to go out, etc.

But that's not the reason why I ask. Last night I was at my parents' and I found some old journals. Some of the stuff was from 2003/04, 4 years before what I thought was my "full blown" condition. And there are pages and pages of odes to how I hated myself and calling me names for being what I considered to be overweight and one of the entries shocked me as I narrated how I had felt guilty after eating out with some friends from uni and then forced myself to purge for the first time ever. And how good it felt to be able to do that and in control. I was shocked because I honestly didn't remember those things or those feelings. I know I've always hated myself and the way I look, but I didn't remember I had had an episode before 08. As I read it became clearer to me I had gone through similar stuff before (restricting, lying, purging, taking meds, etc) and recovered when I quit uni. I don't remember what motivated me to do so, but then in 08 it happened again, and now it's happening again after a brief "normal" period... Is this gonna be my life forever? Is there something wrong with me (other than the obvious)?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My former boyfriend has left me because of my EDNOS - how do I cope? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-22 17:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been with my boyfriend for nearly two years and throughout those years he's known I've had EDNOS - he's never really coped that well when the issue arises so I've tried not to raise the issue too much. But recently things have been tough.

This morning, I received a message from him with the dreaded words...

"I think this is too much for me and I can't deal with it anymore. I'm so sorry. I'll be asking to see your doctor on an individual basis to discuss everything I know. I'm taking it into my own hands whether you want it or not and I'm afraid I'll have to leave it there."

I'm really desperate, even crying whilst I type this, because I have nowhere else to turn. I'm so sorry to have to post something as insignificant as this but nobody I'm currently in contact with knows about my ED aside from my ex.

My first question is - how on earth can I cope knowing he's left me because of my eating disorder, when that in itself is the most triggering thing ever for my eating disorder to continue?

And two; how on earth can I stop him from going to my doctor and getting everyone involved, when I know from previous personal experience that that broken trust and any kind of forced recovery never works?! (EDIT: He has already gone through with what he said and has told the receptionist at my doctors who will forward his concern to my GP. I'm from the UK and I'm 20 years old so I am aware of the notion of confidentiality, but I'm beside myself as I don't know how this would apply in this situation - it's all so complicated because he brought my severe depression into it too).

Thanks in advance if you read.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: What to do about sister </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-22 12:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My sister (older teenager) 3 years ago started to show signs of being anorexic. We were oblivious about it for too long-you never think these things happen to you. For a while we didn't get any professional help but merely tried to encourage her to eat more. This didn't work so well. Things slowly became worse. She became very moody, reclusive and her eating habits became stranger and stranger. Recently she went to a clinic for eating disorders after she became dangerously thin. ( heart rate was 30-40 bpm and she looked very sick) and that seemed to do nothing besides managing to get her back up to a semi decent weight. However since then her weight has clearly dropped once again. She absolutely refuses to believe she has a problem and gets very aggressive when we try to approach her about it. It's caused a LOT of stress in our family and right now we're just running out of options. I can't see her going

Have any of you ever been in a situation like this? What can I do as her brother? (I'm several years older.) I've really noticed it straining my parent's marriage. I'm especially worried that it may affect her younger sisters (ages 8-13).

Any advice would be much appreciated. Thanks you guys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Triggered after therapy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 23:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently submitted a post about whether or not the 'something isn't right' feeling is a good indicator that my behaviour might be disordered. Since that time my eating disorder has progressed but I also decided that I wanted to strike now and possibly prevent many years of heartache and struggle. I had my initial appointment with a psychologist yesterday and while I feel that it went well and I really liked her and valued the space to talk about what's been going on, I found the whole thing very emotionally draining and therefore quite triggering. There was a lot of numbers talk (which she assured me was just the first appointment) and I found that particularly difficult, because I have gained a bit in the last few days which obviously is tough. The first thing I did when I left was binge. You can guess the second. I'm just wondering if anyone else has experience with therapy being triggering and how you have coped with it? Is it appropriate to ask my therapist to work with me on some strategies to avoid b/p or major restriction after a session? I want to stick with it but not if it's going to be like this every time.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 15:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful post:

[Dieting vs Eating Disorder](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1l40q4/post_request_how_do_i_do_things_like_try_to_eat/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 15:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful links and post:



[Anorexia and Bulimia and fertility](http://www.webmd.com/mental-health/eating-disorders/news/20110805/eating-disorders-affect-fertility-pregnancy)

[EDs and Pregancy](https://www.nationaleatingdisorders.org/pregnancy-and-eating-disorders)

[Pregnant and disordered](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2ivccs/request_pregnant_and_disordered_how_can_i_make/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Post request: How to differentiate between orthorexia and just wanting to be healthy? Healthy diet vs ED? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 15:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm one of those people who have jumped on the health and fitness bandwagon, but along the way, I did realize that some restrictive behaviours developed. But since then, I have made the conscious decision to recover.

So I'm just wondering how you would differentiate an orthorexic from someone who just wants to be healthy? Like, if someone doesn't want to eat a cupcake because they know it's not the "healthiest" option, are they orthorexic, or just health conscious? I guess what I really want to know is if I'm hindering my own recovery/wellbeing by wanting to eat clean, stick to healthier foods, and live healthily, etc.

Thank you so much!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I think I need help, teen with bulimia, parents don't seem to know what to do. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 15:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in high school, and meet (and exceed) the criteria for bulimia nervosa. 

My parents found my texts when I confessed my story to a friend, so they know most of it. Thing is, they don't do anything about it. I guarantee they hear my purging, and they're around when I binge. I don't know if I should push the issue and ask for a therapist or not. I kind of want to, because I can't talk to anyone else about it. I'm too scared to text because of what happened, but I'm also too nervous to discuss it in person. 

I would rather avoid the topic entirely, actually. I cry and break down if I do talk face-to-face about it.

I guess my situation is that I don't know how to go about recovery. I feel like I can't begin to recover unless I get officially diagnosed, otherwise I feel like an attention-seeking teenager who exaggerates her problems. Putting a diagnosis to it would be like saying, "Yes, your problems are real. Now go fix them." Does that make sense?

I'm so conflicted about the whole thing. I feel like bulimia has taken over me, like a sheet. And underneath that sheet is EDNOS or something, as another sheet. Then underneath that is me. Because if I'm not overeating, I'm not eating at all. Like if I manage to peel off the top layer, another ED is waiting beneath it. I'll cross that bridge when I get there, I guess.

How can I get help?

How do I talk about this with my parents?

Does therapy just mean a diagnosis and then "Now go fix it"? 

Would therapy help me learn to change? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Has anyone gotten pregnant while coping with ED? Can EDs effect the chances of having children? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 15:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if this belongs here or r/pregnant, but I have been battling bulimia for 5 years (shortly after I had my first child). My BMI is on the cusp of being underweight. I've been better though. Eating more and purging less and I have not had an incident for two weeks (I have done this multiple times a day at times). My periods are always regular, but now I'm two months late with a negative three negative pregnancy tests. I've been feeling healthier and don't have any other underlying issues as I just saw my primary doctor a week ago.

How likely is it that i messed up my chances of having more children? Has anyone had success or know anyone that has?

Thank you.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Post Request- I'm spiraling into an eating disorder, family history of EDs, I don't know why my mood keeps going like this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 15:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even know where to start. I started losing weight and while I've always hated my body, I didn't think I would spiral into an eating disorder. I didn't start off counting calories, but I get so upset now if I don't know the calories in something. I haven't started purging yet, but I sometimes feel like it.

This is horrible and I don't want to keep feeling like this. Sometimes I feel completely in control and the next moment I'm obsessing over what I just ate or thought about eating. I kept denying that there was anything wrong, but normal people don't cry about eating in a restaurant or about how much oil someone has used in their cooking.

I feel like I might end up triggering my mum as well. She was severely anorexic when she was younger and nearly died from it and while she's been recovered for years, she admitted that she still cries sometimes when she looks in the mirror. I feel like my entire family is insane because basically every girl on my mum's side has had an eating disorder. My sister has tried starving herself and has cried about being weighed and my oldest female cousin nearly died from anorexia. My other female cousin has recently gained some weight after showing signs of an eating disorder and now I'm dealing with this.

My parents are trying to help, but my father telling me that 'I'm going to be exactly where I belong soon' and telling me that he is going to lock me in a hospital EVERY time an issue with with my eating comes up, is making me want to scream and cry and either break down or destroy something. I feel so unstable right now and I don't know why my mood keeps going like this.

I'm going into treatment, but it's still a month away and I don't know how the hell I'm going to cope until then because I know that I'm getting worse every week. 

Does anyone have any advice or anything to alleviate my mood swings slightly? 

How do I deal with my parents? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How did you accept the fact that you will gain body-fat during recovery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 04:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I consider myself to be on a recovery from a restrictive eating disorder, but I still haven't gained weight. I believe this is because although I believe I am eating more, my ED is still influencing my decisions.

I've learned that if I am going to gain weight, I won't be able to do it with my safe foods. However, the idea of eating unsafe foods without recording how much I am eating still scares me. I'm doing moderate weightlifting, but what if all my excess calories just makes me fat?

I'd like to reach a normal BMI and don't know if it will lead to binge eating. As a kid, I ate junk food all the time. However, I don't know if I can return to that lifestyle without killing my health and becoming obese.

How do you accept the fact that you will gain weight, body-fat, during recovery?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to tell my housemate I have bulimia? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 04:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been bulimic for 13 years. I eat everything in the house and purge regularly. I have a feeling my housemate knows. I want to tell my her but am afraid. Any advice?

Thanks!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-18 16:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This post has a reply with links, [here](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2izjwj/request_talking_to_my_sister_about_her_eating/).

Consider searching "help gf" or "help friend" on this subreddit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> REQUEST: Help talking to a teammate with a potential ED (TW!). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-18 04:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Hi, long story short, I think my teammate has an ED. I went to her room today with another teammate (who is oblivious) and some little notes caught my eye. They said horrible, horrible things. 

I myself have fully recovered from EDNOS/bulimia (as much as one can) and I am happy, healthy, and even lucky enough to not be susceptible to triggers.

But I've been to that dark place and seeing those quotes really flashed me back for the first time in over 3 years. They are the things you would see on the pro-ED blogs that I frequented long ago. Her roomie also made a comment about how she brings her toothbrush everywhere, and while that could be just her thing, its just SO many red flags. If she doesn't have an ED, she's definitely having disordered thoughts.

Me and this girl are fairly close, we both have anxiety and depression and have bonded a little over it and we've reached out to one another after panic attacks. I think that if anybody could reach out with respect and care, I think I could.

Because I recovered without anybody confronting me, I need a little help on what might be the best way to do this. I'd like to invite her one on one to my apartment and offer her a shoulder/venting space, a cat to cuddle (she loves cats a lot), or just my love and support and encourage her to see our free psychologist. I also would like to share my story with her so she knows that I at least can empathize with her.

I know not to accuse or be forceful and I understand firsthand the attachment one can get to their disorders and how defensive/angry/scared they can be. I know I shouldn't threaten her by outing her. I'm also not a Christian but she has a strong relationship with God and I wonder if she might like relevant scripture or something like that.

If she's receptive, where do I go from there? What if she denies? Or if she's angry? How can I get the most positive reaction? I want to offer myself and my experiences as a resource for her and let her know that help is available and encourage her. I'm very worried for her, so any advice would be great. Thanks!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Very concerned about a 7 year old. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-18 04:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suffered with anorexia in and out of the hospital for two years, and of course it affected my whole family. It has now been about a year since i've been out of the hospital, and i'm doing better. 

The problem is that my younger sister, who basically had to grow up watching me destroy myself, is now restricting what she eats, because she wants to be 'tall and thin like her older sister as she's heard my family say so many times that i am tall and thin. 

I am very concerned about her health and that this may progress dangerously. I want to do whatever i can to get her as far away from this mindset as possible, but i don't know how. 

I've got her coming to visit me as a 'play date' at my apartment, so i can show her that i eat, to show her that i do not restrict. She's so young and i don't know how to deal with these issues in a 7 year old. 

I would really appreciate any advice on how to approach this. I could never forgive myself if this progresses in her the way it did in me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Help editing a short script on a person with bulimia. TW </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 17:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to create a short film about bulimia, showing on a personal level of what people with bulimia go through. However I have not personally gone through it myself and I'm unsure how accurate my script is.

I'm wondering if anyone is interested in helping me and clarifying some of my errors I may have written. If interested comment/reply and I'll PM you my script, or just pm me and ask: /u/pamalaandersonstoe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Crazy binge-purge relapse after 8 years of somewhat healthy life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 14:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My ED first started as anorexia about 15 years ago and quickly evolved into bulimia. For ~8 years I've been living normal life, with some ED thoughts but nothing serious. My relationship with my SO hit a really rough patch lately, and I'm now on a three-day long binge-purge marathon, and I don't know what to do. I don't have any contact to health care/therapy at the moment. I'm on antidepressants.

My SO and I are planning to meet a couples therapist soon, and I'm not sure whether I should talk about this there. Is there any way to stop this now, before things get even worse?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to handle lunchtime with dieting colleagues and their talk, particularly comments to me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 21:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am currently a year in to my recovery for binge-purge bulimia. I have managed to stop purging (with some relapses over the year) but binge eating and body image are still areas I struggle with.

I am currently having difficulty with the lunchtime situation at work. I have no option but to eat with colleagues. We bring in our own food, but I work in a school and so there is often a surplus of the children's cooked dinners (this often includes trays and trays of desserts). I am currently trying to include desserts into my diet in a healthy and moderate way but I still struggle a lot with guilt and sometimes portion sizes - I have a tendency to binge.

My issue is that my colleagues are quite competitive dieters and often very restrictive in what they eat. I have come far enough to know that this type of dieting is extremely triggering and unhealthy for me. I am trying to step away from the thin ideal and restricting but this is something my colleagues believe in and engage in.

It is really starting to get to me as I am trying to feel comfortable eating a dessert after lunch and eating carbohydrates etc. My colleagues often make comments such as "oh I see you struggle with willpower too" or "its not good to eat x, y, or z in x, y, or z quantities" or "I've cut out x, y and z nutrients because they make you fat" or moan about feeling fat/guilty if they do indulge in certain foods.

I am finding this a minefield. I'm really at the beginning stages of trying to feel comfortable with my size and eating desserts etc. The comments my colleagues make about themselves and what they are eating stresses me out. I am not willing to discuss my eating disorder history with them. I am certain they would be extremely understanding if I did, but it doesn't feel professional somehow and it's not something I am comfortable doing.

Any tips on staying strong and comfortable with my decisions?

Also suggestions for ways to avoiding this from becoming triggering would be extremely helpful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Designing an Outpatient Facility- thesis research by someone in recovery from an eating disorder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 21:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I struggled with an eating disorder for over 9 years. Because of this close personal connection, I decided to do my Interior Design senior thesis on a outpatient eating disorder facility. I was always afraid of getting help because I believed I 'wasn't sick enough' or I was just afraid of getting better.

My goal is to design a community rather than a 'clinic'. I want my design to encourage social support, remove stigma, and encourage recovery.

As part of my research, I would love to get input from other people suffering with ED.

 * What made you decide that you needed to seek treatment?

 * How did you make your decision on whether to do outpatient or inpatient? How did you choose the facility?

 * What were issues- if any- that you felt your therapy space had?

 * Is there anything that you would hope to see in a eating disorder center?

 * What do you believe to be the most important spaces in a facility towards recovery? What qualities did these spaces have?

Thank you! If anyone would be willing to talk further about a facility please PM me, /u/heathaleatha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 21:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful posts:

[Not sure](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1mo668/post_request_i_have_an_ed_but_not_sure_what_kind/)

[troubles with eating](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2efnqp/request_have_a_lot_of_troubles_with_eating_do_i/)

[Which one](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2apssk/request_i_know_i_have_an_eating_disorder_but_i/)

[Health issues of being underweight](http://www.nhs.uk/Livewell/Goodfood/Pages/Underweightadults.aspx).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 16:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Eating disorders are psychological and somewhat physiological in origin. Let's just consider the physiology of undereating (restricting) and overeating (binging).

True. Eating disorders are mental disorders. Professional psychological help is often necessary for recovery. Dieticians are also often a key part of recovery. 

We can't help all the people all the time, but if we can help some of the people some of the time, it's good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 15:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These hunger hormones are similar to other hormones in our bodies (such as a woman's estrogen cycle) in that they can't be quickly turned on and off. The JAMA article linked is a study that has proven hunger hormones take a long time to return to normal after periods of undereating.

There are suggestions under each of the hormones mentioned for what to do to help them return to normal. For example, for cortisol, try to rest more by lying down even if not sleeping. For ghrelin, eating every few hours (for example, 3 meals a day, 2 snacks) helps bring that hormone back into balance so that binges have one less biological stimulus.

There are many hormones that regulate hunger, more than can be listed and many still not understood. However, the ones listed offer a variety of solutions to begin to help calm the body as a part of recovery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 18:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful previous posts and links:

[Anorexia Workbook](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/qpf61/the_anorexia_workbook_how_to_accept_yourself_heal/).

[Ways to cope](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/25sdga/request_ways_to_cope_when_feeling_fat_during/).

[Therapy for EDs](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/27l0j3/request_best_forms_of_therapy_for_eds/)

[Coping with guilt from not believing ED thoughts?](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/25qg9d/request_exercise_guilt_guilt_from_exercising_less/)

[Before I eat apps](https://www.google.com/search?q=before+i+eat ie=utf-8 oe=utf-8 aq=t rls=org.mozilla:en-US:official client=firefox-a channel=fflb)

[Recovery Record](http://www.recoveryrecord.com/).

[Books by Matthew McKay](http://www.amazon.com/Matthew-McKay-Ph.D./e/B001JOYNJA).


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 17:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Related and hopefully helpful  app links and other posts:

[Before I Eat](https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/before-i-eat-moment-in-zone/id733555197?mt=8).

[Recovery Record](http://www.recoveryrecord.com/).

[Binge eating disorder](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2i4ja3/post_request_binge_eating_disorderhelp_needed/).

[Books for recovery from binge eating](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/247lac/request_seeking_a_selfhelp_book_on_overcoming/).

[Binge eating recovery ideas](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2dc4rb/recovery_sharing_ziploc_bags_and_other_things/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 17:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here are some other posts that may help:

[Friend with an ED](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/218zii/request_friend_just_told_me_shes_diagnosed_with/).

[Approach someone at gym](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/253fi9/request_there_is_a_girl_who_looks_anorexic_at_my/).

[Roomate is bulimic, how to help?](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1umesg/request_roommate_is_bulimic_how_to_bring_it_up/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 16:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These other posts might help:

[Battling depression with recovery](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2303mc/request_battling_depression_with_recovery/).

[Depression and ED](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/28bj65/request_stuck_in_outpatient_for_my_ed_and_need/).

[Managing depression with an ED](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/25z0tx/request_how_to_manage_depression_during_recovery/).

[Starting inpatient, how to help myself](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1qtmbx/post_request_starting_inpatient_treatment_on/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 15:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give it a try and if it states at the top you are in an eating disorder, maybe don't. Or, answer as if you were in the disorder. It could be triggering, keep in mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 16:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful links and similar posts:

[Motivations for recovery](http://www.something-fishy.org/reach/motivations.php).

[Motivational Apps for recovery](http://www.healthline.com/health-slideshow/top-eating-disorder-iphone-android-apps#1)

[Benefits of Recovery](http://www.healthboards.com/boards/eating-disorder-recovery/474942-some-motivation-benefits-recovery.html)

[Deciding to recover](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2gafly/request_how_do_you_decide_to_recover/).

[Things that work](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2dc4rb/recovery_sharing_ziploc_bags_and_other_things/)

[12 Ideas that help in stress](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/148ipq/twelve_ideas_to_help_people_with_eating_disorders/).

[Accepting my body at a healthy weight](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2adr6r/request_suggestions_for_how_be_comfortable_with/)

[Motivation even with depression](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/26epfn/request_staying_motivated_to_recover_in_spite_of/)

[reasons to recover](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1emjg9/post_request_reasons_to_recover/)

[Lack of Motivation](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1zpuvc/request_lack_of_motivation/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 21:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Related posts and link: 

[Dieting vs. Eating Disorder](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1l40q4/post_request_how_do_i_do_things_like_try_to_eat/).

[Ending cycles of binging and restricting](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2f0p7y/anorexia_to_binging_its_not_about_will_power_its/)

[American Journal of Clinical Nutrition: Long term weight loss maintenance](http://ajcn.nutrition.org/content/82/1/222S.long) *may be triggering for anyone with over-restricting, or anorexic tendencies*.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-27 19:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Other posts on Selective Eating Disorder:

[Where do I start](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2dabhy/request_selective_eating_disorder_where_do_i_start/).

[Help, I may have SED](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2a2qvp/request_help_i_dont_think_i_have_an_average/).

[How can I get people to take SED seriously](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1ru46c/request_how_can_i_get_people_in_my_life_to_take/).

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-13 16:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is a post that might help:

[Binge Eating Recovery](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2dc4rb/recovery_sharing_ziploc_bags_and_other_things/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-13 16:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to the JAMA article it can take 6 months to a year for the hunger hormones to return to normal. It's probably a logarithmic curve where they are strongest and steepest in the beginning weeks/months, and then they balance out.

Also, if you have heart issues that are psychological, therapy is a remedy. If the heart issues are physical, see a medical professional.

Stay with it. Recovery is for life. Imagine you started a year ago, it'd be done now. 

edit: This post might help with the binging, [Binge Eating Recovery](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2dc4rb/recovery_sharing_ziploc_bags_and_other_things/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 00:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We had to remove this reply because of numbers regarding weight and a food measurement. 

You can repost a reply, but please follow the guidelines. Numbers can really hurt those in recovery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 02:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We asked this user earlier to edit the post, but since it still wasn't done it's been removed. Giving the mods a note about posts like this is fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-23 18:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> reply fom misspolkadot:

You've identified that you're self-medicating with food, as you were with cutting and drinking, so finding a healthy alternative (or a few) will be an essential part of abstaining/recovering from binging. Journaling, reading, exercising, creating art...have something ready to turn to when you feel the urge to binge. Initially, it takes a lot of will power and conscious effort to make a better choice in those moments, but eventually with practice and time it will become more natural. Especially when you find a coping mechanism that actually fulfills you and gives you joy. Binging gives some immediate, but fleeting gratification and ultimately just produces more shame, guilt, and self-loathing.

Something that helps me out a lot whenever I find myself relapsing with binge-eating is to practice mindful eating. For example, only eat sitting down at a table, use utensils, don't do other things while eating (i.e. watching TV, using the computer, etc.). I never actually binge at the kitchen table. It's usually in my room and I'm typically engaged in some other activity, like watching a TV show, so making sure I sit down at a table to eat is a great deterrent. Makes me think about what I'm doing.

You may also want to avoid trigger foods for a while. For example, I temporarily avoid things like white flour and sugar because it's like once I start I can't stop. A switch is flipped. So it's helpful to just abstain from those foods until I get back into a healthier eating pattern.

As only_one_contact noted, it seems like being alone, particularly on the weekends, might be a trigger for you. Creating some structure for your weekends and sticking to it may be helpful. Plan activities! And then make yourself do them.

Is therapy a feasible option for you? If you can afford it, I recommend working with a therapist to help discover and heal the root of the issue.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-23 18:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reply from only_one_contact :

I am currently making a hard push for recovery on all fronts I used to/still struggle with (bingeing, purging, restricting, cutting, drugs). Being alone is a big trigger for me, too. It helps that I live with my partner, but when he leaves, I experience major urges for a half hour or so. If I can get through that time, I will usually be fine. Can you remind yourself that your desire to overeat is an urge and that it will pass? Do you think you might be restricting during the week, which sets you up to overeat on the weekends?

If you stop overeating, it does not automatically mean you will return to cutting and/or drinking. If you can recognize your addictive behaviors as such, you can sit through the urges for any of them (sit and notice: "Wow, I really want to binge/cut/drink right now. What can I do instead?"). Cutting used to be a daily habit for me, but I haven't cut since 2009.

I still want to sometimes. Which sucks; I had hoped the urges would be gone by now. But at least my urges to cut are manageable. My urges to binge, on the other hand...well, that's my fight right now. I have a lot of compassion for you and wish you the best.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 05:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another post that may help, [here](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1wqyzu/how_do_i_think_better_about_food_and_not_obsess/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 14:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before I Eat app [link](https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/before-i-eat-moment-in-zone/id733555197?mt=8). 

Thanks for this. It looks good and we hope it can help others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-30 18:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Swollen glands are a sign of infection, however, they can also be brought on by eating disorders. I want to send you a message of caution replying to posts here when you are not familiar with symptoms of EDs. You could end up doing more harm than good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-30 03:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many say the book (Amazon) and website **Brain Over Binge** helped them a lot. More power to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-16 18:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you refer to your post, most people don't know which post it is. If you link it (look at formatting help for assistance) they will know which post you mean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-02 14:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Search Selective Eating Disorder on you browser. Use Chrome or Firefox browsers for best results. Or, go to Wikipedia and search the topic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-13 04:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are instructions in the sidebar if that helps. Be aware that we had to have the rules because it can turn pro-ED pretty quickly if there are no guidelines.

If it is an /r/offmychest thing, that may be the place. Also, there is /r/EDRecovery (pm Emmster to gain access) where there is a safe community to reply to the deep challenges of EDs for those in recovery. 

We try to be safe here, too. However, we are also sort of the first place to turn. Those on EDRecovery have been either working on recovery themselves or with a professional (dr., therapist, etc.) for a while.

PM Sacca7 if you want to work on a post request and get more guideance, and/or pm any or all the mods for guideance. We're here to help (just don't pm subject8657). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 17:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 16:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a great reply, but those weights with heights can be triggering to some. Can you please remove them and say "underweight" instead, please? Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 19:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~edits per guidelines please~~

Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-06 14:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This article was a post request. If you see a reputable article (that doesn't have triggering pictures or other material as per our guidelines) please send it in to the moderators and request it be posted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-27 21:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Simply listening is priceless. So often we don't feel heard, or that no one hears us. Your gift of just some extra time to listen to her would be a tremendous gift. 

Perhaps share with her resources you've found valuable. Knowledge is necessary for freeing ourselves from our difficulties, a lot of which can persist because of a lack of knowledge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-17 13:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another way of looking at treatment is to consider the stressful aspects of going now versus going after finals. 

You can easily tell friends you broke your knee and they would not judge you for missing finals. You can imagine explaining not only to friends but dealing with rumors amongst people who barely know you about leaving to get treatment at this time.

It sounds like the girl has a lot to do already, and it will be much less stress for her in so many ways to wait a few weeks. EDs are life threatening, and they feed on stress. I would hope the girl will be better able to focus on, and make the best use of, recovery if she wasn't dealing with finals and such.

If the girl was asking for attention, she did get the attention of her parents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 15:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, This account is just used for posting requests. 

If you want to connect with OP, write a comment/reply to the post inviting him/her to pm you.

Others would like to know your take on Center for Discovery and Oceanaire, so please consider posting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-25 14:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comment by Lilyvanilly:

I agree with the other poster, find an eating disorder specialized therapist and possibly psychiatrist. Also, I highly recommend the book Intuitive Eating. For me, it was like reading my own mind about binging. It was written by doctors who specialize in this and it has comforted me and helped me immensely. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-25 14:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comment by Semiramis6:

First of all, if you have the means, please seek professional help. I have found therapists and the medical community so helpful in my recovery.

Second, I know it seems contradictory, but truly the best way to stop the cycle is to start eating. By fasting, you're setting yourself up for an eventual binge. I used to crave peanut butter, and I would not eat anything all day so I could have a small bowl (yep, a bowl) of peanut butter late at night. I felt out of control, I even started shopping around at different stores for peanut butter so no one store would realize how much of the stuff I bought.

Give yourself a little extra breathing room, if possible. If you have a calorie limit for the day, tell yourself that if you go up to 200 calories over, it's still ok and you're not going to explode! If you are terrified of getting over a certain weight, add five pounds to that and tell yourself that although it's not ideal, those extra five pounds would still be ok and easy to lose eventually. I know this is a scary step. But that little bit of extra breathing room can work wonders, because as your limits probably are right now, you have no room for error. And as soon as you make one slip up, the day/week/month is ruined. I know the feeling well.

Also, start eating regularly. Make yourself a meal plan, with all three meals of the day and a snack or two. AND STICK TO IT! By the time evening rolls around, you will be satiated with the meals you had. Your brain isn't going to be starving for energy and it will make the better decisions. Your body will be strong enough to walk away from the kitchen. By fasting all day, you're basically weakening your willpower muscle, and then it's so weak that it can't resist a binge. Again, I know this is scary. But it is the number one way to break the cycle of fast-binge-fast-binge.

You could identify your triggers (stress? getting home at the end of the day? watching tv?) that make you binge, and change or eliminate them so that the desire to binge isn't as strong.

As for guilt, I have always found it useful to keep busy and keep out of the house. Immediately after a meal, if I'm feeling guilty, I try to leave and go do something, hang out with friends, whatever. I distract myself from the guilty thoughts, and they eventually go away.

You are strong enough to beat this and to stop the eating disorder from taking over your life.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-20 16:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A reply from user--frostfromfire (had a technical difficulty, sorry):

I can only speak as someone who struggled with restriction and had family/boyfriend saying awful things to me. Do not blame her when she becomes overly emotional. Speak cautiously and with concern, not blame. If discussion becomes too heated, say "I am going to give you some alone time" and walk away for at least 15 minutes. Any overtly negative comments can make her think negatively about you while shes upset. It's hard to say/do anything that won't be perceived wrong when emotions are at full blast, so usually it's better to say nothing and wait for a better time to listen/talk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 15:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An excellent book. It's one we've reviewed and it's in [the sidebar here](http://code.reddit.com/wiki/help/faqs/eatingdisorders/faq). And, [here's the link to its specific review.](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/r1239/life_without_ed_how_one_woman_declared/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-09 15:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Balance is the key.

Bingo.  It can all be simplified down to balance and moderation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-27 16:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We made a mistake in posting and had to repost this post request. Your comment was copied there. Thanks, and sorry for any confusion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-27 16:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> earlier reply from : InDisarray , some confusion in posting my fault: 

It's not a silly question. Your willingness is great! Have you scheduled that appointment yet though? Please do, there's a reason why it's been suggested for you to see a medical professional before you try to gain weight. Sorry I can't answer the question, but I'm sending you warm wishes and an internet hug. Keep us posted on your progress. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-27 00:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. It's up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-13 14:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, some people with EDs can loose the ability to recognize hunger signals. 

So, when someone with an ED says they are not hungry, they actually may not know if they are hungry or not. This leads to undernourishment, brittle bones, heart problems, kidney problems, a brain that doesn't work normally (emotions, clear thinking, etc), and on and on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-26 14:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can keep her from knowing, you might mention it to the doctors.

However, they probably know.

This is the nature of EDs. Secrecy (also known as lying) is a big part of it, somehow. The doctors and other resource specialists are well aware that this is going on, however, they are also well aware that if a patient doesn't want to get better, they can do nothing. Many patients gain the weight needed for discharge, only so they can get out and eat (or not eat, or overeat and purge) like they want to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-22 15:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> message was sent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-20 15:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although it seems many EDs are driven by difficult emotions, sometimes EDs are not driven by emotions as the book, [Brain Over Binge,](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/w6mmc/brain_over_binge_why_i_was_bulimic_why/) goes into in depth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
