<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3259</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 05:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's one thing someone should do before they're 20 that'll greatly help their life ahead? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 05:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 05:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you're sad they can sense it and are always there to offer a cuddle or a lick on the cheek.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 05:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jacob two-two </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 05:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slap myself in the face and tell myself to get it together, put down that donut and go for a run.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What should you never trust? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 21:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 06:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably sneak into airplanes and travel for free.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 06:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's sweet:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You're given $1000 and a day left to live. How do you spend it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 06:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When shrinks ask "the question" what do they do when you say yes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 04:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The question I'm talking about is "have you had any thoughts of suicide?"

Now, every time I visit the psychiatrist and she asks me this is say no in fear of what would happen if I say yes. Of course I've had thoughts of suicide but I'm afraid if I let her know that she will commit me or something. I'm an adult but I'm still afraid. 

What do they do if you say yes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I switch to ryerson for next year? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 21:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a part time student at a university in Ontario but am unhappy with my school...how do I go about transferring to ryerson for next year? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 00:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cutting off most of my hair on a whim-with kitchen scissors. 

2011 was not a good year for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Those with depression who are currently successful in life, how do you do it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 00:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone else dealt with this effect from smoking? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 02:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've smoked weed for about 5 years now and I distinctly remember the third time I got high I had the worst time ever. I think it was a precursor to what would happen later on but I still kept smoking. 

Basically I have depression and a family history with mental problems. My mom told me when she smoked weed she had a total freak out. Same with one of my relatives. 

Anyways I knew smoking while depressed can either help or hinder but I was stupid. I smoked every day after school and all of a sudden I just became detached from my body. I don't feel like I'm "living" anymore. I feel like I'm not physically present and I'm just watching myself from the outside. I'm so stupid because I continue to use marijuana and each time I'm high I have a scary out of body experience which worsens how I am sober. When I'm high and think "this is happening. This is real." I start to panic and freak out. My mind is so fucked up and I can't physically feel anything anymore or remember most things. 

I've honestly ruined my life by smoking weed and wish i had never started. I haven't smoked in almost a month because I'm too scared. Is there anyone else who has had an experience similar to this?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 01:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a cute lil heart shaped pepperoni on the bottom right corner. Looks yummy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 07:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say don't do it. Your life is yours to live and at the end of the day no one can stop you from taking it. But why would you end something with so many possibilities. I don't know if you're talking about yourself, OP, but please don't do it. There are so many times I wanted to end my life but the thought of ending my life before I've even begun to let myself live it just wasn't worth it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 07:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBH I think we will end up as they did in wall-e...hovering blobs of fat orbiting in space </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 07:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shitty weather, shitty phone companies/reception, shitty Netflix, shitty exchange rate, shitty shipping and handling prices...and Canada geese (aka satan's spawn)

That being said we have "free" health care so yay? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 07:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strange and beautiful - Aqualung </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 06:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. It's got that edgy kind of feel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 06:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best thing: mozzarella sticks
Worst thing: being born </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You've just created your dream drug. What are it's effects? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 06:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please ignore apostrophe on the its </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 06:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $200 Juicy couture bag </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 06:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Xfiles...minus the last season </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 06:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got me there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 06:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people are good...but it can be hidden under a pile of bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 06:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers to skipping grad! Saved me about three hours of my life by not going.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 06:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's a drunk and makes very rude/uncomfortable comments and literally sexualizes everything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 05:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly think it's the same with guys...most people have Instagram, Twitter etc to post about their lives and to sort of "one up" each other. You can be anybody you want on social media. The more followers the better. Posting pictures help with self validation and the anticipation of what comments you'll get is exciting. With girls I think that it's important that we establish that we have a life, are cute and are interesting. It's something I never really understood to be honest...why people have to constantly post pictures of what they're doing/eating just for a bunch of likes from people they don't even know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What did you end up doing on your prom night? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 05:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 04:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bacon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 22:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In all honesty, when there's a comma in my bank account balance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's something your parents did for you that you won't be doing for your kids? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 22:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 00:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep I was just gonna say that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some trusted online shopping sites which don't charge a lot for shipping? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 20:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently was looking at a nice pair of shoes online and they were such a good price...only problem was when I went to check out, shipping came out to $30 and an additional  10 per item! I live in Canada not some remote place. 

What are some good sites that won't break the bank on shipping to Canada? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 00:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Checked out your other drawings and I've got to say I really love your style! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fudgey espresso brownies with Kahla chocolate icing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 20:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 02:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest, I only notice if their brows are really good, uni brow or pencil thin. I don't judge people or their brows and it's not something I think about when I meet a person.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have any of you traveled alone to a resort? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 02:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking of going on a solo vacation to a resort for a week. I'm not interested in a cruise or anything else; I just need some sun and to relax. I'm 19 but pretty independent. Has any woman here traveled to a resort alone?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 05:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't say they completely helped. They made me happy but didn't fix my problems. It was weird.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 04:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wellbutrin, Prozac and cipralex. My GP prescribed them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 04:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could invest in a bread maker whether it's new or used. Or you can make some stovetop bread like pita, naan and English muffins. I've made pitas plenty of times and they're pretty cool to make.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 18:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably Italy. That's my heritage and I feel like there's so much more history and culture as opposed to where I was born.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 18:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The acne (which I'm still dealing with) and getting used to having my period (aka ruining pair after pair of nice pants) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 18:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My cellphone. Then I'd wikihow to get off said island with my built in data.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 18:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's natural peanut butter then it has to be refrigerated. If not...well that's just fucked up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 18:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kim Kardashian Hollywood. Reached level 11. It's fun but I refuse to pay for any of the in app purchases.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 06:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to a catholic school </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 05:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More religion related, but that premarital sex won't make you a bad person. The idea that people have sex just to have kids isn't the truth anymore and it needs to stop being taught.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 05:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Wally's willy was wrapped, Wendy went wild.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 20:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 20:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mainly because I fear rejection. I like them to ask me out vs I ask them out because this way I know that they have some interest and things don't end up weird.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Ben and Jerry's made an ice cream for you, what would it be called and what would be in it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 20:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 20:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Expensive af. Competitive af. Seems to leave a lot of students broke and unhappy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former smokers, what made you say "this is my last smoke?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 20:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long have you been smoke free for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I go to a resort alone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 20:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking of going away for a week to a resort however I'm under 20 and it would be solo. Is it a good idea to go to a resort alone as a young woman? Or should I go somewhere else instead?

I don't really have anyone else to go with as all my friends are in school.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Those who were seriously considering suicide, where are you now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 18:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is some advice you'd give you former self? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone else with bad skin get all happy and then remember your skin is awful? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 18:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll get excited and plan stuff and then I remember that my skin is absolutely awful and limits me to what I can and cannot do. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where is your happy place? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 02:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
