<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject758</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-09 02:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I googled her and ha, that's not me..but interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-08 15:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in terms of book genres- fiction, surrealism/realism, horror, suspense.

It is somewhat heavy, but it's definitely sort of relieving to read, just in my perspective haha. To each their own I guess!

in terms of music I've pretty much been listening to the smiths or girly stuff like Grimes and Crystal Castles.. and a bunch of classical/acoustic/instrumentals from my favorite movies, 

it's really cliche.. I know.

Thanks for distracting me by the way.. It's helping me not think too much about things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-08 14:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breaking Bad, I suppose. I read a lot of Murakami and I've recently reread Invisible Monsters by Palahniuk. 

I guess it's pretty small stuff like this that keeps me alive. 

Either that, or something bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a 19 (F) and I guess this is my story. Death seems like a great solution. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-08 14:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   I'm a 19 year old girl. 

  I'm mentally ill.

 I don't think I've ever fully typed out my life story on a website, or written it down anywhere before, so prepare for a TLDR or skip to the bottom. 

Ever since I was a young child, domestic abuse was a common thing growing up. My father was abusive towards my family and I, and we had to put it up with it almost every single day. 

Everyone suffered. My sisters, my mother, even my own relatives suspected what was going on but no one intervened.

At age 12, I was molested by my first therapist/counselor at school, I kept it a secret until my early teens. Bullying seemed of the norm or common to me, so I put up with that as well as my grades suffered. I was in denial of what happened for a very long time and I

During high school at age 15, I experienced a traumatic experience from an incident with my dad and I had to leave the house the move in with my aunt. CPS and the police were involved, I had to go to court a lot, it was horrible. I developed my eating disorder at this age and I ended up dropping out of school. I was not missed.

From then on, everything got worse.

 Suicide/OD attempts, jumping into traffic, self-harm, binging and purging- I hated myself. I experienced a lot of shitty traumatic events. I put myself in unhealthy relationships, dropped out of college, and ended up having to go to rehab because I decided I needed help after having my whole family just get so sick of it. I was definitely not sober before rehab, but I pretended to function well and it was taking a toll on my body, along with my eating disorder which is currently very active.

When I left rehab, I relapsed. 

I took all my sleeping pills (a months worth) in one go and drank some booze. I was saved by my sister.

After I left the hospital,

 I went into an eating disorders program, and got discharged the first day I was there. I basically; could not do it or handle it. I am not allowed there again, obviously- and my shitty therapist decided to drop me because she didn't want to be liable for anything in case I actually do kill myself. Now I am left with no therapist, I am currently in an extremely dysfunctional relationship with someone who constantly puts me down, and I always find myself loving him more than he loves me.. But I don't have anyone else.. and I have NO friends, or family to confide in. I have no job, I can't go to school right now until January, and I'm desperately trying to find help.

I feel stupid and useless, and ugly, and just a waste of space.

Everything just seems really fucking terrible. 

And I've put my mother in debt about 50 grand... 

I just really wish I were dead this time.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-07 12:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> two experiences. 

My grandma and auntie had made some shanghainese food- 

simmered pork belly, lobster, with the roe and egg noodles, and shrimp+pork stuffed hot peppers. 

Another was when I was in the hospital, almost dying and eating liquidy bullshit, Ensure, and fake ass eggs for 3 days, later I decided to order some Thai food while I was still in there and it was literally the best thing I've ever tasted. Fucking spicy goodness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-06 06:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my sister and I walked in on our grandpas caretaker screaming because.. he somehow "accidentally" stabbed himself in the eyeball when we were little kids  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 13:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> crying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 07:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wtFFuuHHuhaskjaf. ??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 05:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ridiculously photogenic male bungee jumps in wheel chair. '~' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-30 13:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I bet she fucks like a fairy on acid." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-30 06:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know why but this makes me angry to look at. 
Because I need to split all of them apart. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-29 23:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> too cute </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
