<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6446</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 13:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont mean to sound so rude. I guess I just needed to get some stuff out sorry about that lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 06:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the advice yes I suspect depression. I tryed therapy about a year ago and was diagnosed with anorexia and bipolar type 2, but she really didn't help me. looking back on it I think it made things worse, the therapist I saw kind of ignored the issues that I was actually ready to deal with, and as soon as I came in she said she thought I was bipolar. The psychiatrist she sent me too was her friend from highschool, or something, and she immediately perscibed me medication for bipolar disorder type 2, without even talking to me. The whole thing made me feel like my own opinion and self awareness was unimportant.
Wow way more rant-ish than I intended sorry I guess I just want some opinions on all this bull shit.
I wish I was just fucking normal. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 05:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont want to do anything anymore.
Im on vyvance 50mg, I just switched from 40mg to 50mg this month, and it's not like my medication isnt working. I know it is, but I just dont want to do anything, not even things I love to do. I feel empty, and restless. The strange thing is these feelings only happen when the sun sets...literally when it gets dark outside.  
Someone please tell me what the fuck is wrong with me?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Really need some support (rant) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 14:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My to do list is so long! I have so many things due at the end of the week, and through out the week, I got locked on to one assignment, and spent all of my time on it I now  have only a few days to do these REALLY important things I put off. I feel so fucking overwhelmed!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 22:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also any one struggle with doubting yourself?

I was surprised by the effect the meds have on my appetite when I first took them.  And now I have this nagging part of me that says that I shouldn't be allowed medication, because im just going to use it for weight loss. I'm not trying to use it in this way, and I know that. But when I start having these thoughts, it's hard for me to convince myself otherwise. :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 22:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

Thanks guys! :)

 I will have to try the small meals through out the day thing. I just recently upped my dosage too. So im going to have to try something, because only eating on break days in not helping me maintain for sure. :/ 

So are you diagnosed?  I would just like to hear about how your adhd effects your ED, or vice versa. I haven't met anyone who has both if these problems, and I would love to have someone to relate too about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
