<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6210</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 22:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I think an intro thread would be a great idea! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 19:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't recommend weighing yourself multiple times a day. It becomes obsessive and it won't be your true weight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 18:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't be envious! I still have a ways to go. You'll get there soon too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 17:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This](http://imgur.com/a/ZQ8L5) is me today. I took a lot of pictures because I was feeling vain. I wish I could get rid of the pouch of fat on my stomach and get my thighs thinner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 16:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started having little leaks too! Usually when I stand up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 16:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was, but she knew she couldn't stop me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 06:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can do this! You are stronger than those scones! Drink some water or tea. I believe in you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 06:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just on it and didn't have any problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 06:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you want to chat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 05:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to purge in the shower, but my mom would get mad at me because it's bad for the drain. So I still purge in the shower but I pick up my puke and squeeze the water out and put it in the toilet. That's probably the grossest thing I've done because of my ED. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 05:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay! I love your username btw! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 04:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's MPA? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wish there was more activity on this sub! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 03:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely love this subreddit, I just wish there was more activity on it! I'm often on here refreshing the "new" page, hoping there's a new post. All of the lurkers should come out of the woodwork and participate! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 03:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cinnamon (147)

Lunch: 1/2 red bell pepper (11) celery (6) cucumber (8) and 2 egg whites (34)

Dinner: Rice cake with 1 and 1/2 tbsp of light peanut butter (155)

Snacks: Diet coke (0)

Total: 361 calories
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 19:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome! This is a great place for advice and support. Hope we can help you get to your goals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 18:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god, there are calories in vape liquid? I was planning on buying some liquid today to go back to vaping since I started smoking again, but this is scaring me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 18:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is gorgeous!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 17:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - binge food - pizza pops, I would restrict all day, then get home and binge on pizza pops

- Purge food - the first time I purged was after I had eaten a huge bowl of lucky charms cereal 

- Body dismorphic moment - I don't remember exactly when, but it was when I hit puberty and started to get hips

- First body part I wanted to change was my thighs and my hips. I'm bottom heavy, so my hips, thighs and ass are big compared to my upper body 

- first succeed in losing weight - I would lose a bit of weight when I was restricting, but my first major weight loss was when I became bulimic when I was 16, I would purge every single thing that went into my body 

- my first goal weight was 84lbs (still is), I never hit it, but I'm hoping I will soon 

- I knew immediately that I was developing an eating disorder 

- I never had a never eat it food until very recently, now I won't eat anything that isn't part of my meal plan.

- I never had a specific person as a thinsperation, it was mostly pictures of girls that I found on pro-ana blogs

- people have always found me to be too skinny, I have been underweight my whole life. I remember my friends telling me that they could snap me like a twig when I was 6 years old.

- my first mantra was a moment on lips forever on the hips and nothing tastes as good as skinny feels </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 16:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been having really bad anxiety about school and finals these days. I've never had anxiety before and I've never really been super stressed about exams, but these days I'm just so stressed and anxious about it. Plus the depression makes it very hard to concentrate and study, which stresses me even more! I almost had a panic attack the other which I have never had before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 04:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is how I feel too. I really hope this kills me, and soon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 00:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with 1tbsp of light peanut butter (180)

Lunch: Rice cake with 1 and 1/2 tbsp of light peanut butter (155)

Dinner: Cucumber (8), celery (6) and half a red bell pepper (11)

Snack: Diet coke (0)

Total: 360 calories

So I weighed myself today after not knowing (and estimating) my weight for months and I found out that I'm 4 lbs lighter than I thought! I'm at 92 lbs now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 20:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 19:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  is my main account, I accidentally posted my stats under that account... I thought I had deleted the comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 18:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is your daily calorie intake goal?
edit: I  just noticed that you said under 900.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 17:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have many goals. But my plan is to stay under 400 calories a day, every day. I'm allowing myself to eat (and hopefully enjoy) at Christmas, it's going to be my cheat day. Then go back to my meal plan after Christmas. 

Also to study and do well on my finals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 05:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You want to eat something with protein for longer lasting energy, or complex carbohydrates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 05:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually having a binge will kick start your metabolism when you hit a plateau, so it might actually help you lose weight in the long run!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 01:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I am in the exact same situation!! It would help me study so much, I am the worst studier ever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 00:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cinnamon (147)

Lunch: 1/2 red bell pepper (11) celery (6) cucumber (8) and 2 egg whites (34)

Dinner: Rice cake with 1 and 1/2 tbsp of light peanut butter (155)

Snacks: Diet coke (0)

Total: 361 calories
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 00:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I could get some adderall to help me study (and restrict) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 17:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, for me, when I eat something that isn't planned, even just a bite, I go on a full binge and I can't stop eating and I end up eating thousands of cals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 16:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I eat pretty much the same thing every day. So if it's anything that isn't part of my meal plan then I consider it a binge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 02:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lucky, brain zaps really suck. I had them on other SSRIs, but its been so much worse with effexor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 01:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cinnamon (147)

Lunch: 1/2 red bell pepper (11) celery (6) cucumber (8) and 2 egg whites (34)

Dinner: Rice cake with 1 and 1/2 tbsp of light peanut butter (155)

Snacks: Diet coke (0)

Total: 361 calories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 00:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say to only weigh yourself once a day. Your weight fluctuates throughout the day. So the best time to weigh yourself is first thing in the morning after peeing, but before eating. This will give you your most accurate weight. Any other time you are also weighing your food and water, that's why you go up throughout the day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 00:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was on tumblr for a while, but it got pretty lonely because I didn't really have anyone to talk to. But I just discovered this subreddit and it's so nice to be able to interact with people! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finally reached a long time goal! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 22:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This week I reached a goal that I have had for a really long time. I'm finally able to wrap my hands around the top of thighs and have my fingers touch.

Hopefully I will be able to wrap my hand around my upper arm soon. Only a little bit of space until my finger and thumb touches.

Also, after months of not knowing my weight, I will have access to scale on Wednesday and I'll finally know my weight. So I'm excited and nervous </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 22:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Height: 5'8

* CW: 96lbs

* HW: 115lbs

* LW: 84 lbs

* GW: 90 lbs

* UGW: 85 lbs

* WL: 8 lbs

* BMI: 14.44

* Age: 19

* Gender expression: Female </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 22:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do you get the white chocolate peppermint tea? That sounds delicious! I'm a sucker for both peppermint and white chocolate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 22:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started effexor a few weeks ago. And it does really suppress my appetite, I've been able to restrict so much better now that I'm on it.

Random question, when you started it, did you get really bad brain zaps? Mine were horrible and I'm still getting some mild ones 3 weeks later. So I'm thinking that my restriction might be making those side effects much more intense.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 15:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I could bake and not eat it. But I would go on a total binge if I made food like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 04:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weird... well if you want to chat my username is labellemort. And if I get more people I'll start a group </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 04:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried looking for it, but I couldn't find it for some reason </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 04:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 400 cals isn't a lot! That's less then what most consider a meal. You should just go back to your routine tomorrow and it will make up for this. This is just a tiny little blip in the grand scheme of things. One bad day won't make you gain weight, just like 1 good day won't make you lose weight. I don't know much about EC stacks, so I can't say anything about that. But laxatives won't make you lose any real weight, it will just dehydrate you and you might get addicted to them, which would really suck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 04:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? There's a group? 
If I get enough interest I'll start another one.
If you want to add me you can! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi, I'm new here! Anyone want to chat on kik? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 01:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 01:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with 1tbsp of brown sugar and 1/2 tsp cinnamon (147)

Lunch: 2 egg whites and half a red bell pepper (45)

Dinner: Rice cake with 1 and 1/2 tbsp light peanut butter (155)

Snacks: Diet coke (0)

Total: 347 cals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 23:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently the bmi that people find the most attractive is 19, which is a bit above underweight. I think most people find slightly underweight girls attractive but once you get too low people stop finding it attractive. 

Probably a big part of why people find underweight girls attractive is because of the media and advertising, most actresses and models are underweight or very near it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 04:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the food network!!! You gotta here is my favourite show! I'll have to check out Simply Sara. I also really like going to look at food in stores or at the cafeteria at my uni </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE love looking at food porn? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 04:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love looking at pictures of food, reading recipes and reading menus. I spend hours looking at pictures of food and reading recipes. I actually have a blog were I post a bunch of recipes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 04:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/a/bTK5a This is me from yesterday, ignore my stomach, I was pretty bloated. But my back looks pretty good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 00:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Cereal and milk (177)

Lunch: 2 egg whites (35)

Dinner: Rice cake with light peanut butter (155)

Snacks: Rice cake with light peanut butter (155)

Total: 522 I really regret having a snack, I usually don't but I felt like I was going to binge so I had a bit of safe food.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 04:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Cereal and milk -171 
Lunch: 2 celery stalks and 1/2 cup cucumber slices - 17
Dinner: Rice cake with 1 1/2 tbsp light peanut butter - 155 
Total: 346 cals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 04:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have any old pictures, but I took these today http://imgur.com/a/bTK5a. Ignore my stomach I'm pretty bloated :'( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
