<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8986</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-24 03:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really curious why you had hallucinations. Did you have psychotic depression? Or was the seizure part of your diagnosis unrelated to depression? I know Lamictal is an antiseizure med which has helped with me the most (I don't have any psychotic symptoms though). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-23 10:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a totally sad note about that, I once remember watching Animal Planet (I think) where someone disowned their poodle because it didn't match their new living room decor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-23 10:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm obsessed with the marks your clothing left behind on your lower belly. Beautiful :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-23 07:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My vagina just squeezed a little. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-23 07:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. I don't find anything wrong with her glasses. I have glasses and it's certainly not fun to wear them in bed anyways... *if you know what I'm saying... these italics make me sound so creepy*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-23 06:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's funny how ambien does that. I can't imagine it working for someone because makes people like bricks after 30 minutes. Although I know someone with an ambien addiction who takes like 5 a day, I don't know how she does that. It was fun to take it but I wake up the next day with the phone having 40 minute conversations and things. Nothing too drastic.

I can imagine ADHD being a lot like mania in a way. Not in the hyperactivity per se, but with racing thoughts and impulsivity. I have ADHD and I think it's in my nature to be more impulsive but not for manic reasons. Adderall calmed me down a lot. It was perfect but I can't take it anymore because it made my heart rate too fast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-23 06:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's interesting. Have you tried other over the counter things such as Calcium and Magnesium? I've heard St Johns Wort could have a strong placebo effect. I wonder if that's not true, but something with subtler effects (such as SJW and magnesium) helps better for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-23 06:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hm, I've never had disturbances (would it be like hallucinations?) but I deal with derealization / depersonalization every once in a while outside from panic. My boyfriend wanted to hospitalize me when he didn't know what it was but it's funny that something as simple as klonopin helped. Lamictal helped a lot with that too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-23 06:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I became 88 pounds (being 5'4") but now I'm 104. I'm doing much better. Before I was 88 I think I was like 110. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-22 21:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did you stop risperidone? What happened with your visual disturbances?

I'm glad celexa works for you. It does well with people, that and Lexapro. They're supposed to be very similar. I don't remember exactly why I got off of Lexapro but I took it two separate times so there must be a reason I went through withdrawal hell twice for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-22 21:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, this is the first time I haven't been on a combo. When I first started I was taking lots at once. Usually Lamictal + antidepressant + Buspar or Adderall + benzo. I liked to say I was taking an antidepressant, depressant, stimulant, and mood stabilizer because it just sounded funny like that. It's nice I suppose that I only have to take Lamictal right now, but it's not enough. Hopefully increasing in the future will help.

I'm happy to hear that you're okay with realizing you'll be on antidepressants for the rest of your life. I think me too. It's only really helped.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-22 13:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to have a dream of taking pictures for a living. Now I kind of want to paint but not really, I just say it. Translating emotion visually is so great. I once had a bad grade in a photo class and never wanted to take photos again. That stuff doesn't matter anymore. It's very nice to know someone who was suicidal still takes nat geo photos. That was my goal once, to go into the wild and take photos, that sort of thing. That dream job sort of thing. I forgot about it. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-22 13:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am also 19 and have an interest in indirect suicide. Very different from you, though. Sorry to add in some bullshit diagnosis but being bipolar with rapid cycling can make people feel this way. The death obsession with depression and the energy to do it with mania. But anyways, I don't think death will help. It just numbs you. Being numb is so addicting. I bet especially so with your lifestyle... craving that feeling of finally feeling numb. It's like finding peace but much more tragic. I hope these other people's words help. I just understand that indirect suicide thing, I've never been suicidal but I've not wanted to live plenty of times. Like, eh fuck eating, too much work to keep myself in this condition. I'm not trying to say you'll be fixed one day but I think one day you'll find this thing where you'll like a thing. I don't know what thing. I'm obsessed with kittens and I don't have one but they keep me going. It's fucking stupid but they saved me and I can save a kitten too which is pretty cool. One day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-22 12:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do this when I've been alone for a few hours, to the point of breaking down crying. I'm definitely not trying to 1up you, saying I have it worse at all. But just a small thing, I have been getting better. My boyfriend was sick and house sitting his moms place (we have a dog that can't come) so I went and slept the night. I had no one and I actually enjoyed myself. I also have driving anxiety and she lives in a hilly area with small streets. One year ago I couldn't have done this. Being alone for 5 minutes made me sad (boyfriend pooping for instance??) a year ago. I could not imagine being alone for a few days. And I have complete social anxiety to almost agoraphobia. Scumbag brain at it's worst (for me). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-22 12:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is good. I'm in the middle of college and my (abnormal) psychology professor said that it's okay to take school slowly. She has a PhD so it's nice to get the validation. She said she believed in me getting a PhD, but not now. That was last year. I need something like this. I'm on break from school, no job, so I'm getting no external validation (money or grades) to know how well I'm doing. Anyone saying anything I'm doing fine is lying to me. 

Watching things like Intervention I say things like, Oh My God these people need immediate help. People say, No I need my daughter! And not even having a child I feel so funny saying these people need help, and I can't even take a month off of self care. Whether in the hospital, whatever. I don't need that now, I'm a year past that point, but really... It's extremely hard to judge not seeing how bad your situation is from your perspective. This is a great little comic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-22 12:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been sleeping 14 hours, and then naps in between. I took 2 naps today outside of the sleep. Before being medicated, I would be so stressed I would sleep because it's like finally being able to take a break. It must be part of the relief of suicide. I'm not suicidal but goddamn I need sleep. Which makes me not eat and made me 88 pounds but fuck it, maybe it's all a slow death. I'm wondering if it's related to compulsive overeating, but compulsive oversleeping. I'm bored, I sleep. I'm happy, I sleep. I'm anxious, I sleep. I'm nauseous, I sleep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-22 12:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few days ago I had a panic thing because I heard a song I listened to in middle school. It happens a lot from that time period, when my depression started. I think it's because its such a "losing child innocence" stage in my life. It sucked because I was about to get laid, and I did but it was probably a pity lay, since I haven't heard back from her. She was also a brand new 18 year old lesbian and I'm a 19 year old lezbo grandma (just kidding) but it's like, fuck this is supposed to be sexy. But all I did was cry. I can't smell and I've heard people find smells nostalgic. But there is something quite tragic in nostalgia. I never compare the word nostalgia to something that is happy. It's always a longing. And in depression, I do long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-22 12:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always thought it was interesting how death was connected to my depression. I always thought, I'm not suicidal but I certainly wouldn't mind if I died. Killing myself would take too much work and planning that I just don't have the energy to do. It might be a reason I had anorexia, because I would just not have the energy to feel myself (amongst other things). I always felt like the suicidal ones must be bipolar (or fast cycling).

I understand. I'm dealing with it by getting my dopamine hits. Small little doses of things that not necessarily bring me excitement (so hard), but just the little things that give me a little zap. It's how (recreational) drugs probably work. This would just be more "natural" and more fit to you. Hobbies are so hard to think of now, at least for me. I feel pressure to do well in a hobby. So things like reddit (obviously) help. Anything to get you high as long as it isn't directly damaging (things that'll get your adrenaline or endorphins up... unless it's exercise. But unhealthy sex, vomiting, drugs, although they help temporarily, don't really help in the end). 

With my own personality, it's the things that people make fun of that work for me. People say it's stupid to show a depression person a picture of a kitten, but I've always been an animal nerd since a tiny girl. I don't consider it a hobby, since animals don't judge. Perhaps find something like that. People often say charity helps with that but don't worry about that yet. But have that mindset in the back of your brain. 

Or stupid things like self help books even help. I love the DBT workbook (it's green). Different from CBT but it basically gives you lists you can do without judging you. 

You can have a "fuck it, fuck life" thing too, like.. "fuck i'm going to run to the grocery store and not giving a shit" helps. Like that same anger that comes from "fuck life" but different. The point isn't to make you happy at this point, but for little steps. 

I don't even know what I'm saying. I understand completely though. Someone out there is going through the same things, sometimes dealing with it worse. Wanting and asking for help is such an important step. Jeez, I keep sounding like some piece of shit article. I don't mean it like that. 

Just... it gets better. I feel better than I did 1 year ago. I can make it seem like that means it's been a year since I've only improved a little, but I'm changing my mindset to be like... I showered today, which is better than me not showering yesterday. Just small stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What has been on your list of medications? I want to hear your (chemical) journey. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-22 12:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure a lot of us are here right in the middle of what I'm going through, which is finding the right meds. I thought it might be interesting to compare what we might be taking.

---
Me:

I got off Cymbalta because I slept all day.

I got off Wellbutrin because it made my anxiety worse (I also have GAD and panic disorder).

I got off Lexapro because it was expensive, sexual side effects, and I wasn't sure if it was working.

I got off of Paxil CR because I slept 14 hrs per day and spent that time with nightmares every day, but it did help with anxiety and depression.

I got off of Buspar because I don't think it did anything except when I stopped taking it my anxiety was bad.

I got off of Adderall because it made my heart rate consistently 120+ bpm. Another reason I stopped Wellbutrin. 

I took Strattera for like a month for some reason.

I've taken Lamictal and it helped with stopping my meltdowns becoming extreme. I'm on 200mg, increasing to 300mg and I've been on it for 2 years. I take xanax and klonopin on the side. I've just been switched to taking Paxil 5mg, from Paxil CR 25mg. I think it's mostly placebo.

I'm currently in the withdrawal stages of Paxil and I've been feeling bed bound, overwhelmed with everything from the physical side effects, and emotional, too. I seem to do really badly with withdrawals, from nausea and dizziness and brain zaps and panic and eventually vomiting from stress of nausea. I'm sick of always being in withdrawal, because otherwise I don't seem to get that sick. I know there are lots of medications that I haven't tried, but before I've at least I had an idea of what meds I should take next. I often suggest them to my doctors, since I've done my research. For example, when I went off of Adderall, I suggested Wellbutrin to help with the ADHD. The only thing that I know has worked is Lamictal, and only since I hit 200mg. CBT-based therapy helped around this time as well. I know many people have much longer lists than I do, and many more treatment options, and I'm curious about them all. What was your step after trying out SSRIs, for example? I'm especially curious about (atypical) antipsychotics and things of that sort. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-22 07:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how delicate your body is. So sexy. Also I think I have same/similar undies. Yay :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-22 06:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say the dykey bits :) There's a bit of a difference in the subreddits both link to on the sidebar! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The gorgeous Freja Beha </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-22 03:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-21 12:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the movie "our idiot brother". ahh rashida jones in this is SO cute! i read recently that the stylist dressed her as a boy he would be attracted to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-20 05:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll have to see about the leather, as someone said in this thread about cloth being more sanitary when it comes to multiple partners, being able to sanitize. We both love leather, so it'll be a hard decision. Or not. Maybe both will happen. :) If i do get cloth though, it won't be a cheap one. What you said makes a lot of sense. That leather one really is beautiful.

I have an njoy fun wand that I've used on him (gently!) and he took that pretty well... Although, it didn't go in much, I suppose he was more okay with the circumference... hm, I didn't really think about that until now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-20 05:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I love that purple one, although I think it would be too large for my boyfriend's first. Maybe just for myself when I get the money :P

It's not the g-spot I'm worried about, but general friction, and it doesn't seem to be because of lube for me, since even when I do use synthetic lube I still feel pain after a short while. It's very odd, I can do anal sex much more "successfully" than vaginal. 

Do you know if a low riding harness would add extra stimulation to the vulva? Since I do like pressure on the mound/lower tummy... I suppose things like this are for me to find out with my own body!

Anyways, thank you so much! I love the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-20 03:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate you taking time out of class to write this! It definitely helps.

The cloth idea definitely sounds good, for cleaning reasons. I've seen some great looking cloth ones too. 

I don't necessarily need a sparkly dildo, just to explain how I want it in the general gist of things. :P

I always thought I wanted a double ended dildo, but I'm not sure anymore since my vagina gets overstimulated pretty easily. Is there a problem with that? I can imagine it might bother my urethra as well, since it would be in the middle of all the stimulation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-19 20:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose I was listing reasons to not have sex in the dark to make an orgy better. So, I listed the analogy to add to the confusion of protection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-19 14:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i am proud to say that i am not into bestiality.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-19 14:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> right now i'm writing on ambien with no glasses on so i might speak a little out of order but i have insomnimania so its ok. i mean like, let's say in a group of hot people, let's use the stupid rating system, of people from 8-10. of course you want to touch 9 and 10, but the 8s you're less likely to want to touch. maybe, to me, it feels like a high school dance? like.. "id go out with those skaters, except that one" but when it comes to orgies, you have to be like... the chance of you being with someone you don't want to be already messes the flow in your head. unless they're all identical twins. no one has the same amount of trust and know each other with everyone. oof. if you want, you can ask me specifically and i can respond better once I sleep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-19 13:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh. yeah. nitrous oxide, not those cute spindly things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-19 13:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not so into vibrators. Maybe I just need the whole shbang hitachi, but it's a little boring to me. maybe having to adjust, and not having it lost, and when is it time to stop using it, and i hope the dog doesn't get to it if it fell of the bed... (disclaimer: i have generalized anxiety :P) but even without those thoughts, it arouses me like 3 out of 10 at best.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-19 13:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that wiring thing you described is great. It really is just as if touch has a different sensation. there can be ones that have no sharpness. It takes a pretty good understanding of how it works (which I don't have that well down) but being on the receiving end of it, I don't like any pain related. I had probes in v and ass and since so much surface area was being touched, it basically was a low gentle vibrator. Another cool thing is using props like wiring through the dom's body to a whip with metals inside, or vampire gloves... kissing is great too, touching tongues with that little tickle in between. also, the adrenaline of the entire experience. I don't think i could ever come to it, and maybe not have it be sexual but more sensual.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-19 13:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Protection, but someone once told me that there's also the one person in the group you most likely do not want to have sex with. That person that might be fuckable when you're drunk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-19 13:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, same with me except instead of pizza it was whippets so basically it was just a big strange movie. Then I went to the kitchen and got some snacks and went back in and wanted more whippets. This was the first time I did whippets and it's still my favorite little thing. I was naked though and I love being naked but it's more of one of those bachelor things where I poke my boobs while watching TV and not wearing undies so I can do push laundry day to another day and there's some background moans going on somewhere.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-19 13:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. I think a lot of people see being able to be with a girl as an experience that will most likely be purely sexual and short-lived. It wasn't until I was fully aware that I was bisexual instead of wanting to "experiment" and letting myself check out girls and be open to be with a girl in a long term relationship that I loved to have sex with girls. Not to say I don't love casual sex with girls too. God I love fucking girls. This is fun to talk about. It makes me want to come out to the whole world. "Here's your groceries" "Thanks I love girls". Luckily the internet cares less about me saying things like that so boobies boobies boobies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-19 13:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same! There's a part of me that might feel self conscious, but it doesn't explain not finding pleasure in receiving. I think for me it has to do with liking a broad surface area. I love grinding, for instance, and can / prefer to come with my undies still on (not having to do with the self consciousness). I get overstimulated much too quickly. One of the reasons I can last longer with anal sex than vaginal. Receiving oral is kind of boring to me though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-19 13:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> while there is an aspect of fearing of being a voyeur, i don't feel that way in threesomes. i guess it helps the small bit of exhibitionist in me, even though i'm usually the one to give. i suppose there's always room to touch... there's actually more available areas :P mouths, genitalia, holding hands, whatever. i've never been in a foursome, but to me it sounds like it might as well be an orgy or 2 couples having sex in the same room. totally personal preference though, since i'm not attracted by the idea of orgies or orgies i've been in the same room with. although, when i have been in a room where an orgy has been going on, i want to cling to my boyfriend even more, so maybe that's what the not feeling left out thing comes in. also sorry for the skipping around of this, ambien writing..! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-19 13:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're focused on the dynamics of things, which is fine when there's someone who clearly knows what they're doing / are experienced / are a good top. that's "easier", at least. i've been in ones where it's basically 2 girls pleasing the guy, and the encounter was all very casual. it was good but afterwards it's like, eh i could've done without it. recently i've been doing ones where it's mostly like me and a girl playing, and i'm also paying attention to my boyfriend, but the 3rd is more like a toy. this is important to me since i'm more on the lesbian side of the spectrum at the moment. it was also not sex based, but like... cuddling extreme, where there was no pressure for orgasm. of course, the individuals is what makes the dynamic work, even when its 2 people. it's just more to think about with 3 people. i don't think it has to do with jealousy (and i can be jealous, just not in 3somes i suppose). i think there's more pressure to "perform" in general. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-19 10:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll keep all of those in mind, especially the first one. I haven't even thought of that (mixing and matching). There's so many options... 

I thought, well of course I want high quality! But realized my boyfriend might not like it at all. As with all sex toys, I suppose. 

I'm definitely going to a store after all of this browsing. I don't think I can tell well enough what is considered high quality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-19 09:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That position is great if you need a large surface area, which sounds like what your friend is looking for, unless it really is just the texture. I'm similar in that I need a large surface area, and I love being on top (physically, not mentally). I masturbated while grinding on pillows, so I find that position to be the easiest to come to. Another good one is grinding against the partner's thigh, or that position which is grinding against the pubic bone which can be done without internal stimulation if that can be uncomfortable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm buying a strap-on for the first time and need advice! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-19 08:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, for my birthday (in March), my boyfriend is going to buy me a strap-on for me to use on him (and the ladies I get to fuck every once in a while!) (which happened last night btw I'm happy for getting laid, A+).

I'm trying to research them but I have no idea where to start, and thought I'd ask my fellow redditors. Are there any cult brands that I should know about (like njoy toys)? I'm a small/thin girl, is there a specific thickness of harness that is known to be more comfortable? What about harness materials? 

For the guys, especially the hetero ones: is there anything you can add about your experience with them? My boyfriend likes prostate stimulation but not penetration. We have an aneros but find that fingers work nicer. Is an extra small dildo helpful? Is one that gives a bend nicer? What would seem the least intimidating?

Some things I've got down is that I wouldn't like it to look realistic in terms of color and details and would love a pink girly glittery cock with hearts and stars and rainbows, at least for now.

Help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-17 01:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i say either a very rich/dark red or brunette, i think too bright of red or too dark of black will make complexions look worse. not absolutely sure though! but i'm sure you can pull a lot off, the haircut suggestion above sounds great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-15 08:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, try Kewpie mayo. Mentioned a few times here. It makes a world of a difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-15 08:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would it be like itadakimasu?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-15 08:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Growing up with only Kewpie mayo, regular mayo disgusts me! Thank god I live by a Japanese market. It's much smoother and creamier than other mayo. Regular mayo is like Kraft cheese next to Kewpie.

Also... thanks for the recipe, OP. Simple recipes of things I already have is one of the greatest feelings. Makes me feel like my kitchen is well stocked even with an empty fridge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-14 07:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this made me excited :) i saw your boys undies post the other day and went off to go look for some. i love boys undies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-12 13:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are some varying definitions, like the person not being able to stay at least 85% of their ideal body weight, and the refusal to gain. There's also the difference between Anorexia Nervosa and anorexia, which is just about a loss of appetite. They used the term very casually which is upsetting for an article that is trying to convey an accurate measurement of what "normal" is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-12 12:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in that situation right now. I love my boyfriend, but I'm also free to explore girls while he stays monogamous to me (by both our choices). There are plenty of girls out there who are willing to fulfill your girly-needs. For me, one of the top priorities in being with a girl is someone who is okay with me being with a man. This girl doesn't sound like the greatest addition to your relationship. If she already isn't okay with it, I'd be worried she would be jealous in the future, so you have to be very careful if you do plan on moving forward with her, and she gives the OK for some reason. My personal advice would be to move on, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-12 10:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i agree, though... the undies look so soft. cuddling you would be like hugging a kitten with hearts all over it while eating a cupcake, i think! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-12 10:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have scars in the same area. it was surprising to see.

you're beautiful 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of these things is not like the others </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-12 01:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-11 05:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i don't think she's "ruined", but since plastic surgery often has similar results (noses end up looking similar, etc), i'm not sure i could recognize if i saw her in public. she just blends in more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-11 01:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> are you... serious?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-08 12:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have that color right now, different answer. i'm in the process of going white, but to take a break in between bleachings, i went a light pink. so the bleach is yellow, and "cotton candy pink" in manic panic mixed in with conditioner works. i also didnt wash my hair for a few days before the dye, so it rinsed out quickly... but its a very easy color to maintain otherwise, for a light color. mostly because you don't have to worry about toning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-08 11:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this. my back hurts just looking at it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-08 07:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you! she's such a gorgeous </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-08 07:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [portia de rossi!](http://www4.images.coolspotters.com/photos/1380/portia-de-rossi-and-iggy-pop-lust-for-life-t-shirt-gallery.jpg)

i also vote her and ellen as [cutest couple ever](http://26.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_lxa4rr4TSy1qixsnco1_500.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-07 04:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i wanna join in on the fun!

[:) :P](http://i.imgur.com/ZEmzV.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-07 04:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you two are so cute!! lovely </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-05 01:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm not sure what a katniss braid is, sorry!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-04 13:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> on another note about bisexuals being open. i think it might be related to being open about sexuality in general. for instance and with great generalization, a closeted person will most likely want to be in a long term, monogamous relationship for the image, security, etc. whereas coming out has fears on its own, so it might be easier to know what you want/ask for in terms of being poly, kinks, whatever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-04 12:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well helloooo there... :P

you have awesome morning hair! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-04 10:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [new pink hair :)](http://i.imgur.com/hutAN.jpg)


[this is also a nice little website with a similar feel to this thread](http://lesbianswholooklikeumlesbians.tumblr.com/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-04 03:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the worst was the poop diapers stored in the bath :( i had to stop watching </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-04 00:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i recently heard a guy in the background giving a suggestion or something. i think they forgot to edit it out. i died. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-03 10:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm exactly the same! i'm in a very serious relationship with a man, but only get off to girls. hetero porn is such a turn off for me... i don't think i've watched it in years, maybe accidentally. i'm guessing a lot of it has to do with how guys are portrayed in porn, too. it's often kind of... greasy (if i remember correctly). it might also be that i'm satisfied with the man cravings... but not the girls! i think i'm obsessed with girls. i think we all are.... but... augh :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-26 11:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that was great. I'm not blind, but I've never been able to smell. I loved the image of the lady whose head is a flower, and I didn't realize it related to my lack of smell until I showed it to my boyfriend. It helped me understand why someone would like to wear perfume, in a visual image, instead of just saying "oh, it smells good".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-23 12:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> your excited response made me watch it. this, and i like princesses and jellyfish... i've been watching this on hulu since you posted. i'm about halfway done. i'm not even that big of an anime fan either. thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-23 12:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what does make character design for you, then?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-21 10:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i understand that feeling, being (half) asian, and young. but it's totally about your self esteem. any girl could say that a guy is flirting with her just to bang her, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-22 09:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was also a tutorial around Halloween around here using jello inside straws to make jello-worms and they said they ran the straws under hot water for a little bit and they slid out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-21 22:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on what kind of art. I've noticed younger artists (probably a background in illustration) have cheaper art, ~$300. I like Gallery WWA in Culver City, they had a little back room filled with art when I went which I'm sure is still there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-12 01:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> stress/weight loss can do this as well. the hair cycles every 3 months, so if your stress was from 3 months ago, this sounds right. you could be stress-free now, but your hair is still 3 months behind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-10 23:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i was thinking omurice (omlette-rice), as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-08 20:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> kcgjlc;iug

kick_luigi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-05 10:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't say exact citations or anything, but it reminds me of something I read recently about being surprised. That is, humans become surprised when there's a sudden change in scenery, like light or sound or object. Obviously to protect from predators and etc etc. So the "fight or flight" mode would turn on during these times. With a commercial/jump cut, there's a bunch of sudden changes, but I guess it becomes a positive reaction instead of negative. Kind of like how tickling stems from pain is what I'm guessing, and how people like horror movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-26 08:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you can put purple in without rebleaching :) it would be different if you wanted to go, say, pink. but you could go purple or aqua-green really easily. 

there's some other tips out there. some people recommend dying every 1-2 weeks... it's easier because you can put the blue over your black hair and it won't dye it. you can rinse out with vinegar to keep from fading. you can also mix the dye with a conditioner to keep in your hair while you shower. 


also, dark pillowcases!


i love hair dye :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-19 21:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it? His recipe is still [here](http://www.foodnetwork.com/recipes/alton-brown/beef-jerky-recipe/index.html). I don't remember what was in the 2nd half, but that's all you really need to know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-19 06:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw his stuff through Gallery 1988's newsletter, too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-19 01:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even cheaper is using a box fan instead of a dehydrator. [Alton Brown explains.](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rIK4DVLHf7Y) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-14 12:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i don't know if it's just me, but she looks like michelle from skins too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-01 23:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> trying to recover from anorexia nervosa right now (and always). this one quote my nutritionist said sticks with me:

"Telling someone with an eating disorder to eat is like telling someone in a wheelchair to get up and walk."

other addictions, in my opinion, get easier with time. i'm not so sure this is the same for anorexia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-27 17:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is what kept me from learning how to drive, although i finally did a year ago. it was especially sneezing i was afraid of. i get too much anxiety in a two-lane. too much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-23 21:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the same is happening to me right now. i had $4k out of high school, but in less than a year, got down to under $100 (from no job). finally got myself a job, and my bank account is $600-ish. this is with my parents helping me, too, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-05 00:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to gain weight as well, and see a nutritionist.  There are a lot of great ideas here that I'll keep in mind (thanks again, Reddit!)

I eventually got really tired of eating nuts and avocados and heavy things, so I recently found that juice is helpful.  A glass of juice can have as many calories as milk (just not as much protein).  Eating a lot can get tiring, at least for me, so variety is the most important thing. 

I recently got a crockpot, too.  Throw in a bunch of beans, seasoning (bouillon, curry spices, etc), eat it with some rice. Cheap as all hell. Mixed beans, lentils, split peas... throwing in frozen veggies are an easy way to make it interesting, too. Meats are delicious and everything, but I find that they aren't a lot of calories for it's price/hassle.

I also drink generic Ensure Plus (350 cals per 8oz). It can seem expensive (I think $1-2 per bottle) but the amount of calories is worth it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-22 04:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i agree. i got mine a couple years ago. i don't remember it being a painful experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-20 06:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it can still be obsessive-compulsive behavior. not a disorder, but this can still be a (small) part of OCD/OCPD.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-17 06:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have difficulty eating, and i'm trying to gain weight. more sugar in my diet is actually "good" for me, since sugar is still an energy source. it's more nutritious than nothing. fruit juice, for me, is better/healthier than water.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-12 20:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i thought the same thing, specifically with the stars and rainbows. i love stars and rainbows! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-05 06:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's where he must have gone after [eating the cat treats](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B8ISzf2pryI). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-04 01:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sort-of source: john green and his brother, hank, make videos under the name "vlogbrothers". they have a big following. very possibly real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-03 18:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have it too, and you don't have to have any symptoms to be diagnosed. i've never weighed over 110 pounds. ultrasound+blood test is enough, as it was for me. it could have been that they never caught it, and it was only made worse by the weight. also, the fact that when sufferers lose weight, their symptoms also go away also says something. in any case, the disorder sucks. good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-03 09:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PCOS isn't developed by weight gain. the symptoms are only exacerbated by the weight gain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-03 06:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> same with hawaii. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-01 07:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my boyfriend has a vision of the coasts and canada joining to become "americanada" and the rest becoming "jesus land". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-01 07:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i took it for a few months. it was great. i stopped because i have a fast heart rate, to which i haven't found out why. i'm also on wellbutrin (stimulant) now, and cutting down. 

just for some background: i'm also on lamictal, birth control, buspar, and take xanax and klonopin as needed. i was on lexapro when i was on adderall (instead of wellbutrin+buspar). i would say adderall and lamictal have helped me the most. 

the first week or so, your body will feel the effects more, in a high kind of way, as previously described. your body will get used to it. 

the best part of it for me was to find out which of my behaviors were related to ADHD. for instance, a lot of my irritability went away. a lot of tension and anxiety went away. that's why i loved it the most. i only took 10mg every morning, and 5mg when i felt i needed it during the evening. it still didn't help me read. i'm assuming that's behavioral.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
