<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5711</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 06:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes cats make people fat because dog people go for walks ( FYI i LOVE cats i have 1 but i have 2 dogs)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 04:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when they say that people must find fat woman attractive but they will only date fit men  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 01:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well they might be setting them selves up for failure just so they can say that it doesn't work also i find that a lot of obese people want to have anorexia ( i do know that overweight people can develop anorexia but they won't stay obese due to the fact that anorexia will make you lose LOTS of weight).
also they think that its a quick fix oh if i don't eat for 2 days ( YAY right) then i can eat all i want for the next 3 weeks because it will equal out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 01:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I Don't care about spelling make me a mod :) hehehe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Meta] Fatlogic Contradictions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 01:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 01:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes i will add that eating 0 calories 2 times a week won't make up for the 5000 you eat on the other days. But specifically i meant if you weighed your self then didn't eat for 2 days and were exercising you could not then weight your self and have put on weight. if that makes any sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 01:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the doctors and science are very clear its not possible to not lose weight it you go days with out eating ( EAT LESS+ MOVE MORE= LOSE WEIGHT) it is scientific law when it comes to weight loss. 
so when people say they can go days with out eating and they exercise all the time but still gain weight they are lying. you would lose at least water weight you CAN NOT put on weight if your putting in less calories then you are burning. Sorry fat logic you cant and she wants so much to know its not her fault but it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 00:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YAY dick jokes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 00:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should try therapy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 00:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so it smells like smoke? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 05:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOVE LOVE LOVE to be a mod I'm on like 24/7. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 02:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Facebook has lead to an increase in depression among young adults and teens.

people are also developing FOMO and that is fear of missing out 

look it up its true  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 02:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Murica

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 01:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NASTY!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 01:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't care what people say about oh i eat only lettuce and i never stop working out but i still weigh 500 pounds.

NO matter what you say if you are eating LESS calories then your BURNING you will not gain weight its not scientifically possible.

don't care what you say is wrong with you thyroid problems only cause maybe 50 pound weight gain and medications from a DR will reverse that 
as well there are NO conditions (apart from fat logic) that make it IMPOSSIBLE to lose weight just more difficult. BOTH my parents are doctors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 01:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i cant she moved across the country for me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just try to give a shit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 01:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my partner has ZERO empathy for me if i get hurt all she says is " Well i didn't feel it" her exact words. There are times when i just need to cry and i get told to stop it and I'm acting like a child.
if I'm cold she says " well I'm not so i don't know why you are" as if i have to be warm because she is.

this is just a few examples of what happened in the last 2 days  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-05 00:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> could you have been drunk 
maybe you sleep walk 
were you drugged 

there really are thousands of possibilities

ALIENS  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-04 22:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i agree with it being really expensive but with an obesity epidemic do people really need pizza. HAHAHA just kidding try looking up pita pizza recipes they are super fun and taste so good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-04 21:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i just don't see anything wrong with hating a spacific group everyone does hating black people just has a name 
everyone hates everyone thats just how the world works i am never mean to black person never in my life i simply choose not to be friends with them or place my self around them on purpose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-04 03:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i am racist  (there is NOTHING wrong with that ) and i chose to apply to different housing on the grounds of different religion and beliefs i got moved in a few days 

its not worth it to stay there if your not happy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Hate the sound of guitars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-04 03:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-03 22:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok thats it  i am officially mad I'm sick and tired of TITP and FA people getting mad at woman because they look good every single picture of someone thinner then them in bashed into non existence  now who the FUCK is body shaming.
How dare get to flaunt around your FAT( that is a term you like right) body and tell us that we HAVE to love it and then a thin woman posts a picture of something  she WORKED for and you treat her like shit.
Go FUCK yourselves  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-03 21:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yea sorry i have a voice recognition softwere program and its really bad at punctuation sorry.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-03 21:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i always forced my self to have sex to make her happy but then i just couldn't make my self do it anymore. i began to feel violated because i really didn't want to do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-03 21:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have tried for years to enjoy it and have fun and feel good but it doesn't not for me anyways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-03 21:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes only because i am a very emotional person and i think you cant have sex with out emotion i just think that sex is a waste of my time  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-03 21:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there is no injury or illness i just really hate sex  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-03 21:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have been told i cant be asexual because i like to kiss and make out once or twice a year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-03 21:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> because i really do love my wife but i just don't like physical relationships  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-02 00:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was the White pride website called i would really love to know?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I HATE sex </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-01 23:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have had sex with about 6 different people in 6 years men and woman 
and i have NEVER liked sex ever 
i don't think its fun i don't think it feels good i am currently married to a woman and she thinks i don't find her attractive because we don't have sex anymore but in reality i do think she is very attractive and sexy but  i only have sex when it gets to annoying to handle her begging anymore
i want to kiss and cuddle but other then that i don't want to be touched. 

P.S i am a female and i am 20 and no i have not been sexually abused   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-30 02:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its odd that you have an ED i have severe anorexia maybe theres something about having mental illnesses yourself makes you need to take care of other people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-30 02:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do you mind if i ask how you dealt with it 
and or what came of it sorry if thats to personal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You Have No More Options </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-29 23:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My S.O has a lot of mental health problems she's always telling me that one one will help her the problem is we cant help her anymore she will not take ANY medication even if it helps and it does 

she REFUSES counselling or therapy and will not even consider going and so the doctors place her in the hospital she then stays for a few days then lies her way out.

then she gets really angry that no one will help her and gloating that she was right and they won't do anything for her.

she just doesn't realize that there are NO MORE options for her 

she won't take any help thats offered and does not see that they are giving every option they had and you won't exempt any of it.
P.S i have a software that types for me do to a physical disability and its really messed up with punctuation so i apologize its all messed up  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-29 05:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i agree so much but then i sound even more like a dick  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-29 04:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i am right there with you trust me 
but my girlfriend ( yes we are both girls hahaha) thinks its funny as hell to torment me about it i cant really say much to make you feel better but its nice to no that your not alone here  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suicide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-29 03:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i don't think we should stop people from killing them selves i mean its there life

why should we stop them from doing what ever they want 

i have a S.O that is constantly suicidal and theres nothing i can do about it other then tell her what to live for but ultimately thats all i can do 

( and yes i have REALLY tried to get her help but she turned down medication and won't take it 
refuses counselling and hospitals won't take her seriously anymore because they just admit her she lies then gets out and does it all over again oh ya then gets mad that no one will help her) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-28 04:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes i believe that all fast food should be illegal or you should get a card once a month that you must pay for it and every time you buy fast food it should be stamped with no more then 5 a month  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fat shaming </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-28 04:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i LOVE to fat shame i devote about 6 hours a day to fat shaming 
and because i hate fat people so much i actually keep myself 99LBS at 5feet6inches 
if i see that your overweight or obese i will shame 
and thats NOT a crime </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-28 03:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> because pot is just as bad as smoking it still cause lung cancer and people say that pot is good for you but they thought that about smoking for over a century and then they realized that its bad for you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-28 03:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes as a matter of fact yes they should be  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pot should stay illegal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-28 02:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no i don't believe that it should be legalized i think that everyone who smokes it should go to jail and that liquor should also be illegal  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-27 03:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i consider it a confession because people say to me that i am encouraging Eating disorders amongst kids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obese child </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-27 00:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will not let my child be fat every i cant allow it i will do anything to prevent it from happening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
