<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9229</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> National Guard and Cancer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 23:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Warning. Medical stuff ahead. So fuck me right? I recently visited a civilian doctor in regards to a growth on my testicle. The doctors are 95% sure it is cancerous. Fuck. I recently joined the National Guard (September 2014) and haven't even gone to Basic or AIT yet (I ship out in a few months).  I've been at an RSP unit since September. They say it is a easily treatable form of cancer and that I should be fine, but all I care about is if it will force me to get medically discharged? I planned on doing ROTC at my college and going active duty after that as well so will this have any effect on that? My MOS is 31B if that changes anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Build Help] H440 Case Fans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 22:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a way to attach the fan hub to the motherboard to control the fans rather than having them t speed 100% just attached to the PSU?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Build Help] H440 Fan Hub </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 01:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm rehooking up my fans after doing a bit of cable management with their wires and was wondering if it matters which slot I hook each fan up to. Does it matter which I hook the molex up to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Build Help] PCs and the Cold </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 23:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I bough my parts on Friday and they started to arrive today. First off, holy fuck, these part are massive. I was expecting smaller sized parts but ATX parts are massive. My GPU alone is half the size of my old desktop. That leads me to my question, My pats were sitting out in the cold do a few hours as far as I can tell. Will this hurt them in any way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [USA-OH][H]Paypal [W] SATA 3.0 cable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 19:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought a HDD and it doesn't have a SATA cable and I need one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A quick question about performace </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 04:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I just bought a Sapphire R9 290 as my first GPU and I was curious if anyone else here has the same card and could give me an idea of how it runs Fo3 and NV. Obviously it should kill both games, but does anyone have any benchmarks and FPS readings? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Build Help] XFX DD R9 290 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 03:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been doing a lot of research on this card, but was wondering If anyone could post their experience with it. It's currently $250-$30 on Newegg and I'm extremely tempted to buy it. Mainly I have heard that it's cooler sucks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [USA-OH][H]Paypal, $250 Amazon Credit [W] R9 290/290x or GTX 980 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 19:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazon + PayPal for a GTX 980 to be clear. Sorry for any confusion. I'd also do just Amazon or just PayPal or a combo of both for a 290.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Build Ready] Here we go, my build is finalized (again) hopefully for the last time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 22:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was hoping some of y'all could look over my build. I had a build all set up with SLI GTX970's but the VRAM issue turned me off to it. I have since decided to go with a single GTX980 and SLI it with another GTX980 or a GTX980Ti (if it will ever exist) in the future. I have explored my options with other cards, namely the AMD R9 290(X) in Crossfire, but have settled on the GTX980, with plans to SLI with it in the future. For now, it will be run off of a 1080p 60Htz HDTV, so its definitely overkill, but I plan on upgrading to a 1440p or 4K monitor in the future, and will probably SLI at the same time. My main goal was to run games at 1080p and ~70 fps. 

[PCPartPicker part list](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/3rZB99) / [Price breakdown by merchant](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/3rZB99/by_merchant/)

Type|Item|Price
:----|:----|:----
**CPU** | [Intel Core i7-4790 3.6GHz Quad-Core Processor](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/intel-cpu-bx80646i74790) | Purchased For $255.00 
**CPU Cooler** | [Cooler Master Hyper 212 EVO 82.9 CFM Sleeve Bearing CPU Cooler](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/cooler-master-cpu-cooler-rr212e20pkr2) | $28.75 @ OutletPC 
**Thermal Compound** | [Arctic Silver 5 High-Density Polysynthetic Silver 3.5g Thermal Paste](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/arctic-silver-thermal-paste-as535g) | $6.90 @ Amazon 
**Motherboard** | [ASRock Z97 EXTREME6 ATX LGA1150 Motherboard](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/asrock-motherboard-z97extreme6) | $141.98 @ Newegg 
**Memory** | [G.Skill Ripjaws X Series 8GB (1 x 8GB) DDR3-1600 Memory](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/gskill-memory-f31600c9s8gxm) | $60.30 @ Newegg 
**Storage** | [Crucial MX100 256GB 2.5" Solid State Drive](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/crucial-internal-hard-drive-ct256mx100ssd1) | $104.99 @ Adorama 
**Storage** | [Seagate Barracuda 1TB 3.5" 7200RPM Internal Hard Drive](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/seagate-internal-hard-drive-st1000dm003) | $48.88 @ OutletPC 
**Video Card** | [MSI GeForce GTX 980 4GB Twin Frozr Video Card](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/msi-video-card-gtx980gaming4g) | $549.99 @ SuperBiiz 
**Power Supply** | [EVGA 750W 80+ Gold Certified Fully-Modular ATX Power Supply](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/evga-power-supply-220g20750xr) | $80.99 @ NCIX US 
**Operating System** | [Microsoft Windows 8.1 (OEM) (64-bit)](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/microsoft-os-wn700615) | $89.75 @ OutletPC 
**Wireless Network Adapter** | [TP-Link TL-WN881ND 802.11b/g/n PCI-Express x1 Wi-Fi Adapter](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/tp-link-wireless-network-card-tlwn881nd) | $18.78 @ OutletPC 
**Other**| Custom H440 White/Blue w/ 3x Noctua fans and stock fans| $110.00 
 | | **Total**
 | Prices include shipping, taxes, and discounts when available | $1496.31
 | Generated by PCPartPicker 2015-02-02 15:59 EST-0500 |

**CPU** 

I got this CPU for a fairly good price over at /r/hardwareswap. I was originally going to use a i5 4690k, but since I wasn't ever planning on OCing, I went with the  i7. Plus it's hyperthreading will be used for engineering stuff.

**Motherboard**

I chose this motherboard because it matches my color scheme I am going for and has more than enough of the features I'll need.

**Memory**

I went with 8gb since I'm on a budget and couldn't fit any more in. I chose 1x8 so I have more room to upgrade in the future. I know 2x4 would be better performance but I want to be able to upgrade to 32gb later to use some as a Ram disk.

**Storage**

Pretty standard stuff. I chose a well reviewed 256gb SSD and a well review 1 TB HDD. It is more than enough space for me. 

**GPU**

Its expensive, but its a great card. I chose the MSI Twin Frozr GTX980 since it has the best all round performance. I love how it shuts off  its fans when its idle. Probably not the best price-wise but I think its worth it

**PSU**

Its a well reviewed PSU and is just enough for SLI GTX980's

**OS**

Doesn't really matter what I have since I'll be upgrading to Windows 10 when it is released. 

**Wireless Network Adapter**

Its cheap and allows me to use Wi-Fi. 

**Case**

I have arranged with a guy on /r/hardwareswap to buy this case and 3x Noctua NF F-12 case fans for $110. (Case $70 + Fans $40). Very good deal for me IMO. 



Should be a beast of a build. Probably a bit overkill and it just barely fits in my price range.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Build Help] MSI GTX 980 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 20:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I take off the fan shroud on the MSI twin Frozr? I'm trying to go with a blue and white build, but the card is red and I'd like to paint it blue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Help] OHP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 17:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I do OHP and bring the bar to the back of my neck instead of my chest? It seems to work my shoulders better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Build Help] crossfire sapphire Tri-x 290x or MSI Twin Frozr GTX 980 (and SLI later) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 00:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a bit torn. Cost isn't really an issue, but I would like to spend as little as possible for great performance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WTS]Guns and Gear (Prices Reduced) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 18:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Hey y'all I'm trying to finance a new computer so I'm selling most of my airsoft stuff.

[**Pics**](http://imgur.com/a/dyCjY)


I have my baby that I hate to get rid of, but sadly never really got a chance to use and as such has less than 300 rounds shot through it. It is a custom built **Colt Commando (basically a fixed carry handle M4)** based on the rifle carried by Delta operator Gary Gordon in the Battle of Mogadishu (Black Hawk Down incident). Internally, it has a reshimmed G amp;amp;P gearbox and a 6.03mm tightbore.It also has a brand new SHS hop up and bucking. This thinks shoots insanely well. It is full metal and comes with a mock suppressor, a Surefire Scout Mini (and two batteries), a Red Dot scope (with red/green and multiple dot styles to choose from) a 300rd high cap, and an 11.1v lipo. This thing shoots lasers with the 11.1v and it can easily out range most other AEGs. It shoot ~375-390 fps


**I am asking ~~$250 shipped OBO Now $175+shipping**~~ **Now $145+ shipping** Does not come with Surefire. It was parted out and sold. 



I have a brand new **CYMA M14 Socom** in black. This thing was never used and has had less than 200 rounds shot through it. It was literally opened, tested  to make sure it worked and then never used again. It comes with one high cap magazine. The red dot sight in the pictures is not included. It has a battery, but one of the wires got pulled out, so it needs reattached. It shoots ~340 fps.


**I'm asking ~~$100 OBO.~~ Now $70+ shipping**


Next up we have the gear.


First up, I have a real steel PASGT helmet in large. It was used by the US military from the late 70's up until recently. It has all the suspension and chin strap stuff needed. It is in excellent condition. They usually sell for around $90-100. I'll throw in a helmet liner in M-81 as well if you want it.


**Asking ~~$65 OBO~~ 50+ ship**


Last, I have a real steel M-81 PASGT flak vest in small. I'm 6'3" and this fits me perfectly. This vest is rated to stop up to a .44 magnum round. It was also used by the US military. One of the shoulders had a small tear, but it was fixed. These usually sell for around $80-90


**Asking ~~$55 OBO.~~ Sold**


Miscellaneous Items


**Echo-1 Stag-15 plastic body $10 .20 G amp;amp;G BBs (1kg) $10 **


**Speedloader x 2 free with the purchase of an aeg or PASGT component- just tell me**


**M100 spring-unused $7 3-9x Scope $20**


All prices are OBO and I may part out. Prices do not include shipping (again I'm open to offers for price if mine are too high) Trades are PC parts or more airsoft stuff


I also have some ALICE gear if anyone is interested, but unsure if I really want to sell it, I have LC-2 suspenders and a LBV along with tons of mag, canteen, and butt pouches </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Build Help] Sapphire R9 290 Tri-X </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 04:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the opportunity to pick up one of these for pretty cheap ($220 shipped) but I am unable to find any performance reports on the card. Any help? Or any anecdotal help? Will this card run 1080p @ 60fps? What about 4k in crossfire? I'm a bit lost since my build was going to use a 970 until recently. I have no clue about AMD cards.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [USA-OH][H]Paypal[W]R9 290/290x </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 19:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [USA-OH] [H] PayPal [W] Corsair C70, 8-16 GB Ram (Blue), GTX 970 or 980 (Gigabyte G1 Windforce preferred) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 02:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [W]Stock Intel i7 cooler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 01:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wondering if anyone has one laying around they don't want. I can pay for shipping  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [USA-OH][H]Paypal, [W] Cheap PC Case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 23:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking to spend around $30-50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Build Ready] Gaming Build Ready, Critique Wanted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 20:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [PCPartPicker part list](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/WNYz99) / [Price breakdown by merchant](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/WNYz99/by_merchant/)

Type|Item|Price
:----|:----|:----
**CPU** | [Intel Core i7-4790 3.6GHz Quad-Core Processor](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/intel-cpu-bx80646i74790) | Purchased For $0.00 
**CPU Cooler** | [Cooler Master Hyper 212 EVO 82.9 CFM Sleeve Bearing CPU Cooler](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/cooler-master-cpu-cooler-rr212e20pkr2) | $28.75 @ OutletPC 
**Motherboard** | [MSI Z97-G55 SLI ATX LGA1150 Motherboard](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/msi-motherboard-z97g55sli) | $108.99 @ Newegg 
**Memory** | [Corsair Vengeance 16GB (2 x 8GB) DDR3-1600 Memory](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/corsair-memory-cmz16gx3m2a1600c10b) | $135.37 @ Amazon 
**Storage** | [Samsung 840 EVO 250GB 2.5" Solid State Drive](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/samsung-internal-hard-drive-mz7te250bw) | $122.98 @ Newegg 
**Storage** | [Western Digital Caviar Blue 1TB 3.5" 7200RPM Internal Hard Drive](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/western-digital-internal-hard-drive-wd10ezex) | $51.88 @ OutletPC 
**Video Card** | [Gigabyte GeForce GTX 970 4GB WINDFORCE Video Card](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/gigabyte-video-card-gvn970g1gaming4gd) | $358.99 @ NCIX US 
**Case** | [Corsair Vengeance C70 (White) ATX Mid Tower Case](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/corsair-case-cc9011019ww) | $109.99 @ Newegg 
**Power Supply** | [EVGA SuperNOVA 1000G2 1000W 80+ Gold Certified Fully-Modular ATX Power Supply](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/evga-power-supply-120g21000xr) | $109.99 @ Newegg 
**Operating System** | [Microsoft Windows 8.1 (OEM) (64-bit)](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/microsoft-os-wn700615) | $89.98 @ OutletPC 
**Wireless Network Adapter** | [TP-Link TL-WDN4800 802.11a/b/g/n PCI-Express x1 Wi-Fi Adapter](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/tp-link-wireless-network-card-tlwdn4800) | $38.75 @ OutletPC 
 | | **Total**
 | Prices include shipping, taxes, and discounts when available | $1155.67
 | Generated by PCPartPicker 2015-01-22 14:24 EST-0500 |



I bought the i7 on an impulse for $240, which I think was a more than fair price. I was going to use a i5-4690. but got this for only a few bucks more.

I'm hoping to run games at 1080p or better and 60+ FPS which I don't think will be any problem at all. Can anyone who has a similar setup give some idea of what it'll run at?

Anyway I can make it cheaper without changing the specs of the CPU, GPU, and Ram? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Build Help] I7 4790 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 03:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm about to purchase a i7 4790 because I'm getting it for $20 more than a i5 4690k (what I planned to use). Is this a good deal and is it worth it? Can I use it later if I want to overclock? Is it better than the 4690k? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [USA-OH][USA-OH] Heavy Duty PC case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 23:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [USA-OH] [H] PayPal. [W] i5 4690k, i7 4790k, or better CPU, Liquid CPU cooler, 750w PSU, GTX 970/980, SLI:Crossfire capable z97 MoBo, 2-4x8GB Ram, </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 20:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgot the country/state the first time. So this is the correct post now. 

Edit: I actually need a 1000+W PSU not a 750W </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Paypal [W] i5 4690k or i7 4790k and Liquid CPU cooler, cheap 2x8GB RAM, 750w PSU </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 20:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WTS/WTT] Guns and Accessories and Mil-Surp Items </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 22:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello y'all. Today I have some items to sell. I guess this is my getting out of airsoft sale sadly, since I am selling most of my stuff to finance a new computer. Speaking of which, trades are for PC parts from this list or any 1080p/4k monitors/keyboards/mice

http://imgur.com/a/dyCjY

[PCPartPicker part list](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/pYMGt6) / [Price breakdown by merchant](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/pYMGt6/by_merchant/)

Type|Item|Price
:----|:----|:----
**CPU** | [Intel Core i5-4690K 3.5GHz Quad-Core Processor](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/intel-cpu-bx80646i54690k) | $219.88 @ OutletPC 
**CPU Cooler** | [Cooler Master Hyper 212 EVO 82.9 CFM Sleeve Bearing CPU Cooler](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/cooler-master-cpu-cooler-rr212e20pkr2) | $28.75 @ OutletPC 
**Motherboard** | [Asus Z97-A ATX LGA1150 Motherboard](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/asus-motherboard-z97a) | $128.99 @ NCIX US 
**Memory** | [Corsair Vengeance 8GB (1 x 8GB) DDR3-1866 Memory](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/corsair-memory-cmz8gx3m1a1866c10) | $82.99 @ Newegg 
**Memory** | [Corsair Vengeance 8GB (1 x 8GB) DDR3-1866 Memory](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/corsair-memory-cmz8gx3m1a1866c10) | $82.99 @ Newegg 
**Storage** | [Sandisk Ultra II 240GB 2.5" Solid State Drive](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/sandisk-internal-hard-drive-sdssdhii240gg25) | $103.77 @ OutletPC 
**Storage** | [Seagate Barracuda 1TB 3.5" 7200RPM Internal Hard Drive](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/seagate-internal-hard-drive-st1000dm003) | $49.88 @ OutletPC 
**Video Card** | [Gigabyte GeForce GTX 970 4GB WINDFORCE Video Card](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/gigabyte-video-card-gvn970g1gaming4gd) | $359.99 @ Amazon 
**Case** | [Corsair Vengeance C70 (Black) ATX Mid Tower Case](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/corsair-case-cc9011016ww) | $129.76 @ OutletPC 
**Power Supply** | [EVGA SuperNOVA NEX 750W 80+ Gold Certified Fully-Modular ATX Power Supply](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/evga-power-supply-120g10750xr) | $79.99 @ Newegg 
**Operating System** | [Microsoft Windows 8.1 (OEM) (64-bit)](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/microsoft-os-wn700615) | $89.98 @ OutletPC 
**Wireless Network Adapter** | [TP-Link TL-WN881ND 802.11b/g/n PCI-Express x1 Wi-Fi Adapter](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/tp-link-wireless-network-card-tlwn881nd) | $19.98 @ OutletPC 
 | | **Total**
 | Prices include shipping, taxes, and discounts when available | $1376.95
 | Generated by PCPartPicker 2015-01-11 15:22 EST-0500 |

On to the guns.
I have my baby that I hate to get rid of, but sadly never really got a chance to use. It is a custom built Colt Commando based on the rifle carried by Delta operator Gary Gordon in the Battle of Mogadishu (Black Hawk Down incident). Internally, it has a reshimmed G amp;P gearbox and a 6.03mm tightbore. It is full metal and comes with a mock suppressor, a Surefire Scout Mini (and two batteries), a Red Dot scope (with red/green and multiple dot styles to choose from) a 300rd high cap, and an 11.1v lipo. This thing shoots lasers with the 11.1v and it can easily out range most other AEGs for some unknown reason. It shoot ~375-390 fps

I am asking $250 shipped OBO

Next up is my ICS Full Metal MP5. It is in good condition, with the only problem being that the selector switch is a little loose. It still functions fine and won't move unless you try and move it. It just doesn't click into place very well. It shoots ~330-350 fps. It comes with the red dot sight currently pictured on the M14 in the pictures, a Tokyo Marui claw style rail for the red dot, a railed handguard, a laser, 4 magazines, and a bunch of miscellaneous parts. 

I'm asking **SOLD**

Lastly, I have a nearly new CYMA M14 Socom in black. This thing was never used and has had less than 200 rounds shot through it. It was literally opened and then never used again. It comes with one high cap magazine. The red dot sight in the pictures is not included. It has a battery, but one of the wires got pulled out, so it needs reattached. It shoots ~340 fps.

I'm asking $100 OBO.

Next up we have the gear.

First up, I have a real steel PASGT helmet in large. It was used by the US military from the late 70's up until recently. It has all the suspension and chin strap stuff needed. It is in excellent condition. They usually sell for around $90-100. I'll throw in a helmet liner in M-81 as well if you want it.

Asking $65 OBO

Last, I have a real steel M-81 PASGT flak vest in small. I'm 6'3" and this fits me perfectly. This vest is rated to stop up to a .44 magnum round. It was also used by the US military. One of the shoulders had a small tear, but it was fixed. These usually sell for around $80-90

Asking $55 OBO. 

Miscellaneous Items

Echo-1 Stag-15 plastic body   $10
.20 G amp;G BBs (1kg)   $10
Speedloader x 2  free with the purchase of an aeg or PASGT component- just tell me     
M100 spring-unused   $7
3-9x Scope   $20

All prices are OBO and I may part out.
Prices do not include shipping (again I'm open to offers for price if mine are too high)
Trades are PC parts or more airsoft stuff 

I also have some ALICE gear if anyone is interested, but unsure if I really want to sell it, I have LC-2 suspenders and a LBV
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Build Ready] My First Build-Take 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 23:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I changed a few things around (actually a lot of things) and I need some critique before I pull the trigger on this build. My main goal is to run modern games at least at 1080p w/ ~60fps. I'm fairly certain it will, but will this build do that? 

 [PCPartPicker part list](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/vzxhdC) / [Price breakdown by merchant](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/vzxhdC/by_merchant/)

Type|Item|Price
:----|:----|:----
**CPU** | [Intel Core i5-4690K 3.5GHz Quad-Core Processor](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/intel-cpu-bx80646i54690k) | $218.98 @ OutletPC 
**CPU Cooler** | [Cooler Master Hyper 212 EVO 82.9 CFM Sleeve Bearing CPU Cooler](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/cooler-master-cpu-cooler-rr212e20pkr2) | $28.75 @ OutletPC 
**Motherboard** | [Asus Z97-A ATX LGA1150 Motherboard](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/asus-motherboard-z97a) | $129.99 @ Amazon 
**Memory** | [Corsair Vengeance 8GB (1 x 8GB) DDR3-1866 Memory](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/corsair-memory-cmz8gx3m1a1866c10) | $62.99 @ Newegg 
**Memory** | [Corsair Vengeance 8GB (1 x 8GB) DDR3-1866 Memory](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/corsair-memory-cmz8gx3m1a1866c10) | $62.99 @ Newegg 
**Storage** | [Sandisk Ultra II 240GB 2.5" Solid State Drive](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/sandisk-internal-hard-drive-sdssdhii240gg25) | $103.77 @ OutletPC 
**Storage** | [Seagate Barracuda 1TB 3.5" 7200RPM Internal Hard Drive](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/seagate-internal-hard-drive-st1000dm003) | $49.88 @ OutletPC 
**Video Card** | [Gigabyte GeForce GTX 970 4GB WINDFORCE Video Card](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/gigabyte-video-card-gvn970g1gaming4gd) | $359.99 @ Amazon 
**Case** | [Corsair Vengeance C70 (Black) ATX Mid Tower Case](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/corsair-case-cc9011016ww) | $109.99 @ Amazon 
**Power Supply** | [SeaSonic 750W 80+ Gold Certified Fully-Modular ATX Power Supply](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/seasonic-power-supply-ss750km) | $129.99 @ Newegg 
**Wireless Network Adapter** | [TP-Link TL-WN881ND 802.11b/g/n PCI-Express x1 Wi-Fi Adapter](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/tp-link-wireless-network-card-tlwn881nd) | $19.22 @ Amazon 
 | | **Total**
 | Prices include shipping, taxes, and discounts when available | $1276.54
 | Generated by PCPartPicker 2015-01-08 17:24 EST-0500 |

I am also not planning on overclocking at this time, but I chose the i5-4690K because I probably will in the future and having the cpu unlocked is better IMO. My main concern is the cooler I chose. I do not know if it will be able to handle the increase during overclocking. Will it to maybe to 4.0-4.5ghz?

I chose the Asus MoBo mainly because it was cheapish and is SLI capable. I plan to buy a second GPU in the future. I don't see anything that could interfere with the build in regards to this motherboard, but does anyone see anything?

The GPU I chose is kinda straightforward. Its a Gigabyte G1 Windforce. No foreseen problems here, as I made sure it will fit in my case. 

Speaking of cases, I chose the Corsair Vengeance C70 in Black. I wanted something that looked heavy duty and military-esque and this fit the bill perfectly. My main gripe is there are only two USB ports on the front, but that's a minor issue.

I chose 16GB of ram because I like to overcompensate. Pretty much the only reason.

Same with the PSU I chose. Overcompensation. I probably don't need 750w, but I'm going to SLI in the future, so I guess its better to buy one powerful enough now so I dont't have to spend more in the future.

I chose a well rated SSD and a good 1 TB HDD for storage. I probably won't need that much space. My current laptop has a 250GB HDD and I haven't even filled it halfway in the five years I've had it. 

Last of all, I need the wi-fi card because I am too far away from my router to hook up directly. 

Before I pull the trigger, does anyone see any glaring issues or problems? 
Will I need any more wires?

Are the C70's stock case fans good enough?

Should I switch to a CPU water cooler? I was looking at Corsairs liquid cpu coolers, but I'm unsure. Plus my case has a spot on top for a radiator and it feels like a shame to let it go unused. 

Anyone know wher I can get 8gb RAM sticks cheaper? I couldn't find any.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Build Ready]My First Build. Unsure if it's correct </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 01:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is going to be my first build and I put this parts list together. I am unsure if I should do anything different and I need critique. My budget is/was $1400. Anyone have any changes to make it cheaper? My goal is to play games at 1080p @~60fps

[PCPartPicker part list](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/VVxXdC) / [Price breakdown by merchant](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/VVxXdC/by_merchant/)

Type|Item|Price
:----|:----|:----
**CPU** | [Intel Core i5-4690K 3.5GHz Quad-Core Processor](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/intel-cpu-bx80646i54690k) | $219.99 @ SuperBiiz 
**Motherboard** | [ASRock H97 PRO4 ATX LGA1150 Motherboard](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/asrock-motherboard-h97pro4) | $83.99 @ SuperBiiz 
**Memory** | [Team Zeus Blue 8GB (2 x 4GB) DDR3-1600 Memory](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/team-memory-tzbd38g1600hc9dc01) | $67.97 @ OutletPC 
**Memory** | [Team Zeus Blue 8GB (2 x 4GB) DDR3-1600 Memory](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/team-memory-tzbd38g1600hc9dc01) | $67.97 @ OutletPC 
**Storage** | [Samsung 850 EVO-Series 120GB 2.5" Solid State Drive](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/samsung-internal-hard-drive-mz75e120bam) | $89.99 @ Micro Center 
**Storage** | [Seagate Barracuda 1TB 3.5" 7200RPM Internal Hard Drive](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/seagate-internal-hard-drive-st1000dm003) | $49.88 @ OutletPC 
**Video Card** | [Gigabyte GeForce GTX 970 4GB WINDFORCE 3X Video Card](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/gigabyte-video-card-gvn970wf3oc4gd) | $339.99 @ Amazon 
**Case** | [Corsair C70 Military Green (Green) ATX Mid Tower Case](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/corsair-case-c70militarygreen) | $114.99 @ Micro Center 
**Power Supply** | [EVGA SuperNOVA 1000G2 1000W 80+ Gold Certified Fully-Modular ATX Power Supply](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/evga-power-supply-120g21000xr) | $162.98 @ OutletPC 
**Operating System** | [Microsoft Windows 8.1 (OEM) (64-bit)](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/microsoft-os-wn700615) | $89.98 @ OutletPC 
 | | **Total**
 | Prices include shipping, taxes, and discounts when available | $1287.73
 | Generated by PCPartPicker 2015-01-06 19:14 EST-0500 | </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Gun Purchase </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 04:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not new to firearms by any means. I've grown up around them and shooting them. That being said, I'm about to turn 18 in a few days and am looking to get an AK pattern rifle. Currently, I (or rather my father) own a Tikka T3 Lite and a Winchester Hunting Shotgun (they're my firearms but technically are owned by my father since I'm 17). I've mainly used them for hunting and shooting skeet, but now I am looking to get a rifle that's semi automatic and is more of a "modern" rifle than my T3. I was looking at a AK pattern rifle in either .556 or .308 and was wondering if it's possible and if anyone knows where I could get a rifle that takes STANAG mags or 7.62 SR-25/AR mags that's also an AK pattern. I was looking at VEPRs and Saigas and thinking of doing a conversion. Any thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alternate to hyperextensions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 19:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been doing ICF 5x5 and working out at home over the holidays and can't do back hyperextensions. Is there an alternative?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WTB]Non Magazine Molle and/or ALICE Pouches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 03:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for utility pouches and misc. pouches. Not sure what I want, so offer away. I prefer any solid colors, Tri color desert or M-81 woodland. Anything other than digital camouflages and multicam are fine as well. 

Also looking for a hydration pack still, one that can hold gear as well as the reservoir. Something like a MBSS/MAP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Wtb] Molle Hydration Pack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 04:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for something similar to an MBSS or MAP pack. Does not have to be specifically hydration, just a pack that can attach to molle vests. Also, anyone know what the name of the medical backpack the assault class in Battlefield 3 uses? I'm also interested in one of those if anyone has one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Welcome to /r/Project_Horizons! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 01:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This subreddit is currently under construction by me, but feel free to post anything related to Project Horizons. The only rule is that it has to be at least slightly relevant. NSFW is allowed, I'm not really picky about what is posted, I want to see what the community wants and give that to them. More rules ma be added in the future as things get going (if they ever do) but for now I,m just here to get the sub going.

Also install better ponymotes if you haven't already, because I haven't set up emotes yet so that'll have to do for now. 
[](/bjshake) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Defender vs. Discovery I/II/III vs. Range Rover Classic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 03:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been looking at Rovers recently and I   am a bit curious to which you think is better for off-road/overland type stuff that can also be used as a daily driver. I live in the USA, so obviously Defenders are few and far between unless I import one, which is a pain in the ass with the 25 year limit. I like the loons of the Defender a lot more than the Discovery, but is there any significant difference in off-road ability, other than the V8 in the Discovery vs. the Diesel in the Defender?    Despite their rarity of parts in the US, I am still leaning toward a Defender because of their Diesel engines and looks, but I cannot find of they are importable into the US with the diesel? 

Also just watched the Top Gear Bolivia special and I was surprised by Clarkson's Range Rover. I never really considered them mainly due to me thinking they were just sissy luxury SUVs, but obviously I was wrong. Any thoughts on them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Running and Gaining </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 15:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should I be eating enough on days I dont lift but run to make up for calories burned running plus 500 over of should I just eat to maintain my weight? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OHARNG RSP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 00:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have my first drill for RSP tomorrow in the OHNG. What should I expect? I've been told what to wear, where to go and when to be there, but I still have little idea of what I'll be doing when I get there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm at MEPS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 00:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I'm looking at jobs. My choices are 11B, 13B, 68W, 25U, and 19H. I'm really interested in 19K since it's a combat job and it has a enlistment bonus and kicker. Any tankers In the guard have any input or reason to do/not to do it?

Edit: actually I chose 31B as that came up as an option. Woo hoo! Enroute to my first day of RSP this weekend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found a 4runner. Have some questions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 02:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a first gen and seems to be in great condition minus some fender damage that was poorly repaired (not a big deal). It also has a rear locker, 35" BFGs, and a rebuilt 22re motor with 5k miles on it. but the owner says that it needs a front axel seal (it has a solid front axel) and a front U- joint installed. He says it still drives in 2w d fine, but I'm worried about the cost and skills needed. Are those difficult parts to install and is that something I can do without any special tools? Also would it be a bad idea to drive it without those parts installed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Off Day + Running Diet Questions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 00:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all, I searched and couldn't find any answers to this. 

My current schedule is lift M/W/F and run 6 miles T/Th/Sat or Sun. On the days that I run, should I be eating TDEE + Calories Burned running + another 500 or should I just eat to maintain? I know it sounds stupid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm currently at MEPS and I have a decision to make </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 11:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Gen Possible Purchase Help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-22 22:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking to get a first gen as my first truck and was wondering if there is anything I need to watch out for. I currently drive a 97 Ford Ranger, but I co-own it with my brother and since I am going off to the army and college, I'm looking to get my own vehicle to be a daily driver and a fun off-road vehicle. 
I really like the design of the first gen with the removable top, but is there any reason I should get a second or third gen  over a first gen? And what do I need to watch out for?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WTB] M4/M16 Upper Assembly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 03:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for a complete full metal upper I could throw on my M4, not really looking for anything specific, and it does not need a hop up or inner barrel. Doesn't matter if it's painted either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help with understanding Guard/ROTC relationship </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 23:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm joining the guard very soon and I'm hoping to go to college and do ROTC at the same time. Should I apply to colleges now as well, or wait until I am in the Guard? Also, do I have to use the GI Bill while in the Guard, or is there a special guard scholarship? I'm hoping to go active duty after college as an officer if that changes anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WRB]Lots of gear. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 05:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My high school cross country team recovers some bad new today... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 02:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We learned that our former coach, who had to resign due to having cancer, passed away this morning after a long struggle with his disease. We all knew that it was coming, but it was never the less a sad day. He loved coaching and the day he had to resign was the only time I had ever see him cry. He was always great at pushing us and making sure we were the best we could be. I never got to say it to him, but thank you coach. Your coaching made me a better runner and a better person. You will be missed by everybody.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WTB] M4 Mags </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 03:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for cheap mid or high cap mags. Doesn't matter how many. Just need them to be standard metal mags.  Not looking to spend a lot. I need them somewhat cheaply.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WTB]Smart Charger and batteries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 00:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for a cheapish smart charger and some batteries that will fit in a buffer tube. Non lipo preferred, unless you also have a charger/discharger to go with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CJ-3B Question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 02:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found a CJ-3B on craigslist for $800. It needs a lot of work, and It doesn't run, but do you think it would be worth it to restore it?

http://columbus.craigslist.org/cto/4667642819.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WTB] ALICE IFAK Pouch, ALICE SAW Pouches, plus more in description </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 04:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for the ALICE first aid pouch that has the hard green plastic container inside it. Also looking for ALICE SAW pouches. I also would like to get any unusual ALICE gear or any gear from the 80's and 90's. USGI issue is a requirement. Not looking for repro gear. Also possibly looking for the M12 holster and pistol magazine pouches that go with it. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WTB]M16A2 or Support weapon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 02:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has to be an A2. Need the fixed carry handle. 

Also looking for an M249 or M60 or M240. Any support weapon really. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WTB]MBSS, MAP, or similar molle pack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 00:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for a pack that can carry hydro and mount to a molle vest. I prefer if it was either black or green, but I'll look at any  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WTB] US military style airsoft gun and L85\86 or any bullpup </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 02:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for any guns used by the US military in the last 30ish years. Preferably a LMG or M4\M16 with a fixed carry handle and no rails but I'll look at anything.  

Also looking for a L85, F2K, or NY other bullpup style rifle that isn't a UAR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boots </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 21:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any of y'all know if tanker boots are authorized? I'm looking to get a pair for field work and wasn't sure because they have straps instead of laces. My current boots get mid everywhere in the field and I'm a bit tired of having to unlace them completely every time something happens to them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WTB] M4 style rifle with fixed carry handle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 03:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Preferably G amp;P but any offers will be looked at. Preferably I need an XM-177E2 or a Colt Model 653 or 727  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help with gun for a retro SF kit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 04:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm putting together a somewhat generic SEAL/CAG kit from the late 80s early 90s and cannot find if I should use an XM-177E2, a Model 733, a Model 653, or any other retro M4.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone in NE Ohio? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 20:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really would like to do airsoft somewhere,  and there are no fields around here that I know of. The closest field is all the way in Mercer, PA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MP5 Selector Issue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 00:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The selector on my ICS MP5A5 functions fine, but is very loose. Would any of you happen to know if there is a fix for this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WtB] MP5 Magazines </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 00:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Preferably high caps because mid caps don't work well in my gun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WTB] Ranger Body Armor or PASGT Vest, preferably with soft and hard armor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 02:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for one of these in woodland for my 90s SEAL/SOF loadout. Real Steel is preferred </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WTB] MP5 Mags and Accessories </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 02:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just traded for an MP5 and am looking to get some magazines. I don't really care what they are as long as they feed in an ICS MP5. Also looking for accessories that are MP5 specific (ie flashlight handguards, rails, scopes, etc)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WTS][WTT] ASGI Custom G4-A3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-14 18:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have my Airsoft Gi G4 I am looking to get rid of. Looking to trade for anything really or sell the gun. I'd really like a US Army style M4 with the KAC RIS. The gun will come with a 300rd high cap and and 450 rd high cap magazine. I can also throw in a battery and a Magpul VFG. 

This gun is in good condition and other than a scratch on the barrel, there is no wear or damage. I currently have it wired to a mag pouch I have attached to the stock, but I can rewire it to the buffer tube if you would like. I also have a full M16 stock I can throw on if you'd like 
The gun chronos ~380 fps. It is currently missing the flashider as well, but I will include an orange birdcage style one with any sale or trade. 

I'm looking to sell for $120 OBO.
Again, I will accept offers for any trades. 

http://i.imgur.com/0Kor46U.jpg

http://i.imgur.com/lhUmByE.jpg

http://i.imgur.com/U1YmTvW.jpg

http://i.imgur.com/5Xxn9My.jpg

http://i.imgur.com/judKnmV.jpg

http://i.imgur.com/Cashdvr.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ WTB] L85/L86 , M249, M60, SCAR, M4, or AK-74 [WTS/WTT] Guns and Gear </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-13 04:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sold my old primary and am looking to pick up a new one of the types in the title. 
Looking to not pay more than $250 but I may make exceptions  so offer away. I'd prefer that the gun works. 

Edit: Also looking to buy/trade for a M16A2 or A3/4
 

Now onto what I am selling and possibly trading. I'll take any offer for these, not just what's listed in the title. 

**Guns**

JG G36C

Pics: http://imgur.com/a/0fZJR [1]

This gun is nearly brand new. It has ~300 rounds through it total. This is the new version that was released shortly before JG among other companies were forced to cease production of H amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;K style airsoft guns due to copyright infringement or something along those lines. It will come with two(2) 350 rd JG high cap magazines.

I will sell for $90 OBO

Cyma M14 SOCOM

Pics: http://i.imgur.com/EZ8XDOG.jpg [2]

This gun is almost brand new as well and has no external issues or internal issues whatsoever. Even the bolt works along with the working bolt release. It shoots ~350 FPS. It will come with one(1) 350 rd Cyma high cap magazine.

I will sell for $100 OBO



**Gear**    pics: http://imgur.com/a/8IYYI

USGI Enhanced Tactical Load Bearing Vest. 
This vest attaches to an ALICE style belt and has four single M16 pouches and two frag pouches permanently attached. ALICE or Molle style pouches can be attached to the included improved ALICE belt

I will sell for $50 OBO



Paraclete RMV in Smoke Green (XL)

This is the plate carrier that was used by Delta/CAG around 2006-2007. It is real steel gear and is brand new. I'm looking to sell because its a little big on me It includes two double mag pouches, a horizontal utility pouch, a quad fold medical pouch, a night vision pouch and a radio pouch. All pouches are in smoke green and manufactured by Paraclete

I'm looking to get $150 for the Plate Carrier and all the pouches included. I will trade for a gun or another Plate Carrier In medium or large. 


**Misc Gear**


9 x ALICE Triple M16 Ammo Pouch  $7/pouch, $2 for the pouch with the frag pockets cut off. Buy all 9 for $50

ALICE Canteen Pouch + USGI Canteen    $8 each

USGI M1956 Canteen Pouch, ALICE Compatible  $5

USGI M1956 Canvas Field Pack  $20 

USGI ALICE Field Pack     $10

Rothco IIFS (this is the vest system the load bearing vest is from) Woodland Field Pouch- ALICE Compatible  $5

ALICE Y-Suspenders and Belt  $15

USMC Vietnam Era M14 Pouches and Belt and Suspenders   $25

Echo 1 Stag-15 Upper and Lower Reciever $15 total for both

Echo 1 M16 Length Outer Barrel and Front Sight  $15

Echo 1 M16A1 handguard. $10

3-9x NC Star Scope     $20

Unknown M4 Mid Cap - $5

Trickle Charger $5

Prices do not include shipping but all prices are OBO
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tweak that let's me use PNG as wallpaper? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-06 18:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back in ios6 it would let me set png images as a wallpaper and resize them so there would be a black background around the image. Now in ios7, it constricts the image to the borders of the image instead of allowing a black background  anyone know of a tweak that will change this back to ios6 style? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WTS][WTT] Guns and Gear </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-05 00:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello y'all and Happy Independence Day. I have a lot of stuff I would like to sell or trade. I'm specifically looking for a VFC or TM SCAR or  any brand M4, I can include cash as well for partial trades. I would also really like some kind of support weapon. I will consider all trades though because this is literally all of my airsoft gear. I have nothing else. I'm trying to start over. Better pictures will be added of specific items if requested. 

**Guns**

JG G36C

Pics: http://imgur.com/a/0fZJR [1]

This gun is nearly brand new. It has ~300 rounds through it total. This is the new version that was released shortly before JG among other companies were forced to cease production of H amp;amp;amp;K style airsoft guns due to copyright infringement or something along those lines. It will come with two(2) 350 rd JG high cap magazines.

I will sell for $100 OBO

Cyma M14 SOCOM

Pics: http://i.imgur.com/EZ8XDOG.jpg [2]

This gun is almost brand new as well and has no external issues or internal issues whatsoever. Even the bolt works along with the working bolt release. It shoots ~350 FPS. It will come with one(1) 350 rd Cyma high cap magazine.

I will sell for $100 OBO

Airsoft GI M4 Custom


I have my ASGI G4 I am looking to sell. Gun has no issues except for a few scuffs on the barrel. I bought it secondhand off of a friend who said he had put a tightbore barrel in it and reshimmed it. The base gun for the G4 series is a G amp;G M4 Combat Machine so this gun has the EBB system in it. I you don't like it, it can easily be disabled. 

I'm looking to sell this for $150 OBO

**Gear**    pics: http://imgur.com/a/8IYYI

USGI Enhanced Tactical Load Bearing Vest. 
This vest attaches to an ALICE style belt and has four single M16 pouches and two frag pouches permanently attached. ALICE or Molle style pouches can be attached to the included improved ALICE belt

I will sell for $50 OBO



Paraclete RMV in Smoke Green (XL)

This is the plate carrier that was used by Delta/CAG around 2006-2007. It is real steel gear and is brand new. I'm looking to sell because its a little big on me It includes two double mag pouches, a horizontal utility pouch, a quad fold medical pouch, a night vision pouch and a radio pouch. All pouches are in smoke green and manufactured by Paraclete

I'm looking to get $150 for the Plate Carrier and all the pouches included


**Misc Gear**

3 Point Sling     $7

9 x ALICE Triple M16 Ammo Pouch  $7/pouch, $2 for the pouch with the frag pockets cut off. Buy all 9 for $50

2x ALICE Canteen Pouch + USGI Canteen    $8 each

USGI M1956 Canteen Pouch, ALICE Compatible  $5

USGI M1956 Canvas Field Pack  $20 

USGI ALICE Field Pack     $10

Rothco IIFS (this is the vest system the load bearing vest is from) Woodland Field Pouch- ALICE Compatible  $5

ALICE Y-Suspenders and Belt  $15

USMC Vietnam Era M14 Pouches and Belt and Suspenders   $25

Echo 1 Stag-15 Upper and Lower Reciever $15 total for both

Echo 1 M16 Length Outer Barrel and Front Sight  $15

Echo 1 M16A1 Handguard   $5

Magpul VFG - missing a screw, attaches fine    $10

3x 8.4V Batteries, brick type    $10/each

3-9x NC Star Scope     $20

G amp;G M4 High Cap - Extended   $6

Unknown M4 Mid Cap - $5

Trickle Charger $5

Prices do not include shipping but all prices are OBO
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gaining while training for cross country </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 03:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do any of you know a good program that is upper body only, 3 days a week? I know that it's generally frowned upon to skip legs, but my times have been increasing ever since I started doing leg workouts. I was focusing on lifting then , but now I need to focus on cross country and let lifting sit on the back burner until XC is over so I need a program that will fit this need. I cannot do my XC program while I am also doing leg workouts because I am often too sore and my legs are too tired when I need to run.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WTB] V2 Gearbox and Motor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 07:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just looking for a gearbox and motor. Has to work in a CA Scar-L, which I don't believe is any different from a normal V2.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WTB] M16 Length inner barrel and M16 Length (12" or more) rail system or handguard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 05:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just got a few new parts for my gun and am looking for a rail or handguard system for my gun. I also need a new inner barrel. I will also take a M16 + suppressor length barrel  if someone sells me a suppressor, which I also need. I'd like to keep it fairly inexpensive,  but if the offers right, I'll take anything. I would really like a DD 12" rail that is used on the M4 Block II </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WTT][WTS] Cyma M14 Socom, JG G36C </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 06:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would really like to get rid of these guns. I have no use for them and all they've done is sit around. I will trade for almost anything if I like it, so offer away. 

**JG G36C**

Pics:  http://imgur.com/a/0fZJR

This gun is nearly brand new. It has ~300 rounds through it total. This is the new version that was released shortly before JG among other companies were forced to cease production of H amp;amp;amp;K style airsoft guns due to copyright infringement or something along those lines. It will come with two(2) 350 rd JG high cap magazines. 


I will sell for $100 OBO

**Cyma M14 SOCOM**

Pics: http://i.imgur.com/EZ8XDOG.jpg

This gun is almost brand new as well and has no external issues or internal issues whatsoever. Even the bolt works along with the working bolt release. It shoots ~350 FPS. It will come with one(1) 350 rd Cyma high cap magazine. 

I will sell for $120 OBO

Edit: lowered prices

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request ] A tweak that allows you to tap and hold a picture in AlienBlue and save it to your device. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 23:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm tired of having to open links in a browser whenever I want to save them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WTS][WTT] JG G36c New Version </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 03:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a near new G36c that I am looking to trade or sell, although I prefer trades. I really don't know what I want for it trade wise,  so offer anything.  AEG, GBB, I don't care. I would really like an M249, MK48 or M60, though, but obviously the G36 is worth less compared to those so I could throw in some money as well. And as I said, offer anything. 

The gun only has about 300 rounds through it and has never been used in a game. It will come with two JG 350rd high caps. Keep in mind that this gun is discontinued because of the cease and desist from Umarex/ H amp;amp;amp;K so you likely wont see many of near new ones around much longer. 

Pics: http://imgur.com/a/0fZJR

I would really prefer trades but I'd sell it for $130 OBO. I can take PAYPAL or USPS money order

Edit: I also have a CYMA M14 SOCOM I would like to sell/trade 

Pic: http://i.imgur.com/EZ8XDOG.jpg

Similar condition to G36 but has only had ~100 rounds through it. Almost brand new. I traded for it new about a year ago.  Solid gun, amazing range, comes with one 350rd high cap.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Plate Carrier Help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-10 00:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I am in the process of purchasing a XL Paraclete RMV. I'm wondering if anyone has any experience with it. I'm a tall guy (6' 3") but pretty skinny so I was wondering if anyone would happen to know if it is going to be too big on me or if its adjustable enough to fit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found a CJ-5. Have a few questions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-22 03:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There are ants in my house... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 22:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by getting Pepper Spray on my hands. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-11 23:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So today I was going though my desk looking for a pencil and I came across a container of pepper spray. I tried spraying it, but apparently it was old, so it just dribbled down onto my hand, so I threw it away and washed my hands. Apparently washing my hands didn't get it all off, so when I tried pissing later, it got on my dick and now it feels like my dick is in fire. 

TL;DR Got pepper spray on my dick. It burns.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WTB/WTT/TTW] M249 or M4 (FMG4-A1 if possible, but i will look at any offers) TTW/WTT a few AEGS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-18 16:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else going to the Hawk Mountain Winter SAR/Survival training in PA this weekend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-28 05:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wondering if anyone has done it or something similar before and have any suggestions on what I'll need or recommend I should bring.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Night 4 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-12 02:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like we managed to stay clear of any lynchings today. Good job. Nothing really special happened although we have the games first winner, although he won without doing anything and at the expense of 20_Percent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help with Fake role message </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 17:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really have no defense for my lynching and I think a fake role message would help. I just need help creating a fake townie message. Anyone who can help please do or I'll probably be lynched.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have recruited a serial killer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 20:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wants three possible targets. Who should I tell him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know what this guys about? He keeps PMing me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 04:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have the support of a likely serial killer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 04:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may remember my last post in which I was asking for aid in deciding a course of action regarding a series of PMs between /u/Mafia_Goon_Pony (My novelty) and a alleged serial killer asking for our aid and protection in return for his services. I have acquired his help and thus we as the mafia gain an extra kill. He is confirming my identity with /u/DangerPulse in order to make sure my alt is mafia aligned.  I think that this is a great opportunity because we have to give him no Mafia members names and we get an extra kill. We run no risk of being exposed either. I will update as the situation develops but it seems likely I can work out a deal with him. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What should I do. I received these PMs. I don't want to screw us over. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 05:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something chart... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 05:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do I see so much hate on here for Rise Against? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-15 02:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were the first punk I heard and I always liked their music, but then I come to this sub and see that many people don't like them. They're still my favorite punk band and I don't understand the dislike. Anyone want to explain why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am /u/subject9229, Plounge Member of the Day, AMA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-06 19:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all, thank you /u/shellbullet17 for setting this up.
[](/bjsmile)

 Sign ups for the AMA are [here](/http://www.reddit.com/r/MLPLounge/comments/1dfanm/old_thread_is_old_we_need_a_new_ama_thread/)

Now on to the basic stuff.

First name: Bryan

Age Sex and/or Gender: I'm a 16 year old dude

Location: A boring town in Ohio  
[](/bjseriously)

Occupation: Busboy/ Dishwasher

Education: Currently in my junior year of high school

  [](/bjshake)
 Best Pony: Blackjack!  

Favorite soup: Beef Vegetable Stew.



Hobbies are running cross country. lacrosse and airsoft. I am currently a cadet in the Civil Air Patrol. After I get out of highschool I am going to enlist in the US Army (hopefully as a Ranger).[](/bjsalute) After that I have no plans. Thats it really, so go ahead and AMA! [](/bjdrunk)


Edit:
Ok. I have to go cut the grass. Ill be back in an hour to answer whatever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every time I click on links to that website. And to top it off, it doesn't link to the image it should! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 02:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> G P Question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-22 01:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am going to be buying my first higher end AEG and have been looking at the G P M16A3. I have done some research and have heard mixed opinions about the internal quality of G P aegs. So my question is, are G P internals reliable?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help meee. I'm missing a part and can't find one anywhere. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-04 03:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I lost the trigger guard and mag release for my CYMA m14 and have tried looking for a replacement part but could not find any. Does anyone know where I can find the part? I already tried Evike and ASGI.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Running help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-30 23:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So my average time for a 5k is (or was) about 18 minutes. Then I went and forced myself to run 7-8 miles about three weeks ago and ever since then I've been getting an average of an 24 minute 5k. That is unacceptable to me. Is there something I did wrong after that long run that made me gain that much time? No matter how much more I run now, I can't get less than a 24 min 5k. Any suggestions on how to recover? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What side am I on! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-02 01:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously. I can't tell.

Now I'm more confused. 

Periwinkle! Woo hoo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wow. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-01 16:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got called out by my heroes for being a Brony. I don't know why, but I made a post on /r/army asking something about contracts and one of them went through my history and starting pulling things out of context and telling me that they don't think I'm Special Operations or Ranger material just on the context of me being a Brony.  Bullshit. I've been training myself for the past 4 years and they know nothing of who I am. 
This was demoralizing at the least. I really thought that my nations soldiers would be better than the average asshole on Reddit but apparently not. 

And for you guys on /r/Army who will undoubtedly go through my history again. Why do you give a shit what I do with my life? I'm trying to do something good with my life and y'all are just bashing me for something completely unrelated. 
     Sincerely,
         A demoralized and angry  subject9229


Thank you everyone. You guys have helped me get a perspective on the whole thing. 

Edit: Me and the dude in question had a chat and I seem to have misunderstood him. He stereotyped me as being the sterotypical brony, which im not, and I said some things I shouldnt have. 
I hope he understands that it pissed me off, and is demoralizing when they  guys you call your heroes tell you you can't do something. I can do anything I fucking want and will. I'll be seeing him when I'm in special forces one day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Enlisting question. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-01 05:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will be enlisting once i finish high school no matter what. How hard is it to get an 18X or 11X Op 40 contract? I have wanted to be all I can be (not quoting army slogan, just telling it how it is) for quite some time and special forces or Ranger is the route I really want to take. I've talked to recruiters but they never gave me a straight answer.


Edit: For all you making fun of me for how I live my life, go ahead I don't give a shit, I didn't ask for your opinion on how I live my life and I'll live my life how I want.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I applied for a job. Yay. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-30 22:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> . Today I applied for a job at a hardware store. I have an interview next week and will probably get the job, because they need people to hire. I didn't really want a job, because school already takes up alot of time but at least I'll have money now. Whaddup with y'all?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Help] Trying to Jailbreak iPod 4th Gen. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 20:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am using evasion and when it gets to the step when i click on the jailbreak app on the ipod, nothing happens on the PC. Anyone know whats up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Plounge Minecraft Server </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 18:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does it exist? I have tried the older one but it is outdated. Is their one in use? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> External/Possible internal help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 06:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I own a JG g36c and have realized its too short for me after shooting ~600 rounds through it.  I am looking to turn it into a normal or k variant, but have no idea what i need to replace to do so. Any suggestions or help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 02:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My skills now say reset to legendary in the skill tree menu? Was this part of the patch or a mod I installed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /b/ raid warning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 01:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're raiding us right now. 
Oh No. /s

Edit: some doubt over if it was /b/. I have no proof but it was them last time and they did the same thing this time. I got my info from another post and I unfortunately cannot find that post again. Sorry for any confusion and to /b/ if it was not them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hate to ask this... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-18 02:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...But do any of you have a .zip of the balloon party album? I don't have a computer that I can use so I can't use torrents, soundcloud or bandcamp downloads won't work. (Blocked because im on an ipod). A .zip on media fire or other site would be much appreciated if it exists or can be made easily. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Music </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-15 02:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone have a .zip file of fallout equestria inspired music? I've seen a playlist of 86ish songs on a falloutequestria website but they're all YouTube links and it would take forever to download them all on my phone  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What music, if any, do you listen to while reading FO:E? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-13 01:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I listen to Makkon- Celestia Origins Extended Battle Theme. It makes everything more epic. I'm getting a bit bored of it though. Do you listen to anything while reading?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/Bronylocator
A subreddit dedicated to finding Bronys in your area </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-06 02:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-03 03:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I, for the life of me. Cannot figure out how to run fo3 on win8. Anyone know how? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Favorite episode? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 04:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm bored and looking to watch an episode of MLP but can't decide which. Whats your favorite episode? Or one you think I should watch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just curious </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-20 01:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many of you recognize me? I madeit my goal when I made this account to try to post more an am wondering if my efforts paid off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best way to break in boots? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-19 01:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just got a new pair of the hot weather boots and they are pretty stiff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need a bit of tech help. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-17 17:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I accidentally fired my gun without a fuse in it, with just the fuse connectors touching, now I cannot find a fuse that will work. I tried a bunch of types which has led me to believe something else is wrong. Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've been sitting here for the past 15 minutes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-16 23:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The assassins creed 3 credits are really long and I can't skip them. Im bored so What's up with y'all?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am trying to jailbreak my ipod </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-09 21:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And my computer refuses to connect to my ipod. It charges, but iTunes, my jailbreak software, (im using evasion) and everything else refuses to connect. iTunes says that it reciever a negative response. I have tried multiple connection cables and all the usb slots and they work fine for everything else. Could it be my security on my computer? Or something else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Offer from a friend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-09 19:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He keeps trying to sell me a D boys SCAR H for 40 bucks. Normally, I would buy this, but the gearbox decided to crap out on the gun. Is it worth buying it for fixing up?(I have never opened a gearbox up to fix it before) 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need some help. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 03:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the new ios6.1.1 jailbreak saved to my computer but when I run it, it says connecting to device and refuses to load at all. Know what's up?

Edit: ipod 4th gen  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dash fighting Changelings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 04:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone else think... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-02 22:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should just get rid of classes? I think it would be much better if you could use a assault rifle with the SMAW/RPG, c4 with assault, etc. Something less restricted  than the current system. Why I say this is because it seems after every patch, one class or another always seems to be nerfed more than others.

Edit: or perhaps a less restrictive class system  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need slight tech/ electrical help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-27 20:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently replaced the fuse in my JG G36 and its shooting g louder than I remember. Any ideas to what's up with it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just had a trade. How'd I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-27 05:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I traded my near broken JG BAR10 for a brand new, never fired CYMA M14 Socom. I think I did pretty good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dragonborn? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 19:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any idea when the DLC will be released for PC? Or ps3? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've been gone for three days. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 02:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's up with bees everywhere?
Also anyone got a link to latest episode? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ranger School Question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 02:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know ranger school is difficult but I have a question about how fit I have to be for it. I have great endurance and can run 8miles easily, but I am not very strong. I can bench 120 at most. I am just wondering if this will be a problem. And what muscle groups should I focus on to bulk up so I am prepared and will have a better chance of passing Ranger school? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happens if the Obama administration or any subsequent administrations ban guns entirely? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 01:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would the gun owning population do? Would there be armed revolts? What would this mean for the future of our constitutional rights, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have no idea where I should post this so here ya go. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 00:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Damn It </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 04:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
I Got Plounge AIDS from Yuki. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HOLY CRAP!!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 03:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I CAN SEE EMOTES! I just got a computer and finally set it up! There is so much i was missing being stuck on my phone. 

Aso whats with Sweetie Belle at the bottom. its creepy.

Also I got Steam. Add me! Name same as reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I got steam! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 02:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Add me if you want.
I am risen_warrior on steam </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Account </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-28 03:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was not very active on my last account(/u/Dashie8107) but now that I have a computer, I can be more active.  Yay for wasting more of my life. So in light of the new computer, I made a new account.  Eh none of you probably knew who I was anyway. But some of you may have.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
