<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1637</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any tips to improve essay writing speed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 19:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm apparently a very slow writer, because I didn't finish my essay this time. After 1 minute of planning, I began writing non-stop until the proctor said, "pencils down." In the end, I wrote a page and a half.

So how can I improve that? I'm working to make my essays better in other ways, but how can I write quicker and fill up more space? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What am I doing wrong on essays? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-28 22:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took the SAT twice, got an 8 both times. None of the guides or tips I find online have helped. So I took a 25 minute practice essay, with a prompt I found online. Can anyone identify my mistakes?

Prompt:
"That which we obtain too easily, we esteem too lightly. It is dearness only which gives everything its value." -Thomas Paine

Do we value only what we struggle for? Plan your response, and then write an essay to explain your views on this issue. Be sure to support your position with specific points and examples. (You may use personal examples or examples from your reading, observations, or, knowledge of subjects such as history, literature, science.)



People only value what they struggle for. Only by overcoming obstacles can a person truly achieve. Without challenge, there can be no triumph. Without triumph, we cannot full appreciate what we have. This fundamental truth is reflected through subjects as diverse as history and literature.

Sometimes, people get something for nothing. Some people are born with money, power, and ability. King Charles I of England inherited a monarchy, and his lack of appreciation for political power caused his Parliament to turn against him in the First English Civil War. If he had struggled and fought for his position, Charles would have known he true value of the crown. This is further reflected in his successor, Lord Protector Oliver Cromwell, who refused the English crown in favor of a republic in which "those who provide by the sweat of their brow" can appreciate power.

A person who does not work for himself cannot appreciate his lot. George Orwell's novel, "Animal Farm," was all about his shortfall of communism. The happiest of all the animals was Boxer, the horse who put in all the work to achieve his success. Because he struggled, he had a deep, honest pride in his work. Other animals, like the pigs, made no effort. Snowball took power without competition, and subsequently lost sight of the value of compromise. When Napoleon ousted Snowball, he did so by force. Neither pig struggled, and as a consequence both were unhappy and incompetent. 

Without struggle, there can be no understanding the real value of achievement. Success is measured not by raw magnitude of victory, but by resistance overcome. Nobody can appreciate the vast difficulty of a task without completing it. And there is no pride in accomplishment without conflict. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IWTL Economics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 08:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really interested in learning economics, but I don't know where to begin. My High School doesn't have an economics class or club. I haven't found much online. I tried listening to Planet Money, and it's really cool, but not what I'm looking for. 

I'm a complete beginner; I've never studied economics at all, and I want to start. I want a real, basic, Economics 101 course, online or in print. A podcast would be great, but I haven't found any of what I'm trying to find on ITunes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why did European colonialism create such a messed up situation in Africa, but not in South America? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 22:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I look at the political map of Africa, and I cringe. So many countries, borders all screwed up, countries inside countries, etc. And Sub-Saharan Africa is generally the poorest, least developed region in the world, from my understanding.

Yet South America is similar in climate and terrain, but today a political map of South America is border porn. To me, at least, it has a beautiful division of land between just a handful of nations, and while that continent certainly has its own problems, they aren't nearly as bad as Africa's. Why is this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What sort of extracurriculars does UVa value highly? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-14 05:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a Hugh School Junior, and I have a wide variety of EC's right now, including Fencing, Model UN, Computer Science, Boy Scouts, and theatre.

I've got some free time over the summer between internships that I want to use to beef up my application. What extracurricular activities would most impress UVa admissions? Music? Volunteering? A sport?

Thanks!

EDIT: I've got a lot of great advice, thanks guys! Just wanted to elaborate a bit.

The reason I'm focusing on EC's is because my GPA is sub-par. 3.8 on a 5.0 scale, and about 3.3 unweighted. My SAT scores are near perfect, 2350. In addition, I've taken the most rigorous curriculum possible, and my school is a well-respected private institution. So the only thing that really brings me down is grades, and those are definitely improving. I just want to maximize my chances by becoming as well-rounded as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Parallels between House of Cards and West Wing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-13 19:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anyone else noticed the absurd amount of parallels? 

Both have an alcoholic Chief of Staff

"Mendoza" is a supporting character in both

In both shows, the President has a hostile relationship with the Vice President

Both see the President potentially facing impeachment for not disclosing medical information

There are more, but none come to mind right now. I'll edit later when I think of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it worth taking Espionage Ideas as a lesser partner in a PU? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-13 18:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm playing as Naples, and I'm the lesser partner under France. I've got Defensive and Diplomatic Ideas right now, and I'm close to Modern Theocracy. I'm thinking about choosing Espionage ideas instead of Religious for the time being. Although Religious ideas are ridiculously good, the Espionage track could make it easier to destabilize France, which would make declaring independence much easier. Thoughts? Is it worth it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why are executives always "asked to resign" instead of fired? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-07 20:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which colleges are most focused on test scores? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-05 05:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got crappy gpa. 3.7 on a weighted 5.0 scale, and ~3.2 on a 4.0 unweighted. But my test scores are good, 2250, and, I'm taking the SAT twice more. I'm also in the process of finding a college to attend. Are there any well-respected universities that care a lot about SAT scores, and less about gpa? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can't get into UVa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 02:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck. It's my top choice for a uni. I can't get in. There's no way. Why? Because of my fucking gpa. My god damn fucking gpa. Everything else is perfect. I've taken the highest level classes my school offers. I've taken two elective AP classes. I got a 2250 on my SAT's and I'm taking them two more times. I've been an exceptional Model UN delegate since I was a freshman. TWICE I've interned for Navy engineers, PAID. I'm an Eagle Scout. And the highest cumulative gpa that a university is going to see is a 3.7. I can get a 4.5 this semester. I got a 4.1 last semester. But freshman and sophomore year I got 3.3 and 3.6. I'm so fucking upset. UVa accepts applicants with an average of 4.2 gpa. If I got a 4.0 maybe I could squeak by. But no. No matter how hard I work, I'll be fucked for college. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Late-game" help? I need advice to bring my scores up from a 2250 to a 2300+. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-28 02:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've checked out advice for taking the SAT given by College Board and by other test professionals, but they seem to be focused on turning average scores into good ones (~1500 to ~2000).

 But my scores are 760-740-750 Reading Math Writing. I feel like many of the normal tips and strategies wouldn't apply, like skipping all questions I'm unsure of. While that would obviously be good if I've been getting a few dozen questions wrong, in this case I only missed one or two per section. The worst of it is that all three sections are relatively even, and I don't have an 800 in any of them. Can anyone give some advice geared towards someone shooting for a perfect 2400? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A sequel to House of Cards, detailing Pope Francis' rise to power in the Vatican. We'll call it "House of Cardinals." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-23 19:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A satire about a logical 17th Century rationalist who encounters a primal tribe with surprisingly accurate myths and legends. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-15 05:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need my hair cut in a 1960's style for a theatre production. Any advice (pics inside)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-11 15:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I need a 1960's style haircut. I'm comfortable with cutting it in any way I need to, but I would like it to look respectable. 

Pictures of my current hair:

http://i.imgur.com/PWoa3bP.jpg

http://i.imgur.com/Yi50K11.jpg

http://i.imgur.com/Sze80mv.jpg

http://i.imgur.com/A2Ukh2Q.jpg

http://i.imgur.com/FObZfT7.jpg

I tried to get the best pictures possible. The costumer told me that it was too long in the back and around the ears. I would appreciate pictures if possible. And while I know that hair grows back, we open in less than a week. So I think a safe haircut would be served best here.

If "1960's style" is a silly category, let me know. I'll talk to the costumer and narrow it down. 

Thanks in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the lineage of wealthy plantation owners in the pre-Civil War Southern US? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-08 20:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been wondering this for some time now. Were the upper-class Southern landowners descended from similarly wealthy men? Or did some impoverished families come to the New World from Europe, and eventually become the landowning, rich, powerful Southern plantation families? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Operation: Poliraft </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-07 02:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help with berries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-05 02:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm trying to make a farming hack for Emerald. I've made good progress on fixing the berry system, and I'm in the process of learning some ASM so that I can change how the clock works. But I've hit an issue with so-called "PlantID's". 

Naturally, a PlantID identifies which plot of land each soil event is, as they all use the same script. But I can't seem to find out how to change the properties of the PlantID's. You know how in the vanilla game you will find soil plots with plants already fully grown in them? Yeah, I'm trying to change it so that the soil plots start off empty, with absolutely nothing growing in them. Anybody know how I could do that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just got this cheap sweater today. How is this look? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 23:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've gotta say, I think I prefer GA's over Crisis Committees. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-13 18:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always thought I was a crisis kind of guy. But I went to two conferences in the past month, one an EU GA committee and one a semi-crisis Historical UNSC. I think I've decided that while I enjoy I enjoyed planning for them beforehand and talking about them afterward, crises are not the most fun while I'm in committee. People get silly, there are too few delegates, and I really prefer resolutions over directives. Plus, I like working with a partner to get things done; most of the other delegates at my school make excellent partners, and all of us are very versatile in our MUN talents.

I've attended at least two dozen conferences, and most of the time I made an effort to get a crisis committee. But next conference I'm going to get a GA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fire Department vs Riot Police </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 19:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100,000 men each, in a crowded big city. They have all the equipment they would normally have, I'm proportion to their manpower. Vehicles included. Not to the death, just to rout the enemy.

EDIT: Riot Police have no firearms, only nonlethal weapons like tasers, batons, tear gas, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there any way to recover an old email address with a forgotten security question answer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 22:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something that worked for me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-04 01:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been biting nails, skin and cuticles for as long as I can remember. This has been working lately.

Every day, I put a bandaid on any "problem finger". That means every finger with a cut, itch, dry spot, etc. It only works with a gauze-like classic bandaid, a plastic one won't work. When I have the urge to bite or pick, I bite on the bandaid. It's been doing great. The bandaids are tough enough to withstand a day of biting before completely falling apart. 

P.S. I'm a guy, in case that matters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are most of /r/MUN's readers College students, or High School? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-01 16:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only done MUN at the high school level, so I don't know quite how popular it is in College. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to have a CS major in college, but I don't know which CS major. Any help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-30 03:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a Junior in HS, took 2 CS classes (Honors Intro to CS, and AP CS A). I'm confident that I want to take Computer Science as a major in college. However, when I look at the majors offered by different universities, I see TONS of majors with "Computer Science" in the name. Examples include:

 Computer Science

 Computer Engineering (General)

Computer and Information Systems Security/Information Assurance

and

 Mathematics and Computer Science.

I really have little knowledge of the difference between these majors. Can anybody here shed some light on what these mean? If I want a job programming in the future, which one of these will be the most helpful?

EDIT: I really need to clarify here. I don't know what college I want to attend yet, just that I want a CS-type degree. So I can't very well just take CS and switch if I feel like it, because the Uni I go to might not offer what I want. I want to ensure that before I pick a college, I have a good idea of what options I want.

That said, I've pretty much been answered by now. Thanks for the input! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TV Show: In a city where all police officers are hot-headed loose cannons, one cop fights crime with a responsible regard for the rules. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 02:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine it: Every cop is headstrong and reckless, except for one. When this man finds a dangerous situation, he responsibly calls for backup and waits. When a suspicious activity happens that was outside his directions, he radios back to HQ to get clearance to investigate. Other officers, whose plans consist of running into action guns blazing, are baffled at how this one man manages to consistently succeed at his job without breaking any rules or laws. 

The police chief might be another stickler for rules, and he would be very happy with the responsible cop and quite upset with everyone else. Or, the chief is also reckless, desribing the rules as "more like guidelines." 

Other major characters could include:

 The reckless buddy cop, who gradually is convinced that "by the books" actually is the best method.

The single police dispatcher, who goes unused by most of the city because the cops are always running off and disregarding rules. He/she develops a close relationship with the main character, because he is the only one who calls him/her to request backup.

A forensics expert, who is the only one in the entire forensics lab because nobody is willing to wait for the test results.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to make the berry system functional in my Emerald hack. How would I do this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 22:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Berries are regulated by the clock, which does not work in emulators. I am looking for a way to either fix the clock or make berry growth operate on another system. Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What character personalities would you like to see in the games? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 03:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you thought of any interesting characters to be included in the games? I think the more recent releases lack some depth of character for the people, and I would really like to see some more fleshed-out personalities. So what traits or personalities would you like to see characters with? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Newb mod idea: Time Travel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 21:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I toyed with the thought for a while, and found [this post](http://www.reddit.com/r/dwarffortress/comments/he8mw/dwarven_time_travel/) from two years ago which pretty much sums it up. Create a world, let it run for 250 years, save all the worldgen data and start playing in Adventure Mode. At some point, your character could discover/create a time travel machine, which allows it to go both back and forward in time. If it goes forward, it just saves the world data and lets the world run for the time. To travel back to the original time, it just reloads the saved world data. 

To travel back in time, the mod would recreate the world, and, using the worldgen data, let it run until the year to which you travel. Then you can experience the world of the past, and when you travel back to your original time, the mod lets the world run until that year. So you could travel back in time, change events, and return to the present to find that, maybe, that Human town didn't get destroyed by an army of Goblins because a mysterious dwarf appeared to fend them off.

And I also had a plan for dealing with your past self. The game records every action you personally make, and when you travel back two days to prevent yourself from being robbed by a kobol, your past self does exactly the same things you originally did. When that becomes impossible (like if it says that he should attack a kobol that he never met, is already dead and is buried 100 yards away), the AI assumes control of your past self. 

Would this work? Is it possible? I have a fair bit of programming experience, so I would like to work on this, but only if it has any possibility of working.

EDIT: Also, if your past self dies, you do too. It wouldn't be possible to mess with other parodoxes because time travel is impossible. So the only real caveat to messing with the past is that if your past self dies, you also do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How could a permanent member be suspended or expelled from the Security Council? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 03:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to JHUMUNC in February, and I'm in the SC as France. The topics are pretty polarizing, and even though I have some good plans for compromise, I would like this option as a backup. I know the rules differ between conference hosts, but JHUMUNC almost completely adheres to UN Procedure. So in the real Security Council, is there any realistic plan for suspending a permanent member? Could I go to the GA for help? Is there some obscure motion for this?

EDIT: found a loophole. Resolution 2758 was a GA resolution that expelled the Republic of China (Taiwan) from the UN and accepted the People's Republic as the true representative of the Chinese nation. So to remove China, all you have to do is get the GA to repeal 2758. The PRC delegate then pretty much has to side with the West.

I imagine that in a modern committee one could do the same with Russia. A neat little loophole, eh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I had a possible method/formula for writing mystery stories, I would like your opinion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-12 21:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First off, I would like to say that I haven't written anything yet (except high school essays). I just get a lot of ideas, more often for methods than for actual stories. I've been toying with a method for writing a mystery, and I wanted to put it to paper and get another opinion. The way I see it, posting to /r/writing kills two birds with one stone.

Method:

1. Write a tragedy. The tragedy should not involve the actual story's main character at all. This is because most events in mysteries are discovered rather than caused by the "detective". This tragedy should involve one or more deaths, several characters with clear desires, and a good heaping of dramatic irony. It doesn't have to be more than a summary of events.

2. Sketch a timeline of events for the tragedy.

3. About 1/4-1/2 of the way through the timeline pick a point for the story to begin. The point should be an event that, in the tragedy, is part of the rising action. In the mystery, it will act as the initiating event. 

4. Decide whether the detective character will witness this event, or arrive after it occurs.

5. Begin writing from the detective's perspective. There should be little-to-no exposition about anything. Assume that the readers know the tragedy, and that you are just retelling it from the detective's POV. Have the detective use the first event as a starting point, and begin investigating. The detective's story should take him to some events in the tragedy, while others he should either not know or only discover later. The detective should either be present at the tragedy's conclusion, cause it or *prevent* it. While the mystery will start off the same as the tragedy, the detective's meddling may change some parts.

I just wanted to get this out there, if you have an opinion or critique to give, great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] Tell me the story of the Angry Fireman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-12 20:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never submitted a prompt before, let me know if I did something wrong, or used the wrong tag.

Details: One of my hobbies is telling really long (~15 min) stories with an extremely anticlimactic "punchline". I find them very fun to just make up as I tell, and refine them the more times I tell them. Usually the prompt I give myself is something like "The [adjective] [noun]". "The Irish Lamppost," "The Windy Barn," "The Elastic Factory." They often seem nonsensical, but I try to work them into the stories.

So, the Story of the Angry Fireman. Give it your best shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need a second opinion on my outftit for a Model United Nations conference </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-09 22:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm representing Ireland in an EU simulation. It's pretty much the only time I get to wear this tie, so I'm trying to keep it in the outfit.

The outfit

http://i.imgur.com/wtw2e3y.jpg

The Tie

http://i.imgur.com/QEMY3WQ.jpg

It's a navy jacket over a white shirt with khaki pants, though I will almost certainly replace them with matching navy trousers. Any suggestions for improvement?

Obviously I will be wearing appropriate footwear in the actual conference.

P.S. I have a green dress shirt that is about the same color as the harps on the tie. I also have another outfit that I will post ASAP, but I'll probably use this one.

*EDIT:* I checked the [Submission Guidelines](http://www.reddit.com/r/malefashionadvice/comments/19bsc1/mfa_rules_guidelines_updates_and_clarifications/), I don't seem to break any of the rules, but I'm getting downvotes. Can you at least do me the courtesy of telling me what I did wrong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way to change the level cap in the Pokemon games? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 01:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to make a small hack with a level cap set at 5. Is there a way to do this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redistribution of Socks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 21:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Laundromats. They should add a feature to their washers/dryers. It counts the socks in the load. If the number is even, do nothing. If the number is odd, add/remove a sock from the load. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could someone help me understand offsets, and how to work with them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-03 19:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, heres what I DO know and understand:

1. My computer has set aside a specific amount of 'data' for the rom. Each byte of that data is numbered in hexidecimal. Much of that data is occupied by scripts. There is also a certain amount that has no assigned value for the rom, so trying to access it without setting values for it will result in garbled gibberish. This is because there *is* information there, but it is information for other things, completely different from the rom. If I give these 'empty' bytes a value that makes sense for XSE, I can use them.

2. When I create a script, there is an offset at the beginning. This offset determines what byte the script will be stored from. So if I have a script of X bytes, and I use the offset 0x100000, the script will be stored in bytes 0x100000 to (0x100000+x).

What I need to figure out:

1. How do I stop *my* scripts from getting in the way of the scripts the rom already has? When I compile new scripts, I often get them cut off halfway through by a script that was already at that offset, resulting in the first half of my code and then a bunch of useless code written by the original designers.

2. What is a dynamic offset, and how does it differ from a normal offset? 

3. What is freespacefinder, and how does it work? If I ask it to look for, say, 200 bytes, it only gives me ~5 available offsets. Does this mean that there isn't enough free space to make a hack with more than 5 200 byte scripts?

4. Finally, a question I asked in an [earlier post](http://www.reddit.com/r/PokemonROMhacks/comments/1u76za/how_should_i_begin_making_a_completely_new_hack/): I want to start creating an entirely new hack, and the only resources from the base game I want to use will be the sprites and the basic systems. No scripts, no maps, I will make my own for all of them. How can I avoid the original scripts interfering with the scripts I write?

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How should I begin making a completely new hack? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 03:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I've messed around with PGE, XSE and AM for a few weeks now, trying to create a rom hack. Initially I thought that the easiest thing to do would be to make only minor adjustments to the base (Emerald) and get more complex after that. However, I ended up with a bunch of garbled scripts due to offset issues, and it got really annoying. So 

I've decided to make a completely original hack, with new maps, scripts, ect. Not changing the Pokemon at all. How would I start doing this? Should I delete every map, event and script in the game, and start from there? Or is there a better way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do I get a static shock when I touch my mouse? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-01 21:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did anyone who opposed interracial marriage claim that it would lead to homosexual marriage? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-01 18:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back when interracial marriage was a contested legal issue, were there any opponents that used the "slippery slope" argument, and claimed that it could lead to legal homosexual marriage? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Trainer Editor should I use for R/S/E? Please provide links! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-29 18:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried A-Trainer, it couldn't execute and had a trojan. Tried several download sites, no dice. Anything else I can use for Emerald? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Courier 6 VS the Dragonborn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-29 01:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **ROUND ONE:**

Courier 6 came straight from the Second Battle of Hoover Dam. He's well armed, but has no allies. 

The Dragonborn came fresh from the final battle with Alduin. He has access to his shouts, magic, weapons and armor.

**ROUND TWO:**

Same as above, but with allies. Courier 6 brings the army that captured/defended Hoover Dam; battered, but very well equipped. The Dragonborn brings the full might of Skyrim's ruling army, be it Imperial or Stormcloak.

**EDIT**

Just felt that a few things needed to be clarified: in Round 2, Courier 6 gets every soldier who fought on his side at the Second Battle of Hoover Dam. The Dragonborn gets every soldier in Skyrim who is his ally. So while Courier 6 has the Bommer plane, and the BoS, the Dragonborn has on his side:

* Every Stormcloak/Imperial soldier in Skyrim (depending on his chosen side)

* The Thieves Guild, Mage College, Dark Brotherhood and the Companions

* The Blades/Greybeards (again, depending on the chosen side)

Also, in Round 1, Courier 6 has whatever he carried with him to Hoover Dam, and the Dragonborn has access to ALL shouts, spells, ect. Except maybe the Wabbajack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IWTL How to make a 3-D video game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-27 23:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking to make a 3-D game of my own, but I'm not sure where to begin. I have a very good grasp of programming concepts, but I am not fully proficient with any specific language. 

The game I want to make is basically a zero-gravity shooter. If anyone can point me towards some tutorials, suggest an engine I should use, ect, that would be very nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where can I safely download A-Trainer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 03:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have found a single download site for A-Trainer, and McAfee detected a trojan on the file when I scanned it. Does anybody know where I can download a clean A-Trainer tool? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Info Dump: Pokemon Emerald intro stuff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-15 23:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all,

I'm working through the Emerald intro step-by-step so that I can get rid of the events like the moving truck, the starter Pokemon event, ect. I decided to make a post as a place to store all the info I've gathered; my goal is to eliminate all the intro cutscenes, starting with Mom welcoming you to your new home and ending with Wally's Pokemon catching tutorial. 

Downvote, upvote, I don't care, but mods, please don't delete this post. It's really more of a way for me to store info without using my horribly organized computer file system. I will do it by editing as I go along, so it won't begin with much info at all.


*  checkgender gives 0x1 for girl, 0x0 for boy
*     "setvar 0x4092 0x6" says that you've already set your clock
* 0x4092 seems to be the controlling variable for the mother's responses. 0x7 indicates that you entered the house, but not your room yet 
*     "clearflag 0x2F8" causes a rival sprite of the wrong gender to appear in your doorway in your room.
* 
*     "setvar 0x408D 0x3" causes the rival's Pokeball to trigger a message ("This is [rival]'s pokeball"). If this command is not executed, the rival's Pokeball will trigger the entrance of the rival and that little intro.
* 
*     "setvar 0x4050 0x1" causes the little girl who stops you from leaving to move, and allows you to go onto route 101 to trigger the starter pokemon event.
* 
*     "setflag 0x331" does nothing I can determine yet.
* 
*     I can't find the code for Mom talking about Dad on the TV
* 0x8004 is the mother
*     I can't find the code for rival's mom talking when you enter her house
* On the littleroot map, the header that "Validates values 0x2", deleting lines 8-9, 19-38 and 41-43 will remove the opening cutscene. These lines begin, respectively, with "warpmuted 0x1 0x0 0xFF 0x8 0x8", "setdooropened 0x8004 0x8005" and "spriteinvisible 0xFF 0x0 0x0"
*     I need to stop mom's talk when I enter the house, stop mom's tv talk, stop rival mom's talk when I enter her house.
* 
*     setflag 0x74 makes the guy blocking the route out of Oldale move
* I'm having some weird formatting bugs, so things might get a bit messed up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pokemon Game Editor not recognizing Emerald? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-15 02:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm using PGE, trying to mod Emerald. When I click "Load Rom" and navigate to my roms and select my Emerald, named "Pokemon Emerald.gba". I get a popup saying "Not one of the Pokemon games..."

Is there a fix for this?

EDIT: Found a fix. I was using the shortcut instead of the actual .gba file. I moved the actual file into my roms folder, and now it's fixed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I thought /r/DIY would be the best place for this. Can anyone tell me how to restore my ~1950's box for French cards? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 19:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here](http://i.imgur.com/PsnU3lu.jpg) is the front and [back](http://i.imgur.com/wOrkvuF.jpg).

[One end](http://i.imgur.com/r5pGDMs.jpg) is missing the big flap and one little one.

[The other end](http://i.imgur.com/FBukkif.jpg) has both little flaps missing.

[One edge](http://i.imgur.com/whBHyTK.jpg) is coming apart in both sides, held together only in the middle.

I bought this (with the cards) at an antiques market in Paris last summer. It was in a similar condition, but the parts were all still on (they were very close to coming off). I have all the "missing" parts, I just need to put them back on. If this is the wrong sub, please direct me to the right one. Thanks!


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Explain the plot of Macbeth like IAMA hardcore Crusader Kings 2 player. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-03 05:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does reinforcement work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-30 01:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't get a handle on this mechanic. I can't get my levies to reinforce in the field, I have to disband them and then raise them again. My special event troops won't reinforce at all. 

I have seen AI players with armies that are very clearly reinforcing in the field. How can I do that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which US presidents could put up a fight against Vladmir Putin? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-28 22:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fistfight, to the death. Assume each president is in their prime, even if that means they aren't currently president.

Which presidents would have the best chance at victory? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [AMA Request] An Interpol officer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-27 05:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **My 5 Questions:**

1. What is your average day on the job like?
2. Do you ever run into conflicts with federal/local police?
3. What was the most interesting case you've worked on?
4. Seeing that the Internet is a worldwide entity, does Interpol target internet criminals at all?
5. Do you ever feel that you violate a nation's independence by acting in some way?

**Public Contact Information:** If Applicable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if the Schlieffen Plan targeted Russia first instead of France? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-21 22:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was listening to a talk today about the beginning of WWI, and this question came to me. According to the talk, Russia's military could field more men but was less organized and less industrialized than the other European land powers (Germany and France). 

What if Germany's plan for war involved not first attacking France through Belgium, but attacking Russia and crushing them before they got their act together? Would Germany have succeeded? Would England ever join the War? America? And on which side?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If the Democratic-Republican party were in complete control of the USA from the Constitution until the 18th Congress, what powers would each part of the government have? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-18 00:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 150,000 men of Napoleon's army vs the entire Roman Imperial Army commanded by Scipio </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 22:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Napoleon's army consists of 150,000 men, with artillery and cavalry in good proportion. 

The Roman Imperial Army, under Augustus, contained 25 legions of about 5,000 men each, amounting to a total of 125,000 men. This army mostly consisted of heavy infantry. It also included 250 auxilia of 500 men each, composed of cavalry, archers, slingers and some heavy infantry.

So 150,000 Napoleonic troops under Napoleon vs 250,000 Roman troops under Scipio.

Edit: Scipio understands the implications of gunpowder warfare, but Romans cannot operate such weapons.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just realized that cool ranch doritoes taste like shrimp scampi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 05:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why is it that data is always unavailable for Greenland? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 03:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you look at Wikipedia articles for the Human Development Index or Economic Freedom Index or any of the sort, Greenland is always listed as "Data Unavailable". Very few other places are listed as such, including North Korea, Somalia and South Sudan. 

Greenland obviously isn't the most advanced nation in the world, but it was founded by modern Europeans. Why is all of it's data unknown?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Newbie question about colonizing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 02:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I downloaded the EU4 demo today and started as Portugal. I got an explorer and explored all the way to Florida. I would now like to colonize what I think is Bermuda (in the W. Bermuda Sea). I have a colonist it says in the little bar at the top of the screen. How do I send it to colonize a province?

This is a really beginner question, but I've never played EU4 before. What I need are exact instructions, i.e. "Click button x in the upper right, then button z on the screen that pops up". 

Thanks!

EDIT: Okay, I fixed it now. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have picked at my nails and the skon around them for as long as I can remember. My fingers are a mess of hangnails. I need help stopping. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-31 13:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't just my fingers. I pick at scabs, cuts on my face, and I pick my nose. The latter I avoid in public as much as possible.

I haven't seen much of this sub, but what I have seen makes me think that most of the people suffering from this are female. Suggestions for nail polish, pictures of polished nails that people bit. So a lot of the solutions might be for ladies only, and would be embarrasingly effeminate for me, a male. 

So, what solutions are there that would work for a man?

Thank you all so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How early could an effective flying machine be created? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-31 02:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, what technologies were necessary for it to be invented? Flying machines were conceived centuries before the Wright Brothers developed an effective airplane. Was it pure chance, or trial-and-error, that led to the invention? Or was it a process that developed over time?

Side note: this mostly focuses on airplanes, but input about air balloons is also welcomed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've seen Francia this far north before, even England, but this... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-27 23:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am a high school Junior with a fair amount of coding experience. How can I start building my portfolio now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 04:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> High School Junior, as I said. Taken 2 computer science courses, one of which was AP (They were the only CS courses my school offers). I have taken several programming courses online, and I think I have a fairly good grasp of Python and C++. 

I'm looking for a way to build my portfolio on my own time. I can't exactly go out and get a job programming, but the bright side is that I don't really expect any significant pay, I'm just looking for something to get started. Any help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hardboiled: A sub devoted to "hardboiled crime" roleplaying. It passed away 4 months ago... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 01:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I get someone not of my religion in my court? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-17 03:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to create the kingdom of Jerusalem, and I don't have Sword, so I created the Empire of Tartaria, reformed Tegriism, and conquered all the way down through Persia, the northern half of Arabia, and, most importantly, the Holy Land. I now want to create the Kingdom of Jerusalem. But I am Tengri, and the Kingdom must be formed by a Christian. I don't have any Christian vassals in my court, at all. All attempts to invite them have been forbidden due to my "false religion".  Is there a way I can get someone, anyone, with another religion into my court? Or, alternately, change my religion to christianity? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EU4 converter questions! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 22:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a few questions about converting a save to EU4. I don't have EU4, not even the demo, so some of these might be silly questions.

1. If I improve a region's holdings, will these improvements carry over to EU4? If so, in what way?

2. Religions. I reformed Norse Paganism, when I convert to EU4, will that be my religion? What about the Old Norse heresey?

3. Republics! Are they operated differently in EU4 than in CK2? How will my merchant empire transfer?

4. Names. I don't know if you can rename titles in EU4, but if I change a title's name in CK2 and then convert it, will it have my chosen name or the original?

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sooo the Kingdom of Ireland is now the de jure ruler of the Duchy of Cornwall... Is that supposed to happen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-08 23:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that de jure territories were set in stone. But when I was going over the map of de jure kingdoms, Ireland included Cornwall and Devon. I checked the realm screen for the Kingdom, and checked the box labeled "de jure". Sure enough, the Jarldom of Cornwall was there. I've never experienced this before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am the King of Ireland, with tanistry succession. If I create the Kingdom of Sweden, will it have Tanistry or Gavelkind succession? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-07 14:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My king always revokes all of my counties! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-06 20:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am having this awful problem. I swear fealty to a king or an emperor with me having a fairly decent demesne (2-3 counties). As soon as he accepts my swear fealty offer, he revokes all of my counties. All of them. And I lose.

This has happened a lot, when I swore fealty to the Ummayad sultan as the king of Mali, when I swore fealty to the sultan of Egypt as the sheik of Jerusalem (and other counties), when I swore fealty to the HRE as a duke in Bavaria. This keeps happening, and I am apparently powerless to stop it. How can I fix this problem?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You are trapped in your house for 5 years, alone. Then someone appears in your living room. What's the first thing you do with them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-22 21:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5:Ubuntu </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-22 19:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is it? How does it work? Why do my friends keep telling me it's better than my current OS? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Merchant Republic: My trade post keeps disappearing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-22 03:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made a merchant republic in Ireland, using console commands, with the capital in Ormond. As the first Prince-Mayor of Munster, I build a trade post in Ormond. For several decades, I held that trade post, built a few others, ect. For about 12 years now, another patrician has been Prince-Mayor. All of a sudden, my trade post in Ormond disappears. No message, it just vanishes from the Republic screen. I checked Ormond itself, and yes, my post was gone. I thought it was a one-time bug, so I shelled out the cash to build a new one and continued playing. Now, a few years after that, my trade post in Ormond has once again disappeared. Any fixes? Explainations? Thanks.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just beat level 9 of Block Dude </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-18 03:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck. Yes. I have been working on this level in my free time during math since March. In hindsight, it looks so fucking simple, but I am immensely proud of my achievement. 

Now, level 10. Fucking bring it.

EDIT: for those qho don't know, Block Dude is a game on my TI 84 plus Silver calculator. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some "crutch words" in languages other than English? Words like "Umm," "Uh" and "Like". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-11 21:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CGPGrey vs /u/Unidan in a battle to see who could teach American History best </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-11 03:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The people they teach are all average to above average High School Juniors. They have all taken the prerequisites. Both /u/Unidan and CGPGrey have to give the exact same test to their students at the end of the year, and they have the whole class time to prepare them for the exam however they like (without cheating by giving them answers). Whoever's class has the highest average grade wins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bob Loblaw vs Saul Goodman in a commercial making competition. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-05 22:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who can make the best commercial? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Truman from "Truman Show" vs Chuck from "Castaway" in a sailboat race </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-05 03:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Identical sailboats, pushing off from one island and sailing to another through various weather conditions. Chuck is the Chuck from the end of the movie, and Truman is Truman at the end of his movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How dense was the population of Native American tribes (Iroquois specifically) prior to European colonization? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-04 23:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As in title. My history teacher mentioned that the Native Americans were not densely populated, but I feel like I have heard of Native Americans having large towns. My history teacher isn't completely reliable, so I wanted to make sure that I don't have false information. Thank you for your time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Wanted] A closed map server </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 02:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am looking for a closed-map server. Essentially, a server in which all the players log on at a specified time, and they only play in an area a few hundred blocks long and wide, surrounded by bedrock walls. Thread [here](http://www.minecraftforum.net/topic/1212125-closed-map-experiment/) for further reading. That one was concluded to be a hoax, but it spawned a small sub-community in Minecraft who, for a few months, ran and played on these servers. /r/limitedservers was the sub. The servers were plagued by lack of interest and dropouts and very few people were willing to run a server. Are there any left? Anything similar? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most modern mod for Mount and Blade that you know of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 06:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Set in a time period closest to the present day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Tesla Model S </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 08:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a car person. I don't know much more than how to drive, use jumper cables and change a flat. Lots of my friends, who are intelligent and respectable people, are going crazy over the Model S. And with today's front page post about its safety tests, I wonder what exactly about this car is so amazing? I get that it's electric, but haven't we had electric cars for decades? Why is the Model S so special? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If there was someone who had access to infinite transplants of everything that medical technology is capable of (blood, heart, ect.), how long could such a person be kept alive and functioning? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 02:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Wanted] A server where pickaxes are banned </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 05:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why was England the dominant force in the British Isles? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 03:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And why did Great Britain have three different cultures, Scottish, Welsh and English, while Ireland had only Irish? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what can we help you with? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 08:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything that we, other members of reddit, can help you with right now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How early could the airplane theoretically have been invented? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 07:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, what technologies were necessary for it to be invented? Flying machines were conceived centuries before the Wright Brothers developed an effective airplane. Was it pure chance, or trial-and-error, that led to the invention? Or was it a process that developed over time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Season 5 of Breaking Bad is now on Netflix </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-05 02:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does the word "understand" mean what it does despite the fact that "under" and "stand" have nothing to do with it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 03:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've run clean out of daydreams </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-21 16:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rather mild offfmychest post. Basically, the title. I have run out of daydreams. I used to daydream constantly, whenever i had a free moment. I would go to sleep daydreaming scenarios of fame and fortune in my head. Thinking about the girl I fancied, or the job I wanted, or some silly shit like "how cool would it be if Pokemon were real?" 16 year old kid daydreaming about Pokemon. 

Now I'm all out. The girl I used to fancy has fallen out of my favor, I've overplayed my scenarios of wealth, and I'm pretty much completely out of things to think about.

It's annoying, mostly because this is what I've done when going to sleep for my whole 16 years. Now I have, like, nothing to do with my time when I'm trying to fall asleep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Diplomacy mod: Why won't anyone agree to any treaties/agreements that I make? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 04:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Playing Brytenwalda, but it seems to be the same diplomacy mod. I got the Rheged at 100 relation (it says that the nation is loyal to me), their king is at like 30 relation and I have 50 right to rule. I send over a messenger (with 6 persuasion) to get a non-aggression pact, and they decline. I've done this same shit with like 4 different kingdoms and it's all the same. Why won't anyone make agreements with me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Forums down? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 23:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have bomb supplies mailed to the NSA bosses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-07 22:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Spaying and neutering </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-05 22:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is it? Why is it done? Do I really have to chop off my dog's balls? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why was Great Britain, specifically England, the dominant force in the British Isles? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 12:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why was Ireland always the impoverished, servile land while England was prosperous and dominant? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any way to get a HM game on the ipod? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-25 22:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to be stuck without a computer for a while, so I would like to get something on my ipop. 4th gen, not jailbroken yet but I am willing to do that. Any HM or RF game is good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MetricConversionBot - pounds to kilos, ounces to grams, ect. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-23 18:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/MetricConversionBot converts units of the English system to the Metric system. It is known that ounces will be converted to grams, but other conversions are untested. Give it a whirl, see which ones work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a border mod </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 11:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking for a mod that shows the borders of each kingdom, and not just the town/castles/villages that they own. Any help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I LOVE AMERICA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-19 23:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't satirical, like /r/murica. I'm serious. I fucking love my country. I'm taking a 3 week vacation in Europe right now. Everyone's way too fucking content. No ambition or drive in sight. People in Italy and France just seem happy to wake up at 10:00 and take a 2 hour nap in the middle of the day. WHAT THE SERIOUS FUCK, Italians and Frenchmen spend HALF THEIR WAKING HOURS EATING. EATING. I love food, but what the fuck? Back home, we finish every meal in less than an hour. 

And the power outlets suck, everything you plug in keeps falling out because the sockets are too wide for the plugs.

There's no AC anywhere in Italy.

Germans are cool, but WHY THE FUCK DO THEY WANT TO KEEP THESE FUCKING SOCIALIST MONEY-BURNERS IN THE EU? "Oh, we should help our Italian and Greek friends, we're all fellow Europeans." THEY TAKE SIESTAS WHILE YOU WORK OVERTIME.

America's in bad shape right now, but Europe is worse. 

America would not stand for this "bail out every deadbeat on the continent" shit. 

Americans have a work-play balance. We work because we're ambitious, we want better for ourselves. It's a constant struggle to get ahead. And you know what? I LOVE IT. Competition drives progress. At the end of the day, would you rather work hard and be proud of yourself, or lounge around all day and feel completely unfulfilled, not to mention FUCKING BROKE.

Thank God for The UK though. My little slice of America in Europe. They speak English, understand hard work and the purpose of it, and the plugs ACTUALLY FUCKING STAY IN THE WALL.

I'm a week into this trip and I cannot wait to get home. I miss my friends. I miss Netflix. I miss working for a purpose and relaxing with comfortable fulfillment.

Our gas is cheaper, our food is cheaper, and our people take an active intrest in something other than the family trade.


AMERICA THE BEAUTIFUL, I MISS YOU.


/rant


EDIT- so I realize now that this is less of a rant about America being good and more of a complaint about Europe. Sorry 'bout that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/BotList: Compiling all knowledge of reddit's non-sentient users. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-10 00:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LinkFixerBot: A bot to fix your reddit links! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-10 00:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Linkfixerbot is one of my favorite functional bots. To summon /u/LinkFixerBot, all you have to do is post a broken reddit link. That is, a link for a subreddit formatted improperly.

Example:

r/BotList

/u/LinkFixerBot will reply with a comment saying "/r/BotList"

There was once an encounter between /u/LinkFixerBot and /u/LinkUnfixerBot which resulted in a really long recursion of comments.

EDIT: It was actually /u/UnFixesLinkFixerBot, not /u/LinkUnfixerBot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JiffyBot: A bot that makes gifs of any youtube video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-09 19:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/JiffyBot can be summoned with the command 

Youtube link
Jiffy! xx:xx-xx:xx

The x's are the time of the video. 15 seconds is Jiffy's gif limit.

Example:
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TlTM7Mbk_SU
Jiffy! 0:04-0:10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brytenwalda for 1.154? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-06 20:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was looking into a mod, total conversion without too many factions and well received. I settled on Brytenwalda. I can't seem to find a version for Warband 1.154. Any help?

EDIT: I probably should have read the installation guide. Fixed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Custom maps thread: Found a cool player-made map? Made your own and want to share? Post it here! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-06 03:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Discussion is welcome and encouraged. Lets see some awesome maps! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Pokemon Centers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 23:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are they free, how do they heal Pokemon, ect, ect. Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Professors create Pokemon through genetic experiments. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 20:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It explains why new Pokemon keep being discovered, and why Professors always have 3 completely unique Pokemon with them to give you. They want to send their creations on a trial run of sorts. The professors give you a Pokedex to try to get a good understanding of the Pokemon that other professors and independent researchers have created. And the reason you have to defeat the 8 gym leaders and the Elite Four? The professor wants to know how good the Pokemon they created is.

To tie this into my apocalypse theory, the Professors are the remnants of the pre-war research group that created the Pokemon that killed so many people. Professors want to create even stronger Pokemon, to topple the current regime of the Elite Four/Gym Leaders and install a different government. 

And Team Rocket could be the pre-war military. Just a random thought.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Level Editor help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 02:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm having some trouble with the level editor, and I need some help.

1. I can't figure out the patrol commands.

2. Wiring makes no sense, I can't get the alarms to go off.

3. Is there a way to add a floor below the ground floor? 

EDIT: Fixed number 1, I used trap wiring.

EDIT: Fixed everything, except #2 which seems so be unfixable. Thanks!

EDIT 3: I still have no idea what the rest of the patrol commands mean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm starting to look into colleges, and I would like one with a good MUN program. Any suggestions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-01 02:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only other requirement is that it has to have a solid CS department. I looked at BU, but it seems to be primarily about Law, Music and Business. Any help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All the Teams in the world used to be united. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-31 22:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So once upon a time there was Team Rocket. It was a powerful organization that lead hundreds of loyal trainers. When the war, referenced by Lt. Surge, occurred, Team Rocket was on the losing side. Top leaders in Team Rocket were defeated by Gym Leaders and the Elite Four, and the organization fractured. They split up, and over time the different local branches took on their own names and identities. Branded war criminals, they dissolved into organized crime, trying to bring down the Elite Four and establish their own rule under the new Team, with their own principles.

Team Rocket today exists as the higher leadership of the original team, and is loyal to it's original goal: 

To protect the world from devastation

To unite all people with in our nations

To denounce the evil of truth and love

To extend our reach to the stars above

They act to take over Kanto and Jhoto, while oblivious to the distortion of their original goals in other regions.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do trainers, even openly hostile ones, give you money upon victory? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-30 23:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they have to. Otherwise your Pokemon will attack, injure and perhaps kill them. Pokemon are fantastic creatures, capable of destroying entire towns sometimes. Wouldn't you feel threatened if someone else stood in front of you, with a powerful creature at their command, while you had none? A team Rocket member might hate you, but if he think's you're mugging him he'll throw you his wallet quick.

This also answers why there is such a different progression of technology in the Pokemon world. They have trains, cars, boats, televisions, lighting and much more. But where are the weapons? Why does no one carry a gun in self defense?

There are no guns, tanks, or bombers because such items would be very ineffective against a purely Pokemon army. Got a tank? We'll drown it with surf, it doesn't work anymore. A handgun? That's OK, plenty of Pokemon are so hard-skinned that bullets will bounce off. So nobody is going to bother with a self-defense technique that doesn't involve Pokemon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Transexuals, Transvestites and Transgendered </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-28 01:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't know anything about sex changes, and everything I read is horribly complex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Why there are no stars in pictures of astronauts and spaceships (from /r/YSK) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-26 04:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trying to make a simple point-and-click game. What language should I learn? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-19 16:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a fair amount of knowledge with Java, and a bit with Python. But that is really all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just represented two of my favorite historical figures, was elected Holy American Emperor (again), and won a gavel. What's the best conference you've ever been to, /r/MUN? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-18 23:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is mostly because I'm excited and want to share it, but I also want to hear what you guys have to say. What conference do you feel went the best? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Discussion thread: Position Papers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-16 18:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thought it might be a fun idea to do a discussion thread every once in a while. We'll see how this goes.

Anyway, position papers! Advice, tips, problems? Post them here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When John Dickinson resigned from the Continental Congress in 1776, who replaced him? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-15 19:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had a lot of trouble finding an answer on this subject. I know it isn't a very thought provoking or discussion provoking question, but I thought this would be the place to ask.

Thanks in advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just realized that pistols are not available as a weapon to the player </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-10 23:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the weapons used by enemies in the game are available as tools to the player(s). Gendarme shotguns, Agent submachine guns, watchmen wrenches. But cops have pistols, which are not available to player. Do you think this might be patched in? Perhaps as a new weapon, perhaps as a new character's special ability? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Plagiarism question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-10 00:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bishop Ireton MUN this year is a few crisis committees dealing withe American Revolution. I will be John Dickinson in the Continental Congress.

Dickinson has a bunch of recorded speeches on his position on independence. Would it be plagiarism to copy-paste the relevant bits of his speeches and use that as my position paper? Again, I would be using only his words and none of my own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When is the level editor supposed to come out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-08 03:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just finished Identity, all cleaned out. When is the level editor supposed to come out?

Also, how easy will it be to share levels you have created and use other people's levels?

EDIT: Another question: Is the storyline going to stop at the Pickpocket's Story? Will there be a Lookout's story? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does the Pickpocket Storyline end with another PvP map? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-04 22:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you feel about participation in MUN by non-school clubs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-04 02:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I run a Venture Crew which seems [retty interested in MUN, but none of them go to schools with a club. How does /r/MUN feel about  a Venture Crew rather than a school participating? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Korea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-19 03:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Treaty of Versailles awarded the Shandong Peninsula to Japan after WWI. It was previously owned by Germany.

Now the United States had promised China that if they joined in WWI against Germany, China would receive the Shandong Peninsula. During the creation of the treaty, President Wilson tried and failed to give the region to China, and it was given instead to Japan. Many Chinese felt betrayed by the USA, and China's relations with the country suffered. Many people in China grew attached to the Russian idea of Communism, and this resulted in the Chinese Civil War in 1927. When it was resolved finally in 1949, China was a communist state. Thus, the Treaty of Versailles resulted in Chinese Communism.

Now after World War Two, Korea was administered half by Russia and half by the United States. In 1948, North Korea and South Korea were established as independent nations.

The Korean War broke out in 1950, when North Korea invaded South Korea. The NK forces pushed back the South Koreans to the very tip of the peninsula, when the USA arrived. Their intervention pushed the North Korean forces back to the border and then some, invading North Korea and taking territory for the South.

Enter China. China intervened and fought the US-SK forces to a stalemate. The Armistice was signed, and North Korea and South Korea both remained.

But if China was not communist, and was a capitalist nation like their former friend America, would they have supported North Korea? No. If NK forces did invade, the entire Korean Peninsula would have been united by American Military force and Communist Korea would be no more.

Thus, North Korea, and all problems resulting from it, is the fault of the Treaty of Versailles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best siege army? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-14 19:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you had to have an army made up of only 1 troop, which would you choose? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 00:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would personally go for Rhodok Sharpshooters. They can handle themselves in melee, and their crossbows are deadly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new kind of battle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-01 23:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The streets of /r/Hardboiled were empty as I walked along them, on that chilly, wet night. Light drops of rain fell on my tattered trenchcoat. There were things on my mind, things I just couldn't figure out. Some new subs sprang up overnight, and they were the talk of reddit. /r/Periwinkle and /r/Orangered. What were they for? Every redditor was called into /r/blog, branded with the mark of their team. I could still feel the burning sting of that brand. I pulled up my sleeve to look at it. A small orange circle on my forearm. A sickening joke those mysterious mods at /r/blog pulled.

The brands weren't all we got. They gave us... things. Hats usually, but sometimes we got other items, strange, unusual items. A scimitar, a tacky golden wand. We were told, forced even, to do battle with the other side. It was brother against brother, father against son. The bloodshed had no meaning that was apparent to me, but I knew there had to be some meaning to this. 

Instantly many redditors developed a fervent loyalty to their assigned color. Orangered, my supposed "comrades" flooded my front page with their silly propoganda. Every moment, my mailbox was bombarded by posts of oranges, of mail, of upvotes. It was a get-karma-quick scheme for many. I just wanted to know what was behind all of it.

I spotted another man walking the streets in front of me. My hand went to my hip, feeling the cool handle of my revolver. Hardboiled was dangerous enough as-is, but with this civil war going on any man could shoot me on sight for my color. He hadn't noticed me yet. He was walking slowly, his trenchcoat and fedora protecting him from the worst of the rain. I walked quietly towards him, until I was but ten feet away. He faced away from me, not noticing, and removed a cigarette from his pocket. 

"Rough night, huh?" I said, pulling my lighter from my pocket, but keeping my gun close at hand, "Need a light?"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIME FOR A COUNTER-ATTACK, PATRIOTS! WE INVADE /R/FRANCE AT 16:00 EASTERN STANDARD TIME. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-31 18:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What supplies did the first Australian settlers have when they arrived in Sydney Cove in 1788? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-30 20:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I understand, the first settlement was a penal colony. What supplies did the convicts have available to them when they landed? Also, what percentage were convicts? I assume that at least some were independent settlers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is my approval always so low? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-26 23:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I play on Prince difficulty. Whenever I look at demographics, it says that I am last in the rankings for approval. Even when I don't do anything aggressive, the AI seems to like all the other players more than me. Why?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As an April Fools Day joke, /r/AmIUgly should critique people's clothing and /r/MaleFashionAdvice should critique their facial beauty. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 17:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if the Republic of Texas never joined the union? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 16:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine that the settlers in Texas, despite being from America, were not as patriotic as they are in reality, and wanted an independent Texas. How does the rest of US history play out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An innocent refugee. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-17 05:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "He is dead."

I wasn't sure I heard the words properly, so I asked again, "May I speak with RedditNoir, please?"

"I told you, he died. Shot by one of karmanaut's thugs. Is there anything else you needed?"

I hung up the phone, numb with shock. RedditNoir. Dead. How could this be? 

"Alright, [deleted], that was that. Now lets get you to KarmaCourt."

I glared at him, the vile man. NotaMethAddict. The Justice who would preside over my case. Not that there was anything just about him. He dragged me away, ripping the phone from my hands. He takes those hands and roughly shoves them behind my back, binding them with a pair of rusty handcuffs. Laughing, he pushes me through the halls towards the courtroom.

I remember when KarmaCourt was just. A court of law where reposters and douchebags were punished according to the law. Now it is a hell-hole. A joke. I was arrested on trumped-up charges of "douchbaggery" because I won an argument with one of the Justices. 

My reminiscing is interrupted as NotaMethAddict hands me over to a bailiff. "Here's the douche, [deleted]. Take him to be judged." 

A muffled voice replied, "Sure thing, justice NotaMethAddict." My ears perked up at the sound of his voice. Could it be? His hat was worn low, covering his face with a shadow. He grabbed my shoulders and gave me a slight push down the hall. I stared at the guard. I felt uncertain, but I suspected him to be a friend. I began to lose hope, however, as we turned a corner and headed straight for the courtroom. My heart sunk, I felt a deep despair. But he took an unexpected left, into an empty room. The guard quickly locked the door behind him and whipped off his hat. "MarcusFlarcus!" I exclaimed. He shot me a look. "Keep your voice down! I'm going to get you out of here." He stepped to the back of the room and removed a small parcel. "Put this on," MarcusFlarcus said. I opened the package to see a guard uniform. I quickly put it on, as MarcusFlarcus watches through the window to see if anyone is coming. Once I finish, he hands me a small object wrapped in a handkerchief. "What's this?" I ask. I know the answer, and I dread it, but I must be sure. "You're weapon," replies my friend. "Smith   Wesson 36. Holds 5 shots. Won't do too much damage, but it was the best I could get my hands on." He looks nervously out the window. "What's the plan?" I ask. MarcusFlarcus gives me a nervous grin. "Act discreet, then run like hell."

Opening the door of the small room we begin to walk down the corridor. Stepping quickly, we head for the exit. It almost looks like we are going to get away, but we round a corner and bump into a short man with his head buried in a stack of case files. He mumbles a "sorry," but stops short when he sees us. "Say... I haven't seen you fellas around here before." MarcusFlarcus and I mutter something about being new, and try to push past him. He doesn't budge. "Are you sure you're real guards?" Marcus looks at him and says, "Look, we are on really important business right now. Could you just save the interrogation for later?" But the little man just stands there. "I think I'm going to have to ask you to-" He never finishes. As his body falls to the floor, I stare in horror at MarcusFlarcus's gun. It still smokes with the powder that killed a man. "Marcus-" 

"No time, [deleted]! We gotta get out of here." We run through the halls at a breakneck pace. One more corner and we see the exit, not fifty feet away. We make a mad dash for it, but MarcusFlarcus cries out only ten feet from the door. He falls to his knees. I see the culprit: A guard with a still smoking gun. I run back to my friend, taking my revolver from my pocket. Another shot. This one aimed at me. I point my gun at the guard and pull the trigger. He falls into a pool of his own blood.

 I return to my friend. MarcusFlarcus is out cold, maybe dead. I lift Marcus up and sling him across my back. I run into the parking lot as quickly as I can and jump into the first car I see. A sleek red convertible. I load Marcus into the backseat and hop into the front. I still remember a few tricks from my mob days, and the car is hotwired in short order. I floor the pedal, driving off through the streets away from KarmaCourt. 

After a few miles of driving, I pull off into an alley. My attention then turns to my injured friend. "MarcusFlarcus!" I shout. I slap him on the face to wake him up. He does not jerk awake, but slowly comes to. 

"[deleted]...," he says, "I won't live through this..." I try to protest but he stops me. "[deleted], take care of yourself. I want you to have this." He removes from his pocket a stack of papers. "A new identity, [deleted]. A new life. Go find a small sub to hide out in for a while, and then..." He gives me a smile as he breathes his last, "You are free." 

I drive for hours. In a secluded spot I pull over and give my friend a burial. I would have been there for a while if there hadn't been a shovel in the trunk. Once he is good and buried, I drive away. 

Darkness falls. I drive past a little sign that says "Welcome to Hardboiled". The car pulls up on an empty street and I look for a place to stay. I cruise slowly through the abandoned town and soon I spot a little place with a neon sign hanging over it that reads, "Blueboy Inn". I stop the car and get out. I don't care about the thing anymore, and I reckon it's impossible to keep something that flashy safe in a place like this.

 Stepping into the place, I can tell immediately that it's a seedy affair. Cloth covers up smashed windows, a few gruff-looking men whisper over their brandy. I approach the bartender. "I'd like to spend the night." He eyes me suspiciously. "Rooms are all full. Find another place."

I sigh tiredly. "Thank you," I say. Manners never hurt. I fell a tap on my shoulder. "Hey, fella. If you're looking for a place to stay, you can come to my place. I got an extra bed." What a relief. "How much?" I ask. The man laughs. "Oh, it won't cost you a dime. Just trying to help a stranger out."

We walk to his house. By the time I got out of the inn, the car was gone. I had expected as much. We approach his door and he asks me, "Say, what's your name anyhow?" I almost say my old name. But that's [deleted] now. I glance at the papers that Marcus handed me. ID's, passports, driver's licence, all with my face, and all with the same name. "I'm subject1637," I say. "And you are?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
