<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8986</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 18:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Half hour showers once a day really sounds within normal behavior. If you are feeling very distressed about contamination, though, you can see a therapist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 03:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Opposite for me. Did poorly in hs, went to cc and was more motivated by taking classes I was interested in. Got help after turning 18. Now going to a top school, and got help from the disabled students program. I heard schools only look at your last 2 years before applying to a 4 year, so you're not out of luck if it's something you're interested in. I went to cc for 4 years before figuring things out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 22:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was on Buspar and didn't feel anything different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 19:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's "fun" in the way that itching a scratch is "fun"... It's enjoyable, but also painful. And it's painful in a bunch of ways, such as feeling shame. It doesn't feel nice when someone else notices you're bleeding, and they ask what happened, for instance. But, if someone told you not to itch a bug bite, a first reaction could easily be, "I know!" but that doesn't stop the itch.

It's difficult about the insurance thing. Do you have insurance? You can seek a therapist for yourself, and then bring in your girlfriend. Many therapists also work on a sliding scale based on income, but it could still be very expensive. Bandaids and creams and antibiotics can become very expensive, too, though.

There's also some more resources on the sidebar, such as /r/compulsiveskinpicking and /r/calmhands </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 19:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She needs to understand that it's bad for herself as well as your son. I wonder if seeing a therapist might help, by having a professional unbiased opinion to tell her that the behavior is damaging. I can relate to thinking self injury as not a big deal, but it was because the stress I got from not doing it hurt me more than the behavior would. I would tell myself and others, "skin heals", and whatever defensive things I could think of.

She has to understand not only can there be skin infections, but more so that the behavior is hurting your son and very importantly, hurting you. I needed the help of my fiance and seeing how much my behavior hurt him to stop. Don't get mad at her for doing it, and don't blame her for hurting your son. The important thing is to get her to stop the behavior, and getting angry isn't going to help her. 

I don't know if this will help, but if it's winter where you are, do you think putting on mittens on your son can help temporarily until you can see a therapist? At this point, it could be an out-of-sight, out-of-mind kind of thing for your son. I'm thinking it could be similar to how parents deal with kids itching at bug bites or chicken pox, if that's a resource you want to look at.

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 19:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm also diagnosed with ADHD, and I *think* it's common with people with ADHD to have a type of hyperfocus. Although, ADHD hyperfocus might be more like focusing on a specific task for hours (risking sleeping and eating), instead of a specific topic for months (or however long). I'd be interested to know if ADHD hyperfocus can be like the obsessions that you describe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 20:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw this a few days ago and I started crying because I thought everything except the counting was what a normal brain was like.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 19:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I definitely have this. Didn't realize that obsessions can be related to Obsessions... lol. I compare it to the same feeling as having crushes on people, but it's about things and topics. My last one was about veganism and animal rights, still is a bit. I remember a few weeks ago I was in class, and repeated to myself over and over "do not bring up animal rights" (it was only semi-relevant to the topic). I still brought it up, and felt completely ashamed of myself afterwards especially because people say that whole "how do you know if someone is vegan" dumb joke.

But I don't think of it as pathological necessarily, as I'm not sure I'd want to change it about myself. It's often now a part of my personality, where I know lots about random topics, and I like that about myself. For me, it doesn't have too many negative consequences except perhaps annoying my fianc. I could imagine this would be a problem if I ended up spending lots of money on new hobbies, or started to skip class or work to research my new obsession. I've definitely been on the brink of that behavior, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 09:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you think will happen if you don't do the rituals? The obsession might just be more subtle. What happens if you don't check? Talking it out (such as with a therapist) might make you understand it better.

Similarly, with Pure O, it's not that there aren't compulsions, they just end up being more subtle. Instead of physical rituals, ruminating might be a part of the compulsion. It might be the same subtleness for the obsessions you might be having. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 08:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't read through this, but it might be helpful: http://www.eeoc.gov/facts/ada18.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 04:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely. I've been selling stuff on my college's Facebook sale page. So easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 18:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on the more androgynous side and just want to say that makeup does not make me happy at all! Just want to put out a differing opinion, that it's okay to not like makeup. The only time I wear makeup is to please other people, but otherwise I hate having it on my face, dealing with removing it, can't rub my eyes, etc. Sometimes I'll wear it to dress up as a costume, but it is definitely not genuine to my identity.

On the other side, taking care of my skin is how I deal with the self-care aspect. I remember when I was younger, hearing that Americans spend $ on makeup, Europeans spend money on skincare. Idk if it's true but I kind of was inspired by that preventative thing. 

I don't brush my hair much, but I found a cool cut that I enjoy (shaved on sides and back). I bleach it, too, so I have great hair and only have to deal with it every 1-2 months.

I'm also sort of anti-consumerist, and am happy with less clothes in my life. Throw away clothes that don't make you happy, find a few key pieces that are nice and comfortable. Spend more money on less stuff, and you can generally afford more ethical clothes too, since you aren't giving in to fast fashion. Win all around.

I realized I hate heels, they aren't comfortable, and felt so relieved when I realized I can choose to never wear heels again. I'll stick to my Oxfords.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 19:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I followed her before, too, but it makes me wonder if there could be a way to combine the two? Because at this point, she's now asking for money most likely from young girls who also don't have money, instead of large corporations that have money. For instance, advertising small businesses for some money, which many small bloggers do, and to just be direct about what items are sponsored. I understand that it's a kind of political move, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 19:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not use a pantiliner? It'd stay way better than tissues  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 17:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flour has more than just calories. There's protein in bread (see Vital Wheat Gluten, it's basically protein extracted from flour by rinsing the starch off, it's what seitan is made out of). 

Eggs here are almost $5 per dozen, and eating 2 eggs is much less filling than oatmeal with some fruit in it, and more expensive. 

I personally don't eat animal products so there's my obvious reasoning for it, but I find that it makes my groceries so much cheaper (meat, eggs, and dairy were always the only thing I spent $5+ on). But there's plenty of protein in oats and beans.  People just don't think of them as protein sources because they connect protein with animal products.

Another cheap food I thought of that's great is russet potatoes! Super high in nutrients (more potassium than bananas), I can often find 5 lbs for $3. You can eat that with beans for dinner too, and switch it out with the rice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 08:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you talking about Monami Frost? Her meals tend to focus on plant foods, like smoothies and stuff, in her other videos. When you eat mostly fruits and veg, you need to eat more because a lot of the carbs are fiber calories that don't get digested the same way as other calories. That's why the youtubers eat 3000k and are still thin. The massive amounts of fiber are almost like laxatives. Someone mentioned Unnatural Vegan, she does tons of videos on what she eats in a day, so you can compare to a more normal vegan diet. A lot of vegan youtubers try to spread veganism by pointing out how much they can eat, but as long as you're not only consuming vegetables you should be fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 04:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously- I'd say skip the animal products (eggs, milk, butter), always more expensive. You can get enough protein from the rice and beans. Use canola oil instead of butter, huge container for a couple of $, but you don't need oil, you can "fry" with a few tablespoons of water. Maybe buy flour for bread (you can make your own sourdough without yeast, but time consuming). Get peanut butter. Dried oats, cook with water, eat with bananas. Some micronutrients are missing but it won't be that big of a deal going without for a couple of weeks. For any leftover $, buy high calorie fruits (best bet is bananas but you might get tired of them, you can get a bag of frozen blueberries for maybe $2 at trader joes as a treat), as veggies have good vitamins/minerals but are lower in calories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 07:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm able to use the bus for free with my college, so I don't personally use Instacart. But the bus here has a fee of $2.10, so that's already over $4 for the trip. I'm thinking in cases like this, it would work well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 07:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at one of the top posts of all time on /r/vegan and there's a great bbq recipe. Putting on the bbq sauce beforehand is great cuz the sugars carmelize and create a sweet skin on the tofu. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 06:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gaby went vegetarian after doing the video. Not sure if she still is, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 06:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I think it's surprising because in the west, eating tofu is seen as something for vegans or vegetarians. In Asia, it's just another food and has nothing to do with not eating animal products. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 04:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bananas (19 cents each from TJs). Bread. Peanut butter. Canned beans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 04:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Banana "nice cream". Keep a bag of frozen bananas (sliced 1", freeze flat on a plate, then store in bag). Blend with some cocoa. Add some liquid if you need it to blend a little. Soooo good and you can have so much of it and not feel guilty.

Another quick grab-n-go snack I like is medjool dates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 19:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look up Jenny Mustard on YouTube. She has a whole plant food mentality to her cooking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 08:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To people considering foraging, use resources like fallingfruit.org. They post local available fruit trees and open dumpsters for freegans.

That's generally for a more political approach to reduce waste, id go for a food bank as was mentioned, to get staples.

edit: just looked it up, I meant fallingfruit.org. Changed original link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 03:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pasta is still super cheap, but takes a tiny bit longer to prepare than ramen, and doesn't come with flavor packets. But it's way healthier (not fried like most instant ramen) so it's worth it. I think it's just as cheap, too, since I can make so much pasta from one package. Frozen veggies are also healthier and way tastier in my opinion. The only canned stuff I get are beans and tomato products (puree to make homemade marinara, paste, diced, etc) which I get without added salt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 07:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't tried it, but Instacart is popular where I live. It's $4 delivery, I think flat rate, and they shop at nearby grocery stores.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 09:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it stops being available there, trader joes sells frozen fruits starting at $2. I don't remember the exact prices, but I got mixed berries, mangos, and blueberries last time I went. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 06:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a parent, but I was brainstorming what I would do. 

I just saw [this](http://www.halloweencandybuyback.com/) recently and thought it would be cool to implement that- they "buy back" halloween candy and send it to troops overseas. Or, separate the vegan candy and non-vegan candy, and bring the non-vegan to work (an idea from a blog I saw recently, don't remember which) or donate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 05:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been volunteering nearby at Berkeley Animal Care Services, and they have similarly low rates, I think around 10%. Glad to hear about Oakland! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 18:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could easily be diet related. Are you eating enough calories? Stress could do it too. I've heard it takes 3 months for your hair to react to stressful events, did anything happen 3 months ago?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 07:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/im14andthisisdeep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 08:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got into the disabled students program this past week. All I had to do was get my psychiatrist to fax a form. They're letting me borrow the livescribe smart pen, which records and I can doodle at the same time. The other program they offered was sonocent, which has a 30 day trial I think for anyone. I'm still in the process to see if I can get reading help, like from a program called kurzweil (text to speech). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 07:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I usually just see people post their diets on their ads looking for roommates. In the bay area theres fb groups like the "bay area conscious community housing board", and just checked had 15k people in the group. It's not veg-specific, but you wouldn't be slammed if you were looking for like-minded people in terms of diet/lifestyle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 19:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was all super recent and I didn't know about her before this incident so no worries. But yeah, she took the criticism pretty well and wants to change! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 19:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She made a newer response saying she's educating herself on animal cruelty, watching earthlings and Gary and whatever else. So she's on her way to be a vegan and understanding why people have been so upset at her original video.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 18:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went over the summer and their stock was suuper low. Like, half the store was empty. I assumed they were closing or something. Has anyone been there recently? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 18:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why I love Jenny Mustard on YouTube. She's from Sweden, and uses ingredients that I can get over here in the US. I wish more people knew about her!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 08:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't think about it til now, but maybe jeans too? Are those leather patches that are on the belt? For some reason I assumed it was... anything but leather. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 08:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably a troll, if not, probably has some obsessive compulsive issues </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 08:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy healthy vegan posts such weird pseudoscientific stuff that I'm surprised it's posted on this sub at all. A lot of their videos are purely monetarily based and for views, trying to ride the coattails of freelee and co. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 19:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's good that this happened so early on though, and not after having her owe you money or something like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 18:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like a horrible person to be business partners with. Id cut ties if there's already that much controlling going on and nothing's even been open yet. Find support elsewhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 18:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a video from Raw Vegan Not Gross on YouTube who makes some movie snacks too. Hummus seems risky to put in a bag. She does some funny things like I think a dried fruit necklace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 18:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. Cronometer works best if you mostly eat whole foods, which vegan diets tend to be because it's a bit harder to find processed foods that are vegan. MFP has a larger database. Wish they'd combine! 

I use cronometer because the calories or macros aren't as important to me as getting my vitamins. It's also interesting to see which of what I ate gave me most of whatever nutrient.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 17:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of that buzzfeed video of people going vegan for 30 days. A guy asks what yummy things he can eat to a dietician, and she said something like fruits and veggies. Like seriously... No mention of vegan cookies, cakes, brownies, chips, anything like that. They're in LA, too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 06:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting! Although, I think Americans use garbanzo beans and chickpeas interchangeably. Or... Maybe I've just been reading non-American recipes. I have no idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 08:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you tried roasted garbanzo beans? It's what I eat for the same reason, so if you wanna switch it up, try it! I make my own and use old bay seasoning or sriracha. So good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 06:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could watch or rewatch documentaries, but it to me it sounds like you're feeling like giving in when you're hungry. The solution would be to keep you fed. Bring leftovers to work, and splurge on vegan treats that you can get online or at whole foods or wherever.   Treats could be desserts or unusual foods you might not otherwise buy, like fancy mushrooms or something. That helps the novelty factor of eating out go away for me. Eat huge breakfasts. Don't get hungry. Maybe you could try one of those vegan subscription boxes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 09:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just on this subreddit just out of curiosity, and probably wont think of having kids for another 5 years, but I'm genuinely curious as to why someone might not breastfeed? I'm not trying to shame at all, just trying to learn about pros/cons. I understand finding out you have difficulties breastfeeding after giving birth, or medication, but why would you decide while pregnant? Just curious! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 07:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that's kind of the point. They'll eat guilt-free one day a week, and realize it's easy to do and they feel better for that meal. Then hopefully it spreads to more days, or just eating vegetarian at home, or cut out certain animals, or whatever... I cut out red meats for a year and then turned mostly vegan over night, and full vegan maybe a month after (finished what was in the pantry etc etc). Cutting out only red meat at first made me conscious and mindful of what I was eating, and made me think of the animal, which I previously didn't. I then was able to question myself as to how it's hypocritical eventually, but if someone told me I was hypocritical, I probably would have gotten defensive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 07:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wanted to point out that, at least for Converse, their glue may be made with animal-based glues, so they can't label themselves vegan. It's not something I worry too much about because I see it as a byproduct, but in case you're wondering! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 06:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently have been volunteering at a kill shelter, but you're right. Kill shelters / public shelters cannot refuse any animal that is given to them. Humane shelters, on the other hand, get to choose which animals would be more adoptable.  A pretty high percentage of them do adopt from public shelters, though.  

The shelter says they only euthanize animals that have very high aggression or very poor health, but the euthanasia rate is much lower than the state average. But a kill shelter's the one that has the old animals, black cats, high energy dogs, pitbulls, etc. Humane shelters get to pick and choose. 

It's definitely not a black and white situation.

edit: Just wanted to add that the public shelters are not perfect also, and the reason I clicked this thread was because I dealt with a similar situation of people seeing a complete disconnect between pets and farmed animals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 06:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another way to think about it is how it's more effective to promote Meatless Mondays and Vegetarianism than shaming people for not being vegan (Unnatural Vegan has a[ good video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=epJfzZXCPwc) on this). 

I was talking about dairy with a friend today, who is omni, and she was admitting she hasn't yet made the switch, but agreed dairy is fucked up after what I told her. In the end, I told her that every bit helps- even Meatless Mondays- instead of shaming her for consuming animal products. You could have ended your presentation with something like Vegan Mondays or a week long challenge or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 18:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another similar argument I always hear is people talking about the toxicity of certain chemicals, like fluoride. But if you look at the wiki for toxicity, it's about how much because technically any substance can be toxic at high enough levels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 18:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, my response to her is that everything is chemicals. It's actually just funny more than anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 09:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cook with cast iron, and drink fortified plant milk! 

Someone posted about a cast iron fish, I'm on mobile so I can't find it now but I think it's easy to find. You don't have to get one but it shows how cooking with it helps iron deficiency. Cast iron skillets would do the same. Unfortunately you can't log it into cronometer so it isn't as satisfying. Same with sunlight and vitamin D.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 09:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know you aren't asking, but if you go back, TJs masala burgers are really delicious. Kind of tastes like a samosa in patty form. Not an exact replica but so good as its own thing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 09:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom said this to me, how plants react to music or some bs. Today, she was saying how I wont get all the nutrients, so I showed her my b12 vitamins and she said "vitamins are chemicals!" I don't even know if she believes what she's saying because it's so absurd.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 07:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The meditation aspect of yoga is definitely the worst for me too. But I personally love getting complicated poses. Makes me feel badass. 

But I'd understand if people were constantly telling me to do something I don't like, like running or swimming, I'd be annoyed too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 01:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cats absolutely should not be consuming milk as an adult. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 19:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't know about /r/veganbookclub or the bloggers! Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 19:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As other have posted, I also ask about if there's eggs and dairy, since meat is usually advertised quite well.

Others will probably disagree with me, but I also am more relaxed in restaurants because it's very hard to know every ingredient. For instance, a food item might have honey or some smaller ingredient  that I might not know about, but I try not to worry about it because being so picky doesn't help spread the idea that veganism is doable. So, that's why I'd ask only if theres eggs or dairy as opposed to vegan. If I'm in a grocery store and can see the ingredient list, that's when I'll be pickier.  I'm also someone who doesn't worry about cross-contamination too much, either. There's different limits for everyone. So, you're doing the best you can! Good job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 19:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was there anything you read regarding feminism and animal rights? I was recently thinking about this too, but haven't read anything about it. I could probably google it. Just wondering if there's literature about it, I'd love to read it!

It might sound a bit crazy, but I've been specifically thinking about the dairy industry and their connection to feminism. I feel like the dairy industry makes me feel the saddest out of all the industries, because there is such deep torture that the cows feel when their children are taken away, and their sexual organs being used. I think just like how there's literature about intersections between race, sex, disability, etc, I think species could definitely be added. And the dairy industry is looking at the intersection of sexism and speciesism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 06:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! I was going to go there this morning, I started craving cinnamon buns last night. I haven't heard of Flore, I'll look into it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 01:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cast iron skillet, large dutch oven, medium pot to cook noodles or boiling stuff, small pot for heating small amount of whatever, blender, rice cooker, microwave.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 01:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm from the Santa Monica area so it's a little bit easier for me, but true! I'm walking distance from so many restaurants in Berkeley, since I'm close to campus. Oakland has great places too. Ethiopian veggie platters are always so incredible. I don't make it out to SF much though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 01:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed- I'm currently in Berkeley but usually live in LA. So easy. I think eating out is the most difficult aspect of veganism personally, and theres so many veg restaurants here, as well as lots of vegan peers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 08:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you guys grind up with bone too? I ask because I grind my cats food, which is chicken thighs with skin and bone, but it's kind of a pain in the ass. I usually do about 30lbs at once. Would that just be really shitty to ask to grind that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 06:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find this recipe is a little more difficult on medium firm- it's best with extra firm tofu. Maybe in stir fry? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 20:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed with cheap blender for now. But, if you want super smooth smoothies without any bits of greens, you'll want a high speed blender like Vitamix or Blendtec, which are a few hundred $. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 18:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see. I thought that non-religious fitness-based yoga was a new trend (not bashing, I practice non-religious yoga) but I thought bringing up the limbs of yoga was specifically religious, as I learned about that in an eastern philosophy class I took.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 18:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a great idea! I love sadness too, as weird as that sounds. I also just realized my mom is in the handmade card making business, so that's also why I thought, why not make your own, because that's what I grew up around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 18:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just woke up to this thread. What a funny turn it took. It's funny how my self-deprecating comment turned into selfishness. I can only imagine it stems from some feeling of "hey, didn't you see they talked about their miscarriage so give them special treatment" because miscarriage/death is a taboo subject and people act defensively.

But who knows. The thread is about cards, not my selfish opinion because Reddit threads never change subject! /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 09:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking, why don't you just make your own? Then I remembered I'm an art student, and this is one of the few perks we have. Then I thought about how making hallmark cards would be a great gig. This is my life right now.

Sorry for your miscarriage, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 09:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you disconnect yoga and spirituality? From what I know, the 8 limbs are connected with Hinduism which in my opinion is spiritual. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 09:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's your dissertation about? That sounds interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 09:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With me personally, as I've already posted, I feel like I'm working towards something larger than myself. I'm also more aware of the sameness of myself and other living things. I'm curious how others respond to the connection of spirituality and veganism, not how they respond to my definition or idea of it.

Of course Reddit is mostly atheist (as am I) but there are a few people who are vegan through religion (Jains, Rastafarians, 7th day Adventist, etc) My dad is mostly vegetarian and his reasoning is through his Buddhist practice, so that was my first experience with someone abstaining from eating animals. I specified ethical because asking someone who is vegan for religious purposes probably understands the question in an obvious manner (for instance, ahimsa) and someone who does it for dietary purposes (I know it's technically plant-based) practices veganism similar to me but I would feel disconnected with the reasoning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 08:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you say the same thing to someone who practices veganism through religion? You should learn that people have different journeys than you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 08:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That can be googled, but Wikipedia even says that there's no one definition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 06:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm neither as well, so it's interesting. I would say that veganism has made me feel a connection to what's around me and feel like I have a purpose on something larger than myself, and I've heard other people describe this as well. It's partially awe, but also something else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ethical vegans- do you consider veganism as part of your spirituality? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 05:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For ethical vegans (as opposed to religious vegans, because the answer is obvious), do you consider veganism as part of your spirituality?

I think I do, so I'm just curious!

Edit: to the few of you that want some concrete definition of spirituality, you can google it but it's your own individual journey and it might not be a part of your thought process. That's fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 09:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So interesting. I have generalized anxiety (amongst others) so I always feel it, but I still am not sure I would consider it a disability. I'm not sure why, and perhaps its stigma. Or, maybe because I'm still in school. Although I wouldn't tell another person with a disability who is in school that they were or weren't disabled. Not sure why I have different standards for myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 09:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still in school but working with people with disabilities is totally something I'm into, and what came to mind. Right now I'm taking a class (sort of volunteering) where I help people with disabilities do yoga. I eventually I think want to go into occupational therapy, although the schooling for that seems stressful. I'm almost done with my bachelors, and not sure I want to do more schooling. We'll see.

Also, op: if you aren't super strapped for cash, consider volunteering first. It's less hours, gets you out of the house, gives you experience and training, and you can try out fields of work in a less pressured environment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 08:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the anxiety that probably affects me the most right now, which is driving to new places and parking. I've had many panic attacks while lost (they go hand in hand...). I think I was driving in the wrong direction once (against traffic) but I don't remember too well nor do I want to. Anyways, it was bad. Basically, as shitty as it sounds, you just have to do it. The more you avoid it, the worse your anxiety gets. I always try to think of it as a challenge, and maybe have a treat at the end. Like, I'll go drive to a new ice cream place so I can treat myself with ice cream. But my anxiety never goes away, it's just something that has gotten more manageable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you consider yourself disabled or with a disability? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 08:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And why?

Do you consider it a disability when your anxiety is so bad that you get funding from the government? Because you're on medication? Something else? Just curious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 07:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless you're going for a messy look, make sure your pencil is properly sharpened, especially with more detailed areas (like the eyes). Be aware 100% of your pencil on your paper. When your pencil gets more dull, draw in a less detailed area. 

Either that, or draw bigger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 18:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make some [no knead bread](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=13Ah9ES2yTU). You'll get sick of just rice and beans eventually. 

Go for frozen spinach instead of canned. Get a bag of mixed frozen veggies while you're at it, so you have more variety in nutrients.

A pretty cheap staple I have for breakfast is making my own granola. It's basically rolled oats + peanut butter + maple syrup (I have some cheap blend based on corn syrup I think) + whatever add-ins you can afford (raisins, nuts, whatever). Bake for 10-15 minutes. It's high calorie, and once you make a batch, it's easy to prepare. I eat it with soy milk since I'm vegan and plant based milks are fortified with stuff nutrients that might be harder to come by. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 17:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just curious, what kind of traits?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 05:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of [this song](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cKiXYveusc0) :) It's not really little-y though... SFW but sex-oriented! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 03:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you tried using a block? The way my class started doing it was to stand on a block, hands on the floor and then try. I'm only at the point where I can stay in the air for less than a second, but I just started. 

You can also try to increase your wrist flexibility and forearm strength.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 09:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can also use this to make vegan cheese! Minikin shinners book uses rejuvelac (same thing) to get the sour flavor.

edit: miyoko... not minikin.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 07:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's always been an issue, you might just need to eat more, and not necessarily change the foods you're eating. Our stomachs can shrink if you don't eat large portions, but luckily they can grow too. It feels uncomfortable at first, like you're bloated, but your body will adjust eventually. Drink lots of water in between meals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request - Homemade adult lunchables? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 01:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw a thread on /r/eatcheapandhealthy ([here](https://www.reddit.com/r/EatCheapAndHealthy/comments/3ndtfg/inspired_by_a_question_on_this_subreddit_i/)) on making their own lunchables. Sounds like a great idea, but most of the things people use have meat/cheese. Anyone have ideas for vegan versions?

I'm looking for more snack-y types of food prep more than rice/beans. Finger foods that I can take to class. Some ideas I have are olives (kinda expensive), nuts, crackers, pickles. I'm not looking for meat/dairy substitutes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 06:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I couldn't find it in LA either, even going to a few asian grocery stores. I eventually went to one in Berkeley that's a vegan specialty grocery store that had it (thank god), so look for those? Maybe a smaller health store would have it, or order it for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 07:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on Ting, which is $6 per month per line, and then you pay extras as you use it. The smallest data plan would be under 100mb at $3, so your bill would be $9/month. Let me know if you want a referral code, they've had great deals!

Edit: Wasn't on my computer earlier, but here's my [referral link](https://zm0ttl25i27.ting.com/).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
