<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1637</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 04:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah and the bonus against mounted units is no joke. Firearms might have great burst damage but their overall dps is probably lower than longbows. I forsee a meta of firearmspolearmscavalryfirearms.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 04:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the idea of gift box. As an arena player, that card would be good value and great fun to play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 09:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nekro Virus - There is no peace, there is only the harvest.

Mentak Coalition - do what you want cause a pirate is free, you are a pirate.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 02:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really is "game day." We start at 8:00 AM and usually go past midnight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 23:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel for you. My group is mostly still in college (myself included) but my parents have had a group for like a decade now that ONLY ever got to play on Halloween. 

Good luck. I hope they grow up to love board games as much as their parents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 23:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our group has a 3-course approach to game nights:

Appetizer: Something fun, simple, and short. Played while we're still waiting for everyone to show up. e.g. Splendor

Entree: One game of Twilight Imperium

Dessert: one or two new games that someone brought


It gives a sense of structure and reliability to know that we will *always* play a game of TI. About half the time, nobody brought anything new for Dessert, so we break out one of our faves from the collection. Usually Blood Rage, Game of Thrones, Star Wars: Imperial Assault, or Axis and Allies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 12:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wasn't though. His prediction was that the population would *always* grow faster than than the rate of food production. It isn't.

When a law is only right sometimes, it's a bad law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 12:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calm down John Malthus. We produce plenty of food for everyone, the problem lies in distribution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 07:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fucked Ted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 04:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> loses to 30 Ice Blocks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After my last class, my professor walked up to me and said "it's been a pleasure" and it really confused me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 05:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like a 400 person lecture class. I only spoke up a handful of times this semester. And it's not like she said this to *everyone.* She walked straight to me after the lecture ended. Addressed me by name. I came to office hours *once!* 

It should probably make me feel happy but honestly I'm mostly just confused. Did I really make that much of an impression on her? I liked her as a teacher but I didn't really put any effort into building rapport with her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 02:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Potion of Madness is excellent in this brawl. Silence is actually playable to good. All in all, Priest is pretty well positioned for this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 22:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, ok. I think I initially misunderstood you. That's a good way of thinking of priesthood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 22:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the book recommendation, I'll check it out.

Do you have any source on priesthood being additional to married life? I was taught that they were mutually exclusive vocations. Though, I'm still uncertain about the doctrine of celibacy for priests (I'll trust the Church though, they're much wiser than I). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 21:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm Catholic, and I had the same question. I kind of thought the Church's policy on homosexuality was "Extramarital sex is a sin. Marriage is between a man and a woman. Therefore, gay sex is always a sin."

I get the prohibition on supporting "gay culture," since it's a "culture" of hedonism that celebrates sin. But "homosexual tendencies" doesn't seem like a good criterion for barring a man from becoming a Priest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 06:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paralysis, confusion, attraction and flinching. The total-lock move set </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 16:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be who you are and be that well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 10:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck Joe Biden. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 21:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been playing Menagerie Paladin, hovering around Rank 15, for about a week now. Is Paladin really the ideal class for this deck? 

Priest has great dragon synergy, Hunter and Druid have great beast synergy... Paladin mostly has Murlocks.  And they're, well, Murlocks. 

Any advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 01:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> R---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 23:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an arena player, whose favorite class is priest, this expansion makes me happy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 06:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The question is: will R3 follow Bean, or Achilles? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 06:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got a Priest first run (8-3), and a Warlock second run (9-3). Currently 2-0 as a Priest. 

Gotta say, I thought my Warlock deck was INSANELY lucky. In hindsight, most of my best cards were commons. If that's a middle-of-the-road deck, Warlock is going to be dominant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 10:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nixon for the spying, LBJ for the intimidation, Clinton for the husband-wife relationship, Ford for the overall method...

He's a combination of many presidents, plus some creative spin by the writers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 09:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Magic (my OG TCG) there's a distinction between "owner" and "controller". I saw the "owner" and assumed it would mean me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL That "owner" means the player controlling the minion, NOT the player who originally played it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 07:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I learned this today, when my opponent (Dragon Priest) gained control of one of my minions. I sapped it so that I could replay it, and it went into his hand...

Lesson learned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 17:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Pokemon Naranja](http://pokemonromhack.com/pokemon-naranja.html). Originally in Spanish, can't speak to the quality of the English translation but I know it's considered quite good as a game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 22:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I call it "level one syndrome." Sometimes, I love a game but I only play the first few levels before starting a new game. Skyrim, Fire Emblem, Pokemon... I just love the first hour of the game, and then I get bored, start over, and love the first hour again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 15:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, it was EDH. Borrowed a deck from a friend, then bought my own, then BUILT my own...

I play Standard competitively now, and I follow Modern on and off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 01:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically one, but I had an extremely good, experienced partner. Got a verbal at the next conference, and a real award at the following one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 14:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You forgot the blue feather. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 04:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why ban it, though? Coal is inefficient, unpopular, and expensive. So long as they don't preferentially subsidize it (*cough* America *cough*), it will be completely obsolete within the decade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 14:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Random data ARE beautiful too

FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 17:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like I said. Fun, but not competitive. 

Nekro Virus will undoubtedly have a BIG impact on the board, everything they do is massive and flashy and powerful.

But they aren't super good at the whole "scoring victory points" thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 11:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow you're getting a lot of downvotes, idk why. Listen: your analysis of the situation might not be totally accurate, since you like this guy. So don't go trying to seduce him away.

That said, if what you said is true, his relationship is toxic and abusive. Talk to him. Tell him that you worry about him, as a co-worker and as a friend. Don't deny that you have feelings for him, but don't make that the focus.

Good luck. Sounds like a shitty situation all around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 00:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rowlet and especially Dartrix seem more like Beauty than Brains. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 11:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks captain obvious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 07:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How's the postgame in Sun/Moon? Like, on a scale of X/Y to Emerald. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 07:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah fam. Rowlett = Niles, Rockenruff(midnight) = Keaton, Lunala = Leo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 06:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a scale of X/Y to Emerald, how's the postgame in Sun/Moon?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 06:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a scale of X/Y to Emerald, how's the postgame? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 08:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a Fire Emblem reference.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 06:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm naming mine "Niles." My Lunala will be "Leo," and my Midnight Lycanroc will be "Keaton."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 23:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you get all those clovers?! I thought weeds only came up at random. Is there a way to force weeds to grow in a certain spot?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 23:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To Kill a Mockingbird. My absolute favorite quote comes from that book, 

Scout: "You aren't really a nigger-lover, then, are you?"

Atticus: "I certainly am. **I do my best to love everybody.**"

Easily in my top 5 favorite books of all time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 01:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't a "Never Trumper," I might have voted for him if I lived in a competitive state. I don't, so I voted for my favorite candidate running. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 22:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Voted for McMullin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was wrong about Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 21:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At first, I honestly thought he was running as a joke. "His campaign will never go anywhere," I said, add he rose in the polls. 

"He'll lose momentum after the first debate," I said, as he killed it on stage.

 "He'll never win a state," I said, as he took New Hampshire.

"He won't last," I said, as the field was narrowed to three.

"He can't won the primary," I said, as he did just that.

"The RNC won't let him be nominated," I said, as the delegates declared their votes for Trump.

"He'll be an easy opponent for Hillary," I said, as she was hammered with her email scandals, Benghazi, and more.

"It's a Hillary sweep," I said, as the voting began.

And then Florida went to Trump. Then Ohio. Then Wisconsin. Then Michigan. And North Carolina, and Pennsylvania, and suddenly I looked at the screen and realized that he'd won.

By my estimation, Donald Trump has performed a dozen miracles in the past year. He's defied conventional wisdom at every turn. He won the primary spending no money, running no ads, just speaking his mind. He won the presidency without every having held political office. Before he was even sworn in, he killed an extremely unpopular trade deal.

Now I hear people talk about more things Trump will never do. "He'll never build the wall," "He'll never impose term limits," "He'll never fix inner cities." And I think they're right. I don't think Trump can do any of those things. 

But you know what? I don't trust my own judgement any more. When Donald Trump has committed to a course of action, he's succeeded. He's been right more often than I have. 

So no more predictions. No more judging, no more condescending, no more "Trump can't" or "Trump won't." Because he's performed miracles this year. And when he says he's going to Make America Great Again? I believe him.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 20:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to church. Even if you don't believe, priests will jump at the chance to help someone in your situation. It's a phenomenal resource for those with nowhere to go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 20:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome. Wow.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 16:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From my perspective, I used to hate netdecking because it felt like cheating. I mean, what's the fun of playing Magic if you're using someone else's deck? Where's the challenge?

Back when I was a wee casual player, I thought that the *game* of Magic was easy, and the real challenge (and fun) was in the *meta*game. 

I still like the meta more than the game, but now I realize that actually playing Magic isn't just rules of thumb and simple statistics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 14:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I *hope* so. Still holding out for a Dack Fayden appearance though. #greatestThiefInTheMultiverse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 08:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UR pummeler? That's an interesting take. I run UG. Can I see your list? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 08:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Standard: ug poisonless infect

Modern: Norin soul sisters, zombie hunt

Commander: Mizzix spells, Animar morphs, and Norin the Wary </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 06:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh. Well, I can't fault you for being inconsistent. I mean, you're still entirely wrong, but at least you're wrong across the board instead of picking and choosing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 06:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listen, imagine you're a defense attorney and you're representing a child molester. And your client tells you, in confidence, under attorney-client privilege, that he did it. 

If you win the case, does that mean that you're more concerned about your job than protecting children?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 04:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man I hate this sub. Do none of you understand what the "Seal of Confession" is? If we tried to compel priests to testify about what they hear during confession, *we would fail*. Full stop. They'd just take the contempt of court charge or whatever. Seriously, trying to get priests to talk about confession is pointless. BREAKING THE SEAL OF CONFESSION IS GROUNDS FOR AUTOMATIC EXCOMMUNICATION. They would be permanently fired for giving that testimony, so they just won't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 00:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm counting 59 cards. Also, what's in your sideboard? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 00:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gitfrog intensifies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 00:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy Reformation day, ya filthy heretics 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 13:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New Magic: The Gathering decks. I've only got Standard and Commander decks right now, but I'd really like to buy a Modern deck (preferably something weird but competitive) and a new Commander deck (Norin the Wary ftw). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 01:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Four legs good, two legs *better*! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 21:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[Starke of Rath]] intensifies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 22:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was advertised in a Freshman PoliSci class, so I don't anticipate it being super intensive. Plus, I'm only taking the intro class because my AP CS credit is for Java. If I was taking CS instead of CPE, I'd be in Data Structures.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interview for my first internship tomorrow. How should I prepare? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 21:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Context: College Sophomore, majoring in CPE.

I've got a phone interview scheduled for tomorrow afternoon. The guy said he's looking for someone with "a reasonable object oriented development background" who wants to try "...a non-academic environment." 

All my programming experience is academic. I'm taking an introductory C++ class, and in High School I took AP Computer Science (Java) and got a 5. However, I'm a bit rusty with my Java, since that was a few years ago.

How should I be preparing for this? Is it better to just review my old Java notes, or should I be doing coding problems? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 02:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't deny that it's good, it just isn't format-defining. I don't internally groan when I see my opponent play t1 Inspector. It doesn't win the game on its own, just provides a lot of value for a low cost mana cost.

Ultimately, it's the kind of card that fits into almost *any* deck in *any* archetype. Whereas [[Smuggler's Copter]] and [[Gideon, Ally of Zendikar]] only excel in one or two archetypes.

Or maybe I'm wrong, and I'm underestimating [[Thraben Inspector]] because it's an innocuous 1-power 1-drop common. But I feel like it's not something you can or should plan against, unlike Gideon and Looter Scooter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 00:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[Thraben Inspector]] isn't too big of a deal. It's a versatile 1-drop common with lots of value, it can fit into any sort of deck that's running white.

[[Smuggler's Copter]] and [[Gideon, Ally of Zendikar]] have the potential to be format-defining though, and that's not good at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 06:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun to play, but not too competitive. I've seen them do well but they have NO way to get allies. Can't do diplomacy, can't do tech, etc. Probably the most different from the other races.

But really, there are no differences. There is only the harvest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 15:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gumshoos as Gumshoe

Stoutland as the Judge

Luxray as Phoenix Wright

Blaziken as Miles Edgeworth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 14:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is exactly what bothers me about minority racial movements like BLM. They have a tendency to draw the "us vs them" line along racial barriers. It's like they're *trying* to start a race war. News flash, if there's a race war, white people will win. It's just not a prudent idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 07:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I actually have felt this way about a lot of girls, that I'm "narratively obligated" to crush on them. It's not something I'm uncomfortable with, it's just... weird, how my feelings are influenced so strongly by "what would make a good story." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 07:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was your mutual friend "Cotton-eyed Joe"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 07:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Four years ago, we went to homecoming together. I remember looking at her and thinking to myself, "I know exactly what this person is thinking right now. When she does something, I know *exactly* how she felt, what she thought, what went through her head as she did it." 

We've drifted apart over the years, we're less similar to each other now. But I still crave that feeling of empathy, and I haven't found anyone else who even comes close to satisfying it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 03:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nah probably heart disease or cancer.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 05:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm rather surprised that there are no Panharmonicon variant decks. It's performed well in testing against a lot of these decks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 03:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing university? Well, running a conference for High Schools is usually pretty profitable, low cost, and reliable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 21:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about " ~ etb's tapped.

{t}: add {g} to your mana pool. If you use it to cast a creature spell, that creature etb's with a Garden counter on it.

Creatures with Garden counters on them have reach." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 02:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Traveling Inquisition. I feel like it should be black or blue, but it's such a flavor win with that mechanic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 09:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bloodrage is the shit. It's the game I look forward to most at board game nights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 09:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cannot fathom why Rubio didn't win. He was young! Likeable! Charismatic! Firmly right-wing, but not extremist. He could both unite the party AND deliver independent voters, plus swayable democrats. This election would have been a piece of cake if it was Rubio v Clinton. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a really big fan of this concept, been trying to get [[Ghirapur Orrery]] to work for a while now.

Have you tested any RG brews of the deck? [[Bedlam Reveler]] seems good. [[Fiery Temper]] is obviously excellent. Plus [[Stromkirk Occultist]] and [[Key to the City]] work well together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ...the second a woman becomes pregnant she loses all rights to her body...

Of course a woman doesn't lose the right to bodily autonomy. But she doesn't get the right to destroy her child's body.

 and it's acceptable to make her suffer further.

If not being allowed to kill an innocent person is "suffering" then yeah, it's acceptable. Just because someone is causing me distress doesn't mean I have the right to kill them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   If you think it's okay for a woman to further be made to suffer after a rape I guess we can't have a discussion

This is a direct violation of rule 2. Please keep the rules of this subreddit in mind when you comment.

 Epilepsy, blood pressure, etc can all cause danger to the woman early on. There are medications, yes, but not all women respond to the safer ones. Pregnancy has also been known to make seizures more frequent and worse for women who already have them. For instance, I know a woman with epilepsy who has grand mal seizures frequently even though she's medicated.

And this is in direct violation of rule 1. Factual claims have to be supported with valid citations.

I was going to report you, but after a cursory look through your post history, you don't strike me as a troll. Please be more mindful of the subreddit in your future comments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 17:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was unfamiliar with this term. After a brief google search, I think it's probably fair to make ectopic pregnancy the sole exception to an abortion ban.

However, I'm still mostly in the dark about this issue, and I'd like to hear what /r/prolife knows about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 10:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pro-life movement isn't generally in favor of exceptions for rape or health issues. The former is punishing the innocent child for the rapist's crime, and the latter just doesn't exist. By the time a fetus is big enough to cause health problems, it's viable and can be born via c-section. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 10:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been fiddling with Orrery for a bit, and this deck is pretty similar to my build. Have you considered Kiora or New Nissa? The latter in particular seems real good, considering her ult works nicely with Orrery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 18:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This worked! Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any place on campus that I can connect my 3ds to wifi? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 01:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eduroam won't work for the 3ds, and I live on campus. Any fellow hokies know where I can connect to the internet with my 3ds? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 20:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None taken, I understand what you mean. But our adviser (the head of the Political Science department) suggested that we appeal to any relevant departments to get funding for the conference. Bear in mind that this *is* a debate team, and the topics for committees include the Center for Disease Control and the Women of the United Nations. Is it just that it works differently at different universities? Maybe some colleges will fund student activities, but others won't? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much money do academic departments have to fund student activities? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 19:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a student at a large (30,000 undergrad) state school, and I'm looking for financial support for our Model UN team to attend a conference next January. Our faculty advisor suggested that we appeal to any relevant departments to get funding for the competition. 

Problem is, we have no idea how much we should be asking for. The conference is going to cost ~$1,000 per delegate, and it's not feasible unless we can get department funding. How much can we expect to request/receive? Is $10,000 chump change for a big department in a big school, or is $500 a more reasonable amount to ask of them?

For clarity, we'll be asking every department we can. Poli sci, history, business, engineering, etc. Engineering is by far the biggest college at my school, and would probably have the most money to sponsor us with.

Please let me know if this isn't the right sub, and point me towards a more appropriate place. Thanks!

EDIT: There is a "Student Activities Fund" that pays for this sort of thing, but we've kind of reached our limit for how much funding they'll provide us. So we're looking for specific funding from academic departments to offset our costs.

EDIT2: We know how to sell it to the departments, tell them why they should financially support us, split the costs and ask different departments to front different costs, etc. I'm really just trying to figure out how much we should be asking for from each department. I have no idea how "department funding" works, as far as I know each department might not even *have* access to any funds. Or maybe they've got a million in grant money just burning a hole in their pocket. I don't know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 14:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I run Long Tusk Cub and Empyreal Voyager as alt win cons. Cub has the massive benefit that you can pump him above a 4/3 if necessary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 04:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm building Bad Infect (UG Electrostatic Pummeler) and the entire deck cost me about $20. It might not turn out to be the most competitively strong deck, but I figure at that price point it's worth a shot.

The deck is combo, and can pretty consistently win by turn 4-6. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 03:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're looking to build a cheap, competitive deck I'd recommend either aggro (WR Humans), or combo (UG Pummeler/UR Aetherflux Storm). Alternatively, you could look into mtggoldfish's Budget Magic brews. The ultra-budget versions are probably within your price range, and are often decent decks. 


As for your question on the two paths you can take, just buy singles. It's never really worth it to buy anything else. Once you know what you're looking for, get a decklist together and order all the cards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 03:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sleeving up UG Electrostatic Pummeler for FNM next week. I'm calling it "bad infect." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 00:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I think the reason I'm attracted to you is that you remind me of my stepdad"

I honestly couldn't believe you could fit that many red flags into one sentence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 00:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you're only trying to get 1 creature's attack through, [[Renegade Tactics]] is strictly worse than [[Slip through Space]].  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 23:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sleeving up UG Pummeler (or "bad infect" as I like to call it) and so far its remarkably consistent. Red just doesn't give the deck anything but energy synergy, and frankly synergy isn't what I'm looking for in a combo deck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 21:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is RG Pummeler really better than UG? Losing access to counterspells and [[Slip Through Space]] hurts, and instead of [[Uncaged Fury]] you can just pay 3 more energy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 10:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry! Your layout looks good. But there's no objectively better layout, it's all a matter of taste. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 09:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking that they should make the DOT *way* slower. Like, double the time it takes to kill. That gives enough time to use a healing ability so the ult doesn't kill you by itself. It gives the ability a much higher skill ceiling, as you still have to finish off your enemies. And it's more interactive, because getting hit by it doesn't just mean "you will die in 5 seconds and there's nothing you can do about it." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 07:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheerios is actually pretty decent, a friend of mine has been fine-tuning a list that's remarkably consistent. 

Have you considered UG/RG Pummler? It's pretty cheap to sleeve up, and it feels like playing bad infect in standard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 06:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes it'll log me out during a game. Usually right at the beginning, and by the time I log back on the enemy team is already at the payload. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 06:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a total noob, but is Skye's ult not brokenly OP? Before and after the patch. The blast radius is almost unavoidable. It has a high ceiling of value, capable of killing the entire team. And it doesn't require much skill to use effectively, you just stealth, run into the enemy, and ult. What's the community's consensus on this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 19:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[Disperse]] can return empty vehicles, as well as combo pieces like [[Aetherflux Reservoir]]. It's close but I think disperse is better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 08:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're a domestic terrorist organization, and the only reason they're not classified as such is because the left is too scared of being called racist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 05:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> idk what episode but at one point Mallory asks Archer "what year is it?" and he responds "Thats... that's actually a really good question."

There's no canonical setting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 01:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, I thought Flash was one of the best implementations of the HM system. It isn't strictly necessary to get by. The move can be learned by many pokemon, and has a consistent value throughout the game in both combat and utility. Sure, they could've made more dungeons where Flash was necessary, and they definitely should've given the move greater accuracy, but it was overally a pretty decent HM implementation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 01:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> KILL THAT FIFTH GLYPH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 01:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woah there Charles Benedict Davenport. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 21:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fundamentally, it is a question of individualism vs tribalism. Black Lives Matter is a movement that wants to improve the situation of the black *population*, not necessarily black individuals. BLM holds *all* police accountable for shootings of unarmed black men. They hold *all* white people responsible for slavery and oppression. When they protest the shooting of a black man by a police officer, it doesn't matter whether the violence was justified or not, because what they're *really* angry about is the fact that black men don't have a good relationship with their local police. 

The reason it outrages me is that this tribalist thinking goes against everything Martin Luther King Jr. stood for. BLM genuinely doesn't care about the content of one's character, only about the color of their skin. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 06:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> blade make sense forever touch ripple charm

Result: Unicorn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 01:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait... in the comics he was sparky-sparky-boom-boom? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 17:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Witty, introverted, and independent. We need to be there to help and support one another, not to be the other's sole reason for existing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 12:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aether Tradewinds has been phenomenal in UW Spirits testing. It's extremely versatile, and bouncing one of your own is often an upside, dodging removal or bouncing a tapped land and immediately playing it as your land drop. It's an incredible tempo piece and I HIGHLY recommend at least testing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 12:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also Aether Tradewinds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 06:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's gonna be Start your Engines, Dramatic Reversal, Lupine Prototype and a *whole* lot of vehicles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 03:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Negate. 2 mana to counter a PW/wrath/targeted removal is good enough to see maindeck play. The fact that it doesn't counter Reflector Mage hurts, but not enough to stop Negate from being maindeck worthy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 15:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really just our K-12 education that's slipping. America still has most of the world's best universities, and students from all over the world still come here to study and earn their degrees.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 19:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting card. It both removes a creature and eats an opponent's removal spell. That's some serious tempo. Could it see play in the sb of UW Spirits? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 22:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh boy, I've been brewing a deck focused on Nahiri's Wrath/Bedlam Reveler to madness-discard your entire hand at once and this is the *perfect* card for it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 03:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair. I mean, I want to cost it as aggressively as possible but I'm very wary of my hypothetical cards being overpowered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 03:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly I was gonna make it 1UR but I feel like that's too cheap. Notice that this doesn't say "non-land," so you could be playing mostly islands and just splashing red for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 00:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scrying, top-of-library tutors, putting cards from hand onto top of library... There are a lot of effects that would make it work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 22:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol yeah. But can you believe that we play a *card* game called *Magic* and there isn't any benefit to being able to do *magic tricks with cards?* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 21:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Magic Trick**

2UR

Sorcery

Reveal the top card of your library, then shuffle your library. At the beginning of the next End Step, reveal the top card of your library. If both cards revealed this way have the same name, take an extra turn after this one. Exile ~.

*Is this your card?* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 07:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how recently have you been getting this issue? I just started this evening after my csec club said it was a good starting point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
