<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject758</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 20:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I miss this!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 07:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had some homemade smoked ham, cut into strips kind of resembling bacon or really thick pancetta to my vodka sauce. I just added like, what I think was the tip or small chunk of a scotch bonnet sans the seeds to this vodka sauce recipe, and it was pretty bomb. (I made a ton of sauce haha) The result was an all pleasantly warm-spicy, but not overbearingingly hot pasta. It was very good. I've done it with habanero before and I agree, it's pretty good as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Catsitting rambunctious non-stop meowing young cat that keeps begging for food and attention. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 07:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adopted 1 yr 2 mnths female Calico, her name is Daisy. Daisy was in a house with 28 other cats, and lived with a really fat old hoarder until she was taken away by a shelter a couple cities away. 



Fast forward, my sister who doesn't clean her apartment (seriously, theres maggots and silverfish) obligates that I cat-sit for her when she's gone. I'm thinking, maybe the cleanliness has something to do with the cats behavior or my sisters and her boyfriends disappearance. anyways this isn't about my sister- For the next week and a half, I have to cat-sit Daisy. a pretty big duplex, two litter boxes in two separate rooms, eats fresh organic chicken with her food half of the time.

 (her meal plan is 2 small fancy feast cans a day over the course of 3-4 meals,
 first fed at 5:30am or earlier ..wtf,
 and then 10AM, 
and then 3PM-6pm.  

a palmful of dry food/organic chicken shreds or ground beef is included usually)

So for the past 3 days, I haven't been able to sleep. She sleeps for like- 5 hours a day (so far) and she is constantly meowing, jumping on me while sleeping, knocking over things/breaking them, sitting in the kitchen begging for food, yowling at like 2AM in my ears.. I haven't actually been able to get any sleep. Keep in my that meal plan was a vets/my sisters, so I've tried to push the meals later in the day but she keeps fucking YOWLING. I really need help guys. Do I buy Feliway or should I lock her in a room at night? 

I can't sleep. :/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 23:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would really want to try making a roasted duck with mint sauce, and maybe some soba noodle salad tossed with fresh herbs, edamame, and shitaake. But eh, it's a maybe! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 21:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If anyone wants to meet up, message me! Everyone in my neighborhood seems like they're red or blue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 10:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet, thanks! this games gonna make me get out of the house more. Mind I mention near the diamond heights Safeway and Christopher playground, I caught two jigglypuffs and I've seen pikachu around but I haven't caught one yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 07:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in Diamond Heights near Glen Canyon, I've found many eevees and eventually evolved one into a Jolteon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 05:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. I live near twin peaks ;-; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 19:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Girl with teal blue hair here. I'm Asian too and Asian hair can be pretty stubborn taking in bleach. Having an orange tint to your hair is totally normal and bleaching it again using the same process you did (in a couple days) should bring you to a more yellow banana blond tone. If your scalp is bleeding or skin is really itchy, I'd wait a week till bleaching again. You can also use a purple toner shampoo or a toner to get the brassy parts out of your hair before you dye it.I used a combination of blue velvet and forest green (I think that's the name) from Special effects, but the green from Joico works as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 22:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took all my trazadone and washed it down with alcohol, in an attempt to kill myself. I had my stomach pumped and the entire time nurses and emts were trying to not have me sleep on them. it was September 11th, 3 years ago. I woke up really confused, not really scared, but I didn't know what I did. I feel like I hit my head really hard. The next week I just put the pieces together, I was just some depressed sop trying to off myself lol. I guess I'm doing better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 22:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully he gets what he deserves in prison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 18:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time I received a dick pic I just texted them back a picture of a bigger dick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
