<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9229</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 17:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How the hell do you even do that? At my OSUT at Leonard Wood, the doors to the barracks were locked and alarmed and there were always at least one DS in the CQ office at all times. Getting by them (not to mention the locked door and alarm)without getting noticed would be one hell of an achievement. Also your platoons recruits on CQ would bust your add for trying to leave the room.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 13:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. I can confirm the double major part of this. I'm only a freshman, but I'm double majoring in ASE and ME. It's only another semester to get a ME degree in addition as well and that's only to take requisite classes. So in the end, it's a 5 1/2 year program for two degrees. Not bad  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. I've been there and visited the USS Wisconsin and it does look like this from a certain angle. It's really freaky the first time you see it. 

On another note, I was there visiting one of my fathers friend friend's son who was serving as an intelligence officer on the USS Dwight. D. Eisenhower at Norfolk Naval Station, and got a tour of the ship from him, which was even cooler than the Wisconsin.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just accept it. I'm pretty libertarian, so some of the politics they support don't line up with mine, but lots of their commentary on social issues lines up with my beliefs, and so does of course the anti-authority vibes that come from anything punk derived. You don't have to agree with someone 100% to find common ground. I support a lot of the same stuff they do, but in the end, they make great music and that's all that matters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I zip ties it to the factory bumper  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I assumed. That must be a pain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it's confined to the 4.0. The 2.5 is pretty much a 4.0 with two cylinders lopped off. I have two YJs with the  2.5 and they both idle a bit odd at some times as well. One has 80k and the other has 140k. I wouldn't worry about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 12:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do they get these out of the tunnel once it's done drilling?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Add wierd floaty wheel things and it could be one of the vehicles from Overwatch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pilots best bet, had the prop blade broken off, would have to be to shut down the engine at that point and attempt to glide to a landing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the "not again" refers to him losing it in the speeder chase at the beginning of AoTC.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wondered what those threads were when I first bought my YJ. Just seemed kinda pointless since a lot of people take the doors off anyways.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish we would go back to the OD (and maybe tan for desert environments) uniforms for non-combat applications. They just look so much better. Would probably be cheaper to manufacture to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *ding* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PRECISION GERMAN ENGINEERING </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 03:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The hunter is his trap  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 00:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an H1. A very different beast than the H2 or H3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After bondoing and painting the past two weekends, I got my rocker guards installed. Nothing fancy, just some adhesive ones to cover up some minor rust and prevent scratches. 

The YJ in the background belongs to my brother. Both are '95s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Installed some rocker guards on my YJ. Looking much cleaner now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 23:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why aren't these more popular? They look stunning and have some pretty good specs to back it up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 23:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Similar to discovery's Junkyard Wars.  Great show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 23:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poor Scout didn't deserve this. Although it's cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 21:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/prequelmemes is leaking  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 12:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant Battlefront 2 lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 02:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I mean, the original BF2 wasn't much different.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 20:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cute snek </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 12:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the same problem. I've had four different cars in the past 4 years. First was a 1997 Ford Ranger, then a 1985 Ford Ranger, then a 1997 Dodge Dakota (absolute piece of shit btw) and now a 1995 Jeep Wrangler YJ. I love my YJ, but damn. The amount of work I need to do to it is ridiculous. Something is always broken. Right now my rear diff leaks, the catalytic converters heat shield is loose, and a windshield wiper arm fell off on the highway. On top of that, there's an area I bondoed that I need to paint before I cover it up with rock guards. Plus I need to flush the radiator and do an oil change.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. Finally a car LW didn't ruin.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 03:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a lot of catching up to do. I haven't watched since season 3. [](/bjwhy) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 03:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've definitely never done this when doing exhaust work on my Jeep.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have gloves in mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Knockoffs are hit or miss. Gatreon blues are the closest to cherry Blues. Others kinda suck.  Build quality of the K70 is phenomenal. It's my perfect keyboard. My only wish is that it had a standard sized bottom row and was RGB.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do 3k @ 70mph in 5th gear in my YJ everyday, not too far off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have this. Ama. It's a great keyboard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 12:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much this goes for any scenario of an invasion of the US. It's just not possible, without devastating (probably nuclear) airstrikes before, and at which point, why would you invade a glassed continent? Also MAD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 12:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Partially. And just different art styles. I like the Rebels art style personally. It's gotten more refined as time has passed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 12:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One thing that always bothers me about space battles is that the ships are always the same side up. Doesn't really make sense since space has no plane of reference for up/down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A 290 can lol. I get at least 144 fps in some games at 1080p easily. I have a Asus VG24QE, which is 144hz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pull the center distributer wire out. Or at least that's what my father does to me when he doesn't want me leaving. :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even have it, so no chance of using it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounds stupid as all hell as well as making a eyesore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 14:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks a hell of a lot like an Kaiser M715. I love it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 13:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well he's in the Clone Wars and Rebels, so not entirely cut.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone made a similar one for the CJ7 as well. No clue who, but I was about to buy one I found on Craigslist and put it on my YJ.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We'll jeep is also a type of vehicle. Or at least was until it became a brand as well. The FJ40 is a jeep, the Samurai, etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 18:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 1995 Wrangler.

I still love it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 14:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha. I have like 5 of these I got from my grandfather's workshop after he died. Nothing like old Craftsman tools. I love them  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 14:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that was only the nuclear variant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 14:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You joke but [Fallout: Equestria: Project Horizons](http://falloutequestria.wikia.com/wiki/Fallout:_Equestria_-_Project_Horizons)

Over 1.5 million words  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not that bad compared to what I see a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol what. I've had the same pair of Chuck's for years and they still look good, just a little worn, which is exactly the look needed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha. That looks almost as bad as my 97 Dakota when I bought it. Such a POS truck. I had the stock brakes and rotors at nearly 200k miles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. I put one in my Jeep since I got a bigger battery for it. Works well and has rubber  corners so this type of stuff doesn't happen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but hacking an ulting Genji is the best since he can't do anything. It's kinda sad. Like hacking a Pharah or Tracer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 03:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's to destroy the runway and make it unusable, so yeah, it's needed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same with Sombra. It sucks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 14:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None. Except maybe my HOA will have a fit because it's currently on ramps in my driveway because I'm working on the exhaust which decided to break all it's old rusted out hangers when I went off road a few weeks back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 14:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Jeep. Tiny 2.4l 4cyl in a massive engine bay? Yes please. Can change the oil without jacks? Yup. Simple as simple can be. It's pretty much a CJ7 with a nicer dashboard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 14:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that I'm one of the few people in the world who liked the Mustang 2. But then again, I like wierd malaise era cars like the Pacer and Pinto as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 14:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still think the Z31 looks so much better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 14:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sold my 85 Ranger (4x4 too!) for $650. The first gens really aren't worth anything if they have a V6 since that engine is one of, if not the worst engine ever created by Ford.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 14:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> US liberal is pretty much the opposite of what the rest of the world calls liberal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 03:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a 90's AWD Civic Wagon  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 03:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think the Civics did, but im pretty sure the Tercel did.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't it just be a heck of alot cheaper to convert to EFI than to buy this nowadays? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rollover lawsuit waiting to happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Game is linked to the Xbox, not the account. Or just a disc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 13:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does that voiceline change based off the situation? If not, it should.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah and the 6.2 diesel in the CUCV line and early Humvee was pretty junk. The 6.5 was a little better though. Both engines are inefficient and don't produce nearly enough power for their displacement either, although they'll run forever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still better than a stock Aztek </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 14:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True fear is using the stock scissor jack that is stored in my '95 Wranglers  engine bay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Buying] I know this sub frowns on gaming stuff, but I'm looking for a new keyboard and could use some suggestions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 02:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A newer Ford Ranger fits the bill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a carbed 2.8l V6 in my '85 that made all of 95 HP (and that was new)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 00:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People keep them. I own like 12  myself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 00:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On top of a brush pile in the woods behind my house  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 23:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What type of Jeep ya got?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently spent a week in a hospital as a patient and wasn't even allowed to have my cell phone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 14:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah definitely this. I play Overwatch with my mouse set to 300-400 dpi and the extra space is great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 14:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Always on my YJ.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 22:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And then they said fuck this shit and left.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 20:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Baconreader too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rubicon wheels for the JK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1997 Ford Ranger 4 banger, 5 speed that I shared with my brother.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steering wheel off center </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a '95 Jeep Wrangler and the steering wheel is turned about 20 to the left when I'm going straight. I don't think it's a problem since the solid axels means it's not an alignment issue. It's been like this for over a year since I bought the vehicle, and I've had no issues, but could this cause any problems in the future? Just got curious when I saw a similar thread asking a similar question.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not having a top on 90% of the time helps. Other than that, my interior is bare metal and fiberglass, so it never really smells no matter what.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 02:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm this. Owned a '85 as well. Ridiculously overcomplicated and unreliable as hell. I loved it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 02:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It likes to fill up with water when it rains because I can't close the vent that let air in from cowl on the hood of the Jeep.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 02:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I have is a Jeep 1945 hat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should. My 1997 Ranger 2wd had Jeep Wrangler wheels on them, which are all interchangable (lug pattern wise) from '87-'16, so you should have no problem. I've also had Ranger wheels on my '95 Wrangler, so it works both ways.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but those are ugly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the utility bed, plus the fact that the rest of the world usually doesn't get those types of trucks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something has gone seriously wrong if an E-1 is flying lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soldier 76s E and Q are swapped in the pictures.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will these fit a Corsair K70? It's just the bottom row that is different from normal, so these should work, correct? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  First season felt like a poor knockoff on Firefly if I'm to be honest. It wasn't bad, but it felt a bit clique.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Danger Ranger rat rod! I love it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 00:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not from a Jedi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 00:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not from this picture, but from a previous thread where someone linked the build post on a forum. (I think it was pirate4x4.)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 21:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's pretty sweet. Those are Dana 60s so it's probably very capable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 21:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Immediately followed by We Will Rock You. I swear all the radio stations near me think they're the same song. Always played back to back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 16:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Culturally, Its definitely European. Geographically, I kinda think if it as akin to what Mexico is to North America. (Not it a bad way, just southern Europe)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 16:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happened? I don't think you can make it look better without replacing it. Maybe clear tape? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 16:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just make a other post there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 23:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> California </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 23:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Southern Ohio sounds right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 23:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the Disney XD cartoon Star Wars Rebels. Kinda a post ROTS/pre ANH counterpart to the animated Clone Wars series </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 23:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind but not really. It's an animated series that takes after ROTS and before ANH. It follows the story of a small rebel cell/ crew of a ship fighting the Empire. Ahsoka is in it, but it's not really a sequel and she isn't a main character. It's really more about the formation of the Galactic/Rebel Alliance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try a YJ with just the stock soundbar. Literally unhearable unless you turn the volume up all the way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SW:Rebels vs Ahsoka was pretty difficult for him
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much do these normally run? I'm debating selling my Saiga for one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't get past the graphics. I love it when it came out, but I just can't play it now because of the graphics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hudson, Ohio.

Totally not biased  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every day at my University </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a lot of Dakka </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm wearing the skinny Flex right now. They're like leggings. So comfortable and look amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love my American Eagle jeans. The skinny Flex 360 ones are so comfortable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 23:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I met him at some skateboarding event once. He was seriously a nice guy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 23:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't let a Marine hear you call him that. He's a drill instructor, not a drill sergeant. It's a Marines vs Army thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dodge made a first gen Dakota pickup convertible in the early 90's.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 14k, which is about right for a 710k </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
