<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5711</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-25 23:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i do disagree because I'm in a wheelchair if you look those spots are larger because wheelchair ramps have to be able to open up to get the wheelchair out.

but good use of meme </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-25 23:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i am sure my dad thinks the same thing when i was a teen. 

he had 6 girls in he house at any given time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-25 23:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i am not into incest but i think if its between 2 consenting adults 
then who cares go a head  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-24 22:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what if they HAVE a pretty face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-24 02:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this picture i think i was i last week on post secret 

but i think thats exactly how i feel  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-23 22:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> she doesn't seem that concerned about it

or in much pain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-23 22:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i fully fucking agree with you 

everyone is over sensitive and take everything to heart.

i dont believe in being politicly correct either  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-23 22:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be so upset that she was going to the same school i know this is drastic but personally i would put in for a transfer to another school.

You can not grow as a person if your sister is there you will make every decision in school as if your sister was right there next to you with your parents.

all you will be able to think about is what would they think and that will wreck your collage experience.

i know that personally for me i am being followed by my sister to a city that i picked purposely to get away from her and I'm PISSED so i could not imagine how you feel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to become vegan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-23 05:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i want to become vegan but i don't even know where to start 

and how do i convince my meat LOVING wife to at least give it a try 

thank you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to do a green tea fast </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-23 05:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm new to the fasting world but i want to do a green tea fast 

i really would like to do it but i cant find much info maybe you can help.

any info would be amazing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-23 01:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it was by a male and my own father </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-23 01:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes i have been sexually molested and i got therapy and moved the hell on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unpopular Opinion Puffin (story in comments) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-23 01:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-22 21:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when i was 15 i told my bf for 2 years i was on birth control 

nope i wanted to become pregnant and i did  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-22 21:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i am canadian an believe that Starbucks is way better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People that have been sexually abused: Get over it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-22 21:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 04:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well I'm already married 

but i don't have my high school yet and i guess that is what is making me feel like I'm so far behind everyone

and i had to give a year of my life up to be with my mother who was very sick but has gotten better so i can now move on  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> i feel 21 to old to turn my life around </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 04:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i am going to turn 21 on march 20th and i am about to get my life started 

go back to school 

get my own place 

finally get everything i want started and get my goals straight 

but i feel like 21 is to old to actually do something with my life 

i hate feeling like this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 21:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> those LEGS  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 21:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my mother is a size 12 and comfortably fits in a airplane seat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 23:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BUT BUT theres is cheaper 

fat privilege!!!!!!!!!!!!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Me [20F] with my wife [31 F] Wife thinks i am lazy because of my disability </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 02:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have been in a wheelchair for 10 years i have a genetic disease that has made my muscles to deteriorate. i have been married to my wife for 2 years 

so i don't have any strength i can't even lift a pillow

there is not a cure or any known treatment that work.

but all the time she says to me just learn to walk its not that hard.
or if you just worked harder then you could walk.
or she will push me and say well if you worked out your muscles they would work.

no thats not how it works i can not grow muscles.
what do i say to her.

i have MD and she wasn't like this before we got married

---   
**tl;dr**: Wife thinks I'm lazy for not being able to walk  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-18 21:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-17 22:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my nephew is in size 5 diapers the largest one and is in almost 18 month clothing and he's only 7 months he's not fat he's just really really husky  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if I'm wrong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-17 22:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what if I'm wrong and my mother was a great mother and that maybe I'm just a mean hateful person 

who hates her for no reason 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just a post about my mothers beliefs do any of these should like your Nmom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 21:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> things my mother believes:

-Emotional/mental abuse is not real (its made up)

-Doesn't believe in doctors 

: Days doctors are purposely trying to kill people, they know nothing, they don't care and if i ever go to the doctors again i will DIE they will (she yelled that).

-Doesn't believe in police 

-Only believes in homeopathy medicine 

- Doesn't believe in school or teachers 

: school only teaches kids to do as they are told and never question everything and to not talk back like the government wants 

-Doesn't believe there should be any laws other then don't murder.

-Doesn't believe any drugs should be illegal.

-Believes that mental illness is fake there is no such thing 

-Says that she will not renew her licence because theres no law that says they she needs one theres only bylaws and they don't count 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 21:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my sister does the same thing with doing anything to get me going. also she does the questioning my intelligence at everything.

but every time i say to my nmom about it she says well she never got the attention she needed because your disabled and were sick when you were younger.

basically she saying its ok for her to hit me in the head with a chair ( just one example i can think of) because i am in a wheelchair.

she's just the worst person i know next to my mother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 21:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i also smoked for 3 years 

i quit on Halloween in 2013

i know this is a bad opinion but for me i smoked half to 3/4 of a pack a day and i didn't find quitting smoking VERY hard i just threw away the pack and moved on with my life.

i never even craved 1 smoke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ATL: Fat shamer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 05:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can someone find the stuff where she is fat shaming 

like before she was fat.

thank you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: what do Nmoms do/ act like </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 05:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i cant seem to find a simple explanation.

thanks guys  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Being forced to love family </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 22:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> for as long as i remember i haven't really loved my emediat family 

but i always loved the side of the family my mother HATED my nana and aunt(mothers sister)  i am just like them its like i was my aunts child 
i always suspected thats why i was not liked as much as my there 2 siblings 

but i have always hated my sister the most next to my mother 

but people always tell me she's the only sister you have 

she's your mother you have to love her 

you will change your mind and love your family as you get older 

BUT that never happened 

i feel that i am being forced to love people i really don't love 

anyone else get this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 22:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow this is a strong confession and i think that you did a VERY good thing 

good luck  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 02:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i want to know if there are others like me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 02:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i don't know about that but she gets a great kick out of destroying my life 

has to have children before me after i have been trying for a little while rubs it in my face 

anything that she might do better then me she shoves it down my neck

she even named her child the same name of the son i lost 

but my mother makes me talk to her and gets upset if i say i hate her but i REALLY do hate her i went 2-3 years with out talking to her and i was happier then ever 

every time i talk to her i get sick to my stomach and shaking and get an anxiety attack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Me [20F] with my wife [31 F] I love my wife but i hate living with her </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 02:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finally getting to move away from Nmom but being followed by GC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 01:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have been living with my nmom for the last 8 months i am now getting to move 2922 km away i picked a smaller town and i just found out today with 1 week to go before i move that my GC sister is going to follow me there and  live JUST down the street from me. 

i freaking hate her i want her no where near me but now I'm going to have to live near her i keep leaving the cites i love because she keeps following me.

I'm going to only stay in my small town for a few months then move i don't think I'm going to tell them where I'm going.

sorry i just needed to rant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-14 22:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> don't they have the fat olympics 

i think its called competitive eating  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-11 02:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> please for god sakes YES  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tv Moms </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-10 03:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i just heard my mother say to me 

you watch to much tv moms are not like they are on tv 

we actually care about other things  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-09 02:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm planning on doing the same thing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you ever question your memories </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 02:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have memories of lots of bad things when i was little but the most for example 

my mother used to spank me really hard but she claims that she never did and i am just saying that for any reason to say she's a bad mother.

my grandmother ( who was never around ) and my dad says she never did it but i can swear she did 

but maybe my head is making it up 

do you ever question what you know  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 02:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> at least my mom pretends to care </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 01:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the doctor was going to perform surgery on my curved spine when i was 16 because it caused me so much pain my mom said no she will never have surgery.

i am not 20 and its to late for me to get the surgery and I'm in constant pain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 01:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to disappear for being so thin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 05:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is there any new updates
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
