<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1913</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 07:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sub is hard because it's very much about loving who you are *regardless of weight*, but recently it's shifted into a "losing weight or getting 'healthy' is evil!" sort of feel. It's why I'm not really here anymore. I lurked for a long time and basically made an account to confront people who were thin-shaming. 


While what you say is 100% true, there are some very vocal members of this subreddit that will probably flame you! It has it's positives...and also it's negatives. :) I hope you don't get flamed for this post. It's insightful and kind and nonjudgmental and empowering. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 07:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's beautiful that you found a person who loves you the way you love yourself. I wish my partner hadn't told me he preferred me clean-shaven (he isn't!) because I was already self conscious about that sort of thing and now I won't even let him touch my legs if I didn't shave **that day**.  This is, obviously, my issue and not his, because we're all allowed to have preferences. I'm just not courageous enough to do it anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 07:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hair removal has kind of been a thing since we started walking upright and wearing clothes. :) I just wish it wasn't considered *disgusting* for people to have their own ideas about grooming. As long as it's affecting no one else (hygiene is a different issue, and really has nothing to do with shaving no matter how much people insist it does) it shouldn't matter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 03:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm. That's odd. 


Well, I want to say thank you for the rest of your post, it was very nice of you to reach out. And I was also not saying that I currently have an anorexic body mass, but in the past my BMI was ~15. :) I went through recovery, and they taught us that you always have anorexia. It's like being an alcoholic...you can be in remission, or recovery, but there is always the chance it could come back if you indulge anorectic habits. 

But, every country has different guidelines. :)

As for rape, I honestly think that's the truth, you don't ever want to believe a loved one was raped, and my dad is the King of Denial. He's always been spectacular at lying about something until he honestly believes he's been right all along. It's bizarre. And it sucks. 

I never downvoted you, I sincerely appreciate that you were trying to help and I also understand that sometimes these things come out offensive when they're not intended to be. Just be careful with it in the future! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
