<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3094</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 04:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cilantro! It is the only thing I simply cannot tolerate. There's no hiding it in food, and if I taste it, I can't take another bite. I wish I liked it, but I just can't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shut Up and Train - An Article </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 21:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Shut Up and Train](http://www.muscleforlife.com/shut-up-and-train/)  
  
I've been reading this guy's articles for a while now, but this one in particular has really stuck with me. I've always had an issue with making excuses and doubting myself (as I'm sure most of us have at some point) and this article basically just bluntly shuts down every excuse I've ever had. He lays out excuse after excuse and squashes them.    
  
Do any of you have any go-to articles or resources that give you an extra kick in the ass? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 20:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! I'm a 23 year old female, and I'm completely new to this sub.  
  
My goals are mainly fitness goals. I have struggled with anorexia since I was 14 years old, and I was diagnosed when I was 17. I have relapsed a couple of times, but I'm finally in a place where I feel I can work on my body without being destructive.  
  
**Main Goals for R16**  
* Become consistent with my workout schedule. I have a great plan, but I am the queen of excuses. No more!  
* Become consistent with my meal plan. I still have trouble swinging wildly from eating too little, to eating too much. I'm aware of it and I just need to be more conscious of my habits. I have a great meal plan also; I just need to stick with it!  
* Lose weight the **right way**. I'm slightly overweight, and it needs to change. Basically if I stick with the first two bullets, this one will take care of itself.  
* Spend more time actively involved with my daughter. It amazes me how easy it is to let an evening pass by in front of the TV without even noticing it. I know I spend a lot of time with her, but I think we need more time with NO other distractions. Just small things, really.  
* Start making small progresses with my house. There are a lot of things my boyfriend and I would like to do, but we do a lot of talking and not a whole lot of DOING.  
  
That's about it! Really, all of my goals could be summarized by less talking and more doing. I have to learn to stop beating myself into a week-long depression for missing a workout or eating a cookie. My daughter deserves a happier momma, so I'm really excited to see where this goes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 23:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to pop diet pills (HydroxyCut, etc) like candy, and I can tell you that it's not worth it. The more I took them, the worse the effects were. Chest pains, heart palpitations, racing pulse, lightheadedness, etc. I also built sort of an addiction to them; if I didn't take them, I felt worse than I did when I would (which was still awful.) I highly advise to steer clear and stick to strictly caffeine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 23:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did see a nutritionist, but it was when I was gaining weight from being extremely underweight, so the concept is a little different. I guess what I'm trying to find out is if, instead of gradually increasing 100 calories per week, if I were to just increase to the point that I SHOULD be able to maintain or lose at (that my metabolism is not yet caught up to), if after a bit of initial weight gain, the gaining would plateau like it would with the gradual increasing.  
  
Thank you for sharing! I'm glad to see you made changes for the better. :) It really is AMAZING the difference in mood, health, and motivation you feel when you start caring for your body.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 23:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I've done a lot of reading on it, and I what I'm wanting to do is just eat the macros and calories that I should be eating at my height and weight for lifting, etc (instead of gradually increasing my calories week by week). I'm wondering if, by doing this, my metabolism will eventually catch up (with a bit of initial weight gain) like it would with the gradual increase. Does that make any sense or do I sound crazy? Haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
