<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3132</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 11:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with /u/thro_w_away12
Plz bby </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 19:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Warehouse burger at Le Meridien in Garhoud is great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 16:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet username mate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 16:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great reply! This is more in check with what our teacher has informed us in the past. I didn't think comparing and contrasting was required. Have you got any tips for paper 1? Thanks again, good luck with your exams :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 19:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could be 166g of the dried kind of yellow corn (that is used for popcorn etc).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 13:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the help. My teacher did say that writing completely over one text, then the other is more optimal than a running commentary. I don't know which way to go. What do you suggest? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 13:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is 5 paragraphs all that is required? Thanks for the help :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 13:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the help! We really appreciate this.
One question: do we write the paper 2 as a running commentary on both texts, or do we discuss one then the other? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> English A: Language and Literature help! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 08:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all, 

Unfortunately my Lang Lit teacher has fallen extremely ill this past week and will not likely be coming into school next week either. A couple of us students are partially in the dark regarding papers 1 and 2. 

*  **Has anyone got any tips regarding how to structure paper 1 and 2?** 
*  **In paper 2 where do we compare and contrast the two texts?** Throughout the essay or in a paragraph preceding the conclusion? Our teacher recommends, that in both paper 1 and 2, that we structure it as -intro-context text 1-context text 2-text 1........for several paragraphs- text 2.....for several paragraphs-. 


Thanks in advance :) We appreciate all help and tips. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 18:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I refer to a 'sanger' as more of a bread with a sausage in it (diagonally) smothered in tomato sauce (not ketchup). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 09:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Colloquial term for 'sandwich' in Australia (and maybe other places).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 09:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peanut butter sambo with some eggs on the side. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 09:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2x 700g fresh chickens, 6 hours in a buttermilk brine (with salt, pepper, garlic, dehydrated onion and rosemary), roasted in the oven at 190 Celsius for approx. 45 minutes. Served with roasted Brussels Sprouts and roasted carrots with honey. 

SUPA JUICY AND GOOD  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Winner, Winner, Chicken Dinner! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 08:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 20:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which Carrefour did you go to? Carrefour at MCC definitely has Skippy Creamy and also a honey roasted one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 18:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also at Carrefour! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 16:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/food/comments/4cvqjb/mum_let_me_loose_in_the_kitchen_made_some_thai/d1mzgqn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 16:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/food/comments/4cvqjb/mum_let_me_loose_in_the_kitchen_made_some_thai/d1mzgqn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 16:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * 1 cup of Sticky Rice (aka glutinous rice)
* 1 can (400ml) coconut milk (make sure not to get the 'light' kinds)
* 2 tablspoons sugar (any works. I used caster sugar. Would love to try coconut sugar with it)
* 2 teaspoon salt
* 1 teaspoon Pandan essence or Pandan leaf



Soak the rice with 1.5 cup of water for 8-20 hours (the longer the better I find).

Steam the rice for 20 minutes. I don't have a traditional thai bamboo steamer so I improvised. If you have a [steaming attachment](http://pad1.whstatic.com/images/thumb/9/91/Boil-Eggs-in-a-Rice-Cooker-Step-2.jpg/aid2648174-728px-Boil-Eggs-in-a-Rice-Cooker-Step-2.jpg) to a rice cooker, find a pot that it fits on and put water in the pot to boil. Place a muslin cloth or tea towel in the steaming attachment, put the rice in (drained) and add the pandan leaf or half of the pandan essence. Fold the excess tea towel/muslin cloth edges over so the rice is in a enclosed 'parcel'. 

Once the water boils, put the steaming attachment on and cover with a lid.

After 10 minutes, mix the rice a bit so it all cooks evenly.

When you have about 7 minutes left on the rice, put the coconut milk on to simmer. Once simmering (NOT BOILING), add the sugar, half the salt and the rest of the pandan essence.

Take the rice out when cooked. It should be a bit chewy and clear. Put it in a large bowl. Pour 3/4 of the coconut milk mixture on the rice. Let soak for 5ish minutes.

With the last 1/4 of the coconut mixture, add the other half of the salt and pour into a small jug so that whoever is enjoying your dessert, can pour more on if they want.

Serve with mango. Any works. I like a less ripe mango as the sourness cuts through the sweetness of the rice.

The pandan is not necessary but it makes it go that lil but further.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 15:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excuse the potato picture. The mint was also unnecessary but oh well.

I missed summer in Phuket so this brought back good memories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mum let me loose in the kitchen. Made some Thai Coconut Sticky Rice and Mango () </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 15:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 18:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there! I am doing Topic 3 as well. HL too. Stalin, Mao and Hitler. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 17:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will do, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 17:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonderful to hear! Thanks for the tip </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 17:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glutinous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
