<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8657</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Do I have and ED? I only feel good when I have no food in me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 12:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I have food in me, all I feel is guilt and bloat. It's really not very fun and I wish that I could go back to when I was younger, and loved to eat. I'm trying to eat healthy, because I do personal training at the gym I go to and my trainer tells me to, but I seem to just not eat and I get super tired all the time.

Idk what I have, but I think it's bad.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to deal with food poisoning after Bulimia recovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 12:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tl;dr I got food poisoning and threw up after 2 years of not purging.

I could use some support - I am terrified.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to check whether someone has eaten yet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 11:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! I wanted to see if it was okay for me to post a request on different ways to ask if someone has eaten yet. I have a friend who is Autistic and Anorexic and told me last night that she hasn't been eating as often or as well since she moved out of my house, because she knew I would ask her if she had eaten yet and nobody is doing that for her right now. She asked that I message her around meal times to check up on her because she thinks it will help, and I made it clear that if it was bothering her to let me know right away. Basically I just wanted to ask people different ways to ask if she's had breakfast/lunch/dinner, if that would be appropriate. Thank you!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request for Academic Survey Participants: California State University San Marcos Scale Validation Survey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 11:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are Invited to Participate in an Online Research Study California State University San Marcos Scale Validation Survey (IRB Code Number: 893513-1)

A new scale is being developed for people with various psychiatric diagnoses. The purpose of this online study is to test the validity of the scale among people from diverse backgrounds. It is hoped that this work will lead to further research and potential clinical applications. This online survey will involve completing a series of questions for approximately 25 to 45 minutes.

You must be at least 18 years old, fluent in English, a resident of the United States, and diagnosed with a psychiatric disorder to participate. You are not eligible to participate if you participated in our recent interview study. To participate in this online research study, please visit:

https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/redditc

To learn more about this research study, please contact the researcher, Stephanie Price (price049@cougars.csusm.edu), or the advisor, Dr. Heike Mahler (hmahler@csusm.edu). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I'm suffering from chronic hunger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 11:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm recovering from EDNOS and I'm constantly hungry. Food doesn't help at all. I've tried filling up on carrots, I ate so much I was gagging afterwards, but I was still starving. I've tried planning out my meal times, but this hunger is making my life miserable. I often wonder what's the point of eating if it doesn't satisfy me. 

How do I make the hunger cues go away? Will they go away? If they will go away, what's an estimate of when? It's not a possibility to just eat freely and gain massive amounts of weight. I've tried recovering three times now and each time I gained over ten lbs, I was thrown right back into a worse eating disorder. I just want to be able to sleep without turning in pain. I don't get hunger pangs, just this chronic hunger feeling.

When I started recovery, it would be much more extreme, but it would only last for about 4 hours and then it'd go away. Now it's milder, but constant.

If anyone knows a good way to ignore the pain or kinda 'escape' my body, I'd be very grateful as well.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I don't know how where to go from here </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 23:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am 18 years old (f) and for the past two years have had an ED. I was already slightly underweight and it got worse within 3-4 months. After that time, I was still under eating but not as badly and was made to seek treatment. I saw a counselor for a couple months but I didn't want to recover so nothing ever came of it. Today, I am still underweight and struggling day by day. I think about food all the time, like how much and when to eat, and what the scale says. I hate being trapped like this but don't know if it's "bad" enough because I am maintaining my weight. Body image is also important to me, I guess I haven't recovered sooner because I am afraid of what my body might look like. Since college is on the horizon, I also want to get a hold of this issue before it goes further. 

My questions are, what should my first step be? How do I tell my parents that I still have a problem? And how do I accept that recovery is NEEDED? Thank you for reading.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Recovered from ednos but have no appetite. How do make sure this doesn't trigger anything? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 22:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've been "recovered" technically from ednos for about a year now. I'm at a healthy weight. I don't have much for body image problems. However over the past few weeks I have no appetite, nothing sounds good. Doesnt matter what I try to eat, high or lower calorie, I take a couple bites and I just can't eat anymore. I have no interest. I'm not depressed, I'm actually pretty happy. I'm just worried this might trigger an old problem to resurface. I really don't want that. There's a very small part of me that's enjoying this, but it's maybe 5% the other 95% does not like it at all. 

Has anyone been in this situation before?  How do make sure this doesn't trigger anything? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: New Year's = Triggering/Trouble with Eyes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 22:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am an adult who is mostly recovered from BN. In the last few years I have developed a lot of suspected allergies to food (my doctor currently has me taking antibiotics for intestinal bacteria overgrowth), and while I used to overexercise, I am now largely sedentary and suffer from chronic pain. As a "recovered" adult I am no less depressed than I was with BN, and tend to binge-drink instead of binge/purge. As a result, I am at the highest weight of my life, and it is becoming incredibly distressing.
With the arrival of the new year, I am seeing a lot of focus on people losing weight, and I am starting to slide into unhealthy habits and more depression. The few times I have purged in the last year, I've had a new and disturbing side-effect - the blood vessels in the skin around my eyes has burst, making it look like I've scraped the skin all around. 

Has anyone else experienced or been able to treat this problem with my eyes? How worried should I be about permanent damage? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Friendship and relationship problems </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 04:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm struggling with letting people into my life and keeping friends close while trying to recover from my eating disorder. Do you have any tips on how to help this? This was a big reason my last relationship ended and has become a long term problem in my life.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I think I have EDNOS, but could this be exercise bulimia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 04:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I have EDNOS, but could this be exercise bulimia? I've read there's something called Night Eating Syndrome but usually it makes people overweight and I'm not.

I count calories every day. I'm not overweight, I'm on the slimmer side but normal. I don't eat all day and then I eat dinner very late. And around midnight I have the equivalent of a large meal. The bulk of my eating is obviously right before I go to bed. I exercise a lot every day to account for all these calories which is the only reason I can maintain this weight. I weight myself every day and if I start gaining a pound or two I go on a very restrictive diet until it's back to normal and the cycle continues.

I know it's probably related to not eating all day so I'm going to start having a meal a few hours before dinner but I don't think I'm ready to start eating three meals a day. For some reason eating all my food at night is like a reward. It's interfered with my sleep schedule but I don't have a job or morning classes to go to so that isn't as important. I also have depression. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Intimacy Issues while Recovering </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 23:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been dealing with various disordered eating issues for roughly 6 years. I struggle a lot with intimacy and do not even want to take off my shirt in front of my boyfriend. How have others dealt with this? I've been struggling with this and going to the beach/pool as well
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Relationships   Eating Disorders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 12:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My significant other of a few years just (sorta?) ended our relationship on the pretense that she doesn't want to recover from her eating disorder, that she won't recover, and I supposedly deserve better than that. She entered treatment a year ago after collapsing in her dorm building from restriction, and just recently left against medical advice after just over a year in treatment and has been steadily losing weight since.

I've been extremely supportive of her recovery and have nudged her back to treatment every time she's wanted to leave, but financial concerns have made it impossible for her to stay this time.

She said tonight that she expects her disorder to kill her, and that dying from her disorder is better than gaining any weight.

I'm concerned for her well-being, and I want to help her get better, but it's impossible if she doesn't want to recover. From those who have had these same feelings, what can I do to help?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Have any of you guys recovered without professional help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 01:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And how?

*Friendly moderator note: Please remember that calories, clothing sizes, weights, discussion of "good/bad" foods, etc. do not belong in this recovery subreddit. We encourage you to keep your advice number-free and not provide guidance that should be reserved for professionals.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How do I figure out if I have BED? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 01:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suspect I probably have it, but that might just be wishful thinking for myself and trying to take responsibility out of my hands. I've tried looking online and I can't find any answers on what to actually do if I suspect I might have it. Do I go to a general practitioner? Take a test?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: An old friend confided in me about her relapse, how do I help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 01:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Hi, I would normally call one of the eating disorder hotlines, but they all seem to be closed for the holidays. A girl I was involved with about 3 years ago contacted me and after talking for a little while she confided in me that she has relapsed with her eating disorder. She was previously institutionalized for her ED, and had reached an equilibrium where she was eating sufficient calories, but was balancing it by working out for hours a day. She has told me that she has maintained her exercise regime, but has cut back her calories to an unhealthy level. 

Looking back at her Facebook photos (hardly an idea way to judge, I know, but she is in a different city so it is all I have) it looks like she has been losing weight for a while, and she has told me she hit a certain low weight and then regained a small amount and has been maintaining at an underweight BMI. She sent me a picture of her ribs and sternum so I could see that she was underweight, and she said "Yeah, I know it isn't healthy, nor is it sustainable, but I like looking sick or smthg... idk... I'm crazy".

I don't know if there is anything I can do to help her get back to a healthy weight, but I feel like she is reaching out for help and I don't know what to tell her... Please help me to figure out what to do
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I'm worried about my friend and I don't know what to do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 18:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We would talk during PE in high school and sometimes I would talk to her during lunch, but we didn't start hanging out outside of school until we both went to college. She just asked me to hang out with her and her friends one night and it went on from there. One day I went bowling with her and her guy friend who was crushing on her. We worked up quite an appetite and went to get some Chinese. She went to the bathroom and while she was gone he told me that he was upset because she never eats. He called her out on it in front of me and she rightfully got defensive.

But it's true. In the nearly six years we've hung out I've only seen her actually eat once (it was a cake pop on her birthday several months ago). If we're supposed to eat she always has an excuse as to why she can't. We even made brunch plans and she didn't eat a thing. She lost a lot of weight at the end of high school and it's been decreasing steadily since then. I just saw her a few minutes ago for the first time in months and she looks even skinnier. Like, underweight, and her voice is all scratchy.

But in truth we're not "friends." We hang out, but our friendship is not deep at all. We mostly just go to the movies and talk about trivial stuff, mostly surface facts about her. We've maybe hung out like this 20 times in the six years I've known her. I was actually thinking of maybe fading out because it's just not fun hanging out anymore, but it feels like a dick move. I have no idea what to do. I don't even know for sure if she has an eating disorder.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RequestL Holiday Triggers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 18:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I (21f) have been doing quite well recovering from EDNOS. Food isn't nearly the big deal it used to be, and I've been feeling much better about it. But I knew the holidays would be hard, and here I am, Christmas eve, really struggling. I've put on weight in my recovery, and am even more overweight than I used to be (not by body dysmorphia measures, but real ones).

I don't like spending time with my family in the best of times, but being terrified at what comments might be said made me even more anxious and not wanting to go to my parents house. The first thing my grandfather said when he saw me today was "looks like they fed you well!" He's had a history of making mean comments towards me and my weight, even mooing at me years ago. My grandmother hasn't said anything directly, but we were watching Jann Arden on tv, and the first thing she said was "she has a fat face, doesn't she!" (Jann Arden isn't a size 0, but much smaller than myself). It's so bad I felt like I had to watch how much I ate at dinner, lest I be judged.

My grandfather also pushes people to eat more, and it takes several no's to get him to lay off. All in all my anxiety is super high, and I'm so scared for feelings to return and for there to be progress lost.

Any tips on how to deal with family at holidays? Tips for someone in fragile recovery around the holidays? And tips for how to deal with small setbacks? I, like many I think, find it hard to not see small setbacks as catastrophic.

Thank you all so much, and hope most of your are having happy holidays!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I'm worried about my girlfriend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 12:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is not eating, and is only drinking boxed wine.

I'm worried that she could suffer severe organ damage or die from this. She has not eaten anything substantial since last Tuesday or Wednesday. She has been drinking boxed wine (the 5-liter boxes, going through a box every 2-3 days) and is now having trouble getting out of bed even to go to the bathroom due to muscle atrophy, general weakness, alcohol intoxication, and a hormonal imbalance that she is currently being treated for.

She's having extreme stomach pain and vomiting a lot from that (she has also purged in the past, but this is more an issue of the alcoholism and continuous drinking), as well as severe emotional pain and EXTREME mood swings. She's taken a few swings at me in the past few days, and has gone from listening to music or watching tv with me to "I need to pause this for a sec" then screaming at me, crying, becoming completely enraged, or (fill in the blank).

She will not go to a hospital. Any time I mention anything that could help (drinking gatorade for electrolytes, trying to eat something small/something she likes, going to a hospital at least for the electrolyte IV they can give) she says no.

I'm worried she is drinking herself to death. She has been suicidal in the past but is not currently (doesn't seem to be and she says she isn't), though she does have a lot of other mental health symptoms going on at this time that make it difficult for her to take good care of herself.

Does anyone have ANY advice for how to handle this situation?

She has a history of extreme trauma both with police and with hospitals, so I will not call 911 unless I absolutely have to (if she stops breathing in her sleep, etc) but I can't monitor her 24/7 as I have to work and sleep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Proper way to fix my eating disorder? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 23:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe I have a minor case of anorexia? I skip a lot of meals. I almost never have an appetite and only eat because I feel cold and weak not because of hunger. I have this irrational fear of getting fat and also have poor body image to the point where I can't really live normally. 

I'm a 19 Y.O. male who is in the "underweight" level. I always ate less than I should have my whole life, but only recently did it get this bad, mainly because of my other issues too.

Anyways, how do I fix this the right way? How should I start, what would my goal be, and how fast should I progress? I skip meals, so I have a long time between them. My meal sizes vary depending on what my mom makes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How do I recover from an ED? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 21:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 16 and I've lost a great deal of weight in the last 2 months, I eat very little or I feel guilty and vomit, and I exercise every day - sometimes till I throw up. I'm taking dieting pills right now and my arms get shaky and my heartbeat speeds up. I have a normal BMI, yet knowing that doesn't help. Another thing is I can't notice the difference, and yet everyone else can. I think I may also have body dysmorphia. :( I did this to make myself more confident to help get rid of my social anxiety, but I think I'm getting worse. Any tips on how to get over this? I know what I'm doing isn't healthy at all. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weird food related anger, reaching a road block </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 15:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have adhd and was recently prescribed concerta. In short has helped my life and depression immensely. But I lied to my dr when he asked about my appetite when upping my dose. My appetite sucks ass. And it feels awful and I kinda hate it, but I love hearing in my head how much weight I've lost. I don't want to gain it back. I get anxious around food, yes, but it's not because I don't want to eat it, i just ask myself: am i eating enough where I dont feel like utter crap and Am I eating too much and will gain ALL the weight back? I lie to my mom and bf when they ask if I ate, but it makes me so mad when they are concerned about my eating. My mom says I lost too much weight or I look skeleton I get angry and deny it. I want to lose more weight, but I dont want to look like a twig. So I'll work out. That's why I dont think I have anorexia or whatever.

Im worried if I go to the dr they'll take the concerta away which has helped me become an independent and functioning adult.  Should I get help, or am I overreacting? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: When does recovery bloat go away? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 03:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been struggling for about eleven months with disordered eating. This has never happened to me before. It's absolutely horrendous and I just feel massive. I've found out that recovery bloat is very common and I know why it occurs, I just need an estimate of when it'll calm down. I know all bodies react differently, but I need to know if we are talking five days or five years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Advice Overcoming Binging Triggers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 03:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lately I've been trying to overcome by history with binging, but I find that one of my worst triggers is feeling sick after eating. It makes me sad that I've become so accustomed to it that feeling nauseous desperately makes me want to eat more. I don't know how to remove this association in my head since it's become ingrained over time. Once I get that urge, it doesn't matter if I try to stop myself; I can think "This is a really bad idea. I don't like this, and I don't want to do this," before going right back to eating. Which, of course, just makes me feel more nauseous. I was really hoping someone could help me with desensitizing myself from this trigger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: how to help my girlfriend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 03:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont know how to help my anorexic girlfriend.. I'm 14, and my girlfriend is 13 (we're in the same grade though) I love her a lot, but she hates herself so much... We both have depression and anxiety, and we were both hospitalized for it at one time. I'm the more mentally stable one though, as I have been getting help and recovering since april. She has anorexia, and thinks she is fat. She used to be obese when she was younger, but lost a very large amount of weight in 6 months.

She was hospitalized and extremely underweight. we've been dating for 2 weeks now, and I know that's not long but we have grown really close in that short amount of time. She's at a healthy weight now, and looks great and beautiful just the way she is right now. She keeps trying to lose more and more weight though and she thinks she's fat but she isn't at all... I told her that i would love her regardless of her weight, I wouldn't care... She still doesn't believe me though, and she's been purging and cutting and... I don't know what to do to help...

She has a therapist that she visits but she still self harms and stuff... It makes me really sad to see that she has to resort to it. I have been 3 months clean from self harm and am trying to lead by example but I just don't know how to help... At lunch she never eats, even though she brings a lunchbox. (She always "accidently" leaves it in her locker.) I offer her my food but obviously she doesnt take it...

Idk if this is relevant but I'm going to throw out a few more things: I'm biologically male, but I am androgynous leaning female She is biologically female, and she is androgynous leaning male We are both bisexual

Can you tell me what kind of things I should/shouldn't say and do? i really want to help but I don't want to fuck it up :c </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: ED affecting outlook? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 03:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My (30M) SO (26F) has lived with an ED during their youth which actually led to them becoming a healthcare professional and writing a paper on EDs and how society denigrates those deemed to be "fat".

She has put on weight recently and is very depressed as a result. I don't think she has relapsed but more and more she is telling me how people were a lot nicer to her when she weighed less, and says even people shes known for a long time are being nasty because of her appearance.

I know that women far more than men get unsolicited comments/"advice" about their weight, but I am concerned that she could possibly be perceiving a lot more than is actually occurring due to her mindset and the way her self-worth is tied to weight. 

I feel it would be insensitive of me to raise the possibility with them, it could be interpreted as invalidating and of course she could actually be 100% correct, but is this at all something recognisable?

I am also at a loss as how to support her with this, as she is almost literally an expert on the matter and I feel like anything I could say is trite and ignorant.

All advice welcome and appreciated . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to help someone who says they want to put on weight but doesn't actually want to? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 10:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My daughter says she wants to put on weight (she's been losing weight and is already underweight) but I suspect she actually wants to stay very thin. She refuses any money to take to college to buy anything, saying she doesn't want to spend my money, and she finds reasons why any food I offer is not suitable. She's also recently become a strict vegan. She used to see a therapist and has self-harmed (cutting) in the past. What can I do to help her? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Feeling Overwhelmed/Having to Make a Decision? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 12:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Things have been going poorly lately in terms of my eating disorder, and now I have only a few weeks to make a decision about treatment. I'm about to finish my first semester of college, and I don't want treatment to interfere with education, but I also feel like I can't do this on my own. I'm stuck between deciding what level of care I need and if I should do treatment at all, or, if I do, if I should limit it to over winter break. If it's relevant, I'm struggling with restricting, bingeing, and using various compensatory behaviors every day now. I feel like if I take a semester off I'll feel lazy and behind and even more depressed than I already do. I'm so overwhelmed right now. Help :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Appetite/Hunger Stimulants? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 13:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 33 year old male. Recently dumped again primarily due to behavioral issues that my therapist and I both believe are closely related to not eating. I have to force feed myself to maintain an "underweight" BMI.

I have almost no appetite. I've spoken with several doctors over the past 6 years and all of them have recommended smoothies. That's their solution. Not much of a solution when I have almost no interest in eating and when hunger appears it quickly passes.
I'm getting psychosocial support, but I think that medical intervention is necessary. I've read up on appetite stimulants, but nearly every one seems to have some pretty serious side affects. 

The rational part of my brain does not want to be emaciated. I want to eat. I just have very little appetite.

Can anyone help me navigate how to induce appetite and hunger? What has worked for you? How should I be talking to my Dr about this? Do I need to see an eating disorder specialist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Grocery shopping help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 02:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I'm trying my best to recover on my own (currently in therapy and occasionally go to EDA). I suffer from anorexia with bulimic tendencies. My boyfriend just moved in with me and he knows a little bit about my situation (moreso about my BDD). Anyway, we are planning to go grocery shopping together for the first time this coming week and I'm really stressing about it.

Are there any websites that give tips or help on how to grocery shop/make lists if you are struggling with disordered eating? 

Any and all advice is appreciated. Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I am underweight but I don't think I am anorexic because I binge. What is going on and how do I overcome it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 04:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i used to be underweight (still am, but much less so...) and restricted my calories to an unhealthy level. i'm now somewhat less underweight and restrict maybe one day a week and binge (ie i meet the minnie maud recovery requirements, if that helps). sometimes i purge (aka whenever my gag reflex allows me to). other times i just leave it. i maintain my weight like this, somehow, but its hell. its hell to count every calorie, obsess over what you eat, and still not lose a thing because all you ever do is binge. 

i dont think im anorexic. i was diagnosed, way back when, but after starting ""recovery"", i never got out of eating that much. i have bed, in my eyes, even if i maintain and underweight bmi. it doesnt count. i got my waist measured today, and i was asked if i was really bloated because apparently it wasnt believable that someone my height could have such a high measurement. i wasnt. i just dont know what to do. its like i restrict one day, binge for two, and ultimiately lose nothing. im not looking for tips on how to starve btw, lmao. 

im curious if a) id be considered anorexic anymore (highly doubt it, my off-limits food list has gone out the door and while i feel uncomfortable going above a certain calorie count i do it anyways. i go way above.) b) if id be considered to have bed (i do eat a lot in a sitting sometimes and feel out of control) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> REQUEST: Would really appreciate hearing about any one's recent experience at an eating disorder clinic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 02:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am trying to decide on places and am really scared to make the commitment for both financial and personal reasons. I have had bad experiences in the past and so am reluctant to try again. Would love to hear of any positive outcomes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Bad Breath during recovery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 02:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been struggling with eating disorder recovery on and off for 10 years now.

My boyfriend notices sometimes that my breath smells very bad when I'm restricting (unintentionally) some nights during the week... which is embarrassing to say the least. (Obviously I brush my teeth and use mouth wash as much as possible)

I was wondering if anyone else had this issue and what steps I can take to help this issue, any other that others have found helpful during recovery?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: how to be properly supportive of my boyfriend with anorexia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 11:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I apologize for the length of the post. Thank you for hearing me out. 

My boyfriend and I grew up in the same small town and have been friends for over 6 years, though we only got together this year and are doing long distance until I graduate. He has been struggling with anorexia for years, probably for the whole time we were friends, but I didn't really know the severity until recently, obviously. 

Somehow, half a year after he started opening up to me about his feelings, I have convinced him to go see a therapist as soon as we return home for winter break (in 2 weeks) until we can find more specialized help. 

He asked me to go with him (which I was going to do anyway) because he wants me to make sure he doesn't lie to the therapist. When I asked him if he wants to get better he said that logically he knows he should want to but he's really not sure. It breaks my heart every time he eats a small meal and immediately feels guilty and fat. 

I have seen a lot of articles about supporting girlfriends and wives with EDs but never really about how to help a male partner. I know it should really be the same but I can't help but feel like it's at least a slightly different dynamic? (don't know how to properly word this feeling, sorry) 

I have been reading up on anorexia and the psychology behind it to help better understand what he is going through, but I know that I will never really understand. I just want to make sure I can be as supportive and helpful as possible without saying anything that will make him feel worse. I especially would like advice on what I should do when he says he feels fat. I feel pretty useless during these times cause what do I say? no you're not fat? you're a wonderful amazing person? I feel like it doesn't help at all..
What I do now: I won't talk about food or his ED unless he brings it up first/wants to talk about it. I try to make him feel as comfortable and loved as possible when he is feeling depressed about having eaten or gained weight. it seems to help when I tell him that the feeling will pass and that it is ok to feel bad now because it will get better and I am with him every step of the way. There is more but this is pretty much it generally.

I'm not sure if what I'm doing is good or not. He says that it helps and that it means a lot to him to know I care so much. but I'm worried about him and his health a lot. After he calms down from feeling depressed/fat and goes to bed, I am up late feeling very anxious about the future. I know he's going to get help, but I'm still scared and don't want to lose him to this. He's only going to therapy because I want him to. But I try to keep my cool because I want to be strong for him, to be someone he can feel safe with. I also worry that I'm overbearing. We both have anxiety issues, if that means anything.

I would really appreciate any input you guys have, or any personal experience if you would be comfortable sharing. Thanks so much.

tl;dr - My boyfriend has anorexia. He is going to get help very soon, I would like any advice on how to be supportive without being overbearing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I need help figuring out how to tell my girlfriends mom about her ED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 03:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all, My girlfriend has struggled with eating since I've known her (about one year now). She's usually been able to cope until lately

She is very very underweight. She believes she's consuming a ridiculous amount of calories when in reality it's much lower. She's had panic attacks over eating one tiny thing. She's even started to have her hair fall out and be extremely weak.

Other things that aren't an ED are talking about how she doesn't plan to be alive next year and how she self harms herself 

She's too young to take herself to the doctor, her mom has to be there. Usually, I wouldn't tell a parent, but Im scared for her life. I know she will probably hate me, but I know in the end this is for the best. 
This is the message to her mom that I have so far, but I think it kind of sucks. I need help figuring out how to really show her mom how bad it is and not sound lame.

"Hey again, I know you're really busy with the house situation and everything but this is really important. I love (girlfriend) more than anything and I want her to be okay, but she's not. Ever since I met her she's had trouble with her body image and eating but it's gotten very bad lately. I know about her current medical problems of not being able to keep much down, but before this happened she would throw up her food on purpose all the time. She actually has an Instagram account where she posts about trying to loose weight. Her "current goal weight" is (low weight) pounds. She actually had a panic attack when she ate one grain of rice. She told me she tried to kill herself a few days ago but she threw up the pills. She's always trying to figure out how to hurt herself weather it's cutting or hitting herself. She thinks she's fat and she's planning on starving herself, and she said she doesn't plan on being alive for next year. I know she's going to figure out I told you and I know she's going to hate me for telling you this, but she needs help. She needs professional help because Im so scared to loose her. I can show you screen shots of some things if you want, but I don't know if you want to see them. Thank you"

The current medical problem was actually caused by her not eating. Not going too much into it, she had to be at the doctor a few days ago because starving herself so much made her throw everything up for a few days, but she lied to her mom about it.

Thank you so much for reading </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How Can I Speak to my Dr. About an ED? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 03:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few months ago I was at a point where I barely ate or drank, which led to me passing out in public. I was mistakenly diagnosed with epilepsy because when they asked me in the ER if I could think of any reason I might have passed out and had shaky limbs, I got scared to admit I hadn't eaten and couldn't say anything. After it all happened, I knew without a doubt that the incident was due to a lack of food   dehydration. I have finally gotten an appointment with a new doctor, but I've never ever spoken to a doctor before about my problem and I'm scared to. 

How can I bring it up and are they going to be mad at me for not saying anything the last time? I am a 21F Canada, if that makes a difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How Was It When You Started Eating More? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 03:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have Anorexia Nervosa, but I probably have Anorexia (unintentional weight loss due to under-eating). I'm currently underweight and need to gain weight for a long list of reasons. 
I've been to a nutritionist and I know what I should be eating, but I can't manage to eat all that food! I'm already eating several small meals a day and eating calorie dense foods, and I'm still having trouble eating enough, let alone extra.  I don't think there's any physical reason for this except a small stomach and a small appetite.

For those of you who have learned how to eat full-sized meals again, what was it like? How long did it take? Any advice? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Tracking and planning thats not calorie counting or intuitive eating? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 03:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Through recovery, Im trying to be healthier in general with my eating and my body but Ive hit some serious road blocks.

I havent gotten any helpful advice from fitness or health subreddits here because they only suggest calorie counting and macro counting, and thats not something I can do with my ED history. I obsess about food every waking moment, which is worse mentally than when Im not eating enough.

I even tried food journaling both in written and picture form, but it feels useless because I dont know if Im eating enough or too much (both in quantity and quality).

The other big thing they promote is intuitive eating, focusing on listening to your bodys cues. (Eating when youre hungry, not when youre not, etc). Unfortunately, I have chronic physical health issues that prevent me from feeling hungry.

Ive learned routine is important for me for planning, but that only tells me when to eat, not what. I cant afford a nutritionist and custom diet plan. I tried the eatthismuch website as well (would suggest for some people), but it works best for 3 meal a day routines (i have to eat 5 small meals) and the leftovers function leaves much to be desired.

I just feel like Ive tried everything and none of it worked and now I dont have more options. Can anyone offer advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Research Help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 11:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good evening mods. My name is Paul and currently I am working on a paper for my psychology class. I chose to research eating disorder in an attempt to learn more about the topic because I know very little. Someone close to me suffers from an eating disorder and I want to help them, but because I know so little it is hard to help. For the paper I am required to read about studies on the biological, social, and development causes and effects. Is there any that you would recommend? I know that I could just go out and google to find a few, but I thought I would ask you guys because I wanted to use studies that people who know more about it find useful. Thank you so much for anything that you do for me, and thank you so much for all the work you do helping the people on this subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How ED finds its way back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 11:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had a history of eating disorders and they have largely been in remission for a few years. Through the years of recovery, I've really taken an interest in health and fitness for health and longevity reasons. I've been trying a new feeding method called time-restricted feeding, as the scientific evidence for its efficacy in circadian and metabolic regulation is quite compelling. 

However, I've been troubled by the fact that now, since I've been somewhat restricting my food intake due to the time limit, my obsessive tendendencies regarding food and body weight are starting to lurk back in...at the same time, I do notice the benefits of not eating so late at night, mainly I can sleep better and wake up earlier. I am at a normal body weight with a fitness level of body fat. But now I can't stop thinking about how I want to be below this normal healthy range. How do you balance striving to be healthy but not let it be a gateway to ED? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: suspect my BFs sister has an ED. Need help with how to talk to her. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 11:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all, could really use some help with how to talk to my BFs younger sister (21)

My BFs sister has always been quite thin and a picky eater. I've never been sure if she's just thin or has had disordered/restricted eating that has gone by without escalating/unnoticed. I am fully recovered from AN, btw. 

She recently got out of a 6 year relationship. It ended badly and has lost a bit of weight and is very underweight. I spent the weekend with my bf and his extended family, they are all quite worried but no one has said anything to her (and tbh I don't know if they would. They are debilitatingly afraid of conflict and time is crucial when it comes to EDs). 

My bf thinks I should talk to her because I would be an empathetic/understanding ear but I'm not sure what to say or how to approach talking to her and expressing my concern for how she is going?
My only concern is it might not be an ED, it's also possible that she's just thin, and in this understandably shitty post breakup time she has lost weight so I want to be sensitive to that.

Thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Help with approaching a bulimic roommate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 11:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need some tips on how to approach a bulimic roommate. I dont know her too well but I am aware of her situation (she pukes almost everyday). This may come off selfish but it is also negatively affecting my living condition since we share washrooms. I plan on talking to her but am looking for the best possible way to do it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I don't know who I can talk to about this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 02:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a 16 year old guy that has been struggling with disordered eating all my life. 

From when I was 2 I refused to eat most meats or vegetables. The only food I do like are "convenience foods" that aren't as healthy. I ended up overweight when I was 12. 
Needless to say I hated myself.

Then I started high school. I rode my bike there everyday and skipped lunch due to my laziness. When I got home I would eat loads of less-healthy food. I lost a lot of weight. Now I was at a "healthy" weight and stayed this way for about a year and a half.

Then I started restricting because I wasn't satisfied with my body. It spiraled out of control.

Now I've lost a lot of weight in a month. I liked the way I looked a few pounds heavier but my mind tells me if I start eating normally I'm going to be that fat, miserable kid again.

I feel like I will be teased by my siblings or my parents won't understand if I tell them. The worst part is I live in Canada where there is a huge lack of ED resources, especially for a boy.

I just want someone who cares to hear what I have to say and maybe offer some help.
TLDR: I'm a 16 year old boy struggling with AN who has no one to talk to about what's wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Bruises </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 02:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think small sized bruises ALL over ones legs/thighs (new ones daily) could be related to an ED/food intake? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: When does picky eating become a disorder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 10:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm getting pretty worried about my boyfriend's 10 year old daughter. When I met her, she almost bragged about how she never ate fruit or vegetables. I shrugged it off, figuring it was an exaggeration. It isn't.

In the 6 months I have known her, the only non-grain plant life I have seen pass her lips was in the form of a virgin version of a frozen drink. It's not just that, either. Foods she does like are bypassed because they aren't the "good" kind, she only likes them from restaurants, and not homemade, because she simply feels by refusing to eat them, she is gaining control, etc.

When my boyfriend was still married, his ex-wife was a SAHM. Despite being an athlete, and very nutrition conscious (she might actually have orthorexia. I don't know her well enough to say) with her own choices; she never made the kids eat anything they didn't want to. They always ate different dinners from the adults and each other; primarily of their choosing; largely composed of breaded, packaged, bland ingredients. They eat a bit of a larger variety with their grandparents, and with their dad (he has them 30-40% of the time); but the 10 year old still refuses about 90% of the food offered to her. The list of things she will eat, seems to be shrinking too. The younger child might complain, and throw some tantrums, but will eventually eat at least a small portion of about 65-70% of what she is offered. I feel this is pretty normal for a 7 year old.

I am not trying to blame this on just his ex wife. I feel both my boyfriend and his ex-wife have let this go too far; and are being too lax about it. They are writing it off as picky eating; and maybe it was at a point; but I think it goes beyond that.

I can't imagine how it feels to watch your family fall apart (the separation was 2ish years ago, with little warning). I imagine some hope was held out until the divorce was actually signed (about a year ago). I imagine watching one parent move on (by starting to see me seriously) added to that stress. In that way, I am responsible too.

I realize that a lot of times food is a tool of control and comfort; especially for younger children, who feel like they don't have control over much else (I think this is the same reason she refuses to wear deodorant). I might just be overreacting, but I'm starting to be afraid for her well being. Her dad told her she couldn't have dessert last night unless she ate one bite of a butter soaked green bean. The reaction was akin to what I saw the last time I saw my friend's parents try to get her to eat one bite of a meal, before they had to hospitalize her for anorexia. It was despair, fear, helplessness... It was like eating this one bite of a veggie she had never even tried, and had no way of knowing she didn't like, would kill her.

Am I overreacting here? I get along really well with his kids. They seem to trust me a lot. I don't want to destroy that trust and affection by needlessly pushing this. I know my boyfriend is taking my concerns to heart (hence him trying to get her to eat a green bean). At the same time, I understand his fear: She's eating enough calories. He's afraid that if we make too big a deal out of this, we'll turn what is maybe just a phase into a disorder.
I've only ever seen eating disorders from the outside. My mom had one. A few friends of mine have had a really rough go of it. I've been lucky enough never to get there. I'd really like to hear some perspective on this situation from people who have more knowledge in this realm.

Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Should I stop exercising? (In recovery, heart racing and getting dizzy) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 10:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had anorexia for about 5 years, but was never hospitalized or officially diagnosed. I definitely had a terrible relationship with food and exercise, though, and had a lot of the tell-tale physical signs of anorexia: severe acne and scarring, hair loss, always feeling cold, terrible nails, bloating, constipation etc etc.

Now, I've been in recovery for 11 months, and am completely weight restored. It's been really tough accepting my new body, though, because all the weight has gone to my stomach, butt and face. I've read that the weight redistributes, but it's been such a long time, I don't think it will. I've started doing light exercises in my own home, like planks, squats, push ups and lunges, just to tone up a bit... but I often get really lightheaded and need to lie down.

The thing is, I've seen multiple doctors who've tested my blood pressure, heart rate, listened to my breathing, etc.... and they all said I'm fine. Should I stop doing these exercises? Or is this normal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: So many issues I don't know where to start. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 23:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I currently am a healthy weight, although I am unhappy with my body. I honestly believe that I would be happier if I was just a little bit leaner, but as I have had a history with restricting/purging, years ago I decided I was not "allowed" to try to lose fat. Well recently I decided I was in a healthy enough place to try again. I started counting calories and weighing myself daily. I totally fixated on it. All I could think about food. I also have no idea how many calories I need per day because I exercise a lot, so I think I was tending to way under eat, and then I was starving, but I couldn't tell because I'm not in touch with my body and can't tell when I'm hungry. So then I would binge on junk food because I felt like a failure. And then I would severely restrict the next day to make up for it. Starve, binge, restrict, repeat. 

Am I ever allowed to try to get leaner? I also want to love myself no matter what shape I am, but it seems like I should be allowed to make what I perceive to be a minor change? I run ~5 days/week, and sometimes I struggle with which workouts to do because some workouts will make me stronger and faster, while others will burn more calories. I have started telling myself "I would rather be strong than pretty," but that makes me sad too.

I wish someone would just tell me what I need to do to get better. I've tried flooding myself with body positive blogs/instagrams/etc. but I just don't really believe it. I can't tell that it helps at all. On one hand I feel like if I was a little bit leaner, I really would be happier. I don't think I'm the type of person who would just keep going and keep going. I know this because when I am slightly leaner, I actually am happier with what I see in the mirror. On the other hand, I feel like I am a bad feminist for not just sucking it up and loving myself the way I am, but I honestly don't know how to. I don't understand why this is so hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: What exactly are the steps that are taken when someone starts recovery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 23:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like most of the questions are about support or knowing if they are, but when I hear someone is recovering from an ED, I'm not sure exactly what is going on behind the scenes. What are they changing? How do they get rid of the constant fear of overeating and the desire to push their bodies to lower and lower amounts? What steps do they take to stop obsessive tendencies like meticulously counting every calorie and weighing what little food they eat without being overcome with the fear that they're overeating? My girlfriend becomes uneasy at just the idea of her counts being underestimated, so how do you guys make it easier? I've searched coping methods and they all sounds pretty useless. One was "take a bath!". Thats not going to help surpass immense fear of overeating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Adderall and Anorexia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 22:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been taking prescription Adderall for two years for my adult ADHD, and a well-known side-effect of the drug is weight loss due to a suppressed appetite. The problem is that I have been diagnosed with anorexia and have suffered with it on and off for nine years (I lost a lot of weight purposely in 2014 when I got on Adderall for the first time. My anorexia was the worst it'd ever been). Sometimes I take more than my prescribed daily dose if I'm craving fatty food (like two weeks to a week before my period) resulting in me finishing my monthly bottle of pills a week to sometimes two weeks early. When I run out of Adderall, my appetite kicks back in at full force which results in me binging everyday until I can finally get my pills for the next month, and thus gaining a shit ton of weight/retaining lots of water weight. 

How do I stop this?!?! This is not healthy and it's honestly scaring me what this rapid weight gain (even if some of it is water retention) could be doing to my insides. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I think girl i've been dating has AN, not sure how to push her in the right </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 22:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there, I've been dating a girl who I believe has A.N. She has every one of the classic symptoms. But of course she is in complete denial and believes she is fine.
 
It was a bit of breaking point for me today because she had all the symptoms of a severe low blood sugar (i'm a type 1 diabetic so i'm familiar) but she kept refusing to eat or drink anything. Finally she had a little orange juice after a big battle.

I've never told her straight out that I think she has an ED. I'm not sure how to approach this. Thank you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Holiday Survival Thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 16:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With Thanksgiving coming up tomorrow and Christmas, Hanukkah, and New Year's around the corner, I thought it might be helpful to start a holiday survival tips thread. What helps you to have a happy and balanced holiday season? Do you have any recommendations for others with eating disorders to enjoy a binge-free, purge-free, restriction-free, and overall behavior-free time? What helps you to focus on the company of your family and friends instead of food, exercise, and body-image? How do you deal with negative comments from that one pesky aunt? How do you avoid going on a food rampage at the company holiday party? Or avoid the stress of eating around other people? ...you get the idea. I'd love to hear what helps others and share what helps me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My friend has anorexia, and I would like to support her, and I am not sure how </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 11:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am well versed with most mental health issues, because of my own issues and i am studying counselling. However, supporting a friend with anorexia is something that i don't know much about. I am also overweight, and I feel worried that this might complicate matters.

My friend talks about her eating disorder, but other than showing unconditional support and empathy, i am at a loss. There are times she will have difficulties eating. Is it better for me to not bring attention to it or gently encourage her? or is that something that varies from person to person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How do I tell my mother about my disordered eating? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 12:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, I am a 20F. I've been having sporadic episodes of disordered eating for years now. By that I mean that I can spend months not worrying at all about my weight and caloric intake, and then suddenly start seeing myself as not skinny enough, and consequently restricting. This usually lasts for a couple of months, then I go back to normal. 

For the record, I've always been underweight, even when getting an healthy caloric intake. But since last spring, when a close relative of mine was diagnosed with a pretty severe ED, my relationship with food and body image has gotten worse. I spent 4 months restricting , then 1 eating more or less normally (not eating really much, but not extremely restricting either), and now a couple of weeks ago I started restricting again, and way worse than I've ever done. It has gotten to the point that I constantly feel dizzy, my hair is getting thinner and thinner and has started falling out, my skin is dry, I am anxious and depressed all the time, and occasionally paranoid. I have troubles concentrating and my academics results have greatly suffered from this. I recognize this is obviously getting out of hand, but I can't stop. It started as a way to be in control, but now I am beginning to realise that I am not in control anymore. 

I recognize I may need external help to get out of this before it gets even worse, but I have no idea of how to ask for help. I am afraid to tell my mother (who is the person I trust more than anyone) because I don't want to hurt her and scare her. If I told her, I'd have to tell her about my issues with self harm too, And that would really be hard on her. I know she would feel responsible for my state, even if she has absolutely no fault in it. I don't want my father to know, because honestly he's one of the reasons for my ED. I don't want my sick close relative to know, because I know how competitive EDs are, and she's already having an hard time recovering without me adding to it. Furthermore, since her illness was the "trigger" for my own to spiral out of control, I don't want her to feel... guilty. 

I am scared. I don't know what to do. 

Any advice would be immensely helpful at this point. This is the first time I write in this sub, so I don't know if I did it correctly. If not, I apologize </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How do I choose recovery? My ED is destroying me but I feel like I can't change. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 03:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently going through a really tough time with a relapse. I've been struggling with my ED since I was an obese child, I've had diagnoses of bulimia and OSFED (atypical anorexia). I'm 22, have spent two years actively acknowledgeding I have a problem, I was in treatment but the services available to me aren't great, and I was also in an abusive home. Fast track to now, I live elsewhere and am in a better position for recovery due to lack of negative comments and abuse from my family. However, I relapsed, big time. 
This is making my relationship really hard and also my friendships. I've been invited to countless things in the past month, at least 4 or 5 a week. I've only gone to maybe two things this whole month, I can barely spend time with anyone if it involves food or alcohol. I feel comfortable eating only with my boyfriend, no one else. However it's making my relationship bad now too because my sex drive is just completely gone, I also have endometriosis and have started a new antidepressant, but I used to at least feel some desire. I feel like a blank, robot. I just, I don't know. I care about my boyfriend but find it so hard to be with him because I hate being touched and looked at. I don't like anyone looking at me and it puts me off even going to class. 
I've been avoiding social eating because it makes me feel violently angry after I've eaten, I don't purge anymore but the thought is still there and I end up wanting to hurt myself instead,i haven't but it's horrible enough. I'm in more psychological pain than I have been in a long time. 
My problem is that I know this is destroying everything. I have started feeling dizzy, weak, and faint too. But the weight loss encourages me. My doctor gave me bloods to get done but I'm putting it off because in scared there won't be anything wrong with me. I'm still overweight and no one ever takes me seriously about the ED. 
I don't know how to want to get better. What can I do to make this easier? Why am I destroying myself?? I have this stupid idea that I will feel better in x amount of kg and then I can get help, reality is I won't, and also I probably won't get there. But it's driving me. Im scared of getting worse because I live alone, but I don't know how to want to get better, I don't know how to even approach recovery again. It was so so hard last time. Please, any advice would be so appreciated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How do I tell my SO I'm entering treatment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 03:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've suffered from Binge Eating for a number of years now, with each year getting more severe than the last. On Monday of next week I have an intake appointment at a treatment center and it's very likely that they'll recommend inpatient treatment. 
What do I say? He has noticed some of my binges in the last few months but he knows that I'm self-conscious about food and my weight so he's never really said anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Seeking recovery advice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 03:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Help with struggling to eat and recovery...

I'm a 30f who's been suffering on and off from bulimia and anorexia for 10 years now. I've recently started a relationship with the most wonderful man. He wants me to be healthy, supports and helps me, and for the first time in a while I truly want to fully recover.

However, I'm having difficultly keeping with my meal plans. Last night I simple couldn't eat dinner and I've noticed the water retention in my body completely freaks me out. I was wondering for any tips to keep with meals, not skipping and dealing with the negative thoughts coming from the symptoms of recovery.
Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Trying To Support Girlfriend But Don't Know How </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 03:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So my girlfriend and I met after the summer because I was out of state and she got hired at the place where I worked. One day she asks if I can cover her because she's been sick for a while and doesn't feel well so I say sure. A few shifts after she was in the back eating food and spitting it into a cup which I guessed was because she didn't want to upset or stomach and gave her some space to do so. Flash forward to later, I left the store but liked her so we start dating but after the first date she tells me that she has an ed. Apparently over the summer she started throwing up every time she would eat (not purging, her body would just reject it) and would cry, try to eat, work, sleep, repeat all summer. She now can only eat pancakes, drink ensure, and eat fried eggs without the yolk. She's so terrified to try to eat anything other than that because she doesn't want to throw up and now she lost a substantial amount of weight over the summer and if she goes further I don't know what to do. We have an English teacher who really inspires her and she confided in her and the teacher told her that she used to be bulimic so I thought that would help her a lot. It really just ended up helping her a little but also making her feel weird because she feels like her problem doesn't match that of our teacher's. She told me that she feels isolated in this because she hasn't been able to find anyone that has the same problem so she doesn't have anyone to show her the grass is greener. Can anyone here tell me how to help her? I really wish I could but all I feel like I can do is tell her to keep moving forward and reassure her that it will be alright.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Need help finding an app that will count protein but not calories </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 15:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had issues with eating in the past but have been fine for the past 2 years. Recently I've started strength training and because of this I'd like to be able to track how much protein I'm eating daily, and because of various allergies I need to make sure I'm getting enough iron, vitamins, etc for my health. It was calorie counting and those apps in general that took me from wanting to loose a few pounds to spiraling out of control, and while I consider myself 100% recovered I know that if I start calorie counting again things will start to slide. Does anyone know of any apps that you can track your eating and it will tell you your daily grams of protein, fat, carbs, vitamins but WON'T show you the calorie intake? Thanks so very much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Has anyone suffered from anal prolapse as a result of their eating disorder? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 00:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been struggling with my eating disorder for about 7 years. For all of that time, including the months I was in-treatment, I have abused laxatives. I haven't grown fully dependent on them, so medically speaking I could stop if I had to; not sure ED would be too happy about that though. 

Long story short, I started noticing that I wasn't feeling anything when I went to wipe or that it felt like a heavy weight was on my bottom. I began having to go to the bathroom when I had literally nothing in my system, and it never felt like my bowels were empty. One day, I grew curious and took a picture; I was horrified at what I found and realized I probably had an anal prolapse for years now. Has anyone had to deal with this before as a result of their eating disorder? It really is killing my self-esteem and I can't bring myself to tell my family I have yet another problem medically because of this. When you look it up, it typically only ever happens to elderly people. I don't know what to do. I was hoping someone else understands what it's been like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Not sure if my issue is serious enough to get help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 10:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello,

In the beginning of 2016, I started a medicine named Zyprexa to treat psychotic depression. One of its side effects is weight gain. I maintained my old eating habits while taking this medicine (aka barely eating), and I ended up gaining weight enough to go from underweight to healthy weight. My doctor was happy I was finally normal, but gaining weight made me so upset that taking Zyprexa made me suicidal. So, I stopped taking it in September. I was supposed to see my psychiatrist about starting a new medicine but it didn't happen because he really wanted me to stay on Zyprexa despite how it made me feel.

In October I experienced a loss that made me very depressed. I started starving myself and I didn't get up from bed aside to go to the bathroom. I barely ate at all (I've only ever done this once in my life when I was suicidal enough that cops had to be called to my college to take me to the hospital). My eating habits got bad enough that I went to my doctor to get advice. She said I wasn't "seriously sick" since I was at a healthy weight, though it is kind of close to underweight. She then told me in order to help me, I had to help myself first and eat. This really bothers me because for a month of barely eating, I should have lost enough weight to be underweight. I actually did lose weight, but not much. The Zyprexa has changed the way my body is and makes it very hard to lose weight. I can't exercise it away due to some health conditions. And also, I just cannot eat normally. I don't understand the reasoning behind it, but when I'm depressed more than usual, eating makes me feel bad enough to want to self-harm, and I only eat when I'm feeling very weak,  or if I need to leave the house.

My question is, what do I do? If it's not serious enough to get help, should I wait until it is? I can't tell when it's serious. I feel sick and weak, the same way I felt before I was hospitalized in 2014, and yet my weight is normal and healthy for my height.

Also, how do people get better without a support group? I can't see my psychiatrist or my doctor until January, and I'm very short on cash so I can't see my therapist. Family is out of the question since they disregard anything that's wrong with me and we don't talk despite living in the same house. I'm 19 by the way. Sorry if this is confusing, I'm in an odd mental state right now.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] How to explain my ED to my boyfriend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 10:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is my question to the community: I have been struggling with an eating disorder for the past 8 years. I am working with doctors and psychologists in order to get better. I just recently got together with my [22F] boyfriend [23M]. We have been together about a month and have gotten very close in that month. I have told him about my issues with binge eating and bulimia, but I feel as though I'm not explaining myself very well. He has been nothing but great and supportive, and has even offered to come to an appointment at my psychologists with me. I feel very lucky to have found him.

I have been having a very difficult time these past two weeks but I don't know how/if I should tell him. Although I have told him about my issues, I don't think He really gets the extent to which I am suffering. I don't want to scare him off, but at the same time I don't want to lie to him and say that everything is fine (which I kind of have been doing). My eating disorder is very complex (which most of them are) and so I don't really know where to begin explaining things to him. I think a big part of it is that I'm embarrassed about my ED, even though I know I shouldn't be. I've basically been holed up in my bedroom for the past two days doing nothing, and I haven't told him that. I get embarrassed talking about it with anyone.

I have ruined all of my past relationships because of my issues, but this guy is very special and I don't want to ruin it this time. I want to make it work. If anyone has any advice, it would be greatly appreciated!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Unsure of how to help girlfriend recover completely </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 14:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Evening folks,

My girlfriend struggled with bulimia/purging disorder earlier this year. After a several tough months, she gradually improved to the point where she stopped purging completely. Since then, she has been doing very well and eats normally. However, she still shows signs of being affected by the experience and I am still worried for her well being.

The main problem, as I see it, is her low self esteem and a less than positive body image. I've been trying to boost both, but we have for a few months now engaged in a long distance relationship, so I don't feel like I can support her as much as I did before. It also seems that I, besides herself, am the only person still concerned with it.

I've noticed that her thoughts start to revert to the old pattern when she is in a period of great stress, or has been unable to exercise due to illness or lack of time. At social events, she feels guilty both when eating a piece of cake and when refraining to do so. However, my girlfriend seems to force herself to eat it, due to it being "normal", rather than to enjoy it. Although I do not want to admit it, I am concerned that she might relapse or come near a relapse in the future.

I am aware of the fact that a complete recovery is a long process. However, there is much more material on the web regarding the support of someone with an "active" eating disorder, than there is on supporting someone who has struggled from it previously. Thus, I'm in the need for some advice.

Should we try to get her a second appointment at a psychiatrist? She has only had one before. Although she is unsure on that point, I don't see the harm in being careful and playing it safe. Any opinions on this? I'm also trying to find a book (not on the self help format) to raise her self esteem.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Looking for male eating disorder survivors willing to be interviewed for article </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 03:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My name is Evette, and I'm the senior news and identity editor at Revelist, a site for millennial women.

I am currently working on a story about male eating disorder survivors sharing the one thing they want everybody to know about what it's like. 

If you are a male survivor of an eating disorder, and you would be willing to participate, you should contact me a contact me at edionne@revelist.com. The interview can be anonymous. I'll need to know your age, how long you've had/used to have an eating disorder, and one thing you wish people knew about what it's like to have an eating disorder as a man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I think my girlfriend has an eating disorder and I don't know what to do </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 13:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First some information about me:
I used to have an eating disorder but I managed to overcome it. I still struggle with feeling guilty after eating too much and sometimes I really feel disgusted about my body, but that's all there is to it. I cook healthy food for me each day and I eat at least 3 times per day. I do sports and live pretty healthy indeed.

However my gf is very very thin, to the point I'm afraid of "breaking" her when I hug her. I had thought that's just like she is, but in fact she rarely eats anything and when I ask her if she had breakfast she always tells me that she already had tea which counts as a meal in her opinion. I try to cook as often as I can for her but I can't do that every day and often she just refuses to eat because "she already had lunch"
She often feels weak in my arms and her heartbeat is racing like crazy

I'm so afraid 
And I don't know what to do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request]How can I help a distant friend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 04:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over the past year a friend of mine's girlfriend has lost a significant amount of weight. She was at a healthy weight before but now is significantly smaller, to the point that me and a few of my other friends worry about her having an eating disorder. I know its bad to make assumptions, but we are worried for her. How can we help her?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request]: How do you have sex while you feel gross? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 18:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I already have a low sex drive because of some unknown issue, but lately I've felt extremely disgusting because of the way I look (after accidentally gaining weight--I was in the healthy range a couple years after recovery and okay with it, but now I'm slightly overweight although no one else sees that... but the numbers are there) and it's made my sex drive go from low to just nothing. At all.

It's very distressing for me and my fiance. Do I just force myself to do it? I've refused to take my shirt off in front of him for months now, and just keeping my stomach covered isn't helping. I think I've just stopped seeing myself as a sexual being. Like, to think about myself having sex actively turns me off.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Needing distractions and coping skills </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 04:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lately I feel like I've either been bingeing or restricting and I cannot escape the cycle. Does anyone have some good distractions or coping skills I can use to keep myself on track? The trouble, I think, is mindlessness...I know I need to be more present. Anything that could help me achieve this? I'm kinda desperate and in a time crunch, so any answers would be much appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] The girl I am seeing is anorexic and I'm pretty sure is relapsing. What can I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 03:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know where to start, so this might be a little ramble-y. I am 18, almost 19 years old, and the girl in question is 19. She has been diagnosed with anorexia for many years, even going inpatient for 7 months (iirc). I have only known her for a couple of months. We immediately got along really well, and now both acknowledge that we like each other a lot, but just aren't ready to rush into an actual relationship just yet. 

A little while back she decided to tell me about her ED. I honestly had begun having suspicions, as she had never eaten in front of me, and she would constantly talk about loving food. Like most people, I had no idea what anorexia really did to you. Since she told me, I have read countless articles, posts, anything I can to try to understand what it is that she suffers with, and how to best help her. She told me that I would never know how helpful I am and how much I mean to her just by doing what I am, and by saying the things to her that I am (which I admit, are mostly word for word what I have read is good to say to people suffering from the disease)

The other day she went to the doctor, and she wouldn't tell me what her doctor said when she got back. She's been pretty open with what's going on, but these past few days she has done a 180 and is now saying that she wants to do what she wants, and that it isn't hurting me so I shouldn't be worried. It's none of my business, she says.

Obviously, that seems like a pretty good clue that things are pretty bad. Not only that, but she has recently been wearing looser and looser clothing, constantly degrading how she looks, and has been misinterpreting things I say and twisting them to make it seem like I am judging her. For example, we went shopping the other day, and she told me that the tights she got were too big, but she liked them anyway and got them. She wore them the next day, and I accidentally mentioned that they weren't big, and they looked great! I have been very purposeful to not mention things like that, but it slipped. She got offended and thought I was calling her fat. From what I have read, these are all things that are common for someone with anorexia who is relapsing. Last night I asked about it again, and we had a long conversation with many tears where she basically told me that she wouldn't blame me if I left her, because she doesn't want to hurt me, and everyone else in her life has left her before too. She made sure to say that many times, and that she wouldn't be offended at all, as she knows she is a pain and shouldn't have to be dealt with by other people. I told her that I chose her, and that I didn't care what others had done.

So here is where it gets a little more complicated. She told me one day that she has an instagram account where she posts food pics and talks about her eating disorder. She said the people following her have been basically the most helpful people she has ever had in her life, because they are constantly encouraging each other to fight, etc. One day she gave me her phone to play music, and she got a notification for that account. I did not immediately look at it, as I know it is private and I wanted her to tell me about if only if she wanted to. However, worry got the best of me today, and I looked at it. Her latest post was her telling everyone that things were bad. Very bad. Apparently her doctor had told her that if she didn't schedule to go inpatient before the end of December, she wasn't going to see her anymore. She went on to say that that was fine by her, and that she didn't even think she was doing bad enough to go back yet.

Reddit, what can I do? What should I do? How can I help? Can I help at all? I am at a loss, I am clueless as to what to do. I know a lot of other stuff about her ED that I can answer any questions about if I missed something that is important for advice. Thank you guys so much.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] What to do as a last resort for a loved one with an eating problem? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 03:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I care a lot about my roommate and his girlfriend, but his girlfriend is anorexic to the point that it is affecting their relationship and her health. She is becoming irritable and is lashing out at him about petty things, which my roommate, being a sensitive soul, isn't taking to well. She is also constantly complaining about headaches, stomach aches, and the other day nearly collapsed from exhaustion after just a couple hours of standing. He's tried to personally approach her about it, but she denies it is a problem, and it simply keeps getting worse and worse. Is the best course of action to force her in some way to seek help? We thought that telling her RA (we're in college) would be a good first step, but we're honestly just lost and worried. We're scared that trying to be supportive of her is going to just let her get sicker and sicker, but we don't want to be too forceful either. Please help!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Addressing roommate behaviors? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 21:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey,  I was hoping to get some advice from the community about my new roommate who I suspect is suffering with bulimia and I am really stuck how to handle it. 

Background: my flatmate takes 2-3 showers per day, which always begin with the bath taps running and really loud music. I can hear coughing, spitting and occasionally retching (but I often wonder if thats in my head). After around 5-10 minutes, the toilet flushes, shower goes on and the air freshener goes off. Now at first I thought she was maybe just self-conscious of pooping, but it's the routine of it which gives me the feeling things aren't quite right. She never buys any unhealthy food and really doesn't ever have a lot of food in, however if I buy anything remotely unhealthy it won't last more than a day. If I ask her to replace the missing food she gets really upset like she's about to cry and I feel like I have to ask in a really non-accusatory way so she doesn't flip out. She's ill all the time, with colds/flu and her skin is  dull and pale.

I don't know how to handle this situation and this sounds really, really horribly selfish of me but I find this mentally draining. I have a history with eating disorders, specifically bulimia, and when I hear her purge (or what I suspect) it brings up a lot of bad memories, which although I am semi in recovery, is really difficult to be around. I am in my final 2 months of my masters degree and cannot afford to mess it up, having taken a lot of time off for mental health reason and at last I am in the final straight. I have a big deadline in a few days but even now I am so worried and distracted about what to do I can't concentrate.

This all sounds very self centred of me and I feel sad that someone else is going through it and I don't know how to help. If I speak to her she might resent me for it and life in the flat will be very uncomfortable or potentially she could ask me to leave (she owns the apartment). Or she might become emotionally reliant on me, which I just don't think I have the capacity to handle right now, as bad as it sounds. 

Alternatively, I considered speaking to her sister or close friends, but I don't know if again she will feel betrayed. I feel very guilty that I can't help her and feel pretty helpless. Equally I wonder if I made this all up in my head, but I think instinct is quite important in judging matters like this.

Any advice would be hugely appreciated right now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Helping girlfriend with negative thoughts after eating </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 21:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I'm writing to you guys because I need help.

I recently got together with my girlfriend, and she has had a history with bulimia and anorexia. I really enjoy looking at her eating because she looks really happy, but after our meals, she would say things like how she feels disgusted at herself since she eats so much.

I'm really distressed and don't know how to go around helping her. I'm already constantly reaffirming her that her weight and her figure is fine, but she seems to be accepting it as a way to make me feel like I'm helping.
What advice can you guys provide for me? I'm sorry if I'm asking questions that can be answered easily but I couldn't find anything pertaining to my situation. However, I'll still be searching.

Hope you guys can help me, thanks a lot:)

The OP, /u/rollingon2, has requested to have their username added so you can PM if you wish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] How can I stop restrictive thinking and enjoy food without the impulse to exercise? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 00:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been struggling with what started out as a very restrictive diet at the end of college and beginning of law school, but am now stuck in a period of overexercise to compensate for all the food I eat. I feel like I'm ready for my next step of recovery but am still having some issues actually "pulling the trigger" and trying to balance my calories in/calories out as opposed to burn more calories than my estimated intake each day.

One of the things I'm struggling with is that I really enjoy eating out on the weekends but am afraid that I will not enjoy it anymore if I am unable to "work it off" through exercise during the week. **Does anyone have any tips for how to manage this in the real world?** Haven't let go of that pathological worry of gaining weight.

That being said, I recently (aka, past few weeks) have seen a large uptick and the scale despite being relatively careful about my diet. Has anyone experienced weight gain despite restriction--or, perhaps, because of it? I have some thoughts that perhaps my body is hurting and is for some reason holding on to extra pounds in the form of water/something else because it fears starvation? I ask not because I feel like I need to lose anything, but because I think understanding what's going on with my body or feeling like eating and exercising ini a more balanced fashion may be more motivating that way...

In any case, thanks everyone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Is it "okay" to eat the same thing every day in recovery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 02:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know recovery is all about giving up rules, and "normal eating" is all about being flexible.

But I'm really worried about my intake because my insurance doesn't cover any form of treatment, and I'm trying to navigate the physical aspects of recovery on my own. Like many of us in recovery, I've rediscovered many foods I forgot I loved. One of these is scrambled eggs (with a little cheese) on buttered sourdough toast. I eat it every day, since it's cheap and I like it.

My other meals have lots of variety -- pizza, salad, fruit, etc etc... But is it abnormal to eat the same meal for breakfast every day? I realize this question might sound stupid to some, but I honestly don't know what 'normal' eating looks like anymore, so I'm looking for some perspective.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Feeling devastated after problems with my psychiatrist. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 02:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted to r/EatingDisorders earlier this year with a general timeline and list of symptoms asking if it were possible if it sounded like ED behaviour. After discussion with my GP, she expressed concern about the bingeing and over-exercising but doesn't want to label it as an ED yet.

She gave me a referral for a dietitian who specialises in weight loss and EDs. So far she has been so positive and while I find myself questioning some of the choices she made on my food plan, at this stage I'm trying to trust her judgement.

My GP advised me to tell my psychiatrist also, referred to as P. P knows that I have ongoing weight issues (she raised my seroquel and prescribed effexor and valdoxan). But I've never said anything about previous or current bingeing/over-exercising concerns. I started off by describing what the dietitian was like and the overall plan - when I mentioned that breakfast was cereal P stated that it was too full of carbs and stated I should drink milk. When I mentioned eating every 3 hours, she said it was just a common dietitan tactic. I got as far as saying 'I have to tell you something', before she started talking about her morning routine with milk involved. Afterwards I didn't think I could tell her; maybe she would think my concern over my ED behaviours were an excuse to get out of diet and exercise? I was so panicked I went mute and we had to finish the session.

I called in sick for the next two sessions. I was anxious and didn't know what to say. This morning I went in and 1) missed the first 5 minutes because I was too anxious to go in and 2) when I did go in, went mute again. P's response was to threaten to send me someone else (which I expected - I have such a hard time trusting medical staff because either they screw up or they give up). I got upset, wrote down that I should have expected it and thanks for proving me right, then swore at her and left. Called my girlfriend, who talked me down and convinced me to go back in and talk with her.

Attempted to try and talk with P, but things got heated and I started yelling when I mentioned the milk. She called me abusive. Then she commented that I must be like that with other medical staff if I feel I should have expected it. She mentioned that I cost her a $1000 by not showing up to the previous sessions and threatened me several times more with writing a letter to my GP and firing me after stating that I do no work in the sessions.

This all just broke me. I honestly didn't think we had that much of a problem. And I still never even got to talk about my ED issues, which upsets me.

I just don't know what to do now. Can anyone help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Doctoral student seeks participants for online study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 12:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I am a doctoral student conducting an online study on eating issues. In order to participate you must be over the age of 18 and experience eating struggles. The goal of this study is to determine underlying issues that contribute to irregular eating habits, which will ultimately inform more effective mental health care for individuals with eating disorders. Participants will be asked to complete a series of questionnaires that lasts about an hour. You may stop at any time if you feel triggered by the questions asked. The study is completely anonymous and information is kept confidential. After participating, you can enter a raffle to win one of several $100 Amazon gift cards. If you are interested in participating in this exciting and important new research, please click here: https://tinyurl.com/BodyExperiences You can also contact the primary investigator, Alexandra Grundleger, LCSW at foodbodyresearch@gmail.com if you have any questions.

edit: You can PM the investigator at /u/FoodBodyResearch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to cope with unplanned weight gain? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 02:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been recovering from AN-b/p for several years now. For the past few years, I've maintained a slightly underweight BMI, and I've gotten used to the idea of staying there. Recently, however, my weight has been trending slightly upwards. I am now maintaining a lower-range, but technically healthy, BMI. I feel like it should not be a huge deal, but I just do not know how to cope. I know that I need to accept where my body goes naturally, but I'm struggling with intense urges to both restrict and binge. Does anyone have tips for accepting a healthy body weight, dealing with weight gain, or working on body image distortions? I am afraid I will slip into old behaviors if I can't get a better handle on this soon. :(
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I've just realised I have bulimia and I need help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 12:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disclaimer:I'm under 18 and male (not sure if that will help with my question)

I want to keep this short. For the last 6 months I've been obsessed with my body image and trying to lose weight. However I've started to vomit half of what I eat. It started around two weeks ago and now I've only realised this isn't normal. I've started to become more tired and lose more energy (not sure if that's a side effect of having bulimia) and I am worried about my health. Even now as I am writing have the urge to eat a lot but I don't want to for fear of vomiting. I can eat normal meals, but it's when I eat any snacks outside my meals, I vomit them up.

How do I stop myself? Is there anyway I can stop myself binge eating, and therefore lose the feeling to vomit what I eat.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] How to help my little sister </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 04:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think my little sister (11 y/o) might be showing some early signs of disordered eating habits. As her role model/someone she looks up to, is there anything I can do to prevent it from getting any worse?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request]Being overweight while in recovery has me scared of relapse. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 03:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm having a really hard time in recovery lately. Despite eating better and working out, I am still overweight. I am trying to not focus on my size, but it is so hard when I can't even shop in stores I like because I am too large for all of their sizes. All I want is to be the size I was before I started with this eating disorder... 

Does anyone have any kind words? Or even advice on how to get my metabolism back to normal? Or on how to eat properly? I left residential in July and don't have a nutritionist; the one there simply focused on intuitive eating and our chef made everything as she instructed, but the nutritionist never told me how to balance meals on my own or anything...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Are there any good resources for ED recovery WITHOUT insurance? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 03:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm struggling to recover from anorexia. I live in Milwaukee Wisconsin, if that's relevant. I have some form of Obamacare, so I don't have mental health coverage, and I can't see a nutritionist without a diagnosis, which I can't get now that I'm weight restored and eating adequately.

Are there any other options for someone like me? I've been getting 100% of my information for recovery through the internet, which is okay, but I feel so alone in this. I have so many questions about my body and am always on the point of relapse. I really need a therapist, or at least some sort of guidance aside from my general doctor, who isn't an ED specialist.

Is there anything? Or am I screwed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request]Best Residential Treatment Centers in USA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 03:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apologies if this was asked already (I searched and couldn't find anything): Does anyone have personal recommendations for Residential Treatment centers for eating disorders? Everyone's websites make things look good, but I am curious what others have to say about personal experiences, either from yourself, a friend, loved one, etc.

Thank you!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Article on BED] 7 things you should know about this 'secret' eating disorder that's more common than anorexia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 02:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: "Set Point" in intensive outpatient recovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 02:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am currently in an intensive outpatient setting, and have been for a little over four weeks (not including a week of hospitalization). I reached a healthy weight just today, and have currently been overeating (calorie prescription to gain weight - if this is important to know, it's over the "minimum recovery guidelines" that I have seen floating around online). I have been gaining at a steady rate even at levels before my calorie prescription, but they have been increasing it anyway to meet the weekly requirement of weight gain. However, my treatment team is saying that if I maintain over the weekend (the program is weekdays, and during the weekend we are at home), they will increase my calories again so that I will gain more. I've been struggling to accept "set point theory" and trusting my body, but this is kind of messing with me. If I am eating above "recovery guidelines" and maintain at a healthy weight, wouldn't that mean that I have reached my 'set point'? Why would they need to increase the prescription?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Should I ask my doctor about medication to help with one of my triggers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 02:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have childhood hunger based BED. My biggest trigger is how -painful- my hunger gets. I'll eat and eat to not feel the awful pain of it. I can identify normal hunger, and when I'm too hungry, nausea, and this feeling is next in line. Is this just related to hunger hormones? Should I see a doctor or a therapist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] How to get help while maintaining my career </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 15:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been thinking on this for MONTHS, and finally want to just toss out everything going on in my head to those who may understand and have some suggestions.

I was first hospitalized inpatient for anorexia at age 11. I went inpatient again at 15, 19, and 23. The 23 was the kicker because that pulled me out of a job and it was VERY hard to get back into a career again afterwards, strained my relationship with my husband (who was also dating me when I went in at 19), and caused all sorts of life pain.

I am now 36. I relapsed 2 years after the last inpatient visit and haven't rebounded since. I am at an unhealthy weight and have been there for quite some time. (no numbers). I have not just established myself in a new career, but have advanced highly in it, have two kids, and a lot more responsibility than I ever have. In other words, I feel as though I can't just leave this time to do any inpatient, residential, or partial programs without risk of losing the position that is paying the rent and bills, losing my husband, and being away from my children.

One week ago, I have my yearly physical. All the bloodwork, EKGs, tests came back positive. Healthy. Normal. Except the doctor warned me I was a ticking time bomb. And I get that. But I am also trying to logically think how this would play out if I "went anywhere" to "get help." How would I pay the bills without a job? Not just medical bills, how will I keep up on rent if I just leave? Can I, do I, should I really walk away from where I am good at what I do and highly respected for it? Everyone says "well if that's the case, then gain the weight yourself." It's not like this is my first rodeo, that I don't know WHAT to do- that I just "want to run to a safe haven and not take responsibility." I do as much as I can, I push it, but then get to that tough point, that part where it's so hard to push through on your own, where you need an extra push for more than just a half hour chat- a good month-long push to not just go through it with, but to CONTINUE through with it until it no longer seems as foreign. But can't I just do that myself? "Come on, think of reasons."
In a way, I want to get help. Finally kick this damned thing and be free of it. But in a way, what's that help really going to do or look like? As I said, I've already been in treatment centers 4 times in my life- 3 different treatment centers, and I still ended up relapsing. What would be any different? How would it all work out so I'm not jobless, with a divorce, sharing custody of my kids, maybe even homeless? What treatment centers are even our there that are any good?

Sorry for the rambling, but these have all been things going on in my head for the longest time and I just needed to vent them out in a safe place. I am in no immediate danger, but there's also nothing healthy about maintaining what I'm doing. There's no easy answer. There's no straight up "easy answer." I'm not expecting that. Just any input. Ideas. Suggestions. Or just a safe place to let this all out.

Thanks everyone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Help with avoiding being triggered by other's eating habits/overeating? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 04:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been working very hard on overcoming my eating disorder (EDNOS) lately. One thing that I haven't been able to fix yet is not letting other's eating affect me. For example, recently at my boyfriend's family gathering, watching everyone overeat around me almost gave me an anxiety attack. This is probably because now I am VERY mindful of only eating until I am full and eating slowly.

In general, my boyfriend triggers me a lot, either by him eating really quickly, or breaking the "rules" I had set for myself when I was deep in the disorder.

This is really the one thing that seems to be preventing my recovery the most--when I see other people eat in certain ways and situations, it makes me want to purge almost immediately. Does anyone have any ideas as to how to work on this? I don't want to be so affected by others and I want to be able to enjoy parties and family gatherings more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Survey Request] Request survey input for my university dissertation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 01:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey! I'm doing my university dissertation about eating disorders due to my own battle with one, i'm playing catch up as I was in hospital over my ED all summer and would like to share the survey in the subreddit (it has no images, no mentions of specific weights, no numbers about weight etc and has international helplines on final page)

https://www.surveymonkey.co.uk/r/PXBDRQR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Girlfriend has bulimia and refuses to get help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 00:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend has bulimia and refuses to get help. She seems to be getting worse and I wondered if anyone had advice for how I should help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Wondering if I have an eating disorder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 04:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've struggled with poor body image for a long time. I've always felt ugly and gross. It isn't just my weight, but my face, acne, and teeth as well. But, well, for the purposes of this post, I'm wondering if it is just poor self esteem or if I actually have an eating disorder. While I'm not actively starving myself or checking for calories, I always feel fat or overweight; whenever I look at my body I pinch my stomach and breasts to check for excess fat and am absolutely horrified if I have any fat that pokes out over my underwear (ie "mushroom top"). I go through periods where I exercise religiously and try to make sure I only eat a very low number of calories a day. I weigh myself nearly everyday and always feel ashamed when I look at the scale. I don't typically let it rule my life and often don't really think about it, but whenever I am in the shower or changing clothes - and sometimes when I eat too, I guess - I feel deeply ashamed of my appearance."

Do I have an eating disorder? Can anyone offer advice?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My friend has anorexic tendencies, and I need help with knowing what to do </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 00:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I'm mostly looking for help on how I can be as helpful as possible regarding my friend. She has told me she has issues with seeing herself as overweight, despite being (previously, at least) at a healthy weight. She has recently lost a significant amount of weight, bordering on being dangerous if it goes much farther. She is involved in gymnastics, which takes up a significant portion of her day, every day. She has told me that she has bulimic tendencies, and it doesn't help that she has a gastrointestinal issue which makes eating painful. Right now she has told me she has set a target ( which I don't know exactly ), but I can't imagine it's good, on top of the already significant weight she has dropped in recent months. She has said that she doesn't need help / does not want treatment, and has told me not to tell anyone; I will not unless it becomes very necessary as it will cost the friendship, I'm sure. She also has trust issues (ie believes people will become her friend to find out about her and ruin her life), and I'd prefer not to reinforce that notion, unless, again, it is absolutely necessary. Further compounding the issue is that she is mostly a online friend, meaning I see her very little to not at all for extended periods. We are also minors, if that means anything. I'd like to know what I can do, if anything, to help her given the complex circumstances. I'm very concerned for her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Struggling with BED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 00:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I have struggled with BED since last year and it is ruining my life. I grew so anxious last year due to this that I refused to attend school for the second semester because I feared what people thought of my weight. Over the summer, my binging decreased (but I still binged occasionally). I am now back in school, and sure enough, my severe binging has returned.. 
Any time I attempt to diet, I always end up binging even more by the end.

I went to a psychologist and a psychiatrist when I stayed out of school and into the summer (over 5 months) but they really didn't help at all. I am reluctant to visit any others at the moment because I feel like I will have the same experience.. I don't know what to do for myself.

It would be great if someone could give me advice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Struggling with 'disordered eating'. Is there something I can do myself? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 00:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do not have a history of eating disorders, however I do struggle with anxiety and depression. Recently I've been put on some medicine that caused a decent amount of weight loss. I'm still a healthy weight, but if I lose much more, I will be in danger of being underweight. 

The issue I'm having stems (I think) from the medicine. It kills my cravings/appetite. I've been eating only about one full meal a day for months. I'm just not hungry. There's inevitably a day or so each month where I'm super hungry and over-eat. This always makes me very sick and I return to eating next-to-nothing out of necessity. 

Not sure it's classifiable as a disorder, but it's definitely disorderly. Is there anything I can do to to make this any easier/healthier or do I need to consult a doctor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Dealing with Bloat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 04:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there. I've been in a downward spiral with my ED's. I've dealt with various parts of the spectrum of ED's for years, and the past few months things have gotten mentally and emotionally much worse. I keep feeling panicky and have had to leave work and drop my courses for the semester since I'm so afraid to be around people due to my poor self image. One thing that I'm struggling with severely right now is bloat/stomach issues. I rarely eat a full meal and I know how irrational that is, but when I do eat, my stomach gets very upset and bloated feeling. It makes it difficult to resist purging. Plus, at this point I'm not dealing with amenorrhea, and starting birth control in the past three months has influenced this, but bloated pms symptoms are also really making me feel so out of control. Is there any way to deal with that? When your body image is already so out of control awful, it is torture to feel like you're losing false control. Also, I was incredibly restrictive with my eating and running dozens of miles weekly earlier this year, but hurt my knee in April and have lost the will and energy and feeling of self worth to exercise. I know I must have gained some weight and lost muscle mass, and am unsure of how to mentally cope.
Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Unsure on how to help girlfriend recover completely </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 18:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Evening folks,

As the title suggest, I'm in need of some advice regarding my role in the recovery of my girlfriends eating disorder. As for some background information, we have been together for almost a year now. At the same time, she started having issues with her body image and lowered her self esteem. She has told me that she had been tinkering with the idea of purging for some time before meeting me, but I believe the actual trigger was her starting to see me.

A few rough months later, things became better. She finally made an appointment with a therapist. Since then, she has only had one relapse involving purging, right before summer. However, I know that the ED still bothers her and she thinks of it as often as every day. The last months have, all in all, been good, which I am extremely glad for.

I am aware of that a complete recovery will take a long time with a lot of support. That to be said, I am glad we managed to progress in a positive direction early on. Lately, has started to exercise almost every day, which worries me. I have also become the only person she still talks to regarding the ED. Since I did not get the chance to attend therapy with my girlfriend, I had to read up on eating disorders and learn the hard way. As a consequence, I have made errors and refrained from taking action too often, putting myself in a helpless position. I am glad she opens up to me, but I neither believe I have the right knowledge to help her, nor that I should be the only person helping her. The latter both for her sake and my own.

I need advice on what to do now, because I do not feel that I can be of any actual help at this point. Would it be wise to convince her to make a second appointment with the therapist?

On a side note: I have trough all this time tried to play a pure, supporting role, because I had the belief that she should get the chance to resolve her issues by herself. At the same time, I tried to be as supporting as I could, but it has been hard on me to. Especially after her mother found out and used much stricter methods, once going as far as telling my girlfriend that she was disappointed in her. Since I did not believe it was in my role to take any action, I still hold a grudge. I tried my best to not transform my girlfriends problem to my own, but paradoxically, it has affected me. I do not regard myself being on good terms with her mother, something I keep mostly to myself. She has also proved herself not to be willing enough to change the family's eating habits, which I perceive to contain unnecessary fat.

I'm not sure about what I should do with my own problems, but I guess I have to help myself in order to help my girlfriend again?

TL;DR: I am unsure on how I can help my girlfriend recover completely after a few months of purging disorder, whereas I at the same time do no longer feel like I have the knowledge and resources to help her. You could say I also struggle with this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to help my girlfriend with BED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 18:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi,

My girlfriend is a recovering binge eater. She's worked hard for a year to eat healthy and lose weight. However, today she had a huge setback. She ate everything in the fridge at her work and even picked up boxes of cookies on her way home. I want to ask the community what I can do or say to her about seeking coping strategies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I feel lost and alone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 22:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my best friends, who I met IP for AN and was my room mate for roughly a month in hospital took her own life just over two weeks ago. The memorial was yesterday and now I feel so lost and alone. She was my biggest supporter and now I feel like I'm slipping back to old habits and I have no idea what I'm doing. Has anyone else experienced something similar? If so, any advice on how to get through this would be very much appreciated x </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] In recovery from AN. Struggling to form healthy relationships with other females </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 22:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there. I just recently discovered this sub so bear with me. 
I suffered from AN for about four years and during that time I started forming really negative views towards other women. Most of this was founded on jealousy over physical aspects, but over time, it was also compounded by the fact that several of the people I dated cheated on me (and because my mind was being afflicted by the AN, I blamed the girls, instead of the guys). 
For the most part, I feel recovered. I still have thoughts once in a while but they're brief and fleeting and nothing comes from them. The main problem is that I still really struggle with other women -- if they're remotely attractive and are near my age, then I immediately feel jealousy and think negatively of them. Obviously this is a really unhealthy behaviour and I want to get over it. I also have anxiety/GAD and depression/MDD, if that matters. 

Does anyone have any tips on how I can get over this and start having healthy friendships with girls my age? Thanks in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Ready for help. For real this time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 11:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've said it so many times, I feel like i'm not gonna be taken seriously. But I finally realized how sick I really do look, after taking a look at my wedding pictures. My husband is fully aware of my ED, we just got married(literally today) ... I don't want to put these stressors on him. But I feel like I honestly need the help. This time I do have something to lose if I don't get better. I just need a little bit of encouragement to bring this up to him.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Constantly slipping back/worried about adulthood </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 10:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to be turning 18 in a few months, so no one will be able to put me in treatment unless I really want to be there and my options for treatment will be pretty limited since I'll be booted out of the program I'm in now for AN (diagnosed roughly 2 years ago). My issue is that with being an adult and moving out of the family home shortly after that, I really don't think I have the capability not to relapse. I already cut corners a lot and slip back into restrictive patterns and over exercising as soon as I get any leeway. I'm currently at the lower end of healthy weight and I've been here for a little under a year. I can mostly manage the eating part without freaking out but mentally and body image wise it's still pretty bad. I'm not sure if I should consider going into a more intensive program (day treatment or residential again) or if I should wait and see how things go on my own? I don't really have much in the way of support other than LT boyfriend but this puts a lot of pressure on him which makes me feel guilty. Any advice on how to proceed or things I could try to counter the thoughts would be very much appreciated xx
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Fiance with Bulimia, Zero interest in Intimacy/Sex </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 10:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iv been with my partner for nearly two years now. I knew early on that he had suffered from Bulimia as a teenager and then about a year into our relationship i discovered that his bulimia had returned. Iv tried my best to be as supportive as possible and done a lot of research but at this stage i'm leaving him to deal with it on his own, at his request.

Our relationship isn't perfect and we have had some issues which mainly stem (for me) from the lack of intimacy. About a year ago, all the intimacy/sex in our relationship ceased. This is coincidentally around the same time the bulimia re-appeared and the same time we were having a lot of issues.

This has caused me to become extremely frustrated and confused and as a female it has made me lose all self confidence (thinking its me and the way i look or that he doesn't love me) and made me very untrustworthy of him (thinking he must be cheating with someone else). Iv confronted him many times and he's given me the following reasons at various stages - I don't feel loved by you - I feel judged by you - Its your attitude and the way you speak to me - I'm just stressed about work - I just don't feel good about myself

In the past year we have had sex twice. Its had a great effect on me mentally and emotionally as i'm happy to forgo sex for months, but he wont even kiss me. The extreme lack of intimacy is eating away at me. The most i get is cuddles in bed.

Iv done some research and cant seem to find that decreased sex drive is really a symptom in Bulimia. If some men on here can offer some insight because i'm going crazy constantly thinking that something else is going on or that he doesn't love me and is just using me as a crutch! I cant wrap my head around the fact that he's gone this long without any sexual desire and have convinced myself that hes cheated!

Please help. I know this may sound selfish but Its been a year of me being patient and understanding and i don't know what to do anymore. I'm a mental and emotional wreck.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I'm falling apart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 10:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really know what exactly triggered it (quitting my job, moving cities, getting married -so much stress right now), but I've fallen so hard back into the b/p cycle and I don't know what to do. I hadn't purged for a year when I started doing it again back in April or May, and now it's a thing happening 2-3 times per week. The binges started off small, just going over my planned calories by a modest amount but now they are crazy. I've been on a week long eating bender since last Saturday and I've gained several pounds. I feel so out of control, but also powerless to stop it. I feel like a terrible person because I'm subtly manipulating my fianc into letting me eat whatever I want - just tons of excuses and little lies. I'm just waiting till he gets fed up with me and leaves. Maybe I should break up with him to spare him the torture that a life with me will be. I love him so much but sometimes I wish he would break up with me so I could kill myself and be done with this world. I'm not actively suicidal, but the ideation is so strong that I can't help fantasizing.

Help please. Im losing it :(
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Getting Help as a Minor? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 02:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been struggling with bulimia for nearly three years now, and have since come to terms with the fact that self-help alone isn't working for me and that I should seek outside help with recovery. I have a decently close relationship with my friends and family, but since I retain a fairly healthy weight and wear very concealing clothing even when I don't, they haven't noticed.

The only problem is that they very frequently crack jokes about EDs and bulimia especially, calling everyone who has them crazy, stupid, overly dramatic, and desperate for fake attention among other derogatory terms. I have even proposed a hypothetical situation with one of my closest friends about how she would react to a friend coming out to her about bulimia, and her supposed response would be to laugh in their face.

Furthermore, I am a minor currently in high school, so I can't pursue professional help without them being legally obligated to inform my parents. I have considered going to my school guidance counselor, but our school rules require them to notify parents of any issues with their children's health.

I apologize if this seemed a bit like a rant, but I'm simply tired of being controlled by my ED and don't know how I can start taking steps towards recovery. 

Any advice?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I really don't want to slip into old habits. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 02:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't want to slip into old habits.

Back in high school I had very high anxiety and part of that led me to restricting eating to very little or what I thought was little. 

My anxiety made me very self conscious about what I ate and how I looked. Never getting more than a certain weight. Sometimes lower though. Then I got put on medication that helped the anxiety but I gained a lot and now I'm in the obese category for BMI.

I'm now trying to get back to at least average weight. But I'm really afraid of slipping into old habits of not eating. I heard the best way is to track calories but when I see how little i've eaten I get too happy. I just really need advice about getting back in shape but not getting into old habits.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How do I cope? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 11:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had a long and complicated history with food. I've almost always been overweight or obese. I won't go into my whole history because it's long and and a boring story. But basically I feel like my dysfunction with food really increased when I moved out of my parents house. I was obese but not as high weight as usual, and at a low weight for me in adulthood. Thanks to constantly binge eating I soon gained to my highest weight. Following a manic episode I moved back into my parents house and kind of bad it but me how terrible I felt. And I started restricting. I've been eating very few calories, with an occasional high calorie binge. I abuse laxatives regularly. I b/p when I'm left alone for a period of time. This isn't the first time I've done This. I've gone through periods where I binge for months and put on a ton of weight and then restrict for months and take a bunch off.

A friend of mine thinks there's something wrong. I don't know. I feel like an imposter. I'm still obese.  I'm so fat it just doesn't seem like I could have an ED. I dunno.

Not eating is the best way I've found to deal with the binge eating. Its like the only way I've found to cope. And it's addictive. I just don't know what to do otherwise. My therapist doesn't help. Nobody can help. I know that I'm too fat for it I've found myself looking at a lot of pro ana and thinspo and stuff like that and its just messing with me mentally. This stuff is all getting in the way of life again and I hate it.

I know this reads like a rant and sorry for that. I'm just looking for someone to tell me what I should do
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Not sure how to describe it, but I've developed a really bad binge eating problem that has started to ramp up lately. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 02:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So let me start with some background:

I'm currently a 21 year old male, 5'11" and and normal weight. About 2 years ago, I began a pretty strict low carb diet to loose some weight (I used to have a lot more fat on my body) while I trained with workouts such as p90x. I got in pretty good shape, and after about a year I loosened up my diet a little bit. This isn't to say I ate whatever, but I wasn't as concerned as I used to be.

However, since that change I began to develop a terrible binge habbit. I would eat well most of the week, but then on the weekend I might end up seriously binging on some food. It started out not so bad, I might eat like a couple pieces of cake or something. But it's progressively gotten worse. Now, I eat a very  large number of calories in a sitting when I binge, like I literally cannot stop. I just don't feel full when I do. I can eat an entire package of cookies and then start to kind of feel full. And even worse, I've developed a guess a minor case of bulimia where whenever I binge I feel guilty and try and toss it up. (I don't do this when I eat regularly, just when I binge or eat bad).

I just don't know what to do. I feel like I can never tell my body that I shouldn't eat something. It mainly happens with "feel good" food especially sweets. If it's in front of me, I'll eat it no questions asked. It's getting bad and I'm to the pint where it may start to become my main diet and I will start becoming extremely unhealthy in my weight and physical appearance. I'm not sure if this is the right place, but I'm desperate for advice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Smoking weed during recovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 00:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been in recovery for BED and Bulimia for about 3 years and have been smoking weed for 1. I gained weight and still suffer from dysmorphia issues. Medical weed has certainly helped with the guilt associated with eating but often leads me to overeat to the point where all I can think about is purging. For those who smoke weed to help with their eating disorder, how does it help/hinder you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Mom might cause relapse? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 00:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in highschool, and I've had weight issues for as long as I can remember. However, I was always pretty good at hiding it. Over the last year I'd thought I was getting better. I was a little over the weight I'd told myself I'd kill myself at, officially a healthy weight, and I was managing to not completely freak out.

A few weeks ago I went to the doctors for the first time in a while. My mom came with me and wanted to see my weight. Since then, she keeps making jokes about how I'm such a tub of lard and stuff. I haven't completely freaked out and relapsed yet, but I can feel it coming. I don't know what to do without telling her about this part of my life that no one knows about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Concerned about whether I have an ED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 18:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have never been overly concerned about my body and how it looked until after high school when I stopped my ballet classes and slowly started putting on weight (in hindsight even during my time in ballet I did worry slightly about weighing too much and at one stage was secretly glad when I got sick because I lost some weight).

Along the way I was dianosed with depression and GAD by one GP and was prescribed Lexapro. I gained weight. I attempted to tell several doctors but since weight gain wasn't an official side effect I was brushed off and after a while I was so desperate I stopped taking them.on my own. But the weight wouldn't move. 
Eventually I had a breakdown and it was decided I needed to be on meds again. I was put on Seroquel. I put on a heap of weight. I started craving chocolate and bread like crazy. I tried to just 'eat an orange' when I got a craving like everyone told me to do, but it didn't seem as easy as that. At the end my weight was significantly higher than it was when I was dancing.

I decided to take things into my own hands and started exercising (interval cycling for half an hour) and drinking shakes to lose weight. And for a while it worked. I brought my weight down. But it didn't last. The weight slowly crept up. And the exercising became excessive. Sometimes I would do the usual half hour two or three times a day, depending on whether I thought I had slipped up and eaten something bad. It got to the stage where it was hurting to cycle and I would have to stop, but I would want to keep going.

So currently as of three weeks ago I'm back up to the weight I was under Seroquel. In recent years my diagnoses have changed slightly: depression, social phobia and Aspergers. My psych has paired up metformin with the seroquel in the hopes that it may help but nothing. I start reading about keto and give that a try. I have lost some weight. I'm happy with this. It seems sensible. But now I'm getting ectopic heartbeats possibly due to the diet not providing enough electrolytes. So I have to have tests and I may have to give that up when it was going so well. On the way home tonight I was seriously considering either throwing up what I'd eaten today or buying some laxatives, as I've had those before when I've been unwell and I know they could work. But I don't want it to come to that.

I didn't realise until now how much I hate my body, how gross I am and how much I really really just want things to go right for once.

Do I have an ED? Can anyone offer advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Entering program for BED next month </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 18:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there, I'm new to all of this... I was officially diagnosed with binge eating disorder nearly three weeks ago and this week was given a place in a program, but it doesn't start for another month.
I feel like I'm in a weird kind of limbo where I have recognised there is a problem, but can't do anything about it yet, and it's messing with my head a bit.

I'm scared about the program, that I'll get there and they'll tell me I don't really have a problem, and I'll be left to my own devices all over again. I keep telling myself I'm wasting everyone's time in trying to get help.

Not sure exactly what I'm asking for, mainly support and hearing about other's experiences at this point in their journey? I don't know anyone IRL who has gone through this, and in fact I haven't told anyone beyond my husband and obviously my doctor that I have an ED.

Thanks in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [REQUEST] Looking for good workbook on nutrition and cookbooks that help during recovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 02:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like more information on healthy eating
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
