<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6210</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 08:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My theory is that it's a lack of fat in our diets. Only 7% of my cals are from fat, it  should be closer to 20%. And peanut butter is super high in fat. Thank god I buy the low fat one, 30% less calories.

The pb I buy is in plastic jars, so I can't even get cool glasses from it, just shame... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 08:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today was another binge fest, but it was my birthday, so I feel slightly less guilty than usual.

I had 2 grilled cheese sandwiches, 4 cupcakes, 2 cookies, 2 macarons, all of which I purged.

I also had popcorn, chicken fingers, yam fries and peanut butter chocolate chip cheesecake which I didn't purge. I promised my mom I wouldn't purge my birthday dinner.

I have a bunch of cake left so I'll probably end up binging and purging it tomorrow. Last time I b/p'ed this cake it was horrible and it ended my binging and purging for over 2 months. So I'm hoping that will happen again this time. That's why I requested this type of cake instead of another one. 

I'm also starting to get sick right now, so hopefully that will help stop the binging. A soup diet would be nice right now. 

Sorry this turned into a long post. I'm laying in bed and I can't sleep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 08:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you make your chia pudding and how big is a serving? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 08:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peanut butter. When I wasn't restricting I barely ever ate it. But now it's my biggest binge food. I've been in a never ending b/p cycle lately and I'm pretty sure I ate 7 jars of the stuff in 2 weeks. I ate a whole jar in the last 24 hours. I'm obsessed with it, just a craving will trigger multiple binges in a day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 07:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like they look thinner than me, but I know in my mind that I'm usually thinner. But most of the time I feel fat compared to them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 06:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make sure to get mio sport, the regular one doesn't have electrolytes. Since I've been drinking it, I stopped getting light headed as much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 20:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never exercise. The only thing I do is walk my dog </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 14:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have my own sloth rescue and sanctuary in Costa Rica. There would be plenty of fruit trees in my yard so I could have fresh fruit all of the time. I would have a few cats and a dog. I would also be able to take a trip or two every year and visit the world. 

I would be a few inches taller and a few pounds lighter with a nice flat stomach and thin thighs. 

I would also have a few pot plants that could sustain my habit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 02:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have a scale, I get weighed weekly at the doctors.

My parents got rid of our scale when I was a teen because I would weigh myself like 15 times a day and I became incredibly obsessed with the numbers. It drove me crazy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 01:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's so cold lately, it was so warm last week </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 01:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cocoa (147)

Lunch: Egg whites (60), celery (6), red bell pepper (11) and 1 cup spinach (8)

Dinner: Shirataki noodles with vegetable bouillon and soya sauce (26)

Snacks: 3/4 cup vanilla yogurt (140), sugar free jello (20), diet coke (0) and mio sport (0)

Total: 418 calories

Today was pretty good, I was feeling not horribly depressed for a bit, so that was a nice change.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 01:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too! I can't believe there's someone else from this frozen hell on here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 00:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm from the prairies too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 23:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are a great writer! There isn't enough media about men's struggle with eating disorders, good job </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 23:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a smoker, I probably smoke way to much, but it keeps me sane. I quit smoking last year, but once I relapsed back into my ed I started smoking again

It's so gross and expensive, but I wouldn't be able to survive without it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 22:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not healthy, but you can get a big bowl of sugar free jello for 20 to 40 calories for a whole box. I've been eating a whole bowl everyday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 18:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This community is amazing. I don't know where I would be with this sub. I consider you all to be my friends in this hard time in my life. I'm so glad that I found this place </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 17:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I woke up with diarrhea this morning, I feel so empty now.

I also have digestive issues, so usually after a binge I get diarrhea. Also sometimes my body doesn't digest my food so it comes out looking the same as it went in. That makes me happy because it means less calories absorbed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 16:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I miss dancing. I was never that good at it, but it was fun. I always wanted to be a ballerina </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 02:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make sure you are drinking enough water and getting enough electrolytes. If you are dehydrated that can lead to passing out because of low blood pressure. Ever since I started drinking electrolyte drinks I almost never pass out anymore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 02:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal (99)

Lunch: Egg whites (60), celery (6), red bell pepper (11) and 1 cup spinach (8)

Dinner: Shirataki noodles with vegetable bouillon and soya sauce (26)

Snacks: 1 cup vanilla greek yogurt (187), sugar free lemon jello (20), diet coke (0) and mio sport (0)

Total: 417 calories

My mom came home today from her trip! I'm so happy, I think this will help me to stop binging and purging because she is at home during the evenings and that's my usual binge time. I haven't had too many urges to binge today, and when I did I snapped an elastic band around my wrist. 

I'm still stressing out about my birthday, I have a big meal planned and I don't know how to plan my day around it. Part of me wants to fast before, the other part of me wants to spend the day binging and purging because the day will be ruined anyways. The struggle is real </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 20:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know how to find it either. I usually buy it from a friend, but her dealer is out of town for a while </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 19:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a daily weed smoker, but I've run out of weed recently. I hate sobriety, the only thing that stops me from drinking every night before bed is the calories. I don't even like drinking, I just need something to numb the pain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 18:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's Cassie from skins UK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 17:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy birthday! It's my birthday this week too!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saw this on postsecret. I think it applies to many of us </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 16:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 16:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to steal that calendar idea!! Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've become a giant whale </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 08:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to apologize because this is going to be a nonsensical rant. It's 1 am, I can't sleep because I've run out of weed and I don't have a dealer right now. This is my first night sober in months. I hate it.

My binging and purging is out of control. I've gained so much weight from it. I'm too embarrassed to update my flair. Everyone says that it's great that I'm gaining weight, even if it's from b/ping. I just feel so god damn fat and disgusting, I look like a whale. I have red patches around my mouth from all of the purging. I've started cutting again because I can't handle this anymore. My suicidal thoughts are much stronger. If I can't stop my binging and purging, I don't think I'll be able to live with myself much longer.

 I really need to get my control back. I need to starve myself again. I miss feeling empty, pure, and light. 

I've made a new meal plan for the week. I have more protein in my plan than before, but I don't have enough fat and I have too many carbs. But I don't know how to modify it to get better macros. I need to rework it for next week. I keep messing around on mpf trying to get a good macro ratio that is low calorie, but it never works.

My mom is coming home from her trip tomorrow. I'm really hoping that will help me stop binging and purging. 

There's just too many hours in the day and I don't know how to fill them other than b/p'ing all day. I'll probably have to give my mom my wallet so I don't buy binge food while she's at work. I wish I could lock my fridge and cupboards to stop me from eating, but I can't. 

I just need my control. I was so good before Christmas. Then the holidays came, I binged, the holidays left and I never stopped binging. 

I'm sorry for rambling. I feel like I post way too much, especially about my binging.

I just don't know what to do anymore... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 05:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Binged 3 times today, but I only purged once. I made a new meal plan that has a lot of protein, but it has too many carbs and not enough fats. Idk where to get more healthy fats though. My mom is coming home tomorrow so that will hopefully help reduce my binging. I need to stop binging. I have 2 weeks to lose as much weight as possible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 01:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone dies, that's what makes life so precious. If we never died we would never do anything with our lives. Once I accepted death as a part of life my quality of life increased </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 18:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Morning is best because that's your true weight without food and water that you've consumed during the day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 04:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ate half a jar of peanut butter. I wanted just 1 tbsp, but I finished the whole jar, then I just kept binging. It definitely sucks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 04:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a major binge today too. I wish I had some advice to give you. But just know you aren't alone and 1 fuck up won't ruin everything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 02:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought I was over my binging, but no I binged again today.

the day started off well, but then I ate an ungodly amount of peanut butter, probably 2000 calories worth. Then I had cheese and a bowl of cereal. Then my dad invited me for dinner so I just kept the binge going. I ate a giant plate of nachos. I fucking hate myself. I'm trying not to purge, but my stomach hurts so much. I just want to starve myself. Why can't I stop binging?!?! I hate it

I feel like my ed isn't even real because I eat so god damn much. I'm  such a fucking fatass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 04:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cocoa (147)

Lunch: Egg whites with partially skim mozzarella and sriracha (120), celery (12) and red bell pepper (11)

Dinner: Peanut sesame shirataki noodles (144)

Snacks: Sugar free lemon jello (20), diet coke (0) and mio sport (0)

Total: 454 calories

I'm feeling really confident that I won't binge until my birthday. I'm excited for my favourite meal for my birthday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chest pain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 21:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chest pain has always been a constant in my life. I've had chest pains for years, even when I was healthy. I've seen a cardiologist and had a bunch of tests, but they never found anything wrong with me.

Lately my chest pains are getting worse, but I'm scared to tell anyone because they'll make me go to the hospital and they'll find nothing wrong with me.

Right now, I'm having some pretty bad chest pains, they are different than my usual pains. I don't know what to do. I'm kind of hoping today is the day I have a heart attack.

Edit: thanks for the concern. My chest pain went away, so no heart attack today </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 02:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cocoa (147)

Lunch: Egg whites with partially skim mozzarella and sriracha (120), celery (12) and red bell pepper (11)

Dinner: Peanut sesame shirataki noodles (144)

Snacks: Sugar free lemon jello (20), mandarin (35), diet coke (0) and mio sport (0)

Total: 489 calories

I'm feeling pretty confident that I will be able to break out of my b/p cycle this time. My birthday is in 6 days and if I don't binge until then I will allow myself my favourite chicken fingers and a slice cake. But I can't fuck this up. 

I also shaved my head today which is a really nice change, it feels like a new me. My mom isn't too happy about it though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 02:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so sorry to hear about your mom. Hopefully it is treatable and she gets better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 01:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A true fast is just water, but most people bend the rules and have bouillon or other low cal liquids </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 23:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel this so much! Sleep is the only escape I have. I wish I could sleep all the time.  I used to sleep 18 hours a day, now I only sleep 9.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 18:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine is from Silver chair's song called ana's song. The lyrics are "ana wrecks your life like an anorexia life". It's a play on words with anorexia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 18:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so depressed lately, as per usual. I cut for the first time in months yesterday. I'm pretty disappointed with myself, it didn't even help. I just need to get my binging under control and things will be much better. I'm feeling pretty confident that I will be able to stop my binging this time. I have no binge foods right now. Plus I have no doctors appointments for a few weeks, they usually trigger binges for me. 

Edit: it's my birthday next week and it's really stressing me out. I have no idea what I'm going to do. The whole food situation and getting older is getting to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you read anything about pseudoephedrine during your research? I can only find pseudo, and I don't know if it works the same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 01:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spent the day binging and purging again. I fucking hate this, I need to stop, but I don't know how. It's causing me to gain weight and I'm freaking out. I don't know how long I can keep going like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 01:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's how I feel these days </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 23:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 23:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, it's just frustrating </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 21:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use oral-b's expensive electric toothbrush, the replacement heads aren't too expensive at Costco </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 20:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not just you, they are notorious for making asses look flat. But I like it because I feel like my ass looks too big </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 20:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love high waisted skinny jeans, but they tend to make your ass look flat. 

When I go out I love to wear crop tops, slutty dresses or short skirts.

For casual I like to wear plaid shirts, cardigans and big sweaters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 19:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is, and I've been waiting since December. Some people wait almost 2 years in my area for treatment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 16:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the state of our mental health care is pretty bad. Thank you for the kind words </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 16:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, pretty much. I'm supposed to get the call early afternoon any day in the next 6 weeks. And when I get the call I have to be at the hospital at 6. It really sucks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 16:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is exhausting, thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
