<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1637</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 15:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On #2, I think think the diversity felt natural instead of forced mostly because it wasn't limited to just a categories. There's not just diversity of race, but culture, sexuality, age, height/weight, disability status, mental health, even species and "life" (Reaper and Widow are basically undead).

The cast is so wacky and outlandish that it doesn't come off as "pc" to most of us. The diversity seems like a by-product of the team trying to create the most crazy, larger-than-life characters possible. And to those who are part of an underrepresented minority, it's comforting to see a character who shares that status. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 03:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Labels are for other people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FINALLY. I love Sombrero but not being able to sit during skirmishes is painful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Balance-wise, *maybe* she's ok. I mostly agree with Krazyguy75's assessment. But what she really needs are some quality of life buffs. 

Translocator is hopelessly bugged, and nothing is more frustrating than dying *after* you teleport away. 

Her weapon spread is frustratingly high, such that I can uncloak 1m behind a half-health Junkrat and not be able to kill him.

And hacking heroes just isn't enough utility to be worthwhile, except against a Rein. Not being able to hack Zarya while she's bubbled is annoying as hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does Tracer's blink "yo-yo" for anyone else? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not talking about lag (at least I don't think I am). I mean when you blink, you see the animation for the blink, and then the game reverts to *before* you blinked. 

For example, I'm like 10m away from a cluster of enemies, and I want to ult them. So I press "right click" then "q". I see my character blink (I move forward, lose 1 blink charge), then it yo-yo's back to before I blinked (I move back to my original position, gain 1 blink charge), then my character throws her pulse bomb.

I'm not sure if I'm describing it clearly, but it's a frustrating and confusing bug that doesn't seem to fit the "Tracer's blink has a weird interaction with lag" explanation. Also, my internet connection is consistently pretty good (ping = ~35ms).

I don't want to be that guy that blames all his failings on lag, but this bug is pretty noticeably affecting my performance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the ECE lounge in Whittemore open 24/7? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm studying in here right now, and I don't think there's anyone else in Whittemore. Am I not supposed to be here at 10 in the evening?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 08:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's kind of a valley between "gay people don't exist" and "I don't care if people think I'm gay" where guys REALLY don't want anyone to think they're gay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not *your* browsing data though; it's the provider's data about you. Nobody's coming into your house, getting on your computer and downloading your Chrome history; they already have this information, and they acquired it through no breach of privacy or rights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't be denied insurance, you can just be charged more.

In any event, the costs incurred by a crime (such as rape) should be paid by the offender, not the victim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  How have you been running programs up to this point? In an IDE or something?

Yes, I use Visual Studio. The only way I know how to "execute" a program is to run it in VS.

 you are in your second year and you don't know how to write code? 

The *code* I can do. It's the... everything else that I have trouble with.

If I wrote that little "hello world" program in a txt file, yeah, I would have no idea what to do next. I'm embarrassed to ask my friends, and the professors just make me use Visual Studio. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm finishing my Sophomore year in Computer Engineering and I feel so lost </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not the concepts that bother me. Sometimes the material is difficult, yeah, but I enjoy the challenge. No, I feel lost because of how much *basic computer knowledge* I just don't have. And nobody's bothering to teach me.

I know how to write programs, but nobody ever taught me to *program*. How do I turn a txt file into an executable? How do I run a program from the command line? How do I make the main function take input, such that I can run the program "on" a file? I ask these questions and I just get looks of "are you kidding me?" 

I'm not an idiot. Nobody was born with this knowledge. But I'm drowning because it seems like everyone is assuming that I have it, and I don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 08:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah it's a gritty Les Miserables reboot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 08:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something similar actually happened in real life! Spain was a fascist dictatorship under Franco, and Franco decided that his successor would be Prince Juan Carlos. To all the world, Juan Carlos seemed like the perfectly groomed absolute monarch: utterly devoted to Franco, and 100% expected to continue his legacy of ultraconservatism.

Franco died, and Juan Carlos ascended to the throne. Within a year, Spain was a constitutional monarchy and power was concentrated in the parliament, not the throne. Turns out, ever since being chosen as Franco's successor, he had been secretly meeting with opposition leaders and planning the Spanish transition to democracy. Only when he was in full control of his country did he start dis-empowering the monarchist elements in the government. In a glorious triumph for democracy, he revealed that he had been *liberal all along.*

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude wtf now that's in my browser history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try amphetamines! I spend hours maniacally doing schoolwork/making memes and sometimes go days without eating!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe they'll pull a Death Note: introduce a new deuteragonist, as brilliant as Lelouch, then make Lelouch so unsympathetic that we root for the new guy.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anime physics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're living in one of those weird alternate universes. Donald Trump is President, Cubs won the World Series, the most popular Broadway musical is a biographical hip-hop operetta about a treasury secretary, and Code Geass is getting a third season.

Nothing makes sense anymore, we're just along for the ride. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 07:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Kennedy Requiem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 06:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, and that's my current plan, but I don't really like it much. I'd much rather just have gone straight from high school to law school </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 06:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm very familiar with the field! Both my parents are lawyers, and the law is really the only thing I've ever been passionate about. Even still, I picked Computer Engineering because if I *do* end up changing my mind, I'll have a solid back-up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man I loved the Pendragon series! Good books. And yeah I agree Black Water was *the* best book in the series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. No movement abilities in a Junktrap.

It's infuriating, and unrealistic, but probably good for balance reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Light] I want to be a lawyer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep seeing motivational stuff that tells me, "follow your dreams! You won't be happy if you major in something you don't like! What's most important is that your career is something you enjoy!"

I'm a Computer Engineering major. And a lot of the time, yeah, I don't like it. But I'm not allowed to just go to law school. I need an undergrad degree first. 

So people ask me, "if you don't like it, why are you doing it?" And believe me, I would love to have some life-changing epiphany about how money doesn't matter and I just need to be happy!!!1!! but *I'm not allowed to do what I'm passionate about.*

I just want to be a lawyer. Why can't I skip college and just go to law school... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats! That's awesome, and very inspiring for me (a CPE Junior with a 2.8). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For calc? Absolutely take the honors class. Sometimes honors means they will be more willing to help you, because they have more faith in your ability.

Plus, if it's the same class, you might be taking the same exams. You'll just be better prepared! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sombra's Translocator hitbox is probably the single biggest reason I don't like playing her. The fact that my teleporter doesn't work *as an escape route* is infuriating. I know that if Sombra was OP she'd be really obnoxious, but fixing the translocator wouldn't do that; she'd be a bit harder to pin down, but then her agility would still be balanced. 

Tracer is and *will always be* a better mayfly character than Sombra. It's not going to unbalance her character if you change the translocator to make it *usable*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> White, and none in particular. I tend to be attracted to white girls, but my biggest crush was on an Asian girl and my first gf was black. Every ethnicity has women who I am attracted to, and women I'm not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbh I'm mostly in it for Thrawn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 09:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is so incredibly frustrating to me. I feel like I can't actually develop a political philosophy, because I'm obligated to defend the party that will defend life. 

Maybe I'm a small-government republican. Maybe I'm a moderate democrat. Hell, maybe I'm a communist. I don't know, because I can't even consider voting for someone who wants *the murder of innocent children* to be legal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 12:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every good deck I played against had white. I went 4-0 with WU embalm. Then again, 7 players at the event pulled Oketra (myself included). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUMO had a big pacing problem. The Totem Pokemon and sometimes the Kahuna fights were tough, but all the other trainers were laughably underleveled. I was either so strong it was boring, or so weak I was frustrated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I heard SMD's story was meh. LOVED Time/Sky's story, how do you think SMD compares? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes that's what I meant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually yes. We held the 2nd point at Anubis round 1, then I realized we were in comp. I got in team chat, apologized profusely, and switched to Pharah. We took both points on attack.

EDIT: Anubis not Oasis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once spent an entire round in group chat, alone, thinking that the group leader had put us in quick play.

I played Sombra for an entire comp round by accident.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm having the same experience. I drafted hunter 3 times so far, took almost every 1-drop and 2-drop, but it just never worked out. I never get offered enough low-cost cards to play anything resembling an aggro deck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The biggest problem I have with the DC system is that penalties are levied on the player's SR for leaving. That might seem like a good idea, but in reality it causes the SR system to be less accurate. High-skill players who are toxic are penalized in rankings for leaving, which means that their next match is played with worse players, reinforcing their belief that *they* aren't the problem, *this team* is the problem.

You get Gold-tier players in Bronze because they're toxic, and they keep being toxic because they genuinely are the best players on their teams. That makes those lower tiers more of an "ELO Hell". 

The ban/suspension system is great, and I've never had any complaints about it. But if players need to be punished for leaving, it shouldn't directly affect their SR any more than a game loss. Not because they don't deserve punishment, but because it makes the competitive environment worse for the rest of us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Nakedness in itself has a purpose

Nakedness is the state of nature; it is how God made man. Before Eve, when man was solitary, he was naked.

It's right to say that man has abused and misused nakedness, but that doesn't make it *inherently* sinful. The abuse of nakedness is a sin, not nakedness itself.

 Nakedness in itself outside of the bedroom is a sin according to the Bible. 

I'm curious about this. Do you have a source?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with the meat of what you're saying, and I do think that OP is trying to justify sinful behaviors because he doesn't want to admit it's sin. 

That said, I don't think we should resort to accusations of heresy. After all, any Christian of one denomination implicitly believes that all other denominations are heretical. In a Pan-Christian subreddit, it isn't conducive to learning and discussion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  nakedness begets lust and therefore nakedness is to be avoided because it is a stumblingblock to the sinful mind.

This is pretty much the same point OP is making though. Nakedness is not *inherently* sinful, but since it almost always causes lust (a sin) it generally ought to be avoided.

I don't think it's fair to say that a man being naked with other men in a locker room is sinful, unless that man has *lustful* urges toward other men, and seeks out that situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 07:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a papist thing. We're not used to that hip new protestant velcro yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There is no middle ground. 

I'm not sure I follow. Are you saying that there are *no* amoral acts? Does this mean that tying my shoe is "good" because it isn't a sin? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 00:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, then it would be called "Bytecoin." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 23:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adams is absolutely a Gryffindor. He was obnoxious, loud, annoying, and despised by almost all of his colleagues, but he had *courage*. When the whole world said "chill out dude," Adams had NO chill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to improve with Tracer, are there any good youtubers that give helpful tips on her? I'm at low gold/high silver. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pharah main here, what's the best way to practice dittos? I'd like to get better at hitting enemy Pharahs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> im so honored </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I mentally add "bitch" to all Zenyatta's voice lines </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was surprisingly tight. I actually think this is better news for the GOP than the Democrats. This shows us that races can be safe on paper but *made* close by enthusiastic activism.

25 senate seats up for election are held by Democrats. Those races could go Republican in places like West Virginia, Indiana, Montana, North Dakota. 

The other 8 seats, currently held by Republicans, are very safe. Texas, Arizona, Nevada, Utah, Mississippi, Tennessee, Wyoming, and Nebraska. I'm not even sure the Dems are putting up a real fight in those states.

But there are some Democrat-held seats that could be *made* close if the party concentrates our efforts. Virginia, Ohio, Pennsylvania, Florida; we can put up a fight there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3v3 seems pretty healthy actually. I've seen Mei, Hanzo, Zen, Sym, Bastion, Mercy, and Hog all player effectively.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What she did was cheating, it was immoral, and dishonest. What you did was just a "dick move."

Ultimately it's her fault, but you enabled it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, but if you want to convince a flat earther that the Earth is round, you can't expect to succeed by saying, "obviously the Earth is round, therefore you're wrong." 

You're invoking the fallacy of "begging the question," just assuming that an initial premise is correct and making the rest of your argument.

I, for one, would like to hear the arguments for and against the claim that "children don't have self-ownership." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This claim, for fairly obvious reasons, is uncontroversial.

Evidently not, since the other commenter (an Ancap, towards whom the original post was aimed) seems to disagree with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speaking of, has anyone tried Menagerie Paladin yet? With Gentle Megasaur and Hydrologist, it seems good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 02:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Technically, no, not from a legal standpoint. From a moral standpoint, maybe.

This really isn't a question of legality. The law should reflect the moral truth, either it is or is not a person. 

 It's a gray area for me which is why I don't agree with it and would only consider it if there was some medical risk from carrying the baby to term (hypothetical, I am a guy).

That's TOTALLY understandable. This is one of the most complex, nuanced questions in all of moral philosophy. 

 I think the rights of the already living mother should come first simply because, well, we know she's a person.

I *know* the fetus is a person. If you're unsure about whether the fetus is a person, you ought to either a) familiarize yourself with the arguments and make a decision, or b) recuse yourself from the debate. 

There's no shame in option b! There are plenty of things that we just elect not to care about, because each person has a limited amount of focus to devote to controversial issues. But the gut reaction to the abortion debate is generally the pro-choice view, because it's hard to see a single cell as a person. There is *so much more* ethical complexity to this, and our instincts really just can't be the basis of our views on this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This whole debate hinges on the personhood of the fetus, so do you consider the fetus to be a person or not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  child-to-be

Well if it's just a child-to-be then fine, no problem. Terminate if you don't want a baby, terminate if you got cold feet, hell terminate if you have an abortion fetish. If it's just a "child-to-be" then there is NO moral objection to abortion.

But if you believe it isn't just a "child-to-be," but that it is instead a *person*, then it just doesn't make sense to support abortion's legality.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So just to be clear... you believe abortion is murder, AND that abortion should be legal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  but we shouldn't have people getting abortions and I won't be getting one.

But why? What's your moral objection to abortion? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like Menagerie Paladin will be great in this set. Gentle Megasaur and Hydrologist push the murloc archetype, while also enabling Zoobot and Menagerie Magician. For dragons, we got Primordial Drake. You might even want to include Sated Threshedon as a 1-of.

I've been fiddling with it and having some success. Winrate is 50/50 after 8 games, at rank 15. Anyone else try it out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I consider conception being when life starts.

So then abortion is murder? This isn't the sort of thing where we can just say "oh everyone has their own opinion." It's literally life or death. 

If you *really* consider conception to be the start of life, and you *really* consider abortion to be murder, then how can you support it's legality? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I am pro-life though. 

But *why*? Why do you have a moral objection to abortion, but not a legal one?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  At what point does the child's life matter to people on the right?

Conception. There's a bit of debate here and there, but that's the general consensus.

 I'm actually enraged that someone would tell me that my safety is less concerning than infringing on someone's right to own a firearm.

 I'm a responsible gun owner, my guns are of no risk to anyone else.

I'm not sure what you mean by this, or what comparison you're drawing. Could you elaborate?

 This isn't a left/right debate. It's authoritarian vs libertarian.

The libertarian, even minarchist approach to abortion should still be pro-life. Only an anarchist philosophy would hold that murder should be legal. 

And anyways, that's a better dichotomy to draw. Authoritarianism is one end of the spectrum, anarchism is on the other. I think most people would agree that the sweet spot is somewhere in the middle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went 12-2 with Rogue last night. First 12-win run ever. 

Near the end of the night, I went up against players who were... less than exceptional. Game 14 ended when my opponent (Paladin) conceded on turn 4. I wasn't even playing aggro. I suspect that this poor performance was because a) it was 4:00 in the morning, and b) the expansion JUST came out.

2 Envenom weapons, Assassinate, and Vinespile Slayer makes for plenty of hard removal. Though in future I wouldn't recommend picking more than 1 Envenom Weapon; you're usually hitting some pretty big guys with it, so you take a lot of damage. Getting any use out of the second one is risky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 11:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3-3 Warlock, 7-3 Mage, and I'm currently 5-1 with Rogue.

Rogue's class cards this expansion are *very* good, I'm enjoying Vinespile Slayer.

My mage run had a LOT of 2-drops and 3-drops. That might have just been an unusual run, but I had 19 cards that cost 3 or less. 

Fire Plume Phoenix is an MVP so far. Incredible value and versatility. 

If anyone has played Priest or Shaman, I'd like to hear your thoughts on those classes. Also, has anyone been offered/picked a quest? Are they even available to draft? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rein usually. Sometimes it's because nobody wants to play Mr. Big Blue Rectangle, sometimes it's because my team's Rein keeps charging into the enemy team solo.

I main Tracer. Yesterday in comp I locked her in and someone in chat said to me, "hey you only have 2 hours on Tracer in comp, you should switch to Rein."

Comp sucks sometimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snowball fights during winter!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that people who went to college tend to be liberal says more about college than it does about political philosophy. How many times have you encountered a *conservative* professor? How often are *conservative* political groups sponsored on campus? When's the last time your college invited a conservative to give a presentation?

Higher education, as a whole, is liberal. Professors and institutions tend to be very left-wing. Additionally, they are set up in a structure that frames them as the "educator." Students are inclined to listen to and learn from their teachers. Thus, it is only natural that people tend to be more liberal after college.

Additionally, 

 A lot of conservative views tend to be based off of gut-instinct rather than a logical evaluation of how a policy will affect the average American.

I grew up on conservative talk radio, and let me assure you that this is EXACTLY what they think of liberals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 02:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a shame [[Alhammarret's Archive]] isn't still in Standard, because this would've been great in my old deck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 21:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats! I've been in this for about a year now, played DOZENS of arenas and my best is still 11.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This is what you agree to by choosing to enjoy the benefits of living there.

I was born here. I didn't make any choices.

 But in no way is taxation a moral theft; it is the payment that you must make to benefit from the advantages your country provides.

Payment without consent *is* theft. And just because I can avoid getting robbed by moving elsewhere doesn't mean it isn't theft. I think taxes are a great deal! Pay, what, 20% of my income to be protected by the most powerful military in the world? Sign me up! But if I can't say "no," then I'm getting robbed. 

 You are offered the choice, and the other option is to go elsewhere because even if you say no to the benefits at face value, by residing within the borders of the country you still benefit from that location in that the military prevents incursions into your property by default.


Should we tax Japanese citizens then? I mean, our military protects them big-time. Surely the security provided means we can levy taxes to pay for it?

The problem with your argument is that you approach the government as cooperative, rather than dominating. Taxation is theft because it *isn't* cooperative. The state doesn't tax people so that they can all contribute to their security and everyone will be happy; the state taxes people because the state has guns, and if they want my stuff, they can easily take it. 

Taxation is not about citizens pooling together resources to provide for common defense, it's about paying tribute to the Men With Guns so that they won't shoot you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 08:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Yes you do have the option of saying no - it's called going to another country

As I pointed out before, if the mob comes around for a shakedown, you can move to another neighborhood. That doesn't make it not theft.

 Want all the stuff taxes buys you? Including the security of living in a first world country protected by its military? Then pay the damn tax.

I agree! That's why I said I don't mind being robbed. But just because I don't mind it doesn't mean it isn't theft.

If I refused to pay my taxes, if I say "this is my property and I won't let you take it," I get a fine. If I don't pay the fine, I get a court order. If I don't show up, an officer of the law will knock on my door to take me to court. And if I refuse to go, they will take me by force.

I like the security and prosperity of living in a first-world country. I know that that wouldn't be possible without taxes. If you offered me the opportunity to live tax-free, but unable to use any government services, I'd say "no" in a heartbeat. 

But I was never offered the choice. *That* is what it means to say taxation is theft. Regardless of how noble the causes, or how great the benefits, I *can't* say no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I'm not a big fan of tariffs, free trade and all that jazz. And I do agree that taxes and spending absolutely need drastic cuts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, if the local mobsters tried to shake you down, you could also leave the neighborhood. Just because you can avoid being robbed doesn't mean it's not theft. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not really understanding what you're saying here... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taxation is theft, because you don't have the option to say "no." For the most part I'm perfectly happy to be robbed; they only take some of my money, and they spend it on things that I need, like roads and national defense.

That doesn't change the fact that it's theft. When I say "taxation is theft," it isn't a complaint about taxes existing, it's a reminder to those who want to tax and spend excessively. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to the sidebar, r/law is for "...discussing developments in the law, jurisprudence, and advice for those currently in law school or legal careers."

How does this qualify? It's an ongoing investigation by a private company into one of their former employees. Is it news? Yes. Is it an ethical dilemma? Yes. But it has NOTHING to do with the law. This is just an attempt to hijack our sub and turn it into another political circlejerk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has nothing to do with law. It's just a politics post. Keep that shit in r/esist and r/politics and r/Marchagainsttrump and the other dozen or so subs.

It's SCOTUS decision season, shit like this should not be on the front page of r/law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am my country's loyal servant, but God's first.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Juries are deciders of fact, not legislative bodies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We don't get political for a particular candidate, a particular party, or a particular point of view.

You are actively supporting the point of view that the government should involve itself in funding the arts and humanities.

You may think that this is an apolitical stance, but where do you think the NEA money goes? What sort of artistic statements do you think they're paying for?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Symmetra has such a high skill ceiling that I'm hesitant to pick her up, but damn if she can't do some incredible things when played well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 04:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought I was in /r/Hearthstone for a second and was EXTREMELY confused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why did McMguireWoods LLP contribute over $30,000 to both candidates in the 2012 Virginia Senate race? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 21:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the question is very specific, but I'm fine with a broad answer about why this sort of thing happens. McMguireWoods donated $38,000 to Tim Kaine (D) and $77,000 to George Allen (R).

Why would a company donate to both candidates? Does the fact that they're a law firm matter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I play this deck!

I call Ixidor "Seto Kaiba" and call it the "you've activated my trap card" deck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  this is one example I've seen: Say carrying a fetus to term would (or at least might) kill the mother. 

This is a commonly cited example, and while I agree with your logic here, the scenario just doesn't happen. By the time a fetus is big enough to cause complications, it can be delivered by c-section. The only exception is ectopic pregnancy, for which, yes, abortion is the only option.

And although the argument itself is sound, it obfuscates the issue. How big is a "serious" risk to the mother's life? Healthy childbirth has risks, do those count? And what about the mother's health? If it won't kill her, but will cause her serious harm, should she have to carry the child to term? How serious is that harm? Does harm to mental health count?

Whenever a provision about "health" or "risk" is written into the law, pro-choice groups always push for the most broad definition of the terms. If a law was passed that said "abortion is illegal, except in cases where carrying the child to term would result in serious risk to the mother's health" then very little would be different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This avoids the whole crux of the abortion argument: is abortion the murder of an innocent?

If the answer is "yes," then one must not only be opposed to abortion but also to its *legality*. After all, if there's one thing we can all agree that the government should do, it's prevent murder.

If the answer is "no," then one must not only be pro-choice but also *pro-abortion*. Because on what grounds could we object to the practice? If the fetus is not a person, then abortion is just another relatively safe medical practice. 

Those who claim to be "morally opposed" to abortion but support its legality don't have a coherent argument. If it's not murder, what's the moral problem? If it is, how can it be legal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 06:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neat! I could see this printed as-is (with an Elemental tag though).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 06:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is *very* good. 2 mana for 3 1/1's OR 2 mana for 3 damage distributed as you choose. 

I might price it at 3 mana, but it's a really cool design. Good job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 05:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get your head in the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Will Lucio continue to fight against her or will he see that she truly wants a better world?

When does Lucio fight Symmetra? I don't remember that in her comic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't watch Steven Universe but that was a very nice song. That voice actress has a beautiful voice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 10:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm surprised Apple would donate to a Republican. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The "pro-life" movement are the same people supporting the military, war on drugs, and the death penalty.

The pro-life movement opposes abortion on the grounds that **killing a fetus is murder**. You don't have to be a pacifist, or anti-death penalty, to believe that murder should be illegal.

 Pro-life until you are born isn't being pro-life, is simply believing that pregnancy should be the punishment for sex, and people shouldn't have sex unless it is for babies with their husbands. 

See, there you go again, attributing malice without cause. Pregnancy isn't punishment, and the pro-life movement doesn't believe it is. 

 The number of people who think that fun promiscuous sex is awesome and think abortion are murder is damn close to zero.

These are two separate things. Plenty of religious people don't approve of premarital sex, but very few of them want to make it illegal. Just cause someone doesn't like your lifestyle doesn't mean they want to forbid it.

 They should be called "pro ruining people in punishment for enjoying sex outside of marriage".


See, statements like this are what make the abortion debate so contentious. It isn't enough to say "you are wrong," oh no, you have to call them *evil*. Evil people! Who want to punish you for having fun! The big, scary, tyrannical bad guys who hate you and everything you hold dear. 

Nobody hates you. Nobody wants to punish you. You're not a victim, even if someone \*gasp* *disagrees* with you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The reason conservatives despise Planned Parenthood is because they perform abortions. Why is this so hard to understand? Why is it always "conservatives hate equality!" and "conservatives hate women!!!" and "conservatives hate the poor!!!1!"?

The pro life movement has been VERY CLEAR about their reasons, their goals, and their motivations. Personhood begins at conception. Therefore, abortion is the killing of an innocent person. Therefore, abortion should not be considered lawful.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest, I don't have enough expertise in healthcare/business. I did find [this](http://dailysignal.com/2017/01/23/a-look-at-four-of-the-gops-obamacare-replacement-plans/) article that outlines a few of them, but in hindsight I really shouldn't be trying to speak with any credibility on this issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 00:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are several workable plans to replace Obamacare. That's the problem: there's no consensus on *which* plan should be implemented. Paul Ryan's Better Way? Burr/Hatch/Upton's CARE? Price's EPFA? The AHCRA?

Republicans could agree that Obamacare should be repealed and replaced; they couldn't agree on what to replace it with. There definitely should have been a stronger push for a consensus alternative before the new Congress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lIterally slept 13  hours last night. The night before I slept 12. When is this going to end? I'm 20 years old and I can't remember the last time I woke up because I was well rested. It's always because I'm hungry, or cold, or I summoned the motivation to go to class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 02:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not even what your quote says. "Serious risk to health" =/= "Serious risk to life". And the point would be moot anyways; except ectopic pregnancy, there are no situations where abortion is necessary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 18:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would transcribe *If on a Winter's Night a Traveler* and see what happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm by no means an expert (still in school) but have you considered something like IT? Jobs that are computer-related, but don't involve software development. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Extra Credits guys made an awesome series about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! The 3DS is a great system, and there's a ton of games for it that I'm sure you'll love. Check out the subreddit /r/3DS for reviews of every big 3DS game. Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 13:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got a 5-star Roy, so I decided to play Binding Blade. Downloaded the Rom onto my phone and... I don't like Binding Blade.

Merlinus seems unnecessary. All the characters so far are pretty bland. All in all, it's not great so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But what if Riverrun is 300m away?? What if the baby weighs 90 kg??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 01:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> literally homosexual </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 06:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the one hand, this is kind of completely useless fluff.

On the other... it's a pretty nice looking font. Very readable.

Well done, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 21:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link in the abstract is returning a 404... You have the full article somewhere? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 19:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're in the middle of puberty, dude. It's not a reasonable expectation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Scout is trustworthy, not honest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 08:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure this is a good idea. Girls are separate from Boy Scouts because we don't expect young boys to act like mature adults around young girls. Why would we expect them to be mature about something as sensitive (and controversial) as transgenderism? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 04:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Birdman* is the most masturbatory film I've ever had the displeasure of watching. It's so blatantly about glorifying the struggles of actors, directors and writers, that to anyone who isn't one it's dull and meaningless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 04:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Mel Gibson for Directing, seems like Holywood has finally forgiven him


Wait what did he do? Why were they upset at him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 02:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/vB9B5.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 01:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Get my groove on.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kAHHFc-gIeI) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 19:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree! Cade and Trump have a lot of parallels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 19:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see what you're saying. My goal was just to outline that, despite the similarities between some Trump quotes and some Richard quotes, that I think they are two VERY different characters.

That said, I recognize that your article was just some funny coincidences and not meant to be taken literally. No disrespect intended, I just get REALLY heated about my problematic fav. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 14:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok I'm a HUGE Richard III fan and I have a lot of problems with this comparison.

First of all, Trump isn't disabled. Richard's scoliosis is an integral part of his character, as the source of his insecurity and frustration.

Second, Trump has only *said* controversial *words*. He's made promises, threats, and commitments that are impossible to follow through with. He's disparaged every interest group under the sun. 

But he hasn't *done* anything. Richard III was widely hated not for his words, but for his actions. He's killed a king, a prince, a lord, a father figure... and that's just before his play begins. We see in Act I Scene III that Richard actually has something of a silver tongue, always diplomatic, always at least pretending to play nice. Trump is the polar opposite of Richard in this regard. His words spark controversy, but the actions of his past are unremarkable. 

Third, much as I hate to say it, Trump was elected legitimately. He won the election fair and square, without any reasonable allegations of cheating. Richard III seized power illegitimately. Not only did he kill his brother (arguably both his brothers), he also undermined the monarchy by being essentially *elected* king. Act III Scene VII has Richard acting humble and pious, rejecting the crown, and telegraphing to the lords of Parliament that he is a) reluctant to become king, and b) easy to manipulate. He *actively cultivates* the image of a weak leader so that ambitious lower lords will be tempted to use him.

Which brings me to point 4: Trump is a *far* prouder man than Richard III. King Richard is fully willing to look weak to further his goals. Good examples of this are Act I Scene II, Act II Scene I, and of course Act III Scene VII. Trump simply doesn't do this; his popularity depends upon his image as a strong, manly-man deal-maker. When challenged, Trump does not use rhetorical maneuvers to change the subject or reframe the question, he doubles down.


When comparing Donald Trump and Richard III, there are few similarities. Frankly the only one I can think of is the tactic of publicly disagreeing with a person/group to befriend their political enemies (Act I Scene III). Even then, they go about it very different ways; Richard plays the victim, portraying his rivals as bullies, whereas Trump directly challenges and insults his opponents.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 14:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> d-deus vult? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 01:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The actual "relationship" part. I'm a pretty handsome guy (I think) and I've known plenty of girls who are into me, but I'm very shy about taking the initiative. The one girlfriend I had got annoyed that I didn't text/call her at all and I just... don't do that. 

For example, just a few days ago this girl I've known for half a year came to a party at my house, and we hit it off. Spent a half hour cuddling and chatting on the porch. But I haven't texted her since. I don't really have anything to say.

tl;dr: Girls like me, I like girls, but I don't really know where to go from there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 04:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an instant-speed, 0-cost way to sacrifice Clue tokens. I don't know if that makes it good, but I know that *I'm* going to play it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Proliferate your Panharmonicons! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 22:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever I face an overwhelming task, I always ask, "how would Ghengis Khan do this?"

And I reply, "one steppe at a time." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 01:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair. And since Totem decks probably lack 1-drops, this could be good.  But I'm hesitant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 21:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Compare Tuskarr Totemic. 3 mana 3/2 plus a totem.

This is essentially a 3 mana 1/2 plus a totem. The minion costs 1, the hero power costs 2. So the only advantage this has over Totemic is extra Totem synergy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 17:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Krod choose surprise! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 22:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree in general with the two points in the article, but I don't really think Standard is all that bad right now. There's a handful of tier-one decks, and a sizeable number of competitive tier-twos. It isn't dominated by any one deck, or any one card; this isn't a CoCo meta.

I'd put Standard right now at about a 6. It's not terribly exciting, but the metagame is slowly developing and there's enough variety to keep my playing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 14:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Lunala is named Leo, for maximum Fire Emblem references. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
