<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3259</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Ladies, are there any ethnicities you will not date? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 00:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favourite meal of the day and what do you usually have for it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 14:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 12:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah! The watermelon one is my fave </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA for when you want an iced (sugary) drink </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 02:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's almost summertime and that means slurpees galore...

Well it turns out that slurpees and other Icey drinks are pretty horrible for you. So I have a recipe for those of you who still want your iced drinks, but want a low calorie and low sugar option. 

Simply grab  frozen fruit of your choice. Throw it in the blender with two squirts of no calorie drink mix (I like lemonade), some stevia, and however much water you want. Blend it and serve. 

It's low calorie, low sugar, and will satiate your slurpee craving for under 100 calories for two cups.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What makes you immediately swipe left ok tinder? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 05:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would you ever hook up with a women who you find unattractive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 19:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do we develop brown spots on our skin after we tan/burn? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 04:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will I gain weight from some cookies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 04:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 11:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel you on this. Started out great but eventually the paranoia and anxiety was too much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 05:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chex and sex </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former pot-smokers of Reddit, what age did you stop smoking and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 05:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favourite thing to cook/bake? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 11:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's cooler the older you do it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 21:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the craziest thing you've had to do to get away from a guy who wouldn't take "no" for an answer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 19:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 02:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Complain about how women dress like sluts but if they're modestly dressed, they trash them. 

Judge any and every woman based on her looks meanwhile the guy himself is a slob. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Women in a relationship with someone of a different skin colour/ethnicity, how did your families react? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 02:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Working or volunteering in the Dominican Republic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 00:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm interested in either working or volunteering for a long duration in the dr. I was wondering what reputable sites and sources I can go to. Also, I'm a 20 y/o female with only a high school education so would that be a problem? Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 05:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that does seem to make sense! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just weighed myself... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 22:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just weighed myself after finding the scale my mom hid from me. 

It said 130lbs. Last summer I was 119. I don't know how to feel about this number. I knew I'd gain weight in my recovery but I feel so fat. 

I'm hoping that it says 130 because I ate a shit ton of fruit and drank a lot of water today. I'll weigh myself tomorrow morning so here's hoping that it's somewhere in the 120s.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Skin concerns] Are there any supplements/pills that help reduce oil on the face? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 18:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have super oily skin and if I don't spray a setting spray on my face after putting on makeup, it's like an oil spill. 

When I was on accutane it was great because my face didn't get oily at all. Now, a year later it's super oily again. 

Are there any supplements or pills I can take that will help reduce oil production? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just need to vent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 02:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No flair bc I'm on mobile

Basically I've always had a horrible relationship with food. I had an eating disorder when I was twelve and recovered through that. 

I grew up listening to my mom reminisce about when she was a size zero and listen to her say mean things about those who were overweight. I became so scared she would look at me and judge me, that I starved myself.  

My highest weight was 143 lbs when I was 17. I ate horribly, didn't exercise and was stressed out. I started running every day and I'm about five months I was at 130. 

When I began work I decided that I would only eat breakfast and a snack. In two months I was down to 119. I can't express to you how it felt to see that number. 

But it wasn't good enough (it never is, is it?) I wanted to be skinnier. I wanted to be 100 lbs. And when my mom dragged me to the doctors a month later and I stepped on the scale to see 126 lbs, I cried for the rest of the night.  

I realized I had a serious problem. But now it has gotten worse. I hate my body. I hate it with a passion. My arms are rolls of fat, my legs are horribly huge. My face is disgustingly fat and I hate having my photo taken. 

I can't eat a normal meal without throwing it up. I eat my breakfast and some fruit.  Anything other than that I have to throw it up. I'm so afraid of gaining weight. I just want to be skinny. 

It felt so good to hear "you're so skinny" even though I didn't believe it at the time. I miss it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 19:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was younger and driving with my well-off friend, her mom accidentally pulled into a Hyundai dealership lot. She immediately said "ew a Hyundai dealership" and my friend began mock-gagging just because they drove a Jaguar. I was like...what is wrong with Hyundai cars??  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any recommendations for a lightweight, full coverage foundation or Bb cream? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 05:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have really oily skin, uneven texture due to acne scars and hyperpigmentation. 

I currently wear Clarins 12 hr foundation and I find it has ok coverage but feels heavy and sinks into my pores. 

I've tried revlon colorstay, ReMarcable foundation, KVD lock-it, Tarte BB cream. None of them have lived up to their hype. 

I just need a full coverage foundation that isn't heavy and won't melt off! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 05:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clarin's 12hr foundation smells like cucumbers:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 04:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> www.foodnetwork.com/recipes/emeril-lagasse/homemade-bagels-recipe.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 12:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I ordered about $100 of stuff from their website and received it in less than a week.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 12:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know right?! How lazy of me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 12:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically bought two small portions of salmon. Took a mixture of salt and brown sugar and coated them really well and wrapped them in plastic wrap then placed them on an upside down bowl inside of a container. I then put a plate on them and smooshed them down and plastic wrapped that. 

Left it in the fridge for about 5 days and flipped the fished every day. All of the juices collected at the bottom so I knew it was working. When you want to serve it just rinse the fish until all the salt mix comes off. Then slice it and enjoy!

It's pretty damn good and all you need is some patience as it is a low matenience recipe!

Thanks btw! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 12:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 12:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah they are pretty ugly aren't they? Recipe called for twelve I said fuck it and made 7 huge ass motherfucking rings of orgasmic bread. Also used a recipe which took less than two hours because I was pressed for time. They were some of the best bagels I've made so far-as I was told since I don't eat bagels.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tonight's spread: homemade bagels with cream cheese and home-cured salmon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 23:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 07:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So pretty:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Homemade gnocchi with meatballs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I get really awkward and function like a little girl with a crush:/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow good luck!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have fun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A night out once in a while is  needed!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enjoy your trips! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Renting sucks, I agree! Fingers crossed you get in:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhhh have fun!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lucky! All you Americans have so many cool things to do and see...I'm jealous! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sucks that it wasn't for you, good luck on your future endeavours!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel you! Good luck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've made it this far so it's not too far off! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw congrats on the pregnancy!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice:) Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goooood luck!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet! Enjoy London and have fun at the concert! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's so cute  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! Congrats on the new house!

Happy Easter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay for independence:) Good on you for taking the time to choose what you want to do. Many people make the mistake of picking something they're unsure of and wasting time and money on it. Good luck with everything! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exciting! Wishing you a safe life ahead! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Treasure them while they're still young! Next thing you'll know, they'll be teenagers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! I've always wanted to go to Miami  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's so cool! Awesome:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woooo! Have fun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, awesome, awesome! Good vibes all around Happy birthday to ya! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry about your arm! Hope there's at least an awesome story to come out of it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay! Congrats </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holiday eating is a free pass to AYCE for a day  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yessss AYCE sushi is the best! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw that's so great! Awesome to finally find the one person who you've been looking for right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god that sounds too good to be true!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
