<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3132</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone able to hook a sister up in the west burbs? So dry atm here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My boyfriend loves his noodles. My favourite photo from our little trip to Hong Kong during the Chinese New Year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much! I love how everyone's style is so different </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, this is amazing! Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't usually smile for the camera... but I did this time :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 04:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heyyyyyyyy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 18:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone know why he has chosen to do it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doner Kebab (w/ all toppings) in Amsterdam Centraal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 21:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 19:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a popular 'traditional' Dutch dish from the Netherlands called Stampot! It's great to use leftover veg + potato </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 18:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were fine - not bitter at all. In cooking, I tend to use strawberries that are on the verge of being "too soft" as some people would say (so, maybe a bit mushy on the bottom, yet not moldy). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 14:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used this recipe [enjoy](http://thesecretlifeofbee.co.za/lemon-pound-cake-with-strawberries/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lemon   Strawberry Pound Cake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 14:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Graduation presentation jokes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 06:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there. A few of my friends and I are school captains and are required to do a presentation at our graduation in a couple of weeks. It was up to us as to what we presented. We have decided to do a funny little "Guide to surviving Grade 12/IB".

We have come up with a couple of jokes such as these:
* "Due tomorrow, do tomorrow!"
* "You can always re-sit an exam, but you can't re-sit a party!"


Any jokes of similar nature, or memes, would be a great help! We are aiming to be a bit controversial given that we are on our way out of this damn school ;) Thanks all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 10:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am the only student at my school that could face up to the known wrath of HL History. It was not easy, though, it could have been much harder. I am glad I picked it over HL bio (as I initially was faced with the same dilemma as you). 

You have to enjoy whatever subject you choose - espcecially your HLs. It makes them so much easier to learn and study will not be hated (as much). I love History and find writing essays to be something I have a good grasp of. 

For History, definitely know how to manage your time and thoughts in an exam. For paper 2 and 3, you will have to be strict with your time No more than 5 mins planning per essay, 45 min writing per essay. Studying is also a priority. There is a fuck ton of content in History, no matter what options your teacher picks. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 08:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In section 1 you want to basically outline your investigation. 
So, 1) WHAT the aim of the investigation is, 2) HOW you intend to approach the analysis of sources in your investigation, 3) a short statement of WHY you are investigating the chosen topic, 4) and a short statement or two on the nature of your sources and your method. 


This section should be sub-200 words. It is meant to be simple and straightforward. Say it as it is, don't exhibit verbosity.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 08:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out any history magazines that you can access. The HistoryToday online archives have some pretty interesting articles on an array of History topics.

 I struggled for weeks to find a topic that would stick but I kept reading articles pertaining (slightly) to route 2 of History HL. I finally got a topic and it was a breeze. Make sure you pick something that interests you, or you're in for a long ride. 

Good luck, I am sure you'll find something :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 20:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no, that is horrible... Best wishes for your other papers and questions :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 08:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which question? I did the anxiety/arousal one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 20:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went in to this paper the most scared I had ever been during these exams. Funnily enough, I came out feeling the best I have so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 14:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would agree normally, though in this case, we were not asked to round it up. The question asked "**During** what year", which, of course, would be 2019 as it occurred in the 4th quarter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 14:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got 19. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 14:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TZ2 - Much better than paper 1. Hopefully I redeemed myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 16:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In terms of Stalin, we are not able to use him when answering a question regarding the 'establishment of a single-party state', right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 12:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Magnification and its various types (near point, infinity).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 17:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am also doing Imaging. I am a little stuck... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 16:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not even in Dubai...
Looks like your friend opted for the buffet and was extremely picky.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 15:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder which Italian restaurant? I'd love to go check it out and verify the complete bullshit of this photo. I have lived in Dubai for 10 years and this would only appear in a buffet at most. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 22:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Iron Whey protein tastes great and mixes to a nice, thick shake. I like the banana flavour. I am nearly out. Anyone tried the other flavours and can recommend one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 09:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not alone, comrade! I am the only History student in my school so I will spend 3 papers worth of time in the examination room with a exam monitor. At least there is no one to annoying you with tapping feet, clicking pens and flicking papers. Have fun and good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 09:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been focusing on themes and symbolism (given that they both run strong in my other text- The Whale Rider). Would you be able to share some notes on the stage directions? That is what I have looked at the least. It would be a great help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 19:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did A Doll's House too!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 19:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yo, a fellow ADH student!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 15:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As in question 4 part d) i ? I got the value of x to be 3 as 148+85 = 233 (whereas before the reaction, it was 236) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 07:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THANK GOODNESS YOU PICKED UP ON THAT TOO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
