<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1913</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 17:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's getting downvoted because this argument is NOT contributing to the AMA. He admitted that he has never read this author's work, but is still telling him to give up on his dreams because "if you're not published, your work is shit so you should stop." If authors took that advice, we'd never have Harry Potter! There are tons of authors that have had to pitch their work over and over and over, despite constant rejections, before they finally find something that clicks and works. 

Yes, some of his points are valid. But this is not the time and place for them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 08:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fuck is a bird-dog? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 08:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh! On the way down on the elevator for the Eiffel Tower, this Chinese woman was literally pressing against me, even though there was plenty of room. It was also over 100*F, so I almost decked her. Boyfriend just got to stand there all with his own personal space.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-27 14:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure that wasn't /r/lacqueristasgw? Yes, that's an actual subreddit. 

As far as I know, /r/lacquerista is just a small version of this sub with like 1k subscribers and nobody ever really posting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-27 14:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love these nail sticker things. I have two packs...one goes over a nail color/design, one is polish and little metal dots. Super cute, OP! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-27 14:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super pretty! Nice job. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-01 01:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it worth the risk? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 07:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She just said "penis size". I took that to mean, "A penis that feels good in my body is the right size." Too big for me, too small for me...either one isn't as great as someone who fits you perfectly. I'd prefer to err on the smaller size because it doesn't fucking hurt, and certain positions and other things (like toys, or whatever) can make it amazing. 

Sex is really important in a relationship, and to deny that is to be seriously deluded. 

You're coming across as really self-conscious. Maybe you should man-(or woman-)up and apologize for being a raging dickhead to her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
