<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3094</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-08 16:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paraoptometric tech here.   
  
A contact prescription and a glasses prescription are different, and most states legally require a separate exam for them. They are also considered a medical device because they are inserted in your eye, so there are added fees that go along with them. Most states require a contact lense training session, and then a follow up appointment to check the fit, comfort, and health. This is legally required before they will release the RX, and then you can take the RX to 1-800 Contacts. Typically offices will charge one up front fee that covers all of this, including any troubleshooting and changing of lense brands until you are comfortable, and it will vary depending on whether or not you have an astigmatism high enough to require corrective contacts. Where I work it's $95 up front for spherical or $115 for toric (for astigmatism) for the fitting, not including contacts. The toric lenses are also more expensive. Typically they want that fitting fee paid half at the training session and half at the follow up, but they have allowed the fees to be paid out monthly. Contacts must be paid for at the time of receipt. I hope this gives you some info!   
  
Edit: also know that these fitting fees are a one time fee, every year after that it's just a $45 evaluation fee and then you get your RX. Also ask about rebates! We're doing a $40 rebate right now for certain brands.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-26 19:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kim is famous because she had a very private tape released to the public without her permission, and instead of letting it ruin her, she took advantage of the situation and used it to give her entire family jobs and careers. But for some reason she's the bad guy, instead of someone who made the very best outcome out of a horrifying situation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-26 19:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She had a private tape released without her permission. And instead of letting it totally ruin her life and instead of living in shame, she took advantage of the situation and created a wonderful life for her entire, very large family. I can think of worse things for people to do, honestly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 06:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went back to look. It doesn't appear that the scars were there during the initial walk up to the building, or in a few scenes during the fire fight. Just acquired somewhere in the scuttle, it seems.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 18:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really pleased with the little bit of progress I've seen so far. I'm finding it easier to get myself to the gym than it has been in the past. I do have some serious gym frustration right now though, because my gym only has ONE free barbell, in a squat rack, to be used for ANY barbell exercises. That means if I need to bench, squat, deadlift, row, etc., I'm waiting for this ONE squat rack. Usually I haven't had too much trouble or had to wait too long until last week. A guy started showing up about five minutes before I do, and he is... he's just the worst. He is the slowest moving creature that has ever drawn breath, I'm sure of it. He does front squats. ONE REP, and rests for THREE MINUTES. He does this for an HOUR. I really try to be patient and not judge other's routines, but COME ON. I tried to get there earlier, and there he was. I came later, and there he was. I've been trying to switch gyms but my gym owner is completely ducking me.  
  
/rant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 21:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also own the 2 in 1 compression with the loose shorts over the top. I have a pretty big butt and thighs compared to my waist. I found that while I liked them and I thought they fit me in a very flattering way, the loose shorts on top bunched up any time I tried to run. The compression shorts make it less noticeable, but that also means that the top shorts bunch up a TON before I'd even really notice. I still wear them just casually, but I ditched them for gym use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 15:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do an ab circuit three times a week that DEFINITELY makes me feel the burn. I do these three exercises back to back, and then rest for 1 minute.  
  
Cable Crunches x 15  
Captain's Chair to burnout  
Bicycles to burnout  
  
Repeat circuit 3 or four times and you'll be burning by the end. I like it because it's quick and it doesn't require a lot of extra setup or prep after I've already done my lifts for the day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 14:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My city just got a Chipotle and people won't shut up about it. The main reason I've avoided it is because I'm afraid it's going to be in everything. Guess I'm not going anytime soon...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 14:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! I've seen that and I swear that's my problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
