<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6681</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fasting for a month: Update </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 07:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well.. I failed. 
But not because of lack of willpower, or anything.

I was in my dorm room, when I felt a little hungry. This was about day 5 of my fast. Naturally, I used water to suppress my hunger. Although I used a little bit *too* much water. I felt extremely light headed and dizzy. I collapsed. When I woke up I was completely covered in my own shit and vomit. My headache was surreal and my eyes were bulging. So I went to ER.

Electrolyte imbalance.

So....I'm dropping out of Uni. My parents want me to come home and "work on my health". Not sure if thats going to look like inpatient or outpatient. Fuck this. There is nothing to do in my home town. I won't be able to get back in until Fall 2017. That's almost a whole year now..

I'm 18. No job. Not a student. And moving back in with my parents. 

Kill me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 08:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I could help you man, 

I am currently in a University dorm and things are not going well for me eating disorder wise. I struggle every single day. 

I've declined meals out with people,

I've been throwing up in the bathroom dorms,

I'll probably end up taking some time off to get my shit together and figure what the heck I'm doing with my life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 08:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another male joins this sub! Welcome!(:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 23:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats to the new mods!(:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Extended Fast: Day 1 Complete </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 21:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [previous post] (https://www.reddit.com/r/proED/comments/5ae0en/fasting_for_a_month/) 

I enjoyed my last week of October,

I got drunk four times

I got high twice

And I even tripped once. 

Why not have a little fun before I embark on this long spiral downwards? 

Anyways, I completed the first 24 hours easily. I've done 7   10 day fasts before so I don't think it'll be an issue. 

Not sure how often I'll do these posts either.. I'll try *not* to every day because that would spam the subreddit. 

Sorry for the ramble, I don't have anyone else in my life who would listen to me about this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 21:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ouch... this hits close to home.

I never felt more guilty than when I saw my own mom cry in family therapy when she said - 

**"I spent 18 years raising my child, but now he is starving himself and I don't know what to do"** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 20:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks3. I promise I will be checking in on this subreddit throughout the fast.(:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 19:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow! Amazing talent! 

A few of these remind me of myself... especially the 7th one because of the long hair. 

I could only dream of being that skinny though lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fasting for a month? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 19:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fasted for a week in September,

I then fasted for 10 days in October. 

I spend every waking moment of my life feeling depressed   like my life is spiraling out of control and I HATE it. Years have passed any nothing changes. 

The only way I can suppress this feeling is through fasting now a days. 

I think I'm going to do this. 

If I die, at least I'll be skinny.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 10:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha yup! On multiple occasions actually. 

I posted about one of my stories [here on this subreddit before] (https://www.reddit.com/r/proED/comments/4vnt3f/i_almost_gave_myself_away/) (: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 01:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Day 9 of Fast**

Alright, it seems like after all this time I am going to have to end my fast now at around 9.5-10 days-ish. The reason being it takes a little while to work your way up to solid foods again after fasting that long and I will be expected to eat food on friday :S. Oh, and alcohol at a party~ 

Not counting calories, because I accidentally screwed up already. whoopssssssssssss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE Have Sleep Issues? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 07:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anybody on this sub have sleep issues?

Usually, I don't have any issues with my sleep. However, when you throw my eating disorder into the mix I find that my sleep issues go through the roof. When I am restricting I sleep wayyy too much because I am constantly tired. When I am fasting (especially for long periods of time) I can't sleep AT ALL. Like right now I am about 8.5 days into my fast and It's currently 1am and I am not tired. A couple days ago I went 36 hours without sleep. This is a problem as it's interfering with my university work. 

thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 22:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Day 8 of my Fast!!** 

Currently feel horrible, but lets see how far I can push this. I have plans to party friday night so I will probably break the fast thursday afternoon, which will put me at 10 days.

Also, I am now 115 pounds, and a 5'9" that puts me at a bmi of 17. woo~ 

Breakfast: 0 calories

Lunch: 0 calories

Dinner: 0 calories

Total: 0 calories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
