<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1953</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 13:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea what you should do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 13:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I hope someone else comments on this too. We're in the same boat. /:
His gain really influenced my slipping back into restriction.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 18:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look so beautuful!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 02:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't necessary leave treatment. I just played along to get my life back as a minor (and my freedom). 
It worked.

There were things I liked about treatment aswell. 

I miss the community too. I miss killer beautiful thinspo. I miss loose clothes. I miss the constant inner battle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 15:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last time I purged I swished my mouth with pepto bismuth ("nausea, heartburn, indigestion, upset stomach, diarrhea").  I don't know if it works or not. I would've chewed up antacids but I didn't have any, that's usually my go to thing. (The mentos-type of antacids that are chewy)

I brush about an hour or two later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 03:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first time I did it I felt nothing too. All I felt was very warm and a tad speedy...but the second time I was sick to my stomach and really uppity. It's worked for me ever since, minus the insane nausea. \\\_()_/ 
Maybe try it again?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 15:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 18:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha that's funny you mention that, I bought some a couple of months back and it was pretty good. I have to have it really cold though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Health Food Store find, worth trying! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 17:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I bought a Virgil's Zero Cream Soda in a glass bottle when I was wandering around a health food store and it is HEAVEN. 

Glass bottle diet soda ftw. I'm fasting right now and really thirsty and water hasn't been doing much. /: So I got Emergen-C Electro Mix too, I heard someone rave about it a while ago on here. 

There's a lot of stuff in that tiny store. I finally have found a place that sells a good variety of Yogi tea. :D 

Any good buys anyone would like to share? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 04:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I can understand that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Rant on mobile] Why am I the only one trying? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 00:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay I just need to vent and I think you guys can relate:

I try hard to look good. It isn't above all the most important thing in my life but I make an effort to look decent. (ED things aside) 

How do other people /not/ care? I work with the public and I can't wrap my head around how some of these people let themselves leave the house. Holy fuck they're crusty. Sorry but it's true. 

How do people just shovel shit into their face with no regard to nutrition or calories at all? 

I think the main reason I'm back into my ED so hard is because seeing someone I know gain and gain and gain and let themselves go really messes with my head. 
That, and I work with the public. I see so many crusty middle aged/old people and obese people ride motorized scooters. Yuck. 

Yeah I'm vain whatever. At least I'm taking care of me and demonstrating personal discipline. I don't need to binge until I hurt a few times a day, as much as I'd sometimes like to, unlike someone I know. 

Basically: I'm frustrated that someone in my life doesn't keep up with themself when I try so hard. 

Anyone ever feel like this? ._. 
Help me I feel terrible about this. 

And no this isn't something I can approach them about. Talking it out is not a conversation I want to have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
