<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5711</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who else just hates Mary? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 07:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't stand her I don't exactly know why they chose to bring her back just for her to abandon the boys and cause more trouble then she is worth 

I want to know how many people agree with me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cheapest groceries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will be moving to Hamilton in June 
My wife and I are broke university students and are looking for the best place to get cheap but quality groceries 
If anyone has any suggestions that would be great  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 00:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lived in brantford for 10 years from 7-18 and left a few years ago 

The hams in brantford is insanity
I will fully agree with you on this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meghan Trainor - "All About That Bass" PARODY </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 02:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My apartment stinks but I cant seem to fit it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 10:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Move my wedding date </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 00:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's 30 hours till my wedding 
My mother just yelled at me for 45 minutes to move the date because it's inconvenient timing for her 

I just needed to get that off my chest I really have no one to talk to  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (F/d) incest videos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-27 02:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Free incest porn sites </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-27 02:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mother won't take my brother to a doctor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 20:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a 6 year old brother and he has not seen a doctor since he was 2. Because she believes that Doctors with force her to give him vaccinations and make her give him medication (he deffenitly has autisum and ADHD but has not been diagnosed) he also won't eat anything they have to constantly nag him to eat he weighs about 43-46 pounds at 4 feet tall 

I'm worried about him I don't know if I'm wrong or right could maybe a parent help me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-14 05:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I don't consider myself any sexual oriantation I just date who ever I want sorry for the mix up   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-09 23:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still madly I love with my first boyfriend and its been 5 years and I'm now married 

I don't think I will ever not be in love with him when I say his name or I hear it I get butterflies  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 21:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my wife loves to wear shoes in the house so we bought her house shoes
we both win. 

i don't want dog shit, dirt or god knows what all over my floors because i put my feet on the couch then maybe i will lay down i don't want it transferred to my face.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 20:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no reals only feels </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 02:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you can try 

/r/confession if you want there good or 

/r/offmychest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 00:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes i fully agree with you 
 
no matter what you say your getting in trouble 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 00:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have a disability and i don't want hand outs i do collect disability in canada but only because they cover wheelchair repairs that can cost a minimum of $1000 for 2 freaking tires  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 00:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats actually awesome advice for a teenage boy. hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 00:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ever visited /r/raisedbynarcissists ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the worst advice your parent's ever gave you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 00:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 00:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people who are suicidal do NOT talk about the fact that they are suicidal.

people who are truly suicidal won't talk about it they will just do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 22:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mine is also so obsessed with autism and if theres a vaccine committal on tv she will flip out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 01:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i do agree with you a lot of this stuff happened 200+ years ago and people are still using it as an excuse to be an asshole </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 01:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> crab mentality  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 01:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in my opinion she's not even that thin 

its just that we are all basically wearing fat goggles its becoming normal to see overweight people that when someone is really actually a healthy weight we see them as to thin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-03 23:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my mother also will diagnose complete strangers with having vaccine poisoning and stuff ( she is so against vaccines that when i got mine with out telling her she got so angry i thought her heart would stop) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-03 01:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i am terrible at grammar we didn't spend any time on it in school deal with it.

in my school we mainly just spend time on doing cursive ( that no one used) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-03 01:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i fully agree my sister has 2 kids in a row they are 11 months apart 

if she says to me one more time "im tired" i will kill her  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-03 01:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> technically it is good job </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is your Nmon/Nparents Fear Mongers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-03 01:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my mother is very against a lot of things mainly the Government teachers and doctors. Now i don't agree with 99.9% of what she's says but she loves to talk about it 

for example i have a disability and have to spend a lot of time around doctors ( not since i had lived with them because she believes the will purposely kill you)

but when i move i will get a doctor again and plan on getting a full physical but my mother is getting upset about it 

they will kill you, they don't know what they are doing, its all for money( we live in canada) among other things 

even though i don't believe her, do to my very very bad anxiety about death  i am terrified to get my chest pain looked at because they will kill me because they don't know what they are doing or about diseases .

btw my mother has NO degree she just has been looking at Harvard research papers for a few years and she only has her GED 

but she is raising money to put her own medical lab in the house because she doesn't trust doctors

i don't know what to do she knows i have very bad anxiety and she still tells me this all the time 

Sorry for the rant i just needed to talk about it 

btw sorry if its hard to understand I'm just really upset   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 07:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you just made my week  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 06:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> one that bugs me is 

" if you don't find fat people attractive your a terrible person"

"i don't find fat men attractive and thats ok"
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 06:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i am not from a incest relationship but i have a deadly genetic disease anyone can get horrible diseases so i don't think its any diffrent  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 05:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i don't see anything wrong with it your not forcing any one and they rant forcing you

have at it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 05:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> please tell me how it goes with yours because I'm have the same situation I'm moving and my brother is 6. he is my world and I'm really the only one who gives him attention or listens to him 

I'm very worried that he will think i don't love him and i don't want to see him 

sorry I'm no help but i just thought yyou would like someone to relate to  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 05:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there adults let them be </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 05:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i lost my virginity at 13 with my 18 year old bf on the couch with my gramma across the room on the computer  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TITP Contradictions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 04:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what is your fave one mine is 

" weight loss is impossible"

"i don't lose weight unless i work out non stop and NEVER eat" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't think incest is bad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 04:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as long as incest is between 2 ( or more) consenting adults of age then i don't think its that bad and people should relax about it 

and no i am not in an incest relationship and don't plan to be  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-01 22:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its really all internal but i get to go once in a while  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-01 04:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> some comments are offensive but she's a mean person so i am kinda used to it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-01 04:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when my wife and i got together we never talked about religion and then we got married in a ceremony at the court house ( i wanted it this way) 

but i am a christian and my wife HATES christians she calls then whores and evil so for the last 2 years she has NO idea I'm a christan  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-01 04:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats what i think that people that really do want help and beg for attention are over shadowed by people mainly attention whores and teen age girls who say everyday they will kill themselves 

so if you really want help people just think your attention seeking  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-01 04:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> online i don't give a fucking shit about my punctuation or my grammar 

this is not school and i don't have to be perfect online  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-01 04:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GOOD 

my mother hates when people renovate the house or buys expensive clothing because there are people in the world that need the money 

yes she's right but in the end its your money and you can do what you want with it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-01 04:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i think that if your going to commit suicide your going to do it 

and I'm not going to stop you because i think its unethical 

ps if you keep saying oh I'm going to kill myself and you never do fuck off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-01 04:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why do you think this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-01 04:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i think people get offend WAY to easy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-01 04:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i think its like that I'm preparing myself for when the doctor tells me at some point in my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-01 04:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no actually the only person in my family that ever had cancer was my dad when he was 9 he had cancer in his shoulder thats it.

every woman in my family lived past there mid 90's  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-28 22:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i couldn't find it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have come to terms with having cancer but i don't have cancer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-28 22:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> im so convinced that i have cancer and I'm going to die of it. To the point where i have come to terms with the fact that i will die of cancer.

I have not and have never been diagnoses with cancer 

i feel like a horrible person for it 

but i don't know what to do about it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TITP Mod pictures </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-28 21:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-26 00:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i LOVE being married 

but i hate hate hate living with someone i much rather live alone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-26 00:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i really don't either  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
