<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8986</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 00:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, thanks! Really interesting regarding not needing coconut water. I think you're right, it probably would be too much work than I'm willing to do. Maybe one day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 07:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can raise animals without eating them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Freeze it. Look at how Smuckers Uncrustables are stored. If youre bringing them to work, it'll defrost by lunch time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My fiance, who has major depression, gets botox in that same region to help with migraines. Curious if its linked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds like those people are already depressed, but use work as a distraction. In that case, the problem isn't the lack of work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 08:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since you're going for Japanese flavors, have you considered trying rice bran? It's a type of tsukemono called nukazuke. I've personally never done it, but love when my grandma does!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 21:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah... hormonal disregulation shouldn't make someone need to have sex with people other than their partner, unless that partner is asexual, or has a much lower sexual appetite (which OP didn't mention either). Let's say a woman has higher testosterone levels leading to a higher sex drive... being poly can help it for some people in relationships with unequal sex drives but it certainly is not a "medical necessity". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 19:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I got done when I had braces was that I got the other lateral incisor pulled, and then with braces, my canines were moved towards my front teeth. Then, my canines were sanded to look like incisors. They're a little 'rounder' than regular lateral incisors but they are symmetrical. The roundness could be fixed with veneers but nah.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 05:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dang, your sourdough starter got a SCOBY? That's pretty wild </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 04:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm reading that now. It just seemed like a coincidence since I just started making kombucha and this hasn't happened before. I have a current batch of kombucha going with unfiltered apple juice, I wonder if that could do anything? I also had an idea of filling the rest of my ACV bottle with leftover apple juice... would I get more ACV? I dont know anything about making vinegar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Funny thing happened: my store-bought apple cider vinegar grew a pellicle. Could that have happened from the yeast in the air from my kombucha batch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 03:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Add silken tofu instead of soy milk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 00:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The carbonation should happen in the 2nd ferment. It shouldnt be very fizzy at all after the 1st ferment. 

For me, in the winter I've been doing 2 weeks for the 1st ferment and a week for the 2nd ferment. In a tropical climate, you could probably do half the time. You need to move it to air-tight containers to fizz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 09:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get this too. I have to keep reminding myself that treatments cost more. Also, I tell myself that I deserve yummy foods. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't have to add it to your resume. I haven't started my masters yet, but I doubt I'll add the fact that I was a grocery store cashier in my undergrad years when I try to find work. Especially if you have related volunteer work and fieldwork that is more relevant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 05:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love using jackfruit like this. I'll make it simple on myself and just add in BBQ sauce. So good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone made nata de coco? How different is the process to making kombucha? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 06:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of curiosity, I tasted a pellicle and it reminded me a lot like Nata de Coco. It's a popular dessert / dessert topping in asian cultures. When I wanted to try to make it in the past, the recipes I saw had a bunch of ingredients I didn't have so I kind of gave up on it (I didn't try that hard). After familiarizing myself with making kombucha, it seems like the process is super similar.

I was thinking of experimenting with throwing in a pellicle in some coconut water + water + some kombucha starter liquid. I'm curious if would work... or is that just how it's originally made anyway? Or should I just rinse and sweeten a pellicle? I just started making kombucha so I don't have tons to experiment with (yet). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 05:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taste it once or twice a day. It'll get more sour as time passes. You can also look into making sauerkraut, which doesnt have a starter at all, it's just cabbage and salt.

I've used a probiotic capsule trying to make cashew yogurt and it was pretty good (blended cashews + water, and added the capsule). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 00:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try [blending beans](http://bitesizevegan.com/vegan-health/the-ultimate-vegan-muscle-gainer-shake-bodybuilder-derek-tresize/) instead! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 04:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could use it in place of peanut butter to make a 'peanut sauce'. Easy way would be almond butter, sriracha, lime, soy sauce. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 21:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently did this but with leftover rice and mushroom gravy. It's what I had but apparently they do this in Creole/Cajun cuisine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 19:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use groupon when I already know what I'm looking to buy, and check groupon to see if theres any deals. For instance, I'm going out to eat with my parents and look for deals nearby, and see a restaurant I've been wanting to eat at. So I'll purchase it at the restaurant on my phone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 19:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Super awesome that your dinner was pretty much vegan! I've never heard of fried apple peels... That sounds yummy.

I'm making mashed potatoes and mushroom gravy (from Hot for Food), a mushroom walnut loaf, and banana cream pie (from Minimalist Baker). It's potluck style so my fiance's mom is bringing cranberry sauce and a waldorf salad, and my mom is making a tofu salad and some sort of kabocha pumpkin dish (she's Japanese). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 19:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I figured trolls want downvotes, so I gave them an upvote. Definitely not clever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 18:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvoted because you didn't even try.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our thanksgiving meal will be fully vegan! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 17:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just bragging and also very excited. Ive been vegan for a year and a half,  I veganized my fiance and just recently veganized his mom. The other guests are my parents who aren't vegan, but since it's a vegan majority, the entire dinner is vegan. Small but ethical dinner  and Christmas might look very similar (but with more guests)! 

I ended up saying, 'if you want turkey, you can bring your own portions' but laziness is making them not. So, yay for also having it non-forced (sort of).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 00:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless I'm understanding it wrong, seitan/wheat protein is less bioavailable than soy products so I would suggest buying some TVP (Bob's Red Mill TVP runs like $2.50 per bag). I usually just dump some TVP with my tomato sauce when I make pasta, quite easy to prepare.

[Source](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Biological_value#Typical_values) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 01:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By having power, I mean more along the lines of society puts power into one role over the other. So, it could be teacher-student, police-prisoner, stronger-weaker, older-younger, richer-poorer, etc etc. Of course it isn't 100%, and the opposite abuse can exist, it still generally is seen along that line and people will often blame the victim for acting out (ie people blaming the BLM movement when police brutality was the original violence). 

Another way to see it, and I just read this today so I'm no expert, was something I saw on /r/raisedbynarcissists where there's the idea of 'catching fleas', based on the idea of how if you lie with wolves, you'll catch fleas. But, the victim will still not be narcissists, but only pick up on behavior that they were around.

My thinking is that the Jasper/Lapis dynamic is following that idea, especially since Jasper is physically stronger for the most part, and that Jasper seems to have abusive behavior towards everyone around her. Lapis has picked up on abusive behavior by what has happened to her (trapping, because she was also trapped by force). But, these are fictional characters, and maybe there is no difference between 'fleas' and a personality disorder. Maybe Jasper was abused in her past, and she 'caught fleas'. 

edit: wow because i am getting downvotes, here's some reading for you all. [here](http://www.loveisrespect.org/content/myth-of-mutual-abuse/) [here](https://www.domesticshelters.org/domestic-violence-articles-information/is-mutual-abuse-real#.WB6_nforLb0) [here](http://unobject.tumblr.com/post/25077747813/five-false-types-of-mutual-abuse-trigger) [and here](http://stoprelationshipabuse.org/educated/faq/#faq12) and just googling anything about mutually abusive relationships  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 23:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> from what i understand, relationships usually can't be mutually abusive because one person will have more power than the other. the one with less power would be acting out because it's okay to be angry if someone is abusive towards you. for instance, if you have an abusive parent and the child acts out in some way, like pushing their parent or calling them names, the child is not abusive. they're only reacting to their abusive parent. it becomes difficult to see what's going on when it's two 'adults', such as the lapis/jasper dynamic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 22:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lentil curry: lentils, water, can of diced tomatoes, whatever veggies you have on hand, a can of coconut milk, salt, sriracha, curry powder. i prefer red lentils. eat over rice.

lentil chili: can of diced tomatoes, can of kidney beans/black beans, water, lentils, whatever veggies you have on hand. salt/hot sauce.

youtube is your friend. type something like 'vegan lentil recipe' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 06:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally. When I went vegan, I saw people who thrived on high carb diets and was relieved to eat this way because carbs are tasty and I feel great. From what I understand, our bodies preferred source of energy is glucose, so it takes more energy to convert fats/proteins into usable energy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 19:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pita bread with hummus and carrots/cucumber sticks, or cherry tomatoes. I cut the pita into 1/4 and dip. Easy and yum.

Also, I make a homemade trail mix, such as sunflower seeds, pumpkin seeds, dried cranberries, dates, whatever.

Date/coconut/peanut rolls are good too. Just blend in a food processor and make into balls. Theres variations online for different amounts.

I keep editing this because this is like my favorite topic lol. Another one I like is getting a tortilla, spread peanut butter on, and put a banana in the middle. Roll it up, cut into halves or fourths. Kind of like a pbj.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 02:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much did you take for it to end up doing as much damage? I'm pretty good at limiting my intake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 02:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like I've lost myself so even basic advice feels really nice right now. It's hard to piece things together. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 01:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, that helps a lot.

Is it just a waiting game? I do have access to klonopin, xanax, propanalol, and high-CBD pot. I don't know if I should take anything or if it'll make it worse. I took a tiny bit of klonopin last night but just fell asleep so I dont remember if I felt any better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> just started feeling it a few days ago. what am i supposed to do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 00:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not my first time feeling dpdr, but before, it seemed to be like a panic attack (severe dpdr but only lasted a few hours), or perhaps related to depression, where it was pretty mild. A couple of days ago, I smoked a half bowl of pot, nothing unlike me (although I've been smoking more the past month because I got my MMJ card). During the high, I felt the change, but I was still euphoric so it was okay. But now the DPDR hasn't left. It's a constant feeling with no break. No fucking break. It's like I'm sliding down a slide with no end in sight. I just want it to stop.

I'm also going through SSRI withdrawal (very slowly) because I just want to know what my body is like. I have trauma with a previous psychiatrist overprescribing me medications and I just don't know what's necessary anymore. 

I've also heard that hormones can cause dpdr and my cycle is out of wack. I can't tell if I'm ovulating (I'm tracking using the FAM out of curiosity). I don't know if this is relevant. 

I'm just so sick and tired of seeing doctors. Should I just wait this out? How long? I'm uncomfortable because I just want this to stop. At least with a panic attack, I'm okay within a few hours or the next day. If I saw anyone, who would it be? Gyno to check for hormones? Psychiatrist (I'd have to find a new one anyway at this point, which is such a headache). 

Am I supposed to stop going to work or school? It feels like I'm sick. I can't remember what happened the second before. I forget the begining of my sentence by the time I finish the sentence. It's hard. Socializing feels so awkward. Am I supposed to stop going to school and work once I fuck up badly?

I just feel so confused and I don't know what to do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 20:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ended up going with this brand, but the 'betsey lou'. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 18:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was propogating some larger leaves and I got mold that looked like this on the soil under the leaves. I just moved my leaves and everything is fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 17:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those look great. Do you know if theyre comparable to Toms? Just looking at the price and they look similar, but more expensive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 17:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I emailed softstarshoes... They have kids vegan shoes, which is funny because it's usually the adults that are vegan. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 03:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Possibly, my biggest concern with slippers is that theyre full of cushioning so I thought this would be a good sub. I'll head over there, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Minimalist house shoes/slippers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 01:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this is barefoot running and this question is neither about being barefoot or athletics. BUT I work as a receptionist at a Japanese wellness center and wear slippers while working. I would be barefoot if I could, as I do at home. I've been searching and can't find a minimalist slipper that would work for my needs. Other things: I'm vegan, so things like soft-soled moccasins are difficult to find without using leather. Would prefer them to be on the cheaper side. Should look somewhat professional. 

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> xPS 13 or wait for zenbook 3? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 04:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * **Total budget and country of purchase:** 
$700-1000, but the lower end is definitely preferred. USA.

* **Do you prefer a 2 in 1 form factor, good battery life or best specifications to your requirements for the money? Pick or include any that apply.** 
 Best specs.

* **How important is weight to you?**
Pretty important.

* **Which OS do you require? Windows, Linux, Mac.**
 Windows or mac (moving from a macbook pro early 2011).

* **Do you have a preferred screen size? If indifferent, put N/A.** 
 Smaller is preferred, for lightness and cost.

* **Are you doing any CAD/video editing/photo editing/gaming? List which programs/games you desire to run. If you have no requirements, put N/A.** 
 Light gaming, light photoshop, have done CAD and video editing but most likely wont in the future. 

* **If you're gaming (leave blank if you put N/A above...), do you have certain games you want to play? At what settings and FPS do you want?** 
 Probably the sims 4 haha. Not sensitive to FPS, willing to game low res. Honestly I'm used to not gaming because of my current macbook so I'm not sure.

* **Any specific requirements such as good keyboard, reliable business grade build quality, touch-screen, finger-print reader, optical drive or good input devices (keyboard/touchpad)?** 
 Not looking into touch screen/2-in-1. Looking for good design and aesthetics. If available in a lighter color or white is preferred. I have a nexus 5x so usb type c charging appeals to me. Zenbook 3's fingerprint reader appeals to me but not necessary. SSD highly preferred.

* **Leave any finishing thoughts here that you may feel are necessary and beneficial to the discussion.**
 I keep getting the thought in my head of, "if I only spend $100 more I can get this...!" but I also am low on funds in life so it would be smart of me to spend less. Aesthetics are important to me, and when I went to the Microsoft store, the XPS 13 stood out to me next to a current Zenbook. But, the Zenbook 3 looks amazing and would probably be around the same price if I got a XPS13 Skylake + harddrive upgrade (~$1000). I'm definitely still considering a certified refurbished XPS13 Broadwell ($650). I don't know the difference in speed, and I'm not sure I need higher power. Every rec I see is to get Skylake, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 21:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if it's internal or external damage. The place we got was a fixer upper. 

Is a shoe necessary? I don't think we have that on the baseboard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 03:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just started doing this, too. I also have a yoga mat to do yoga in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 02:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm repainting my bathroom and noticed some of the baseboard is detached from the wall, as well as some minor water damage. I'm low on budget so I'm repairing instead of replacing the baseboard. Should I just nail the baseboard into the wall with finishing nails, use caulk, both, or something else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 02:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on the traits. It could easy feel like my partner was fetishizing me and only liking me for the idea of a partner as opposed to the whole picture. I'm half asian and if my partner claimed they had "yellow fever" I would run away as fast as I could. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 23:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you looked into Herbivore Clothing? They have a [similar design](http://www.herbivoreclothing.com/good-luck-elephant-racerback-tank-top/) to your description. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 00:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out /r/littlespace if you haven't. That feeling is common enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 22:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as another scar-owner, damn. that's good. definitely looking into Andrea's work now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 00:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it's the same reason I strongly believe in birth control education for humans, so we don't have such a high population density that fucks up the quality of living for so many living beings. 

"Raised humanely" is quite bs too. If someone were to say they would promise to "raise me humanely" as long as I was killed prematurely for them to eat, I'd tell them to go fuck themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 02:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look for Vital Wheat Gluten. You just mix it with water and knead it a little bit. Or, even simpler ingredients if you can't find it, you can actually just knead dough (flour + water) and rinse it under water to rinse the starch away. But that's way more time intensive. They should have vital wheat gluten at health stores like Whole Foods, or look online. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 19:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got back to the gym yesterday even though I haven't gone in maybe 9 months! I have been doing yoga, and as fun as that has been, it's only one class twice a week so I can't expect to make any significant improvements. Went to the gym yesterday with a friend, told him I was nervous right before a deadlift, and had some girls overhear saying "You can do it!" and it made me smile. What sweet girls! I get nervous because I've injured my back (herniated disk, probably due to some hypermobility I have) and I feel like I'll injure it again. But, I didn't injure myself yesterday and feel a nice soreness today! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 01:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think of it as decor instead of just storage. Think of a theme, for instance [this person](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PcfAlyX9hTY) liked the idea of her place looking boutique-ish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 04:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you properly flour the pin, it probably shouldn't stick. I don't usually get dough stuck to regular rolling pins. If it does, I'd just use a brush instead of a sponge and it should come off, and to wash it right away so it doesn't crust. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 09:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wool can be stolen skin. Look up mulesing, happens often. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 08:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okcupid definitely helps. I end up being a little bit more comfortable with the person, and i also know that they think I'm attractive. I also don't have as much anxiety with one on one interactions as I do with large groups of people, or meeting new people. I've been with my fianc for over 6 years now and I feel very comfortable with him, kind of like a surrogate parent with me being the child who has separation anxiety. Which is funny, because I temporarily moved so we're long distance at the moment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 22:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a little more complicated than that. Shelters don't reject any animals that come in, so that's why they have space issues in the first place. Rescues take out the adoptable (cute, young, etc) animals when they have space. Good shelters (with lots of volunteers that allows socialization) will only euthanize because of severe illness or aggression problems. But, they're the ones that will have the less adoptable animals that are perfectly friendly (black cats, pits, chihuahuas, old animals, etc). 

But, if someone is set on a specific breed, rescues make it easier. Way better option than going to a breeder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 08:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another way it may get be thicker is using a high speed blender. I've only made almond milk in a blendtec and it was super creamy. I imagine if I made it in my oster it would be quite watery because of the less surface area of the almonds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 23:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My go-to is pasta (fusilli) with marinara and TVP and frozen mixed veggies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 19:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A box of Vegan Cuts snacks, or a shirt from Compassion Co or Herbivore Clothing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 22:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you looked at CSA boxes near your area? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 09:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about the nuvaring? I took it for a while and it never came out of my body, and you're also allowed to take it out of your body for (I think) 4 hours or so before anything happens. So, you can take it out during sex if you want. You have it in for 3 weeks and out for 1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 09:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was honestly expecting an "elbows too pointy" somewhere in u/yangying's rant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 07:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm imagining it with a chocolate sauce (for "soy sauce") and maybe a cashew-matcha cream "wasabi". Maybe it'll look too similar and confuse expectations too much though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 03:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know you're joking around but you're pointing out an important thing. People can call themselves whatever they want if it's a part of their identity, because they're reclaiming words- like when black people say "nigga", but a white person can't, or a lesbian can call herself a dyke, but a random person on the street calling her a dyke is offensive. Some disabled people also call themselves crips, etc. Someone who is half black and half white can call themselves mulatto if they believe the way they are using it will give power away from the offensive meaning. A white person shouldn't make the decision if they can use the word or not because it isn't a part of their identity, so it doesn't affect them in the same way the half black, half white person would experience the word. 

This is, of course, a controversial topic and everyone has differing opinions. It isn't a black-and-white (heh) issue, so we can't say what will be the 100% right or wrong way of going about it. What works for some people might not work for others. It's just important to respect others, and if someone tells you what you said was disrespectful, listen to them and apologize. If someone from a marginalized identity says it's okay for you to use a certain word, don't be certain that that's the belief of everyone in that group. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 21:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not related to kombucha, but my fianc just had a similar experience of an instant itchiness after drinking some coffee, and it happened multiple times with the same bag of coffee grounds. I think it was a bad batch or something, as we never figured it out, but he's fine with every other coffee.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 23:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's so unfortunate. I want Bernie in office, but Hillary seems to be the most likely candidate and I'll have to vote for her just to avoid a Republican getting in. Non-participation/voter apathy in the youth demographic is basically a vote for Republicans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 23:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Along with Happy Cow, I've also found an app on the iphone that translates what we can't eat in many different languages. It's called "V-Cards". I haven't used it yet but it seems helpful. Of course, you can google "Vegan + (city name)". I also heard a tip that you might want to focus on the experience of travel (socially, educationally, inspirationally, or whatever else) and not focus on traveling for food. You can also consider traveling to places that can be paired with veganism, such as volunteering at animal sanctuaries (like elephant sanctuaries in Thailand, etc)! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 22:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those saying that it might go bad soon-- probably.

Freeze what you can and eat what you can't. Freeze herbs in oil in ice cube trays, freeze other things on a tray before putting in a bag so they're easier to separate. Make stews, and freeze that. Look up what you should be blanching before freezing, too (usually greens, I think). 

Look up recipes that work well with frozen veggies that might get mushy-- for example, I just made an alfredo sauce that's based on blended up cauliflower. I personally probably wouldn't want steamed frozen cauliflower, but if it's blended up, you can't tell. 

With the rest, unless you have a large family, make meals for friends and they might repay you with a meal in the future.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 22:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny enough- I ate more Italian (or, Italian-American?) food after going vegan! I find it very easy to make vegan- pastas, olive oil, marinara sauce, pesto, eggplant-based things, gnocchi, rustic breads, etc etc

I'd also like to mention that it's not a horrible decision to eat vegan all year, and then eat what your family serves on holidays. I personally wouldn't do it, but my fiance does. I think "meatless mondays" are a great thing, and so is being a "flexitarian" (as a stepping stone to veganism). I think a good goal right now is to spread the idea that veganism is the best choice on an ethical level, because society isn't even there yet (even though it seems obvious!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 22:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of when I went to a banquet for my school, and I think I was one of the only vegans. But they had the spaghetti with marinara as the vegan option, and I kept hearing a girl saying "the vegan pasta is pretty good!" It was literally just spaghetti, I found it weird that it kept being called the "vegan pasta".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 09:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not veganism specifically, but people seem to forget about fiber, and how a lot of fiber calories are pooped out without ever digesting the calories (one reason for grinding your flax, too, because the outside is so fibrous, you wouldn't get nutrition- whether is calories or omegas or whatever- unless ground). Vegans in general do have a higher fiber diet because there's less processed foods available. It isn't a blanket statement of course and there are exceptions, but you can eat more calories when eating a high fiber diet. 

Ninja edit- it's why a lot of those vegan youtubers eat thousands of calories and don't gain weight. It's basically a laxative effect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 08:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good thing we're usually more civil than relying on what biology says to dictate our actions. 

I hope you're a troll and not some MRA type. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 04:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't watch them, but I watched some of their recent videos and I loved how they said they stopped eating meat because they aren't savages. I'm excited that they're talking about the ethics of it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 04:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a parent, but I'd love to raise my kid vegan. [This is a video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IR6cj6-i9q8) I saw on a raw vegan who babysits a kid (as well as have her own kid) and how she changed the way the kid she babysat ate. Raw vegan definitely seems more extreme than regular vegan but I thought it had great tips on how to get kids to eat veggies!

edit: Also would like to add that Bite Size Vegan on Youtube has a series for kids on explaining why eating vegan is good, if you want to include him in the ethical side.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 06:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you. Ineffective advocacy does exist. I really like [Unnatural Vegan's video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=epJfzZXCPwc) on it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 19:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you considered that you might be bi? You're still young and finding your sexuality, so it's okay to question it and sexualities do change (sexual fluidity).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 19:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed with mdma, also if you can't find GHB, there's also 1,4B. 

On those that haven't used GHB, you're intoxicated at a similar level as alcohol, but there's no hangover. You  also must dose yourself precisely (you can overdose easily) and you must not drink alcohol or have benzos in your system because it affects the dosing. But if you get it right, it's great.

Edit: also there's the studies of mdma and ptsd helping in a therapeutic setting, so I imagine it might help with other anxieties. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 04:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP's a student. You're usually a dependent at student-age. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 22:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a great thing to add, even though you did say "accidentally", I would also say not to panic if you purposefully ate something non-vegan. I remember I went vegetarian when I was younger (maybe around 12 years old). I had a craving for beef jerky, and ate it and thought I couldn't be vegetarian anymore, so I just went back to a omni diet after that.

I've been vegan now for about 5 months and no longer have crave non-vegan foods, but I think it's important for beginners to not see everything as extremely restrictive, or they might binge and/or go back to a non-vegan diet. "Slipping" is not the end of the world, even if some vegans do portray it that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 22:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I often have a similar smoothie but add some avocado to it and it makes it really creamy! 

I sometimes do frozen berries but I'm less into fruity types of smoothies and more into creamy ones, often with cocoa or something. I always put in a few bananas as the base just to get the calories down, then everything else is flavor or nutrients. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 09:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Re: fruit, I also really like fruits and veggies in slices. It gets boring to be at home and just eat a carrot stick plain, but when you're outside and super hungry, it tastes refreshing. I cut up a few carrots and maybe an apple and put them in a ziploc. Not as "grab and go" as prepackaged, but it's great for some road trips and stuff too. Bell peppers are good too. I try to bring hardy foods, as fruits like bananas smoosh easily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 09:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a friend that has Vegan written on her inner lip. Subtle, and intimate. 

I saw another that is the V with leaf sign on a guys arm.

Depends on your aesthetic. 

Look into vegan tattoo inks, too :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you see veganism as dogmatic (and is that okay?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 09:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The term dogma definitely has a negative connotation in my mind, as I prefer to not live my life without strictness. But, with my own veganism, the stricter I am, the happier I feel because there's a direct link with less suffering. 

I have an ongoing conversation with my vegetarian (mostly vegan) fianc who is against the term vegan because of its connections with dogmatic ways of thinking. It's okay for me because he's doing the best he can, and even if he eats some ice cream once, he doesn't think that he has to go full dairy/egg diet. It's more about moderation instead of complete elimination for him. Honestly, I'm proud of him for making the switch and thinking of the ethics. But, he says even if he ate 100% vegan, he would never call himself a vegan, but of course it's because of stigma. I personally find pride in the label. 

For me, I feel best when I strive for elimination of all animal exploitation. It may be dogmatic, but I don't see a problem with it. The only problem may be sadness /guilt when I accidentally consume something I didn't have control over (like milk baked in the bread). Otherwise, I don't see an issue with striving for perfection in this case.

It's difficult, because in a way my strictness is also pushing away the idea that veganism is accessible, which would be ineffective advocacy.

It gets trickier when speaking about things like the idea of owning animals at all, or horseback riding, or going to zoos, or service dogs, and things like that that I haven't thought about until after my transition. We have many animals as pets (pre-vegan, all rescued). So having conversations on the ethics of this is valuable for me. My fianc on the other hand has completely disregarded my opinion on the subject and pigeon-holed me to a PETA dog-euthanizing sympathizer. I don't have specific opinions on the subject, as I'm just trying to have open conversations. 

Logically, by definition, I am enslaving my cat to be indoors when she clearly wants to go outside, but in practice, she is not suffering, keeping her indoors saves the lives of mice and birds. I often feed her raw meats, for her health but also mine because I have less allergies with her carnivorous diet. Is the death of chickens worth getting rid of my silly sniffles? Probably not, but in practice, I've already saved the lives of many chickens. My allergies does affect the quality of my own life, a life that I can use to spread the vegan message. Can I spread the message with a sniffly nose? Sure. Just some of my thought process.

I'm very emotionally attached to the subject, but I do think some kind of logical philosophical forum would be interesting on these issues. 

A strict vegan may say all animal exploitation is wrong, but is it really black and white? I can understand both sides of the argument, so I find the discussion fascinating.

Total midnight rant.

TLDR; pretty much the title of the post. The rest is my own thoughts on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 08:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, it's one of the most frustrating arguments because it's made by people who could be vegetarian or vegan if it wasn't for the justification of "humane". Soooo close! It's like they can stop thinking about the abuse because they think it's been solved by some bullshit humane certification that means nothing. 

I've been wanting that Humane Meat Doesn't Exist shirt as my first vegan shirt, but I worry about confrontation. 

Fucking humane washing, humane ratings at whole foods bull shit... It literally kills animals! I wish I could be angry and shake their heads, but I know expressing my frustrations in anger can be ineffective activism. Always have to think of the animals first because I feel so emotional about the topics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 08:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People care about what is going on in their social circle more than outside of their social circle, as it makes a more direct impact on their lives. It's not surprising, and it's not necessarily a bad thing. Facebooks algorithm also promotes your post to friends that get more likes quickly, as they program "special events" to appear more readily. So, news about having a child or weddings or whatever usually get tons of attention through algorithmic programming... I don't see anything surprising with your results... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 06:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So excited that the top comments are on vegan diets. Totally agreed, because my most expensive things I buy pre-veganism were animal products, especially with egg prices rising to $5/dozen where I am. The ethical side is what eventually won me over, though.

I do cheap staples with one specialty product per grocery trip and my groceries are usually $30-40 per week to 2 weeks. I eat oatmeal every morning, and my lunches are just dinner leftovers. Mostly beans in different forms (lentils, chili, taco bowls, tofu, TVP), veggies on sale, and a starch like rice, pasta, or potatoes. I eat lots of bananas, too, especially as "nice cream" (blended frozen bananas, I add cocoa) and smoothies in the summer. My splurge today was a $5 bottle of Califa pumpkin spice latte almond milk, but my total was still $32. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 19:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's tons of vegan fitness people around, and I think it's great activism to change the perception (even though I'm one of those skinny yoga girls)! Look up Patrik Baboumian, a strongman and vegan since 2011. If you haven't already heard about it, you can also check out /r/veganfitness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 05:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone know if this is the stuff that makes you fart? You're supposed to rinse off beans to get rid of... stuff (?) that makes you fart, so wouldn't aquafaba just be that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 09:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha. 

She later sent me an email of a vegan paleo diet, but the article stated to cut back on cows milk and drink goat milk instead, and weird things like that. I literally do not care about dieting at all, and try my best to avoid bs articles like that, but good for her for looking into it. But, then she responded by giving me excuses of why she can't (she would be so sad to never eat fish again... never mind what the fish think). It's so frustrating that I didn't respond because it's hard to keep a friendly response to that. I suppose that's how MILs are tough. We have a great relationship outside of that, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 00:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously. I understand people need to make money, but JM seems to use youtube as a way to communicate her art and ideas, and isn't willing to compromise that for the sake of more followers/$. It's irritating when I see people I like such as Unnatural Vegan do videos on other youtubers (like the lacking protein one). I know I'll be happy after watching Jenny's videos, and not have to filter out which ones will irritate me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 22:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a potluck, and I think it's something catered or personal chef-ed, or something. They're very wealthy (like... full time workers in their home wealthy), and my MIL brought up how she just ate around things she didn't want to eat on her plate when she visits them. So, anything I make should not try to overpower what is given to us. It's a weird situation that I'm not used to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 22:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking of trying this dish, Wild Rice Pilaf with Butternut Squash, Cranberries, and Pecans: http://www.onegreenplanet.org/plant-based-recipes/wild-rice-pilaf-with-butternut-squash-cranberries-and-pecans-vegan/

It's festive and filling, yet not trying to compete with a main so others will be more willing to try it. The gravy is a good idea, as if theres some potatoes or something, it would be great for me to add.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 21:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jenny Mustard is probably my favorite, and totally doesn't get enough love! She rarely makes health claims that a lot of vegan youtubers make. Veganism is not about bullshit health claims for me. She's Swedish, an ethical vegan, and makes beautifully aesthetic videos. I love the foods she uses in her recipes as well, generally simple ingredients, especially ingredients that can be found internationally (whole plant foods).

Peaceful Cuisine is nice, but his recipes are definitely not simple and his videos are more for watching than for following. Again, beautiful aesthetics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you always mention you're vegan when invited to a dinner party? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 21:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a situation that I've never gone through, as I've only been vegan for about half a year. I've been invited to a Christmas dinner at some people's home that I've never met. They live in a different state, but I'll be visiting my mother-in-law and it'll be with her friends. I think there will be lots of people, I'm assuming probably 30+ people.

I told my MIL that I would appreciate if she would mention that I was vegan, because it could be as simple as making the vegetable dish with olive oil instead of butter, or putting aside some mashed potatoes without cream, or leaving the cheese off a salad, or something. At the same time, she did make a point on how with her diet (basically paleo), she will make exceptions for her diet during these types of occasions. Frustratingly, I understand her point but veganism has nothing to do with diet for me, but ethics.  She suggested bringing a side, which makes sense. I was thinking maybe a rice type of dish, to fill me up.

We also had a discussion on how my fianc (eats mostly vegan, but generally vegetarian) would eat things he knew had animal products in this situation, where as I wouldn't. I said that maybe if I didn't know something had butter (like sauted veggies), I would eat it, but if I knew it had butter (such as labelling at a buffet), I wouldn't. I'm not sure, as I'm usually not in this situation. 

Should I just stick to eating the side that I would be bringing? Or would that backfire, and show that veganism is extremely restricting? Should I ask my MIL again to let them know I'm vegan? If I was lactose-intolerant, or have celiac, people would seem to be more understanding of dietary restrictions. Now I'm being seen as "picky". What do you do in these situations?

TLDR: Invited to Christmas dinner with strangers, should I just bring a side to eat to avoid confrontation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 03:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people have quirks that can be OCD-like symptoms. Most people can relate to the feeling of, "What if I just jumped in front of that bus?" or something like that. It depends on how much it affects your daily living. If it's affecting your work, school, social relationships, etc, then you should seek help. An example could be, if you're often late to work because you fear harming others by driving into them so you have to take detours. Or, you have been skipping homework and doing poorly in school because you're researching the obsession. The general diagnosis is if these behaviors/thoughts affect you every day for at least 1 hour (usually it's more). 

As others have said, we aren't doctors. Whether you are diagnosable or not, it seems like it it causing you distress and you can seek a therapist to help you out even if you aren't within a diagnosable level of OCD.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 21:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could it be like derealization or depersonalization? Dissociation? I can get like that, it's a type of coping mechanism for anxiety. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 09:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Under eating definitely increases anxiety. I've heard of a theory that it's because our body is in search-for-food-mode. So, it will run for miles to search for more food. But since we aren't running, anxiety increases.

Diet tip - eat tons of high fiber fruits and veggies, and you won't need to cut back on calories. You'll end up pooping out a lot of the calories from the fiber, but you'll still feel satiated since you're eating high volume. Don't forget to drink water, too, because fiber takes a lot of water to digest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
