<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8657</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Realizing in retrospect I may be anorexic/EDNOS. How to deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 11:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL;DR: I was naturally extremely thin/underweight my whole life until recently. Now that Im a healthier size Im starting to obsess over being thin. Looking back I see signs of possible anorexia or EDNOS. Not sure what to think or how to deal. Any advice or comments appreciated. Thank you.

Im almost 30 and most of my life Ive been very thin and petite and not much of an eater. Being skinny was pretty much my defining feature and I was accused of having an eating disorder countless times, including by numerous mental health professionals based on my appearance. Its always been a love hate relationship with my body. I loved having a flat tummy and skinny legs, but I also hated having small boobs and ass. I never tried to be thin. Its just how I was and I felt really fortunate. Being thin is so idealized in our culture, especially where I live. I got a lot of praise and attention from men for being so thin and a lot of jealousy and admiration from women. I always had a perverse pride in being able to go days without eating, like that was some kind of talent.

Obviously, I was barely eating. Even though Id go days without eating and subsisting off protein shakes or tea, there were benign explanations for my eating habits and weight; I have lightning speed metabolism. I'm a picky eater. I hate eating, even when Im hungry. I was too lazy to eat or make food. I was too stressed to eat. I didnt have time. During grad school I went months living off a single protein shake and half a granola bar per day. And lastly, not eating was a symptom of my other serious mental health issues (bipolar disorder/manic depression, PTSD, ADHD, and alcoholism/addiction). But being accused of having an eating disorder used to send me into a fierce rage like nothing else. I absolutely hated anyone who suggested - even with the best of intentions - that I had an eating disorder. I was vicious to anyone who commented on my size or committed the ultimate sin of joking about childrens clothes.

Ive been through a lot of mental health treatment, but only for addiction and BP, never talked much about food. However, I had a therapist tell me I dont have an ED, but I have disordered eating. Is that a thing? It made sense because my bad eating habits correlated a lot to my mood swings. When Im at either extreme I dont eat. Maybe she said that because I was so insistent I didnt have an ED and thought Id fire her, but regardless, she helped me work on my eating habits a bit. Ive known a lot of girls with severe EDs and I never really related to them on that issue. I always thought BP and drugs were my real problem.

Anyways - about three years ago I became extremely depressed in large part due to my tiny size. Almost every day after work/school Id look in the mirror and cry at my emaciated, child-like body. One time I stood in a Nordstrom fitting room and bawling hysterically because even size 00 pants were too big and baggy. I vividly remember the time a guy I liked told me I looked unhealthy and unattractive (out of concern). There were points of despair when I was so overwhelmed because I didn't even know where to begin with getting healthier. So in typical me fashion I did nothing and used it as fodder for self-loathing.
Finally, about 8 months ago I decided to start working out to gain the right kind of weight and feel healthier. Great idea! Working out regularly got me eating better (at least two meals twice a day) and I gained a fair amount of muscle. Basically went from being extremely thin to curvy (Hooray! Tits and ass!).but now Im kind of freaking out and feeling fat and disgusting.

I know that thats not true though and that (as usual) my mind is playing tricks on me with really harmful toxic self talk. Realizing how sick these thoughts are has made me reexamine my past behaviors and relationship with my body. Im starting to think I may have actually been anorexic. In hindsight my passive obsession with being thin seems much more malignant. Why would I get so insanely defensive and enraged at being accused of having an ED or any kind of comments about my size? Why did I continue having "disordered eating" even after getting treatment for BP and addiction if it's a just a symptom of those? Why the fuck was I proud of being able to not eat? Why did I see eating as a weakness or fault? But at the same time - how could I be anorexic if I got depressed over being too thin?

The reason this is an issue is that now that Im a healthy weight the thin obsession is creeping back and I keep telling myself I just need to stop eating entirely like before and that my body is a disgusting lumpy fat blob. Back when I was underweight and depressed Id look at thinspo to cheer myself up. Now I look at it and I miss being that thin. I feel so fat and gross. Objectively I guess thats not true and literally everyone I know tells me I look so much better. But I cant help missing being thin and comparing myself to skinny girls. I hate my tummy and that my thighs touch the whole way down and that I now have cellulite. Im so frustrated by these feelings and I dont fucking understand where theyre coming from. Do I seriously need to have every fucking category of mental illness there is? Is there any size Ill be happy with? (note: No, of course not. I dont deserve that.)


Thank you if youve read this far. Thats commendable. I guess my questions are can anyone relate? Ever gone through something similar? Is it possible I was anorexic or does this sound more a symptom of BP or Im blowing it all out of proportion? Was I in denial? Is it even possible to be so in denial? What do I do from here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My girlfriend might have an ED. How can I help her and also avoid relapsing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 22:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My gf and I are both in college (and both women). In middle school/high school, I had a mild ED but I've been recovered for years now. She has confessed that she worries about her weight, and struggled with body image stuff when she was younger. Recently, she lost weight and makes a lot of excuses to avoid eating. Basically showing all the behaviors I recognize. She seems so unhappy and I feel like I'm losing her, and it makes me so anxious and the only thing that makes me feel better is reverting to those behaviors. If we're eating together, and she doesn't finish her meal, then neither can I, stuff like that. I know that is probably making it worse. What can I do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Having trouble not being sick after eating a meal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 02:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to purge about 4-5 times a week for a year, and stopped suddenly due to problems it was causing. Ever since then I've had problems eating a meal without feeling the physical need to be sick. It's like I can't swallow food properly anymore since it feels like I haven't managed to swallow it properly, and I feels like food gets stuck in my throat. I can be sick without forcing my fingers down my throat, I can just bring it back up without even trying. It's pretty gross, but I don't think I've eaten a full meal in the last couple of years without experiencing this and I don't know if this is normal for people who have purged somewhat frequently in the past.

Does anyone have any experience or advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Performer with eating disorder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last Friday, I saw a professional modern dance performance with my wife. Although we both enjoyed the show, we were both somewhat disturbed by the appearance of one dancer. Although neither of us are health professionals capable of capable of making a diagnosis, this woman's physique suggested fairly a severe eating disorder. The rest of the dancers, men and women, were fit but not at all underweight, so she wasn't just the skinniest among many skinny in the ensemble. While I certainly don't want to judge anyone else's body, I'm also concerned if the money I pay to this dance group is supporting deeply unhealthy body image. I remember hearing that certain fashion shows have now agreed not to use models with eating disorders. Perhaps the same could be done among dance companies. What's the best response to this situation? Keep my opinion to myself? Write a letter to the dance group management stating my unease? Any thoughts are welcome. Please note that I know I'm coming from a place of real ignorance with this question, but if my question is offensive to anyone, I promise it's not my intention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: worried that i'm developing an ED (again maybe?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I've never posted here or even seen the page until I did some fearful googling this evening, but y'all seem like the right community to reach out to. I have major depression and I've recognized one period of extreme restrictive eating in my life (my first half of high school) that left me underweight before gaining it back. I'm in my junior year of college now, and I'm at the lower end of a healthy weight range, starting to worry that those tendencies to restrict could be a bigger deal than I'm equipped to handle. The appetite loss that comes with my depression starts a cycle of self-starving because I don't want to eat, enjoying the feeling of having lost weight, and perpetuating a lack of appetite. I think sometimes I restrict for self harm. I'm scared of the feeling of satisfaction I get at the end of a day with little to no food, and though I can recognize that my low mood is exacerbated by a lack of food, the feeling of getting thinner often trumps the desire to eat for my health. I've never been diagnosed with an eating disorder but I'm starting to worry that I could be doing more harm that I intended. 

If you have any advice or literally anything I just feel a little lost.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Friend has relapsed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A college friend of mine has been open about her mental health struggles for as long as I've known her. She has bipolar disorder and was hospitalised for anorexia nervosa in her mid teens and has been in recovery for as long as I've known her. As I've only known her in recovery I can't be certain of a relapse but, it seems likely. She's moving to another country soon also and I know change can trigger disordered eating. I've noticed recently she has lost a significant amount of weight and I'm concerned. From what I gather it's a big no-no to comment on someone with an eating disorders weight. How can I express concern in a constructive, helpful manner. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to eat that first real meal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a 30 y/o mother of two and I've been struggling with an eating disorder for some time now. I really, really want to get better but I'm having a hard time eating a true meal. Every day I tell myself "today you'll eat XYZ" but then I panic because "if I eat XYZ I won't be able to have ABC later". So my question is how those of you who have recovered had that first REAL meal and what did you eat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Out of options, seeking advice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a 27 year old male that is in the healthy range, after being underweight 2 years ago.

I can only eat a very small amount of food before my stomach wants to flip, everything just tenses up and I can feel the food work its way back up. I have seen two gastroenterologist, done two endoscopies, had a gastric emptying testing, tried a variety of medications such as Tecta and some others that aren't coming to my head right now.

Both have no idea what is wrong with, there doesn't seem to be anything physically wrong. In addition to this, I had developed a chronic cough that seemed to appear at the same time as the eating issue, seeing a Pulmonologist to see if we can deal with that problem as well.

Coughing makes eating harder, symptoms worsen and wanting to vomit makes coughing happen. It is an endless cycle.

I am confident that I am not overeating when I eat what I should be able to, now I can barely finish a normal amount before feeling extremely terrible.

I am actually trying to gain weight, I've been underweight my whole life, and not fit at all, I have put time and effort into exercise and I am finding myself having to manage my eating nearly as a full time job just to maintain this weight.

Others have hinted that it may be a psychological issue, although it happened at the same time as a pretty traumatic breakup of a long term relationship, it has been 5+ years since and I don't see how it is a problem.

The other change that happened at that time was moving back to Home after graduating University, the environment could have an impact on my cough and in term affected my ability to eat. At least that's what I hope it is...it would be the simplest to solve, I vacuum and clean my room and house twice a week now, hoping to improve the air and improve my cough.

Well...I'm actually not sure what I'm asking for, I'm just at wit's end on what to do. Even with no psychological trauma before, the stress I may get from having to manage my meals (small meals, multiple times a day, snacking here and there) just to maintain my weight may affect me in the long run if nothing is fixed.

Does anyone have experience with this, or advice for me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Weight restored, but still messed up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am recovering from a restrictive ED. I am almost fully weight restored since more than a month, but I still have disordered thoughts about food. In a way my thoughts have become more disordered lately, because when I was gaining weight I knew I HAD to gain weight, so I just ate whatever I wanted without any limitation. Now it's different. 

I tried to eat "normally" for a while, but I just ended up restricting again. Not to lose weight, but to maintain it. 
I avoid certain foods  that I ate when I had to gain weight. I obsessively weigh everything and check the nutritional labels. I try to convince myself that junk food isn't really my thing and that I'm really into "healthy food", such as green veggies. I only eat at certain hours. I stop eating when the others stop too and not when I feel full. I exercise a bit (not compulsively) just to shed calories and not because I enjoy it. I tell lies to my dietitian, writing that I actually do feel full after a meal and that I didn't eat pasta because I truly didn't want it. I often weigh myself after a meal and feel happy if the numbers on the scale don't go up. I check my body. I am secretly happy when there is a low-calorie meal instead of a high-calorie meal that I actually like more. And so on.

Yesterday I decided to challenge some of these thoughts. I ate things and quantities that were uncomfortable to me, just because my ED was telling me not to.

Of course, 5 minutes after that I panicked and thought OH MY GOD WHAT DID I DO I HAVE A BINGE EATING DISORDER I'M TOTALLY BECOMING OBESE.

I regularly see a therapist, but he just doesn't seem to help much - he was the one who, while I was in the gaining-weight phase, told me that I didn't need to "go too far" and "become bulimic" and that I had to "eat like a normal person". That's not what you want to hear if you're a recovering quasi-anorexic.

How do I get out of the loop? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to help my SO face the disorder all over again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My SO has an eating disorder. When she was younger it was really bad, and at first i was clueless and she could keep it hidden, etc. It got so bad she was hospitalized, tried to kill herself, we broke up multiple times, etc. But eventually i caught on, learned a lot, and after years it all came out and though it was tough, we worked together mostly. After years of therapy and various treatments she was in recovery. I saw huge improvements in her life. We got very close, i loved the person she was and we got married. Fast forward a couple decades and we are still together, and ive noticed a steep decline in the last year or so (im not sure what started it). Being that i went through it with her the first time, i picked it up quickly. 

Unfortunately, she would rather turn the clock back 20 years. Even if i catch her in the act, she still acts like i dont know what im talking about, and know nothing. She still tries to hide it, and pretends like it isnt happening. She answers "im fine" anytime i ask how she is. Its as if the whole learning process never happened, and she is pretending im an ignorant stranger again, that i never sat through hundreds of therapy sessions where she outlined exactly what she thought and did, etc. It makes it so much more difficult this time, because we have already gone through all this before. and its that much more frustrating for me to be left out again, or treated as if im stupid, ignorant, and worthless. Im back to being the new boyfriend who if she is sneaky enough, will never know whats really going on. I know she would rather me play along and turn a blind eye, but i cannot do that, because i care so much for her. I cant confront her however because she just shuts down, or denies it, or calls me paranoid, etc. Its brought our marriage to the breaking point.
How do i start the process all over again, without making it worse. Especially since this time she seems to have lost all will to fight it.

How do i start the process all over again, without making it worse. Especially since this time she seems to have lost all will to fight it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: California State University San Marcos Scale Validation Survey II (IRB Code Number: 893513-1) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A self-report questionnaire is being developed for people with various psychiatric diagnoses. This study aims to examine if this questionnaire is measuring the phenomenon of interest. We hope that our research will lead to further research and potential clinical applications. You must have a formal psychiatric diagnosis, be fluent in English, and be at least 18 years of age to participate. This study is open to US and non-US residents. You are not eligible to participate if you participated in our recent interview and survey studies. This survey takes approximately 15 to 25 minutes to complete.

To participate in this online research study, please visit: https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/PYKCXST
To learn more about this research study, please contact the researcher, Stephanie Price (price049@cougars.csusm.edu), or the advisor, Dr. Heike Mahler (hmahler@csusm.edu).

Stephanie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Bulimia and Stomach Ulcers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My SO has been a long term suffer of Bulimia for 10 years. He purges almost everything he eats from snacks to meals. As a result he has number of health problems including Anemia, Zero Libido, frequent dizzy spells, acid reflux, little to no energy and some chest pains that tingle his arms. Hes been in DBT for about a year but little progress has been made and hes still struggling with his relationship with alcohol. 

Needless to say, myself and his family is deathly worried for his health and fertility. He's thrown up twice this week involuntarily which isnt normal (and hes not ill either). His mother is worried he might have stomach ulcers. I wondered if anyone has any experience with stomach ulcers that they are happy to share with me?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How do I tell my mom I want to eat a certain way? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to live with my mum in a few weeks for the summer once I get out of school. She found out I was undereating earlier this year and is basic the only person who knows about it. I still get obsessive thoughts and feelings of guilt around food but I'm levels of magnitudes better than I was at the beginning of the year and am usually trying to make my weight go up. It's a lot easier for me to eat without feeling if guilty if I feel like the food I'm eating is healthy. I really worried when trying to explain this to her that she'll think its just my disorder talking. The last time I saw her she got visibly concerned anytime I denied myself some kind of desert and would then pressure me to eat it. I feel like this really only exacerbated the problem and causes tension between us.I know she's coming from a place of compassion and concern. I really don't want to diminish that. I've been thinking about maybe getting a doctor to vouch for my choices but If there was I could resolve this in conversation without having to go that far that would be preferred. Do you have any advice about how to go about having this conversation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: 20F, Help with Bad Teeth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My teeth have been very off-white ever since my adult ones came in. I stopped smiling with my teeth when I was about eleven. Now, eating disorders have further damaged them. I honestly think never being able to feel comfortable smiling is the biggest cause of my depression and anxiety. My teeth make me feel disgusting.

I just don't know what to do. I'm about four years away from finishing grad school, and will have six figure debt at that point before even thinking about a mortgage, etc., so I don't really know if veneers or something of the sort are an option for me. I'm just so lost and don't know what to do. 

I'm so tired of feeling ugly, and gross. My teeth definitely contribute to my body dysmorphia and eating disorder, but I feel like I can't fix them. I don't even know what my overall question is, I just feel like I need some help. I can't do this anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Question about libido and periods after recovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will start off by saying I am not sure whether this is the correct place to be posting about this. If not I would appreciate being pointed in the right direction.

My long distance girlfriend battled with a pretty severe eating disorder for around 2 years, and began recovery just over a year ago. Since then most things have improved greatly. She is eating a healthy amount, gradually feeling better about her body and has a much more positive outlook on life in general. However, I am looking for advice on a couple of things she opened up to me about recently.

First off, she has not had her period at all since the early stages of her ED. She knew that was something that commonly happened during the ED, but now she considers herself recovered from it, she is becoming increasingly more worried about her period still not returning. I have read that it can just take longer in some people, but that doesn't seem to comfort her much.
Secondly, she opened up to me about how she hasn't felt any sexual drive in well over 2 years and that it is something she really wants to feel, but is becoming very frustrated that it has not returned either. We have done some research together and have written a list of foods that are said to increase estrogen in the hopes that it will have some effect. She said that she has also tried watching porn on occasion but it hasn't really done anything for her and just makes her more frustrated that she's not feeling anything. We are also going to be meeting up for 2 months in a few weeks (which is what started these conversations) and she said that she is interested in trying things with me at a slow pace. I am of course willing to help her in any way I can and want her to feel comfortable with these things. 

What I'm really asking is for any advice people may have on these subjects. As her partner, I want to know if there is anything else I can be doing to help her through this and reassure her, and also if there's anything I can be doing to help her regain her sex drive. Thanks for listening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Night Eating Disorder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 11:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi,

I've had Night eating disorder for a number of years now. At least 6+. I usually wake up in the middle of the night to go to the bathroom then i'll have an uncontrollable urge to get something to eat, i'll inevitably give in, in my groggy state. I've only been successful in not giving into this urge a few times, but it takes a lot of mental struggle and I have to prepare myself before bed. 
My question is for anyone who has suffered from this and overcome it. How did you do it? 

Couple things to note. I'm an X-alcoholic. This did, however, start while i was drinking. I've been sober for 4.5 years now though and it continues. 

I suffer from Depression and Anxiety and take anti-depressants for it. 

I have also been vegan for the past 2.5 years. 

Does anyone have any thoughts on this? I could use the advice. 
Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Feeling at a complete loss </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 11:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi,

I'm kind of feeling at a loss with everything right now and just don't really know where to turn to. I feel like going to my GP is pointless as I'm not underweight so I wont be able to get any kind of help.

I've suffered from anorexia for a good 6 ish years in varying time periods over the last ten or so years. The point I'm at now is that to all intents and purposes on the outside I eat ok and I exercise, so therefore everything must be hunky dory and there's no problems at all going on.

But instead I am absolutely miserable, and get so depressed at times that I just want to end everything. Everyday I panic if I don't do my normal exercise plan, if I can't go for a walk in the morning I have a complete melt down, if I can't go for a walk lunch time I'm distraught, and if I can't make this up with a workout DVD at home I feel devastated. And now, to top it off for me, because I may start cycling to work, my whole workout plan is going to change, meaning I'll cycle to and from work but not have the time for my evening workouts which means I am so so terrified of gaining weight as I may not be doing the same amount / enough exercise.

After years of restricting what I eat and calorie counting I've gotten to a semi happy point where I try and eat really well throughout the day, and when I get home eat treats after my evening meal which I enjoy. I personally feel like I eat too much at these points but my partner tells me I don't. Either way, my weight has kind of been stable ish and whilst I still feel like I HAVE to do exercise, I'm kind of ok with my weight.

But I just cannot cope with the upcoming change, where I feel my cycle to work just won't be enough exercise which leads to : I'm going to have to do loads of extra exercise every evening, cut back even more (and the minute I think of any kind of diet I start crying after years of this, and trying to get to a point where I'm trying to just eat what I want and enjoy life) and now I just feel nothing I do will ever be enough to stop a huge influx of weight gain - like an inevitable doom, and I really just can't cope.

I'm just so so tired of trying to balance everything, that everything has to add up to prevent weight gain. I've tried to just eat what I want in reason to enjoy life and food, and exercise to just be fit and healthy, but I'm just lying to myself, and just can't cope with change. Its ruining my relationships, and ruining life for as a whole for me as my whole life revolves around this. I just don't know what to do any more.

Does anyone have any advice or thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I'm worried diabetes is giving me an eating disorder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over a year ago, I was diagnosed with prediabetes. I immediately went on the ketogenic diet to try to not progress to type 2 diabetes, but my A1c at my check up three months later was even higher than before I cut out all sugar and carbs. At the time of my diagnosis and the time I went keto, I was was a healthy weight for my height.

After then, I figured since it makes no difference, to start allowing carbs and sugar back into my diet. I started using an app to track my intake and set my goals to the recommended grams of sugar, and a number for carbs that's considered low-carb (and some random numbers for protein and fat).

If I go over my grams of sugar for the day or my carbs, I feel absolutely terrible about myself, like I am a failure, and like I'm going to end up killing myself because my diabetes can, over time, destroy my body.

If it matters at all, since last year, I've lost a decent percentage of my body weight without actively trying. I'm still a healthy weight, but if I lose another pound or two, my BMI will be too low. Anorexia runs in my family--both my grandmas has suffered from it and one died from it. When my parents saw me for the holiday, they kept asking me if I needed help.

I guess my main question is, at one point does counting carbs and counting calories for diabetes become an actual eating disorder, since it's necessary for diabetics to survive by counting these numbers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My most popular Facebook photo is of me when I was visibly very sick. How can I cope with the negative feelings this causes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it's dumb. I know that I shouldn't be looking for validation from Facebook friends. But I only have 150 friends; all whom I see in real life at least once a week. At my lowest weight, where I could barely stand, passed out walking up a half a flight of stairs, and couldn't remember day to day interactions, I posted a selfie. I rarely post photos of myself due to insecurities I have, so this was the first time in almost a year. Almost every single one of my friends liked/loved it. Told me I looked good even though my collar bones and ribs were protruding severely. My eyes were sunken in so badly that my head looked like a damn halloween prop. Shortly after posting this photo, I started recovery. Around 2 months later, I posted a photo of myself at a normal weight. Smiling, happy, no bones protruding. Hardly anyone liked it.

When I confess to people about my ED and recovery, they say it was very obvious I was suffering. Yet here they were, loving on this photo of me that was essentially a breath away from death's door. I know I could just remove the photo, but I want it there as a reminder to myself. I guess I'm just baffled right now. It used to be very triggering, but now over time not so much. It is more of a lesson now.

Does anyone else have similar experiences? And how do you cope with them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My roommate's eating seems perfect and it's triggering me. How do I cope? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I am trying to get over a longstanding, mild case of bulimia. I'm somewhat healthy, only binging and purging maybe once a week, but the disorder consumes my waking thoughts, and when I do have binge and purge episode, it really throws me off for a few days and affects my self esteem.

Anyway, my roommate is completely opposite of me - she eats super slowly, forgets about her food, eats a third or half, or puts away like three bites for later (whereas I devour most of the food that's in front of me - to not eat the last three bites and 'save them' for later is crazy to me). What's worse is she's now vegan and she basically doesn't buy food in plastic or things you can throw away, so I feel her eating is perfect, and it makes me feel terrible about how I eat. Basically her way of eating makes me extremely jealous, and I'm worried it's triggering me to want to eat less or similarly, which I feel would cause me to restrict then go crazy and binge later. It's stupid to feel this way. How can I get over it and just focus on myself and do what I need to to get better? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Non-ED related doctor visits triggering? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 12:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been in and out of recovery for awhile and had been pretty good about avoiding AN behaviors lately until I had to make a doctor's appointment for horrible spring allergies. Just knowing that I'll have to be weighed in a few days has driven me straight back into restricting and anxiety about it not being low enough/being seen as faking it. My go to coping mechanisms seem to be failing me. I'd really appreciate any suggests anyone has. Thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I'm scared that I'm emulating/spiralling into an ED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 11:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys.

I recently realized that I've been restricting (advertently and inadvertently) the food that I've been intaking for about 6 months now. I'm slightly overweight for my height, and I've recently committed to losing excess weight, but for the past 6 months, I've noticed that when I eat even a bite of something or have a snack (even if it's healthy), I feel disgusting about myself. I had one bite of tofu today to test how it turned out after cooking it, and I just felt absolutely awful about eating before my designated dinner time. Every day, I eat a lot less than the calories required to lose weight, and I've been pushing my body to burn a lot of calories each day on the treadmill.

I've lost a considerable amount of weight in a short amount of time, and I'm scared that I may be spiralling into an ED. How do I stop this? 

I still have some weight left to lose but for some reason, my mentality is that I can lose it faster by starving, strict portion control and rigorous exercise, and that I shouldn't be dependent on food. I used to eat when I was bored, and when I wasn't even hungry, and I haven't started to feel genuinely guilty about it until now. Nowadays, food feels like an enemy or an obstacle getting in the way of a perfect body. I don't feel malnourished/tired from doing this but I'm really scared.

Does anyone have any tips on how to curve this behavior? Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Trying to find a healthier alternative for girlfriends birthday dessert </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey folks,

I have a small request. My girlfriend used to struggle from bulimia, but fortunately, she has mostly recovered. However, she still gets uncomfortable when it comes to desserts. The main problem seems to be that she feels forced to eat desserts in social settings. Having something not too sweet on the table could solve that. Thus, for her birthday, I want to find a somewhat healthier cake or something else. There will probably be several cakes on the table, so one healthier alternative won't hurt.

Any suggestions? I've only managed to come up with some vegetables and dip so far, which could work.
Thanks in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: The scale routine is back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 12:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last week I was at the doctor's for a sinus problem, obviously told them I didn't want to know my weight, and the nurse who weighed me was totally understanding about that. BUT after the appointment, they handed me a sheet with a summary, and guess what, there was my weight, and they'd calculated my BMI as well.

I've been good about not weighing myself for months. It was a difficult behavior to break, but I was doing well until now. But suddenly I'm right back to weighing myself constantly and getting freaked out every time it fluctuates upwards, and wanting to see it go down soooo bad.

I know I can get back on track with help from my therapist, and of course getting that scale out of here. But I feel like emotionally I've taken a HUGE step backwards. I'm scared that I'll never completely leave my eating disorder behind because I'm triggered so easily. I hate how easy it is for something so insignificant to completely take up all of my mind. Why does this have to be so hard?!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Relapse help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 12:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey I'm not sure if this has been posted already but it wouldn't let me put it up. Maybe someone could help or offer some advice please?

Hi all, I have been debating posting this for a long time. I have had an eating disorder for around 20 years but wasn't diagnosed until around 4 years ago when I was in a very severe restriction form and lost (I don't want to put numbers in case I trigger anyone) about a third of my body weight within a few months and kept going. The thing is I regained the weight cos of all the pressure that I felt from family, friends and the health team who advised I would be sectioned if I didn't go inpatient. Now, the ED is far from gone. I'm still in the same habits of purging and controlling/restricting but not losing any weight and I feel like I want to peel off my skin and be the person I was even though I know how sick I was. I am still seeing a psychiatrist but she accepts no more than about 10-15 mins for each (8 weekly session) and even when I've told her everything including my self harm and suicidal thoughts, she barely responds and just offers to continue or infrequently up my dosage. I'm really losing the will. Can anyone help? Can anyone help me to accept help and want to recover? Please.

Thank you so much, I don't want to clog the feed but just feeling pretty bad and low

Edit: Please let the OP /u/mixxvixxen know when you respond.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: binge eating problem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 15:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how does one even go about beginning to tackle a binge eating disorder? i acknowledge that i have a problem, but even that isn't enough. i can go a whole day being "good", eating healthy, only to ruin it at night by eating nearly everything in sight until i have a headache and am breathing heavily.

i feel worthless because i cannot seem to tackle this issue, which is starting to affect my mental health and well-being. if anyone could provide some tips or help for dealing with a binge eating issue i would appreciate it an insane amount. i don't know where to start but i want to conquer this disorder and overcome it once and for all.

thanks for taking the time to read my story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: A couple in need of ED recovery tips? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 15:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me and my gf are both recovering from EDs. Between us we have years of experience with BED, anorexia, orthorexia... we have tried to change the way we approach food on a massive scale by eating out more talking about our feelings on food and so on, but we recently hit a wall. we realized we were rushing too fast into this and needed some help. How do we actually do this? Change our routine slightly each day? each week? how do we adjust it? 

We are scared and worried but we have mutual support all we need is something to guide us in the right direction. We try to measure fullness on a 1-10 scale before and after every meal. we also ditched our old rules but i think we did that too rashly and it somewhat backfired. The amount of blogs, articles and tips on the topic are overwhelming and anxiety-inducing. Also none provide real advice, like "break one more rule every week" or something concrete. We need something that will indicate that we are going in the right direction and also at a right pace. Any tips ?

Tldr, we both lost a lot of weight and have developed bad habits/negative attitudes towards food </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to proceed with treatment when you've made progress stopping behaviors, but still have ED thoughts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 01:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Despite maintaining a healthy weight for 3 years after a 6 year stint with ana, I'm looking for treatment to help with the ana voice and thoughts I still experience often - feelings of worthlessness, wanting to lose weight, fear of gaining weight and overall the obsessive thought that I don't deserve to be loved - all things that have been the root cause of disordered eating in the past.

When I was underweight, I found that therapy actually exacerbated my ED because it forced me to talk about food all the time. I'd like to start a treatment plan to help with the underlying issues but am scared that therapy will force me to think about food more.

Has anyone else had this experience and any suggestions for tackling this next phase of treatment moving forward? I am determined to kick the ana voice out of my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I can only eat when I'm stoned. How can I re-learn to eat normally? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 03:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i've struggled with anorexia for about ten years. for the past four years or so, i've developed a coping mechanism where i'm only able to eat when i'm stoned. when i try to eat sober, the smell of food is nauseating, and i just can't bring myself to take a bite.

i really want to be able to eat under normal circumstances. does anyone else have this issue? What has helped you to overcome a dependence on substances when it comes to eating or avoiding ED symptoms? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Strategies to overcome ED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious about strategies and routines that have helped people to overcome binge eating and anorexia. What has helped face and solve the issue in your life? How did you identify the triggers? By yourself, through therapy, through talking with peers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How can we use our "powers" for good? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the perfectionism and determination...how can we put these types of things to good use in our lives instead of being obsessed with something that in reality doesn't better our futures at all? Losing weight or getting "the body you want" doesn't further our careers or make us have better relationships. If we can put our thoughts into something productive we could probably really excel. What have you found like that that takes you out of your ED head? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: osteoporosis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My sister has a diagnosis of osteoporosis caused by long term anorexia.(almost 20 yrs) I can't find much information about the implications of this online, only that anorexia can cause osteoporosis and there seems to be a less straight forward treatment options than other forms of osteoporosis. is there anyone else in this position or with a relative who has it? if so have they been able to increase their bone mineral density with treatment? how has it affected them?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How do I get over feeling like I don't deserve to eat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm very overweight (100 pounds) and I have a binge/restrict disorder. In the past, I would restrict without realizing it: "I don't have time to eat right now" or "You're probably just bored" and so on. 

Lately I've been feeling like eating is a privilege that I don't get to have. I'll binge or have something that isn't in my plan (soda, seconds at dinner, etc.). I won't enjoy it while I'm eating it and then when I get hungry later I'll convince myself that I don't need anything because I'll probably just fuck up again anyway. It's like I have a voice telling me that the only way to succeed with the weight loss and prevent the mistakes is to not eat at all. I love food. I'm tired of feeling guilty for eating it.

How do I get over feeling like I don't deserve to eat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Physiological Complications with Recovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 11:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been attempting recovery the past several months after dealing with EDNOS for about 6 years now. It's really frustrating though in that when I do eat a meal-sized meal I feel very sick afterwards, and get cramping and severe bloating. This is also triggered by certain foods such as legumes (beans) and starchy carbs (like potatoes) and any grains. The bloating is so painful for me that I have to lay down for a few hours and often nap to relieve the pain. I know this is not just a psychological thing because both my sister and my boyfriend have seen how swollen my stomach looks and are astounded by it. I thought this may be food allergies or gluten intolerance at first (although I've never had any before), but haven't been tested for it. I read online though that years of restriction can lead to the stomach shrinking and not being able to capacitate a full meal's worth of food (similar to someone who's gotten gastric bypass surgery.) I also feel a bit cloudy/sleepy and sometimes overheated post-meal. In addition to the severe bloating, sometimes if I eat a full meal and drink a few glasses of water/fluids with and after the meal I involuntarily regurgitate some of the meal (but mostly liquid.) It's almost as if my stomach is at full capacity and it pushing up and out the extra it cannot fit. I don't have a history with bulimia. 

So I guess my questions are if 1) Is this related to my ED and/or is it possibly related to something else? and 2) Is there anything I can do about it and if so what? 

Thanks x </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Post request: [recovery] healthy intake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have had a restrictive eating disorder for over 2 years now and finally decided I wanted to try to recover last month when I realized I was skipping feeling faint in classes, not able to do certain exercises, and was unable to do almost any work due to  lack of energy and the feeling that my brain was shutting down despite the fact that I was a medium healthy weight. My caloric intake was extremely low and I have made an effort in the past 4 weeks to increase my calorie intake a little...I am not on the high end of a healthy weight and I feel like I don't know what is a healthy amount to eat anymore. I find since I stopped restricting I actually feel hungry more often. I still eat much healthier than the average college student but I hate the change I've seen since trying to recover from the pain of severe restricting. I have no idea what a healthy intake is anymore. Any advice? 

Ps: I realize a nutritionist is an option is like that to be a last resort though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Should I tell my doctor? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suspect I may have an eating disorder - I display many symptoms such as restricting diet to lose weight, hating my body, calorie counting to an excess, a desire not to eat in front of others, etc. So should I tell my doctor? I'm underweight, but I don't think it'll get much worse and it may just be a waste of time and money. It's not very severe at the moment, so should I tell my doctor about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Doctors recommendation is making things worse? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I very recently got dignosed with an ED and this dignosis came to a very huge surprise. and the doctor said that I should try to eat more and track what I eat or he will have to send me to a dietitian. But tracking the food I eat and seeing all the calories I eat is making it a lot harder to eat and to feel better(I feel gross at how much I eat) All these feelings are new as I've never saw my eating As a problem but I've been sick for probably 6 Years I've felt fine up until I've had to track what I'm eating for the doctor, what should I do? Or how do I make my self feel better about how much I eat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Recovering while also getting to a lower, healthy weight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Body Stats: female, 20, short, overweight

Last year I tried to diet, had the "less is better" mentality, and got into the healthy range. But I was miserable, starving, and hurting. Came home for the summer, sort of snapped out of it, started eating again, but now I'm overweight again.

This time, I'm trying to be healthy, make genuine lifestyle choices instead of just dieting. I've discovered I actually love vegetables. But I'm struggling with eating enough. I'm definitely doing better than last time, but some days I have to force myself to eat every bite, and most days I only eat about 3/4 as much as I'm aiming for.

So how do you guys juggle moving towards a healthy weight with eating enough? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Has anyone been treated at the Emily Program? What was it like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 02:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had ED issues of all kinds for a long time now and I just made an appointment at The Emily Program. I understand it's a really good treatment center and it's also pretty much the only ED treatment option in my area. 

My major issue that's being treated is binging but I also have some restrictive tendencies too. I just wanted to know what anyone who's already been through it thought of the program so I know a little bit more about what to expect. I haven't had my assessment yet but I'm sure I'll just be doing the day program, but if you were in residential I'd still like to hear your experience!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Daughter's Friend has asked for our help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 02:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our 18 year old daughter is friend with a 17 year old girl with an eating disorder. Last night, our daughter came into our room and asked us for help. This girl's parents are divorced. Her mother appears to have a similar eating disorder and has refused to help her daughter get medical attention. This girl has asked her father for help as well and has been denied. Over the months, we have seen her lose a tremendous amount of weight. I'm not a doctor but I'm not stupid. 

The girl is wonderful. She does well in school, holds down a job and has been accepted at a wonderful college. 

Last night, my daughter told us, that her friend is now having difficulty digesting food when she does eat. My daughter asked if we would pay for a doctor to evaluate her and/or pay for an in-treatment program. My wife and I want to help and we could find the money so that's not the issue. Our problem is that this girl is 17 and not our child. How do we help her? Are we allowed to? What can we do?

This is serious. This girl needs help and she's asking us. What do we do? Someone help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Research Participants Sought: Do you have an eating disorder or suspect you might have an eating disorder? Participate in our "closing the treatment gap" survey and we will donate $10 AUD to eating disorders charity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My name is Dr. Scott Griffiths. I'm an eating disorders researcher at the University of Melbourne, Australia.

Today we launched a global study of treatment attitudes, media, and stigma, among individuals with diagnosed and suspected (i.e., undiagnosed) eating disorders.

The study is called ["Closing the treatment gap: A longitudinal study of treatment attitudes, media, and stigma among individuals with diagnosed or suspected eating disorders"](https://melbpsych.co1.qualtrics.com/jfe/form/SV_1Y17wI11kbstmtL).
We are seeking individuals who i) are currently diagnosed with an eating disorder, or ii) think they might have an eating disorder. You must be aged 18 years and over to participate.

The study initially involves a 2535 minute online survey and two shorter 1520 surveys that will be emailed to you 3 and 6 months later, respectively.

We will donate $5 AUD for each of the second and third times you complete the survey and you can choose which of 7 eating disorder charities will receive your donation. The charities are located in countries around the globe, including Australia, Europe, the United States, and the Middle East. If you complete both the second and third survey, your total donation will be $10 AUD.
We are seeking 500 participants. Thus, the total possible donation to eating disorder charities is $5000 AUD. The study is funded by a grant from the Australian National Health and Medical Research Council.

[Click to learn more about the study and to participate](https://melbpsych.co1.qualtrics.com/jfe/form/SV_1Y17wI11kbstmtL).

Were posting to r/EatingDisorders because our previous recruitment efforts on this subreddit were a great success. The findings from these (now published) studies led to changes in public policy in Australia, enabled charities to focus their eating disorders destigmatisation campaigns, and informed clinical workshops that trained eating disorders clinicians living in cities around the globe, from Fremantle through to New York.

To learn more about our research on eating disorders, visit our [ResearchGate](https://www.researchgate.net/profile/Scott_Griffiths2) and [Academia](https://unimelb.academia.edu/ScottGriffiths) profiles, where our papers are available for free public download, or follow us on [Twitter](https://twitter.com/Scott1Griffiths), where we provide daily updates on the state of research in eating disorders.

Thank you for your ongoing support of eating disorders research.

Sincerely, Scott </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Online forum where my mum can talk to other families caring for girls with eating disorders? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 17 year old sister has a fairly serious eating disorder. It's heartbreaking seeing her intentionally wasting away to almost nothing. She has now finally agreed to go to an eating disorders clinic and has visited once, but I'm aware that this is just the start of her road to recovery. 

I'm only involved when I return home (about one weekend per month), but my mum deals with it on a day-to-day basis. In an entirely separate incident she's had to deal with her divorce following my dad being arrested, and she's under a huge amount of stress as she tries to look after her children. Last time I was there she just burst into tears and told me about how difficult it was trying to look after my sister on top of everything else, and how she just didn't know what to do.

The person my sister is seeing is a registered mental nurse, which is a good start, but the therapy (which is obviously confidential) only takes place between my sister and the nurse. I'm very surprised that there's no involvement for my mum at all - she's not received any guidance whatsoever on how to act, is not going to be involved in any group counselling, and is still feeling very much in the dark.

Does anyone know of an online forum where my mum can direct her worries towards people who are going through a similar thing? She's in desperate need of a support system that I'm just not knowledgeable enough to provide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Eating issues </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Im guy whos 20 years old and I have this problem that has been bugging me for a while. Anyway I'm skinny as hell which is quite embarrassing for me. I wanted to ask if I should see doctor about it since I dont know if its serious or not. I cant eat much, there are some times when I can eat alot but these happen rarely. Usually I just eat to get rid of empty stomach feel because I dont wanna force myself. (I have tried to force more food but its kinda giving me throw up feel sometimes). Recently I havent eaten much at all due to some emotional issues. I heard that doing exercises and working out gives more hunger feel but for me it works opposite. Every time I do something physical I just dont feel hunger at all after working and it takes like 1-2 hours to get my hunger feel. So should I see doctor about it or its just some genetical issue? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Doctor said I have an eating disorder and I didn't know </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to the doctors a day ago from unrelated issues and he asked about my eating because I am underweight, cold and have a very low resting heart rate, he said that all this can and is related to eating disorders and that I probably have one. Now I've never thought of my self having an ED but I have always had strange habits with food like having to eat things a certain way always even on equal when chewing and with bite sizes and I know I don't eat as much as I should and I can't eat in front of people I don't know or when I'm in public or if I'm in a quiet room. 

My question is can I have a eating disorder and not even know about it? He says that my malnutrition is affecting my brain function and not helping with my severe anemia and would like to test me again for depression and anxiety and send me to a dietitian so I'd really love to know if I could actually have a eating disorder.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Is going from severely underweight to overweight a common occurrence? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have had a restrictive ED. Last April I was my perfectly healthy usual self (I used to hover around the bottom of the healthy BMI range), while in December I reached a really low BMI.

At the beginning of March my dietitian, seeing that I wasn't gaining weight even if I weren't actively restricting anymore, told me that I was "allowed" to eat just as much as I wanted and I just had to follow my hunger without ever counting calories.

That's what I did. I ate a lot. Like, really a lot.

I gained all my weight back in three weeks. But I'm keeping on eating a lot and now I'm really, truly f*cking scared that I'm going to end up overweight. My dietitian says it's close to impossible since I have a "lean body type" and I've never been overweight in my life (heck, I've never even been in the upper healthy range!). My mother and all my family also say the same.

But I just can't believe them. I'm eating like crazy. I'm not exactly binging, I'm just eating a lot, definitely more than what I should eat to maintain my current weight. I'm absolutely convinced that I'm going to keep on gaining weight and become fat. Is that a common occurence among anorexic people, or more broadly people with a history of restrictive ED? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friends think I have an eating disorder. Are they right to worry? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently I went on an overnight trip for school. This was the first time I ate with most of the team, and they seemed really concerned about me eating only two meals a day. I also had a mini-freakout when I realized the single item I'd eaten from Dairy Queen had more than half the calories I normally eat in a day.

Even if I do experience some sort of disordered eating, I'm seeing a school counselor soon, so I could bring it up then. However, I really don't want my friends to worry about my eating. Eating more food seems like the worst option -- is there any other way I could convince them I'm okay? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Advice for a housemate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 12:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She has dropped a massive amount of weight and she wasn't anywhere near an average weight before. She puts up signs in her cupboard in order to stop herself eating, and she recently asked me to go into her room to get something and there was a hand-written sign with aggressive "thinspiration" messages on her wall. There has been other signs but this one is the most aggressive one. She only has bottled water in her section of the fridge. It's a worry to say the least, nothing has been said to her up to this point but it is of great concern as she is always commenting how all of her clothes are loose on her (remember I said she wasn't an average weight before hand), even items of clothing such as stretchy leggings are loose on her.

Just looking for advice as to whether I need to speak to her in order for her to start getting help?

FYI I'm not a jealous female friend of hers that's envious of her weight loss, I'm a concerned male housemate that has nothing to gain or lose regardless of the outcome of all this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Do I actually have an ED? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 11:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a mild eating disorder when I was younger. My mom was very into crossfit and encouraged a restricted diet. I was always underweight, but it was never intentional. I never weighed myself and I was always involved in dancing/ cheerleading/ staying in shape.

Over the last year or so, I've had a lot of family drama and financial stress and I'm struggling to find a way to get through school. I've noticed that my sleeping and eating patterns are very out of whack. I don't know if this is just stress, or an indicator of a bigger issue at work.

I have lost a little too much weight in the last few months, and I think I might be underweight, but I've always had a small frame, so I really don't know. That in itself wouldn't worry me so much if I had a normal appetite. Per the weight-height-range chart sited here, I'm technically "ok", but I feel like my behavior might not be. I've found I rarely have an appetite, and usually the thought of any kind of food sounds repulsive. I've also found myself more concerned about the number on the scale (my boyfriend left his at my apartment) and how I look in the mirror... It's not really a conscious decision not to eat or self restrict, but I've had so much trouble gaining weight and I've felt a lot of guilt if I go crazy on a meal, like eating an entire pizza, but I've never made myself vomit.

I am vegetarian (by choice) and gluten free (celiac), so obviously that comes with some diet struggles in itself. I know that seeing a therapist or psychiatrist is the best option, but unfortunately it's just something I can't afford. Has anyone else had any similar issues? How do you deal with them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Restrictive eating causing horrible anxiety. Need help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm working on the recovery process from anorexia b/p subtype and still have some bad days. When my intake is less-than-adequate, my anxiety shoots through the roof. I can barely get myself to work, I'm worried about everything, I get so frustrated at the smallest things, and I feel completely unsettled. These feelings of inadequacy drive me to restrict further, perpetuating the cycle.

Has anyone found techniques or medications that help? I'm currently on Wellbutrin and seeing a therapist. Any advice would be massively appreciated. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How should I support an online friend with an ED whom I've never met in person </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 03:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently someone I know online and have grown very close to over the past several years confided in me that she has an eating disorder. I had suspected the possibility when she would mention miniscule changes in her weight and stressed about it when in reality she did not appear to have gained at all and already appeared to me as being healthy in her weight. Also from what she talked about eating,  I got the idea that she was barely getting enough calories in a day. She also recently started exercising regularly, and frequently compares herself to skinnier girls who barely look like they weigh any less than she does.

Eventually it came up that she admitted she has been struggling with an eating disorder for some time. I did not wish to pry too deep into her condition for fear of asking the wrong questions or steering the conversation into a dark place. I did learn that her issue is forcing herself to purge after meals, however I do not know the frequency, if it's after binging or just "sometimes". She did mention that she was proud of herself for going three days without an incident, and that the night prior she even had a meal that made her feel "full" but she didn't allow herself to throw up afterwards. She also told me she's only told 3 other people about her disorder because of how gross she thought it was. She seems to understand her problem, and acknowledges it is a problem, but she said she didn't really know how to stop herself.

My response to this was that I was happy to hear of her recent progress, and thanked her for sharing this with me as I know admitting something like this can be very difficult. I also told her I only wanted to support her and for her to be happy and healthy, and she can lean on me in any way she needs. But the fact that I'm not accessable in person and we only really speak online sparsely a few times a week means I feel very limited in what I can do.

Since then we haven't really spoken about this directly and I'm unsure about how I can check in with her to make sure she's doing okay. I did not ask her if she is now or ever has received counseling for this, but I would like that to be the next thing I ask if I can find a way to talk to her about this again. I get the impression, however, that she is trying to do this alone which I'm sure is incredibly difficult and greatly hinders her chances of success. Today we spoke and in the short conversation all of the signals were present that she's still struggling. She mentioned gaining a few pounds recently, and shortly after mentioning how full she was after eating a salad she ended the conversation saying she had something to take care of. I've been stressing ever since with the thought that she left to purge.

I'm afraid to be the one to bring it up again because I don't want her to push me away. I already feel like in the few weeks since her admission she's been slightly more distant with me, as if she possibly feels awkward with me knowing and possibly regretting telling me. Of course I also realize her distance could just be in my own head and I'm over analyzing something that isn't there. She's also in her final week of school for this semester and I fear that any unwanted confrontation on the subject might put her under even more stress.

I'm not exactly sure what kind of help I'm asking for here, or expecting. I don't want to lose a friend, but I also don't want to do nothing. Any advice would be appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Helping my friend who lives abroad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A very good friend of mine suffers from bulimia. As far as I know, I'm the only one who knows about it. I've known for about a year and tried to help her find help. I know that it's almost impossible to get someone to get help for themselves if they don't want it but I'm really concerned about her health. She's still at a healthy weight, but her mental health suffers a lot from her struggles. 

What can/should I do to help her? She lives abroad, so I can only talk to her via phone and I don't know how insurance/counseling works in her country.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: nightly binge eating syndrome </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need help to fight this, I'm sick and tired of what im going through.

Can anyone offer advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How will my girlfriend's behaviour change as she recovers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 10:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend of a few months is still on the road to fully recovering. She saw a dietitian recently who told her that because she's still undereating, she doesn't have the sex drive normal to a 23 year old. I fully intend to continue supporting her, but that does worry me slightly. We're taking things very slow, because we're both committed to no sex before marriage, but what does that mean for us as a couple? As she continues to recover, could she realise that she's not actually attracted to me? I've heard of people coming off birth control, and when their hormones change, they lose attraction to their partner as a result. I know that being underweight and undereating can also affect your hormones, but is this something that could happen? 

Thank you in advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Sponsors? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 10:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In recovery but struggling, and would really benefit from having a positive, "recovered" role model who can support me. Wondering if there were any ways to be linked with a 'sponsor'  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mobile app to supplement eating disorders treatment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 12:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of our subscribers told us about [this](http://abcnews.go.com/Health/treatment-eating-disorders-mobile/story?id=45898259) news story about a partnership between NEDA and the makers of a free mobile for managing your eating disorder.

[Here's a link on the NEDA website to get more information](https://www.nationaleatingdisorders.org/blog/using-all-our-devices-neda-recovery-record-partner-make-it-easier-connect-help) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Repost: Academic Research request for survey participants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 11:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The investigators are still looking for volunteers. 

STUDY ADVERTISEMENT

Our research team at Florida State University is currently conducting a study on risk factors for suicidal thoughts and behaviors. The primary goal of the study is to better understand what thoughts, feelings, and experiences motivate suicidal thoughts and behaviors.
We are interested in recruiting people who use this website to participate in our research study. Participation is completely voluntary. If you are interested in participating, you will complete an online screener to see if you qualify to participate. If you qualify, you will complete a variety of questionnaires online.
The study will involve four online assessments over the next month that should take about 40-50min to complete and you will be compensated up to $70 in online gift cards to Amazon. A few important things to know about the study are:

1. The study includes questions and images regarding self-harm, suicide, and other unpleasant images. We strongly emphasize that some of the images included are extremely graphic suicide-related images. Some people may feel that these images are very disturbing and may find them to be triggering.

2. All information collected will be kept anonymous.

3. Participation is completely voluntary.

4. The link we provide will send you to a website telling you about the study. Once on that site, you can decide whether or not you want to participate.

5. If you start to participate and decide you no longer feel comfortable or you are no longer interested, you can stop at any time.

6. We will provide links to treatment resources throughout the study.

7. This study will include only participants who are 18 years and older.

Please send us a private message at /u/risklabfsu if you are interested in participating. Once you contact us, we will send you a link to the screening questionnaire to see if you qualify and to tell you more about the study.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How do i stop? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 11:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Long story short. I'm a male 24 and had cancer treatment and stemcell transplant at age 9. Got GvH and it scarred my body. I was bullied and left very insecure about my body, looks and weight. Was almost overweight BMI wise but my body composition is quite twisted so yeah. Wanted to lose some weight and did. Too much. 

Now im severely underweight and feel stuck. I'm currently in outpatient contact with a ED clinic.

My weight had risen a little during a few months but because i started abusing a medicine my weight has dropped again. Half by accident really. Lower than it has ever been.

But still i feel as worse as always. I can't look into the mirror or even my shadow. At school i can't take off my scarf to hide my face.

How do i stop? I think i look like a monster. Others say it's all in my head but it really doesn't matter as long as i see myself that way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Weight is Stabilizing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I won't exactly say I binge, but I do purge everyday at least once. Recently I've noticed that nothings really changing and that my weight has stabilized. Is there anyway I can bypass this stage and lose a little bit more weight?
I want to seek help with some of my friends but it's really hard because I'm a guy and I can still be skinnier. I also feel like I'm a huge baggage every time I go to one if my friends and talk about it. Sigh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How should I help my BN friend more? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been supporting my friend with BN for about 8 months now. I bring her food (we're college students), hang out and talk about her state of mind, trying to encourage her to be more positive about herself.
It has felt like a long road and she tells me she feels happier around me and more outgoing in her plans, but at the same time I wonder if there is more I can do. Several things worry me:

1) When I stop by, her toilet has these thick black stains along the side. I thought they were blood, but I'm not sure. Her situation was critical years ago, but not now, so I'm wondering if this is normal.

2) Since I help her get food, I was wondering if there is anything I can get her to protect her teeth. She is fully aware of many of the downsides, but even then I can see stains on her teeth and think about how they're eroding every day. Any techniques or products you guys use on your teeth?

3) Should I nag her to eat less sugar? Considering the acid damage, eating sugar only compounds further damage upon the enamel. I don't want to become annoying though.

4) She tells me she feels like she deserves what she endures as some form of punishment for not accepting her body, which I really struggle to understand, but is this a common thought in your experience?

5) Is recovery common? God I hope so. Eventually I'm  going to have to move away, and she'll be left on her own. I try to run all the outcomes in my head and they're not ideal. Unless she stops now, I forsee lifelong damage, but it's frustrating because I realized long ago it can't be stopped in a day. I guess this is also a vent. I know I'm doing good by helping her, but with the physical damage still being done I feel like I'm doing nothing for her long term health. Again, her weight has increased marginally since I met her, but I just struggle with my own impatience for a quicker resolution. Sorry for the long post.

If you're reading this my friend, know that you are not alone. you are loved. I love you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I think my sister has an eating disorder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 04:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nearly everyone in my family has some kind of mental illness. I have anorexia, and another relative has a binge/restrict eating disorder. Lately I've been worried about my youngest sister. She doesn't like her body, and lately she's been skipping a lot of meals. I've talked to our parents, and they've agreed to take her to a therapist because she's been showing other signs of anxiety, but they don't think her eating is a problem because "she's not underweight". (they also think I'm all cured from my disorder because I'm not underweight anymore) So obviously they're clueless.

I'm glad she's going to therapy, because that is a good first step. But I know from my own experience that it's not going to be enough. Recovery is only possible if you really want to recover, and I don't know if my sister does or not. And even if she does, it's really hard in a family environment as messed up as ours.
I'm worried about my sister, and I want to help her. But I don't know what to do, and I know I can't handle the burden of being her only support outside of therapy. Her eating habits are actually really triggering me to restrict as well.

What can I do to improve this situation??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Found out my girlfriend is anorexic, I want to help however I can </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 23:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend accidentally came out as anorexic to me. I discovered her private tumblr blog that she uses to post thinspo and tips for others. She sent a message to me through that blog by accident, but I haven't told her I saw it, and she blocked my account from that blog shortly after. Neither of us have said a word so far.

I've been in relationships before with people suffering from mental illness, but I've never dealt with an eating disorder, and I'm clueless. I want to make sure I help how I can while avoiding making things worse or creating a toxic relationship. 

It doesn't seem like she wants to be treated, as she frequently requested meanspo on her blog, and encouraged fasting. Also from what I can tell, she doesn't seem to be as severe as others I've seen with the disorder. She hasn't fasted around me, and she and I have enjoyed big meals together. However I'm now worried those meals were her binges.

I need whatever advice you all have, please. I care for her and I want to do what I can. Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How long should I wait before working out again? (AN Recovery) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 22:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Question for those who have experience with ED recovery (anorexia to be specific) and working out. Before my ED, I used to be really healthy. Was at a normal BMI, ate lots of healthy food, and used to run! I loved running. It was a great way to destress. But as my ED reared its head, I gave it up because I was too tired and underweight to even walk up a flight of stairs, let alone run a few miles. I think that's when my ED really got out of control; I wasn't able to do things that made me happy, so I turned to restriction.

I'm on the path to recovery, and it's been going well! I'm still underweight, but if I continue this meal plan I should be in a normal range within the next week or two! I've been eating a lot more and I'm eating healthy foods and foods that make me happy. My body dysmorphia is starting to disappear and I'm seeing now that I was truly happy back when I was taking proper care of myself and my body.

I would love to start running again, but my question to everyone is how long should I wait? My doctor says to reach my goal weight first and then we'll go from there. I plan on doing that. But I'd like to hear about everyone's personal experiences with it, since it sounds like there's a lot more going into it than simply reaching a healthy BMI. I never used running as a way to restrict, but I know it could easily become a form of restriction if I'm not careful after reaching my goal weight. But I really like how I felt and how I could zone out, listen to music, and destress. Does anyone have any possible insight? When did you feel comfortable working out again? Any experiences to share? Etc. :) Thank you so much in advance! You guys have been wonderful! 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Need some perspective about possible eating disorder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 03:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to go to the pediatrician who would tell me every year that I was on the edge of being overweight for my height. She told me to exercise more which I generally didn't listen to, but since she, my parents, PE teachers and more subtly from others around me always were kind of pointing to the fact that I needed or would be better if I lost weight.

For a long time, I didn't do anything about it. I didn't really change any of my habits with regards to exercising or eating but since being in college where I don't have parents or teachers looking over me and mandatory family meals or lunch periods to go to, I began to eat twice a day. Now, I'm at a study abroad program where students have to prepare meals for themselves or go out since there isn't a cafeteria and so while I still eat twice a day, I eat kind of small meals. Recently, I've for the first time noticed that if I splurge and eat more when I go out I feel super gross the following day  in ways that I haven't before.

I'm by no means skinny, not super obsessed with my meals or a diet. It kind of just happens that I eat relatively little, but I definitely have lost weight but I don't feel prettier or happier or even healthier like my family or PE teachers/pediatrician suggested I would. I'm wondering if it's worth bringing up with a mental health professional or my GP or I'm just too lazy to feed myself three times a day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I found out a classmate of mine has an eating disorder- what should I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 01:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was changing in the locker room at school and 2 girls next to me were as well. They were having a conversation about food and exercise that was a bit worrisome (one of the girls has struggled with AN in the past), but there was no concrete evidence that they were suffering. Then, one of the girls mentioned that a friend of theirs (let's call her Anna) had told them she was restricting. The number she told them was VERY worrisome to me.

Should I bring this up to a guidance counselor? I'm not very close with Anna, but what I heard gave me cause to be extremely worried. I don't want her to be resentful if she finds out I was the one to tell someone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Do I have an eating disorder or am I making things up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 01:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi everyone I'm a 5'0, 19 year old girl and I've been trying to figure out if I have an eating disorder or not. This might be a bit lengthy but please bear with me! 

I've been overweight for most of my life. My weight struggles began when I was about 8 years old, I would cry while staring at my belly . Ever since then weight has always been a problem, I started purging when I was 15, at the time I thought it was a "genius" idea because I can eat and still lose weight, I would also exercise every. single. day. Everything after that is a bit of a blur because I wouldn't stick to purging but I would also search for other weight loss methods such as calorie counting. One of the most defining moments for me was when I moved to my home country for two months, I was completely alone and I could spend 2 hours in the bathroom purging with no one bothering me, there were also days where I just wouldn't eat. 

Fast forward to January 2016 I went back to living with my parents and of course I gained all the weight back it was so distressing and I wanted to lose weight again and eventually I did. I lost a lot of weight in 3-4 months, first it started out as a "harmless" diet and the weight loss was facilitated by the fact that I was fasting the month of Ramadan, then I went on a vacation to my home country (which I realize is triggering), I was extremely depressed and barely ate or I purged the small amounts of food I ate. I was there for 3 weeks and lost more weight, food caused so much anxiety and my parents were becoming worried. My dad who is a doctor thought I was developing anorexia for a while he even suspected that I was purging he confronted me numerous times including a month ago but I kept denying it. 

After my vacation I started leaning towards veganism, I convinced myself that it was for the environment and my health but I think it has manifested itself into my mentality for example I fear eating foods made with animal products and whenever one of my friends tries to force me to eat I start panicking and purge all the food I eat sometimes even in my university bathrooms. Recently I started experiencing hair loss, my hairline is receding and I always have to unclog the shower, I missed my period for 3 months and although I do get it now I'm losing an abnormal amount of blood and Im thinking I might be anemic especially because I try to eat a very small number of calories a day so I'm definitely not getting my iron requirements. 

Not fitting one category or another of eating disorders is very confusing (could it be EDNOS?) and I'm at a very normal weight for my height so I really dont know what to think, I keep telling myself that I just need to eat more but I can't do it and when I do I find myself purging. I should also add that I never had binging episodes where I ate vary large number of calories, my binges have always been really really small but I still purge right after. 

I'm at a constant war with myself and I keep telling myself that I'm not bad enough, so I would really appreciate any comments, I just need some clarity. Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to fix lack of appetite? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 12:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have dealt with anorexia on and off for about 3 years. I was in therapy for a long time, but I recently moved out of my parents house, to a new city 150 miles away. I thought I was doing well enough dealing with it on my own; I was so motivated for awhile to gain the weight back. But recently I've been slipping.

I want to get better. I know I should be getting better. But I just.. can't? I have no appetite, no motivation, no plan. I'm worried that I want to get better for other people, not myself. That the guy I'm seeing will find me more attractive if I was heavier. But if my mom wasn't nagging me, if my dad hadn't yelled at me, I probably wouldn't have even tried to recover. If I had been left on my own I don't know if I would have tried at all.

My story is so long and complex, I don't know if it's worth writing it all out. I don't think it matters too much right now.

I'm sick of dealing with this. I want to be healthy. But I can't bring myself to eat. My friend has helped me write out meal plans. My therapist suggested setting alarms for when I have to eat. But I can't. I'm never hungry, I have 0 motivation, and I'm worried that I've already caused long term, irreversible damage to my body.

My only idea now is to find some sort of in patient clinic. But I don't think I'm sick enough for something like that. And my family can't afford it, plus, I can just see them getting angry, asking things like "why can't you just eat??" (Which my dad has already said, on several occasions).

Any advice is appreciated. I can provide more background if needed, I just didn't want to end up writing an entire novel. I don't think therapy will help. It honestly didn't help much before. Thanks for reading this far </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I feel alone and need advice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 12:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last winter ive been really sick I'd always throw up and stuff like that then i started viewing eating not pleasing anymore then i started eating less and less, I didnt felt like eating anymore. I'd always almost throw up whenever i eat. I've also had throat surgeries which make it not always pleasant eating. During that winter i've lost so much weight but it wasnt what i wanted. Since then I gained almost the double. I am now overweight slightly , i am complexed about my weight but not to the point i dont want to eat. I live in a little region and my psychiatrist told me there werent much to do and it left me kinda hopeless. When im under stress of depressed I significantly undereat. I've started noting everything i eat to see how much i eat. I always feel faint , dehydrated, i noticed my hair grows really fast and im more hairy than usual ( which complex me much cause ive always been a bit hairy but now this is really bothering me ). I also feel like my face and throat is swollen. So yes i feel alone in all this and I'd love to get in touch with anyone who went that way and kicked eating disorder . I also wonder if i eat enough daily the hair will fall or at least stop growing? Thanks for reading </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I'm unsure what to do at this point. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 00:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been overeating a lot in the past couple of months. More so then I believe I was at any point in my life (I've always been obsessed with food). I want to get help because I'm overweight. I already have a therapist but god knows what she can do to help since I don't think she specializes in eating disorders. The amount I eat when I'm stressed is bare minimum twice what I normally eat, it's especially bad when I have constant access to a kitchen. I don't know who I should be contacting or anything but I need to start somewhere and soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: 'Extreme' hunger during early stages of AN/underweight recovery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 12:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi everyone. I am in the early stages of AN recovery. Went from being morbidly obese to severely underweight in 2+ years time. I got to a healthy point, but then I bounced from one ED to the next. 

Now in the early stages of recovery with a meal plan. I am very underweight, so at first this increase food intake was very hard to do. But now I'm on day 2 and for some reason it doesn't feel like enough? After dinner I became very hungry, and while I didn't completely binge I ate more than the meal plan which used to be hard to meet. I still have a lot of weight to gain so I know it's not necessarily a bad thing at this point, but I'm worried that if I deviate from the meal plan continuously these hunger pangs will turn into binges and I'll end up going back to morbidly obese. 

Help? Advice? Suggestions? Has anyone else experienced this? Should I just go with it? Posting here because it's the weekend and my doctor isn't in til Monday, and wanted to see if this was a normal part of recovery! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Only binge eat sweets. Do I have an eating disorder? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 12:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure if I have an eating disorder or I'm addicted to sweets, but if I have sweets I binge eat them. It's the only thing I binge on. Is there a possibility I have an eating disorder? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Should I just let it go and listen to my real hunger? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 12:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am recovering from a restrictive ED. My dietitian will soon give me a meal plan, but I already know that it won't be enough to make me feel fully satiated.

I am ALWAYS hungry. No matter what, how or when I eat, I'm hungry. I could literally finish whole boxes of cookies, cereals, crackers, pasta, chocolate, or whole loaves of bread, whole cakes, you name it.

The ONLY reason why I don't do it is because I'm still obsessively counting calories and I know that if I did it I would completely panic and feel horribly guilty for days.

But I'd really love to do it, and I'm afraid one day I'll snap and just binge on everything available in the kitchen.

So, should I just let it all go and listen to my hunger without any restriction whatsoever? Would that be useful? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Struggling with trying to eat and gain weight? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 12:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am underweight,i feel like i eat really well,i eat a lot,i force myself to eat, so I can gain some weight. I do sports and I feel weak,i need more force and strength But often,i am really not hungry. And sometimes when I eat,my gag reflex kicks in and i have to spit my food before I throw up. I am struggling to gain weight but it is so hard to me, and I don't know what to do. I gained a little weight by eating a lot,even when I didn't feel like. But i lose it easily. And I can't keep up with this,forcing myself to eat every time to get to a healthy range weight and maintain it. It's not too comfortable.. Sorry for my english..Do you have any advice ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: End insatiable desire to eat sweets; how do I make this go away? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 12:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I chew gum like a chainsmoker to fill desire to eat candy and ice cream etc. If I do not have the gum, I get the strong urge to eat cookies, candy, ice cream, etc. Then I sometimes want to binge. If I'm eating at maintenance or deficit or surplus it's always there. I have been overweight in the past so I do feel this is my previous bodyweight fighting to come back. 

How do I make this go away? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Advice for talking to my wife about her diet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 16:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a teen, my wife went through a period of a few months of excessive food restriction. Since then, her intake has been mostly reasonable, but she still has a tendency towards irrational thoughts about food and overindulging (I don't think it really qualifies as binging) on the weekend.

She's in her early 30s now. For the last few years, she's been lifting weights after I taught her how and gave her a routine. She asked me about diet, but I told her I thought it was best she didn't worry about her diet.

Recently she's gained a few pounds of bodyfat. She's still normal weight, and I think she looks fine, but she is very upset about it. She is repeatedly asking me why she's gaining weight despite her weight training and what she can do about it. Well, the answer isn't complicated: she eats a pretty hefty amount of calories on the weekend, and she would need to bring that down to a reasonable level. I haven't told her that; I've been doing a combination of 1. telling her she looks great and she shouldn't worry about it, and 2. just brushing her off.

So what I'm wondering is, given that her history of disordered eating seems a lot milder than some other people, can I give her a couple suggestions about her diet without risking her blowing it up into some irrational excessively restrictive thing? And if I shouldn't do that, what should I say to her when she gets so upset about her weight gain? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to respond to "How are you so tiny?" and similar comments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone asked me this the other day and I had no idea how to respond, especially since I'm trying to gain weight. I know these are supposed to be positive attributes in today's society, and that these people don't know what's going on, but it does perpetuate the idea that "tiny" is good, and that I shouldn't try to gain weight. How do you respond to these/react to them/ not let them affect your recovery? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Teen Daughter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 03:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 17 year old daughter is in week 4 of a residential program. She restricts as well as purges. She was doing well the first few weeks, but has been severely restricting the past 4 or 5 days. 

She says she feels hopeless and doesn't really want to get well.
She has so much to live for. She is going to the college of her choice in the fall--if she is well enough. What can we do to help her? I appreciate any and all suggestions! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Not sure if I have a problem or not </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 03:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, so I'm currently overweight, and I've been trying to lose weight, but I think I might be having issues with eating properly and not simply dieting. 

I feel very guilty about eating, and can't stand seeing my calorie count, even when it's not that high. This led to short periods of time (a few days) where I skipped out on eating or barely ate even when I felt very hungry out of guilt. Eating a full meal rather than something simple also makes me feel bad, and I'm convinced eating anything that actually makes me feel full will cause me to gain weight.

At the same time, I've also considered making myself throw up several times, and I have made two unsuccessful attempts at it. The urge to make myself throw up is particularly strong after I eat too much, I guess because I see it as a way of "resetting".

Does it sound like I may have a problem? And do you have any advice, if I do have a problem? I've considered telling others, but my father just ignored me when I told him, and I worry that I'm just making a big deal out of nothing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Masters Degree Research study to try and improve treatments for eating and related disorders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 23:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im currently conducting a study for my Masters of Clinical Psychology thesis at the Cairnmillar Institute to try to better understand the relationship between personality, emotions, self-concept, and obsessive and eating behaviours. I'm hoping that the results of this study will help to inform more effective treatments of eating and related disorders in the future. The study is open to participants (no diagnosis needed) aged 18 or above and is completely voluntary and confidential. If you choose to take part, you will be asked to complete questions about demographic information, personality traits, eating behaviours, how you view yourself, and how you cope with distressing emotions. If you are interested in taking part, follow the link below: https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/M735DDV </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I'm unsure if I still have an issue and need advice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 23:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi everyone I think I'm in denial but I also feel like maybe I'm just crazy. I used to have an eating disorder in high school I went on a diet that started as a cleanse (almost entirely fruits and vegetables) Sometimes I'd eat ice cream after dinner but then I'd be mad at myself and sometimes try to throw up. I was also always obsessively excersising The only time I ate healthy was right before a track meet. Yes I know this was totally an eating disorder. I ended up dropping down to my lowest weight possible. I got so many compliments and I loved my body for once. When I stopped eating that poorly I gained a lot of weight. Anywho today I sit a bit overweight and i have been working hard to get off. I track calories with my fitbit and I'm obsessed it it honestly effects my whole mood. If I eat good that day I'm happy and proud of myself if I go over calories I'm sad and anxious and scared to gain weight. If I go out and cant find the calories prior to going out I obsess about what I'm eating. Sometimes I think about throwing up still and sometimes. I think about going back to the way I was because I was never so confident. And then I think stupid shit like if I really had an eating disorder Id be skinny so I must not have one. I don't know how to combat this because I want to continue to lose weight and im afraid if I talk to anyone about it they will tell me not too.

I'm unsure if I still have an issue and need advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Why see a nutritionist/dietician? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 01:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been dealing with disordered eating ever since I was a child and it's been untreated for all these years. I'm now in therapy for some childhood trauma and my eating is more disordered than it has been in a few years (mostly restrictive). My therapist suggested I see a nutritionist/dietician but I just don't know how that will help me.

Does anyone have any advice or experiences they are willing to share? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Unable to decide on food; is this an eating disorder? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 01:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I want to eat or snack, I usually know what I want. Some other food always pops up though, and then I can't decide which to have. Usually one is a hot food and one is cold (like soup vs. cereal, for example.) After I make my decision and eat, I still crave whatever my other option was, even if I'm not hungry... and I still eat it anyway.

I have an obsessive compulsive disorder, so I wonder if this could be somehow connected, but I haven't seen or heard anything about the two possibly being related; it just sort of feels like it does when I need to do something OCD-like. I also have what I consider to be a fairly serious digestive system problem. I take food in, but it doesn't come out. When I'm eating this way, it only makes things worse, especially when I can literally feel food stopping in my stomach because there's a pile up. We still haven't found the cause or even a working treatment.

If this does add up to be a disorder, what kinds of doctors/specialists should I seek out? I know people usually start with their regular family doctor, but that's not an option for me. Are there any articles out there I can read for more help/understanding? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to ask for help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 13:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a doctor's appointment coming up soon so I should hopefully begin to get help that way, and my boyfriend is being so supportive. One thing I'm terrified of, but feel will help, is to ask my brother and sister-in-law for help too. But i don't know how to open up to them about my eating issues or anything.. Any suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Binge Eating Disorder? Need Opinions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 11:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I have always struggled with my relationship with food. Sometimes I eat very normally, and other times I eat barely enough because I'm just not hungry. And other times it's like my stomach never ends and I just want and could eat everything. These eating phases usually last about a week and a half at a time. The part that btohers me is the part where I just feel like I can't stop eating. I often get embarrassed and will eat a lot before my boyfriend gets home or when I am out. I could three plates of dinner if I wanted to. This has been a struggle for me for as long as I can remember. I remember my mom telling my I couldn't eat a whole box of granola bars in one day because people just don't do that. I am not that conscious of my actual body, as I do not look overweight and have a decent figure, however I would like to feel healthy and like I have control over my body for once. 

Do you guys have any tips or tricks for helping me with this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Doctor who can monitor what I am eating? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 01:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel that I have been suffering from restrictive eating for the last couple months and was hopping to ask for help on finding medical help on my diet. I have already taken blood test that didn't show any problems as well as seeing a nutritionist about what a person like me should eat regularly. Except I feel that to recover I need to eat a larger amount then a regular person would have to eat every day. Not to get into too much detail but the last couple weeks I was starting to feel better eating a large amount of calories everyday while feeling upset about weight gain. 

I read an article online  that talked how someone like myself would need to eat a certain minimum to recover. And I was starting to recover until recently as I got better I told myself it would be alright to cut back on the calories which led me to feeling extremely foggy and fatigued today. I feel that I will continue to recover now that I will not cut back on the calories even if I start to feel better but I was hopping to get help on finding some kind of doctor that could help oversee what I am eating. Like a nutritionist who specializes in eating disorder recovery. 

Can anyone suggest how I might find a doctor or other professional to help me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Dislike of spending money slowing recovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 01:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been doing reasonably well with recovery so far on the whole, but I feel as if I'm relapsing in the past few weeks. Going food shopping is one of my biggest triggers. I become overwhelmed by the amount of stuff and the general supermarket environment (though the supermarket I go to is hardly particularly big), get confused and agitated, and I get anxious about the amount of money I need to spend to maintain a healthy, reasonably-filling, vaguely enjoyable diet. 

The thing is that I do, in theory, have enough money for it. While I don't get much - I'm a PhD Student living on grant money - it's perfectly adequate to live comfortably in the part of the country I'm in. What I dislike is the act of spending so much money on something so temporary and fleeting. The act of buying food just to then eat it and it's gone frustrates me, when I'd far rather spend it on something that will bring me much longer happiness and joy (something food gives me very little of, since cooking and eating is a chore to me). I don't eat what I consider a particularly expensive diet. I just feel bad about it regardless.

Does anybody else have any experience with this or any strategies to get over this block? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to handle guilt and anxiety during recovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am recovering from a restrictive ED. My dietitian told me that I am still not gaining weight like I should - well, technically I lost weight in the last two weeks, but it was only a pound so it may very well be a meaningless oscillation - and that I really should allow myself a little bit more food. 

I tried to follow his advice today. I ate a little more. Now I feel like a disgusting fat pig who's just destined to become extremely obese and I am counting over and over again in my head all the calories I took in, thinking how stupid I was, how should I have avoided that food or that other food etc. I am terribly scared and I feel deeply guilty. I'm already thinking about compensating tomorrow, even if I rationally know I shouldn't.

How can I handle such destructive thoughts? How can I relieve my huge, endless stress and just enjoy an abundant meal - which wasn't even that abundant by any normal person's standards, I guess? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Veganism or eating disorder? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend is a proud vegan, and often talks about the environmental and healthy benefits of her diet. However, I'm afraid something else is going on beneath the surface. It's not just that she thinks not eating anything from animals is better for her and the environment, she says she literally couldn't make herself eat anything from animals even if she tried to. It literally disgusts her. When she's in restaurants, she's afraid that someone might add a hint of something non-vegan in her meal or drink, just to mess with her. It would make her feel dirty, and this is what makes me worried. Though she often talks about environmental issues and animal welfare (though only in their relationship to veganism), she is not interested in political discussions about regulating meat farming. She wouldn't care enough to support a bill reducing carbon emissions, or support a farm where animals suffered less. Her main objective is always to not eat anything from animals. For example, she says she don't drink milk because the cows suffer so much, but the only solution she sees is to not drink milk, not to help the cows in any other way. She also shows no interest in other issues involving the environment (like green energy) or animal rights (like the fur and cosmetic industry). Not that she has to care about everything, but her decisions are ALWAYS concluded by whether it's vegan or not, not if it's good for her, animals, or the environment. When she goes on holidays she puts a lot of additional stress on her family, who always has to locate vegan food for her. Still, her family denies any discussions about her veganism (like the one I'm starting here), out of fear of upsetting her. Since she loves to read books, I've been told not to mention that some glues used for bookbindings are produced from horses, fearing she will give up reading altogether. She had a bad concussion a year ago, and is very often moody and exhausted. Which is not uncommon with bad concussions, but I'm not 100% sure it's not something else as well...

 Is my friend a stubborn environmentalist and animal rights activist with a bad concussion, or is there something more sinister at work? If not an eating disorder, maybe some purity complex, or anxiety of losing control? Please help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: experience with facial misperception </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 02:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have AN, actively struggling and doing well (recently hit a healthy weight!), and BN, clean for a few months now. In addition to stomach/chest distortion, it's happened many times that I look at myself in the mirror or see a picture of myself and the facial features are distorted. My nose/chin/forehead look abnormally large, my eyes move position or rotate, my mouth changes shape or gets very wide, things like that. This has sometimes happened at times coinciding with other body image issues and I assume there's a good chance the two are related. 

My therapist says she has never heard of anything like this and I've looked on a lot of websites but to no avail. Does anyone have any experience with this or any clue what it is? Is this still within the effects of an ED? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: The new movie "To The Bone" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 12:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was wondering what anyone thought about the role that Lily Collins has to play in the movie "To The Bone". She had struggled with anorexia about ten years ago, but did this movie to spread awareness. However, she had to lose a bunch of weight again to play the role. I was wondering if anyone thinks this is very dangerous, as there is such a fine line between relapsing and being healthy? And what does anyone think about the movie? thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I need help getting a healthy relationship with food </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 12:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> During my entire childhood, I was heavily medicated. I have ADHD and the medicine was incredibly appetite suppressing.  I was very underweight up until I was around 11. I went off my medication, and gained a lot of weight over a year from both comfort-eating and general over-eating. When I turned thirteen, I was overweight. I moved schools and began dieting. I lost weight very quickly on simple calorie restriction, which spiralled into an eating disorder. I'm underweight(slightly) as I type this, and I'm really damn tired of this. I want my life back. There's people that make me happy, and I think this is my final attempt at getting myself back together. I want to cooperate, I want to be healthy, I want to do sports, and I want to eat a scoop of ice cream without wanting to hurt myself. I'm sick of calories. I'm so fucking sick of calories.. 

However, binge-eating is normalized in my family. Both my parents are overweight(my dad just slightly, and my mom is morbidly obese). 
 
My mom has been weight-cycling, since she was thirteen. Every month, she'll go on a low carb, low-fat incredibly restricted diet, and about 5 weeks in, she'll break and binge eat. I suspect that she has bulimia, because I keep finding little chunks of vomit in the toilet. 

My dad wants me to focus on gaining weight, and I know he's doing it from a place of love, but I don't want to start shoving down large amounts of food again. He tells me that I won't be normal or 'old-me' again, before I can finish a large amount in one sitting. 

All I want is to be a normal girl. I understand that I'm underweight and I understand that it's unhealthy, but I just really want to focus on getting my food habits in order. 
TL;DR

How much is a portion for a fourteen year old girl? How much veg, meat, starch etc. should be in a portion? How much candy is a normal portion? 

How do I stop counting calories? I know the calories of close to every food, so it's not like I can just avoid, those I can estimate. How do I make sure I'm getting in enough food without counting calories?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How do I regain a healthy relationship with food? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 16:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit. I had a confronting conversation with my boyfriend yesterday that made me realize I have a distorted relationship with food. I have recently lost a substantial amount of weight, and I'm very close to my goal weight.

I had a falling out with my boyfriend recently because the upcoming month is full of birthdays and dinners, which means a LOT of eating. I usually restrict my meals and make sure to only eat what I deem diet-appropriate and therefore this has caused me major stress.

The birthdays and dinner parties are completely overshadowed by the impending doom that is eating and although I AM going to try and just join the celebrations and not stick with the low-calorie option while everyone else is ordering typical celebration food, this is already ruining my days a month in advance. I told my boyfriend I wanted to schedule some days of eating low-calorie dinners, to balance out the bad days, which he agreed to, but also acknowledged I had a lot of emotion about "having to eat bad stuff" and that I am absolutely dreading these days. He expressed his concern about my 'obsession' with food and I have to admit he is right. I really have to force myself not to stand on the scale every day (I'm most happy doing it every morning and every evening) just to keep track of my goal and go to bed feeling bad about myself if I've gained weight compared to the day before (which I rationally KNOW is not a healthy nor reliable way to measure... yet I just can't help needing that control). 

On one hand I think I'm doing this the right way since, on the other hand this is bringing up really strong emotions in me while I could also be like "hey, I'll enjoy myself now and will just pick my diet back up afterwards and get there, albeit somewhat later" - Rationally I know this, but there's this pressing feeling of guilt when I eat I can't get rid of.

Any tips? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How long does it take for the esophagus to heal after BN? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 16:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've have BN for about 20 years on and off.  (Mostly on.)  The worst was when I was barfing multiple times a day for over a year.  I started having some pain so I had it scoped and the doctor acted like it was a horror show.  I've got lots of ulcering and scarring.  I've stopped cold turkey and it's been about six months.  I went back for the follow up and the doctor said it didn't look any better.   I'm curious how long something like this might take to improve considering I've stopped completely.  I haven't told my doctor about the BN, but I think he might suspect because he keeps saying he can't see how my throat and esophagus can look so bad just from acid reflux.  

So should I be seeing improvements by now?  If so then what could be keeping it from healing considering I've stopped?  Is the time table for something like this years rather than months? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Dealing with guilt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 16:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know I have a problem but I don't do anything about it because I'm scared of gaining weight and being fat. When I eat, I feel guilty and depressed but when I don't eat, I feel okay for a while but tell myself later on, "this is wrong" I look in the mirror and ask, "What the hell did you do to yourself?" as I see fat in places then decide to fast (That usually doesn't last long) but yeah, you get what i'm saying. it's just a cycle of that and I'm tired.

How do I get over my fear of gaining weight and how do I get out of my cycle of fasting, binging and extreme guilt? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Could this be considered an eating disorder? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 00:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been talking to a girl for the last month and she brought up her concern that I may have an eating disorder. 
I'm not a tall guy, I'm around 5'6. Since Christmas, I've lost a lot of weight.
 
I used to have problems with self mutilation. I stopped cutting but wouldn't eat when I felt hungry because I felt for some reason that I deserved to feel that pain. 

My problem is that I don't get hungry very often but when I do, I'll typically smoke a cigarette or drink caffeine to curb the hunger. I recently figured out that I do this as a means of control. I work 40 hours a week at a job I despise so in some weird way, I feel like deciding when I eat, I have some form of control over something. 

Could this possibly be an eating disorder? If so, how would you describe it? Has anyone else gone through this, and if so, how did you shake it? I'd be eternally grateful for any help or advice you could offer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Health Insurance and Eating Disorders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 00:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello! 

I have a request. 

So my wife has completed in patient therapy and is recovering very well and I am so happy and proud of her. She is sticking to her meal plans, sticking to therapy and requests from her nutritionist. 

Currently, we have been paying for all of our services out of pocket and it is really starting to take a toll. (Was an independent contractor for a while.) But recently I have received a new job and will have health insurance provided. And I really really want to keep my wife on the right path. 

My question in general: Does Health Insurance cover ED therapy? Or is this different between Health insurance providers? 

And to go deeper, what do I sign up for? Do HMO's cover mental health therapy? Should I go with a PPO? Etc. Etc.

Anybody with any experience in the matter would be very helpful.
Thank you very much!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Do I have it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 21:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've been thinking and I wonder if I have an eating disorder or not. I might go a whole day sometime without me eating. And I always think it is Because I am lazy. But sometimes I think to myself you are getting bigger maybe I should skip lunch? That's what one part of me thinks, but the other one is thinking. What are you doing? Don't starve yourself you are better than this. So maybe I don't have an eating disorder. Maybe I am just bad at eating. I really don't know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My wife needs inpatient treatment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 21:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I [31 M] need help. My wife [28 F] has BN, and it has gotten much worse over the past few years. She ended up in an inpatient facility a few years ago but had to leave early due to insurance reasons. Now the ED is worse than ever. She needs inpatient treatment. The problem is we are broke, she's in grad school, I work full time and take night classes twice a week, and we have a young son. We can't afford the treatment, can't afford the additional child care, and really can't stop school, I know we actually can, but we both ended up squandering early education attempts and need to lift ourselves out of this rut. What can we do? I've tried to help as much as I can but I'm just a guy with no experience or qualifications to help her, I'm as supportive as I can be. She now ends up binging and purging late at night and then needing to sleep all morning, has developed an ulcer that periodically puts her out of commission. She had me put a lock on the cupboard that has trigger foods along with her wallet and keys, but if I forget it gets raided. Food we buy disappears, and it is costly. I just feel lost, I basically know in order for her to have a chance of recovery she needs to go somewhere, but it would be devastating to our already terrible finances and life prospects. She has tried almost everything, we're not new to recovery attempts, information, strategies, and the like. We are at a loss and I'm begging for something. 

Does anyone have any advice on how to get her the help she needs?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How do I convince myself to eat more? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 21:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm recovering from anorexia and am at a point where my calories are up but I'm over exercising as a way of coping with my anxiety. As a result, I need to eat more, because I'm still losing and need to gain. But it's a lot harder/stressful than I thought it was going to be and I keep trying to talk myself out of it.

Does anyone have any suggestions on how to get over this hurdle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Advice on managing anxiety, exercise and ED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 21:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! 

I'm about 3 years into recovery, and its generally been really successful. However, recently a load of anxiety has flared up completely seperately to ED stuff - triggered by general worries aboot graduating college and what to do with adulthood etc etc. 
To help combat the anxiety I've been advised to exercise more and it does seem to be helping BUT I can feel myself slipping back into old habits of control and perfectionism. 

Basically, how do you manage to deal with seperate issues, which need different treatments, without negatively impacting everything? 

Thanks x  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to handle intrusive thoughts during recovery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 02:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi,

I am recovering from a restrictive ED and I feel like I could eat a mountain. My dietitian says it's my brain basically rebeling against all my past restrictions and craving all the delicious foods it had to live so long without.

Thus, in an exceptionally "brave" moment, I called a friend and asked her to meet for a pizza dinner next Friday. She said yeah, why not?

But right now I feel horrible. That voice inside me is screaming "how could you? You're such an idiot! Pizza is gonna make you obese and you should totally cancel the dinner! Why are you such a fat pig? Why can't you eat like a normal person?". I was actually thinking about calling my friend on Friday afternoon and telling her that I'm sick or something like that.

How should I handle this kind of thoughts? I know it's just my ED refusing to go away, but it's scary and I can't completely think rationally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Academic Research request for survey participants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 12:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> STUDY ADVERTISEMENT

Our research team at Florida State University is currently conducting a study on risk factors for suicidal thoughts and behaviors. The primary goal of the study is to better understand what thoughts, feelings, and experiences motivate suicidal thoughts and behaviors.
We are interested in recruiting people who use this website to participate in our research study. Participation is completely voluntary. If you are interested in participating, you will complete an online screener to see if you qualify to participate. If you qualify, you will complete a variety of questionnaires online.
The study will involve four online assessments over the next month that should take about 40-50min to complete and you will be compensated up to $70 in online gift cards to Amazon. A few important things to know about the study are:

1. The study includes questions and images regarding self-harm, suicide, and other unpleasant images. We strongly emphasize that some of the images included are extremely graphic suicide-related images. Some people may feel that these images are very disturbing and may find them to be triggering.

2. All information collected will be kept anonymous.

3. Participation is completely voluntary.

4. The link we provide will send you to a website telling you about the study. Once on that site, you can decide whether or not you want to participate.

5. If you start to participate and decide you no longer feel comfortable or you are no longer interested, you can stop at any time.

6. We will provide links to treatment resources throughout the study.

7. This study will include only participants who are 18 years and older.

Please send us a private message at /u/risklabfsu if you are interested in participating. Once you contact us, we will send you a link to the screening questionnaire to see if you qualify and to tell you more about the study.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Besides therapy/meds, what helped you recover from les less obvious aspects of your eating disorder? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 12:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Other than therapy/counseling/medication, what has helped your eating disorder recovery espeically with aspects not directly connected to the eating part of the eating disorder like anxiety and depression? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I need some advice.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 12:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a 20 year old guy, which admittedly already makes me feel alienated from all this. 99% of things related to EDs is geared towards women. I guess I feel a little invalid? I dunno.

Anyway, I've always felt guilty for eating and starved myself on occasion out of self hatred. I worry constantly about my weight and appearance and no matter how much I hear otherwise I feel fat and ugly. I literally feel like the ugliest person on earth

Recently I started dieting and working out every day. I've been severely restricting the calories I eat every day, and the lower I get the number the better I feel. I threw out my back and I kept working out because I want to be skinny so badly. In the past week I've lost 12 pounds

The thing is, I feel like...I'm overweight, and feel so fat  that this is what I deserve. I don't deserve to eat. I have to hurry up and slim down if I ever wanna have any value or have others not be disgusted by me. I don't care about my health, I just want to not hate my appearance anymore

Logically I know this isn't healthy. I recognize this is becoming a problem. But I feel like I don't "count" as having a real problem because I don't eat even fewer calories and because im a guy. Like if I truly had an eating disorder I would be skinnier and eating even fewer calories a day

This is the first I've really opened up about this, and I guess... I just really would like to hear from some people who understand and get advice on what to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Online research study re-post </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 14:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The investigators have asked us to repost this in hope of finding additional participants before the Feb 15 deadline for this study.

You are Invited to Participate in an Online Research Study California State University San Marcos Scale Validation Survey (IRB Code Number: 893513-1) 

A new scale is being developed for people with various psychiatric diagnoses. The purpose of this online study is to test the validity of the scale among people from diverse backgrounds. It is hoped that this work will lead to further research and potential clinical applications. This online survey will involve completing a series of questions for approximately 25 to 45 minutes.

You must be at least 18 years old, fluent in English, a resident of the United States, and diagnosed with a psychiatric disorder to participate. You are not eligible to participate if you participated in our recent interview study. 

To participate in this online research study, please visit:

https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/redditc

To learn more about this research study, please contact the researcher, Stephanie Price (price049@cougars.csusm.edu), or the advisor, Dr. Heike Mahler (hmahler@csusm.edu). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My Girlfriend [19] wants to quit treatment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 14:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello i desperately need your advice!

**Prologue:**

When I met my girlfriend, about a year ago, she was fresh out of treatment center. She was doing great and we had an awesome relationship throughout the summer. However when she went away to college (4 hours from home) her Anorexia completely took over. Long story short she was hospitalized for few weeks in November(extremely underweight).

**Main:**

She has been in Monte Nido Rainrock for past month. Unfortunately she is not doing very well. She is extremely homesick(her family and I live on the opposite coast so visiting is not much of an option), she claims that she hates it there, that they don't help her, that they make her fat, and that she is ready for the next step. I understand that this is typical ED behavior, however today she signed papers so that she can discharge herself in two weeks. She says that she is going to continue treatment outside the treatment center. The main problem is that her mother, a doctor, has been dealing with her anorexia for past 4 years and at this point she refuses to take her home unless she completes treatment. My girlfriend says that she will discharge anyways and will go to shelter. I'm not completely sure if she's bluffing or if she'll actually do it.

Today she asked me if she can live at my house for a while. I said that she can but only if clinical director confirms that she's medically stable and is ready for the next step. 

**Question:**

I know for a fact that she's discharging against medical advice. Do you think she Is actually ready to discharge, or is it ED talking? Should I keep convincing her to stay? And if yes, then how can I motivate her to stay in treatment center? 

I love her, and to be honest I am worried that she will build resentment towards me if i keep convincing her to stay there.

Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I [17m]need advice on how to help my friend [16f]with her eating disorder and where to find her professional help. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 10:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks to anyone who answers in advance, and sorry for my english as it's not my first language.

Today my girl-friend bought pills to stop her hunger, in order to get thinner. It broke my heart. She is clearly not overweight and she already told me before about how she keeps counting calories in her head, throwing up after some meals, etc. She is clearly struggling with an eating disorder. After talking to her on the phone for a while she agreed to show up if I come with her to a doctor's appointment, or a psychiatrist or whatever she needs. She has a difficult relationship with her parents and so do I, so she's only going to work with me if we keep it a secret from them, she's ashamed of her problem. Since I am the only one she tells this to, I feel obligated to find her help and do something with this, as I've lost a friend to anorexia when I was younger and it's not going to happen again.

What can I do to help her with this? Where do I find professional help? I feel obligated to find her help but I am overwhelmed by this task since I have no idea where to start. We live in The Netherlands.

Thanks reddit! 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Is it possible to go back to eating intuitively after a restrictive ED? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 10:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to have a certain weight that I was naturally able to maintain without ever counting calories and feeling excessive hunger or fullness. 

Now that I am recovering from a restrictive ED I am truly afraid that I have definitively f*cked up my "natural regulation system" and that I'll need to count calories and just be really careful in order not to gain weight fast, because my body won't ever be able to regulate anymore and find its balance like it used to. It's a fact that, right now, if I had to follow my hunger cues I would eat just about everything and gain weight.

Do you have any relevant experience on the matter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to handle the stress of school and social anxiety without relapsing?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 03:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi. I'm a freshman in college, recovering from AN-b/p. My first semester did not go very well...the stress from a heavier workload was rough on me. I also have social anxiety, and I kept myself isolated out of terror, resulting in the fact that I currently have zero friends at school. I want desperately to connect with people, but the loneliness makes me so depressed, and all I want to do is make myself numb to cope. So I spiralled back into the cycle of restricting, bingeing, and purging. 

Over winter break, I've managed to pull myself out of it and I've been doing significantly better. But school starts again next week and I am so scared that I will spiral again once I go back to the stress and the loneliness and isolation. My anxiety over this is increasing daily, to the point where I've been unable to sleep the past few nights. My eating is getting more erratic with the stress and I spent the morning scouring my parents' house for laxatives in a fit of desperation. I feel helpless in the face of my disorder, and I feel like relapse is just inevitable at this point and I will never be able to make anything of myself or handle the pressures of the real world.

 I'm sorry for the rant--I just really need some support, advice, virtual hugs, anything really. Thank you so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How do i get myself back out of this mess? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 03:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, so i have an eating disorder that is mostly under control. I don't really know if the eating disorder is linked to my depression or that it's something on its own. I've never been overweight, but i've always been a bit too preoccupied about my weight (loads to do with my family and upbringing). I got depressed for the first time during my teen years and when i'm depressed i hardly eat because it takes a lot of energy and i don't feel hungry or forget. Between my episodes i've gained a bit of weight but, not excessive and i was feeling a lot better for almost three years. Now i've been struggling a bit again on and off for a year, but i'm getting better at recognizing the signs of me falling into depression so i've not hit rock bottom.

Now, i've had a very good past four-fiveish months. I'm spending a lot of time with friend, going out, traveling, sleeping good (so not feeling tired all the time), etc. so i've gained weight. More than i've ever had. So for about a month i've been struggling a lot with my self-esteem (plus i hate the holiday-period because it makes me kind of sad). I've tried working out more (i used to go to track   field class twice a week when i was still studying), i'm eating healthier, etc. but its been difficult since i'm not often eating/drinking alone like i used to. My friend will think i'm stupid for focusing on this much. They know that i'm trying to eat healthier, but watching everything i eat will be weird for them. 

Now, with new years parties i've come into contact with cocaine again, with which i don't have the best history either. I've had the "grand" idea last week to buy some cocaine to help me not wanting to eat. So i've realized this is just all kinds of fucked up. I've got myself out of that drug-dependency before so that not the biggest issue. It's mostly that i don't want my drug-problem affecting my problems with body image, or them being intertwined. 

Does anybody have a similar story or somebody that can relate to this? I think i mostly want to talk about it and maybe get some extra tips to get me "started" again. 

Thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unheard of ED - Intermittently selective but not picky </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 17:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am concerned about a friend who's 23. She's had this strange disorder since high school and wasn't always picky. Here are some details:

* She's not very picky.
* She feels extremely sick when thinking about eating certain foods intermittently. (For example: She likes food X. If she's not in the mood for food X, and she tries to eat it, she feels like throwing up)
* If she eats the same thing daily, that food will begin to repulse her very quickly.
* Certain bland foods leave an awful aftertaste.
* It all depends on what her body wants.
* Water can have this effect as well.
* She has to eat frequently to avoid "hunger headaches".
* Sometimes all food can be repulsive to her, so she has to choke down a vitamin boost shake. (The kind they give to cancer patients)

Is this weird, or has anyone seen this before? Doctors haven't been able to diagnose her problem. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I think I have an eating disorder but I'm not sure! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 00:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the past ~1.5 years I've had issues with eating. I would get stressed and binge eat (usually candy) to the point that it made me feel sick, and sometimes to the point of physically vomiting. This has progressed to the point where I will overeat at meals, and then vomit afterwards. I don't even feel any nausea anymore, I don't MAKE myself vomit, I just sort of calmly walk into the bathroom, sit in front of the toilet, and vomit. No retching, no contracting of the stomach muscles, nothing like that, the food just comes up. And it doesn't really feel like when I have the flu, it doesn't taste acidic at all and I don't feel sick afterwards. 

I'm trying to not overeat, but I sort of feel like if I eat ANYTHING lately, I have the urge to vomit afterwards. The weird thing is that I can control it too, like if I am out at a restaurant I might gag a little after eating, but not really noticeably (or at least I hide it from people), but I can wait like 30 minutes or however long it takes to get home before I vomit. It's like I don't even need to vomit but then as soon as I get to the bathroom I'll realize, okay I can vomit now, and I just do it. It's more like using the washroom than it is like vomiting, I can hold it for a while if I'm out in public or whatever.

I don't really know if this makes sense or what. Objectively I'm not overweight but I have gained a lot of weight over the past few years so I do feel fat, and because of that I'm not really STOPPING myself from vomiting, and honestly I'm not really sure if I could if I tried to. I'm just confused because I'm not sick, and I'm not forcing myself to vomit, but I do vomit after every meal. 

Has anyone ever experienced something like this? Does anyone have advice for me? 

Sorry if this is confusing, I'm really confused about it myself to be honest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request : Anybody knows how to deal with constant hunger? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 00:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've decided to be healthy and logged my food. It's been about 2 months and I constantly been overthinking about food. I can't think of anything else. Every time I go to school or work, or even just on my way, I think of food. I thought it was just because I wanted to eat for fun and I am just planning everything else but I feel like it is becoming very unhealthy to constantly eat. I don't eat unhealthy, however, I think it's unhealthy to eat like every 30 minutes a full meal. I can't afford therapy or anything. I've tried diet pills but I'm replacing it with green tea but I still binge on almost anything on my hands </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Coping with medically-required weight gain on your own. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 00:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am currently trying to recover from anorexia binge/purge subtype. One of my main goals is to gain back enough weight to menstruate again. 

Every time I eat anything over my BMR, my body dysmorphia and anxiety shoots through the roof. My legs feel like stretched sausage casings and my stomach seems to dig into my waistband. I know its impossible, but the sensation of my body bloating up is completely overwhelming. I keep attempting meals and purging them in a panic later. Plus, the urge to self-harm is pounding in my head. 

On a deeper level, I am terrified of losing the battle with food due to my experience with binging and weight gain from EDNOS. The sensation of actually gaining and outgrowing my clothes was so distressing that I felt suicidal at times. Id equate it to a PTSD-like sensation (not to minimize true PTSD, but it was a severely painful time). 

I am also not weighing myself, which further contributes to this feeling of being out of control. 

Any experience or advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I have a problem with eating and weight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 00:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a 20yo male. I am underweight. I know it. I don't wish to be "skinny". 

Firstly, I am never hungry. I don't get hungry - I eat and don't feel anything besides from getting to the point which I can't eat anymore. 

Secondly, said point is reached extremely quickly, such that I am never eating much when I do eat. I simply can't eat past that point. I eat around twice a day. 

Lastly, while I am eating, the food feels physically strange going down my throat - I am constantly focusing on it. Occasionally, and on every couple of (small) bites, I feel like I am about to vomit or gag. Then I have to stop eating for a long time. Every few bites. I rarely (monthly or greater) vomit - but I always feel as if I am on the verge of it. I hate this. 

What can I do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: why should I get better? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 00:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I struggled with anorexia nervosa for a few years and I was able to regain the weight with the help of treatment. I still lack a healthy relationship with food and cannot find the motivation to try to get better. I am reaching out now because although I have been seeing a therapist and a psychiatrist for a few years, I, with the help of someone who I want to develop a genuine and loving relationship with, have realized that I do not want to get better. Aside from this person being a motivation, I cannot get myself to try fear foods. Food is such a significant part of our lives, especially in my culture, and I know I don't want to be obsessed with nutrition labels forever and I want to enjoy the people and experiences in my life without obsessing over food and exercise. I will be participating in an intensive outpatient program very soon and I feel that I am doing all the "right" things to get better but, deep down inside, I don't think I want to change my obsessive behaviors. 

How do I find motivation to get better? Why should I continue with treatment?

 My family has adapted to my behaviors but the guy I really like acknowledged that this isn't normal. His heart is truly in the right place and I appreciate his concern and his support in getting better but, as he said, he can't want this more than I want it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I can't stop eating </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 00:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tend to eat because of stress or boredom, but even when I'm eating normal things like a meal, I feel absolutely sick after I'm done. I feel like I'm full and fat and am going to break out. However, none of this deters me, and I find myself overeating quite often. I even find that if I make an effort to not snack, it comes back twice (ex. I decide to have a smaller lunch, so I eat 10 granola bars before a huge unhealthy dinner to compensate)

How do I stop doing this? Any ideas on how to control my mindset when thinking about food?
I'm a female at a pretty healthy/low weight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: how to tell between BED and "normal" overeating post-restriction? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 12:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

I am unhealthily underweight and since mid-December I'm trying to recover. During Christmas I gained a bit by massively overeating. Today I weighed myself again and I discovered I had not gained weight in the last week, so I decided I was "free" to eat whatever I want - since my house is now full of all sorts of unhealthy but ridiculously delicious sweets and candies I basically ate during breakfast more than what I ate all yesterday, and most of it was sugars and saturated fats.

I don't know if it qualifies as "binging", since it didn't happen compulsively and in solitude. I just sat there, in front of everyone, and ate and ate and ate. Now I feel ashamed and scared.

I'm already seeing a therapist for my problem and will soon also meet a dietitian, but what I'd like to know is: what is binge-eating and what is my starving body just desperately trying to ingest more calories? I'm terrified of falling from borderline anorexia into a full-blown BED.

Thank you in advance for any reply!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
