<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6210</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 22:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I've been in therapy and on meds for a long time, but depression will most likely be a life long problem for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 22:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I've been in therapy for over 5 years and tried a bunch of different meds, but nothing really helps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 22:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been trying to treat my depression for over 5 years now, meds, therapy, all that fun stuff. But it will most likely be a life long problem for me. I really hate mental illness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think I'm relapsing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 20:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello,
I think I'm relapsing back into my anorexia after going into treatment in February. I've started missing meals and snacks this week and the meals I do eat are much smaller than they should be. 

I thought that I would be happier being healthy, but I'm not, I'm still miserable and depressed. 

I just can't decide if I should keep trying to eat healthy and push down the urges or if I should just let myself slip back into my anorexia. I hate this, I just want to die and leave a pretty, skinny corpse. 

Ignore my stats, those were before going into treatment. I have no idea what I weigh now, but I'm above 130lbs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't know if I can recover... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 04:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 8 weeks ago I went into inpatient treatment and I started group therapy 5 weeks ago. But I don't know if I can recover. I'm eating everything I should be, everyone says that I'm doing great. But I feel horrible, my depression is really bad, I'm selfharming and I've gotten so big. I'm the biggest I've ever been in my life. My suicidal thoughts are through the roof, and starving myself is the only way I'm brave enough to kill myself. I was so close to being perfect and dead.

I don't know if I can do this anymore, but everyone would be so disappointed with me if I stopped. I just don't know what to do anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 22:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put a heating pad on your stomach, it helps with the bloating and pain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 02:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in a treatment program right now, but I'm debating if I should stay. I know I should at least give it a try, but the ed voice won't shut up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 15:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't really lefted. I just stopped posting because I'm trying to recover, but I'm checking the sub everyday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 00:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drink warm water, cold water makes you feel hungrier </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 20:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, it's been really rough. I miss you guys but I feel like I shouldn't participate because I'm trying to recover </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 14:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I am, but I still check the sub everyday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 03:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We know it isn't healthy. But it's for people who aren't ready to recover and need a place to vent or talk about the struggles of this illness with people who won't force them to recover and who will understand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 20:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a super accepting community! Everyone is welcome there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 19:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/proed has one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> inpatient update: one week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 01:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been in inpatient for a week now. I thought I'd post an update because I'm super bored and having a really rough day.

I've been feeling really depressed since I've been here, but especially today. My selfharm and suicidal thoughts are through the roof and the ed voice won't fucking shut up. 

Most meals have been ok, typical hospital food. But I had a breakdown over a sandwich the other day. I just started bawling my eyes out because I hate sandwiches, especially egg salad. 

Today was med review, I got 2 15 minute passes a day to go smoke which is awesome. But they also said that my bmi is almost 16, that puts me at around 100lbs. I feel so fucking fat. All I hear in my head is how fat, disgusting and a failure I am. I've gained faster than they thought I would, so I'll probably start group therapy on Monday. 

I just want to lose this weight. I feel disgusting and horrible and fat. I hate myself, but I know I should try recovery, but I just want to go home and starve myself. 

I'm on a general psychiatric unit. Most people here are nice. There's this one guy who is such an asshole, everyone hates him! 

Sorry, this turned into a really long post, I just feel so lonely

Edit: And my roommate is so thin. She is so triggering.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 14:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just had my first night in ip. It's really strange here, but everyone seems really nice. I'm definitely the fattest one here though, which is really upsetting. Plus I can't go for cigarettes for a while and that is really stressing me out. My first meal is in a few minutes and I'm really scared </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thank you and goodbye </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 00:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I finally got the call to go into inpatient treatment. I have to be at the hospital in an hour and a half. I'm anxious, scared but excited. This is a new chapter in my life, but I hope it all works out.

I just wanted to thank all of you lovely people. You have all be so nice and supportive through this incredibly rough part of my life. I'm so glad that I found you guys, but it's my time to leave. 

I really hope that each and every one of you reach your UGWs and find your happiness. You all deserve it. You are all beautiful people, inside and out! 

Thank you and goodbye!

Edit: oh god, I'm the fattest one here :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 21:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Purging is a really horrible habit to get into, it's super addictive and harmful. It usually leads to weight gain because you think you can have bigger binges, but you still end up only purging 50% of your cals and you absorb so much more because of your now bigger binges. But if you really want, you can pm me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 20:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a friend who told a bunch of people at school, the school counselor and my mom when I was 14. But my mom denies that she was told, so I don't know if she actually told my mom. But she definitely told people at school </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suggestion for a weekly thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 19:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that a weekly (or monthly) thread for health/harm-reduction/beauty tips would be good. What we do really takes a toll on our bodies and if we had a thread where people could ask advice on harm reduction and beauty tips could be really helpful. That way we can help each other stay as healthy and beautiful as possible.

I know I've had problems with some things but I didn't want to start a new thread for it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 17:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have 3 rabbits, a cat, an elephant and a sloth. Plus I bought them as gifts for so many people. They are so soft and such good quality </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 16:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always make sure to plan my binges so the flavours will go together when I purge, so I usually end up with a sweet binge and a savoury binge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 16:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg, that's a jellycat stuffed rabbit! I have so many of those stuffed animals. They sold them at my old job so I would always buy some when we got a new shipment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 16:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI, you can still get pregnant if you don't have your period </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 06:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but I take sleeping pills every night </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 04:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have "recovered" and relapsed so many times I can't even count anymore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 04:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely flushed about 40$ worth of food down the toilet in the last 24 hours. I can't afford to throw all my money away. Thanks, good luck to you too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 04:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw that, I had no advice to give you. Binging and purging is an unhealthy, disgusting and wasteful habit, but so addictive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My plan to stop binging and purging </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 03:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been binging and purging way too much lately, I have gained  lbs in 2 months and I feel absolutely disgusting. Seeing that number made me want to throw up. So I've made a plan to stop. I'm posting this here for accountability. I feel like I've made so many of these posts though, but here we go again.

I b/p'ed multiple times today. I had a big dinner which I didn't purge, I feel pretty guilty about that, but I need to stop purging.

I will eat around 800 calories for the next few days. Then on saturday I'm having lunch with my mom for her birthday, I will order a BLT. Then starting on sunday I will restrict to 600 calories for a few days. After that I will return to my usual 400 calories a day.

I also plan to read a chapter of my book or work on my jigsaw puzzle every time I have an urge to binge.

I really hope this works because I don't think I can handle to go down this road again. B/p really takes a toll on my mental and physical health. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 19:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god no, my life is hell. I've been doing the same thing everyday for almost 2 months now. I miss my old life. I'm reading the Harry Potter books, but I'm not getting much reading done because my concentration is shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 17:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wake up at around 9 am. Go for a cigarette, then I have breakfast and check social media. I watch some tv, have more cigarettes. I have lunch and watch more tv. Then in the afternoon I either watch tv, knit, work on a jigsaw puzzle or read. Have more cigarettes and some diet coke. Then my mom comes home from work and we have dinner. After we walk our dog. We watch some tv or a movie together. Then it's bed time, I get ready for bed at around 10:30. 

Some days I have doctors appointments.

My life is incredibly boring </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 03:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Companies can say something is 0 cals if it has less than 5 calories per serving </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 02:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have any experience with this, but I have a few trans friends. When you go on HRT it's like going through puberty again, and that takes a lot of energy! So it would make sense that it would make you hungrier.

I hope you all the best in your transition! Congrats </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 01:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know how you feel, I spend my days moping around the house, which leads to binging and purging. I have no motivation to do anything but watch tv and b/p. It really sucks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 19:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are weighing yourself multiple times a day, then it will fluctuate because of food or water weight. It's best to only weigh yourself once a day, at the same time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 02:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely love fldebolle, but it's not available where I live. I would probably get so fat if I had access to them everyday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 02:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Chocolate chia pudding (143)

Lunch: Egg whites (60), celery (6), red bell pepper (11) and cucumber (8)

Dinner: Shirataki noodles with vegetable bouillon and soya sauce (26)

Snacks: Vanilla greek yogurt (140), sugar free lemon jello (20), diet coke (0) and mia sport (0)

Total: 414 calories

I left my house for other than cigarettes, food or doctors appointment for the first time in months. I was out of the house 5 and half hours. I am completely drained, I have absolutely no energy left. I really want to eat a jar of peanut butter right now. But I don't have any. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 02:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could definitely go for a jar of peanut butter right now, thank god I don't have any or else it would turn into a crazy binge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 01:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plus you don't even lose weight, most of the time you gain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 17:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to stay under 500 calories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 16:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely binging and purging. It fucks your teeth, electrolytes and organs wayyyyy more than restricting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 06:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't binged and purged in 2 days. I'm hoping that I'm back in the restricting groove </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 04:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my biggest fear! I'm also terrified that they will give me regular coke instead of diet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 02:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cocoa (147)

Lunch: Egg whites (60), celery (6), red bell pepper (11) and cucumber (8)

Dinner: Shirataki noodles with vegetable bouillon and soya sauce (26)

Snacks: Sugar free lemon jello (20), chia pudding (142), diet coke (0), diet 7up (0) and mio spor (0)

Total: 421 calories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 23:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to drink diet soda or vitamin water zero. It's also good to have a bunch of low cal snacks ready, that way you can eat a bunch but not go over your calorie goals. You can save your meals for after you've smoked. 

For me I just avoid eating anything or else the floodgates open and I eat everything, but if I don't eat then I'm fine. Plus eating shortens the high </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 19:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is amazing! You definitely deserve to be happy and to celebrate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 03:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cocoa (147)

Lunch: Shirataki noodles with vegetable bouillon and soya sauce (26)

Dinner: Shirataki noodles with vegetable broth and soya sauce (26)

Snacks: Sugar free lemon jello (20), vanilla greek yogurt (140), diet coke (0), diet 7up (0) and mio sport (0)

Total: 359 calories

I have a bad cold right now, so I'm having lots of soup and diet 7up. I'm hoping this will help me get back into the restriction groove. 

I still have a bit of leftover birthday cake, I've been pretty good at resisting the urges to b/p it, hopefully I will keep staying strong. My mom also said that she will stop buying peanut butter because she knows I will b/p a whole jar in a day.

I need to get back into my groove </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 17:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it can raise your BMR at least 200 calories, probably more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 20:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love sweet potatoes, but without a food scale I can't know the calorie count, so I just avoid them. I wish I could have some </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 19:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your metabolism speeds up when you are on your period </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 18:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's non-perishable you could bring it to your local food bank </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 18:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not when I'm restricting. But I've been wasting so much money on food so I can binge and purge. Spent over 30$ on food yesterday and it all ended up in the toilet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 18:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The closer I get to going into treatment, the more I freak out about weight gain. They want me to have a bmi of at least 20, but I have never been in the healthy bmi range in my life. It terrifies me that I will have to get in that range. Plus it will make me the fatest in my family. 

I also have no motivation to do anything anymore. I have books, Lego sets, knitting, but all I want to do is watch shitty tv. I don't even have the motivation to start a tv series on Netflix or watch a movie. It just takes so much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 17:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes a higher intake helps a plateau. It might boost your metabolism and kickstart your weight loss. 

I wish I had advice to give you, but I'm in a very similar boat right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 17:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand why they lock those dumpsters. It's not like they are using that food anyways. Sometimes clothing stores throw away old clothing and they will cut it up so people can't wear. Why don't people want to help those that have barely anything? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 17:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the app makes it really easy to switch between different accounts if you have more than 1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
