<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3883</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 20:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did, for now. Yesterday was an anger day, today is a sad day. Much easier to deal with. I'm sorry your day was rough too... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 20:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope today is treating you better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 20:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do the music thing too, although it's difficult when it's late at night and my roommate is sleeping. 

I don't pull my hair out but I always want to. I've gotten really good at  Charliehorse-ing myself. Seems to work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 20:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this. I will definitely be trying this out. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My brain won't stop screaming at me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 06:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just chilling with some whisky and cheesecake, all I want to do is relax but noooo, my brain won't let me. It keeps yelling at me. Stick the fork in your eye. Just do it. Remember that time you fucked up 6 years ago? Yeah that was stupid. You're nothing but a stupid little bitch. Take the fork and do it.

Till I can't take any more and my little rage furyball explodes and I hit myself in the thighs. Feels instantly better. Pain helps so much. A few minutes of calm, then it starts again.

I don't know how to make it stop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-26 05:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The things on the ceiling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-26 04:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Used to have major social anxiety. Major as in, completely unable to even order at fast food places, had to wear sunglasses everywhere because otherwise I was convinced everyone was staring at me. This went on for a couple years until I had a sudden realization.

Nobody gives a fuck about you.

Your friends and family, sure, of course. But the dozens/hundreds of people you see every day? They see dozens/hundreds more. You are nothing but a blip on the screen of life for them. Nobody gives a singular fuck. The chick at the counter at Tims isn't going home and judging you in her spare time, she has to serve literally thousands of people in a month. You are nothing to her. She won't even remember your face ten minutes from now.

Bam. Just like that, my social anxiety was gone. Still have a wack of other problems but hey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-26 04:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought so too! Little me had it all figured out; the movie companies would find suicidal people and give them plastic surgery to look like the actors that are dying in the movie.

I didn't figure out special effects until I was 12. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
