<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9229</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 17:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's completely your fault.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 01:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't. I've been taking it for a little less than 6 months and you go through awful withdrawal if you stop taking it. There's no way to avoid it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 14:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or just buy a M715 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 14:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh. Looks like every other foxbody from the '90s. Those body kits were all the rage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 14:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A little too much chrome, and a terrible color scheme, but it's pretty good other than that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 14:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks really good actually. It looks like they just replaced the cab on a semi with a F350 cab </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 14:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was actually looking to do this with my old Ranger when I had it. The front was kinda messed up from my brother rear ending someone in it and I thought this would be a unique and cool swap. But then, I enjoy ugly cars (see AMC Pacer) so eh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 13:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those were just M1s converted to take box magazines IIRC. Weren't they?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 03:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell yes. They didn't have the Sombra set originally so I picked up the Mercy set. Now I have both. Mwahhaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 02:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to know why this failed and then they decided to replicate it with the M14 during Vietnam. Did they expect different results from essentially the same action?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 02:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't titanium flammable? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 02:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh. Super troopers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 02:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like what they did later with the M14 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 17:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually volcanic sand is usually finer and less coarse than regular sand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 17:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. The turrets on the Ghost look they were taken directly off a B17, as well as the turret below the cockpit config. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 14:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just ordered a modmic recently. Would it be worth it to return it and get this instead? I only use it for voice chat in Overwatch. I'm pairing it with ATH-M50xs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shaving. Fuck razor burn to hell.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 20:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks fantastic. That's like my dream Jeep. Stuck with my YJ for now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 20:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha what. And why do you think this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 17:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love the top on the Jeep. Is it an LJ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 14:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ford Exploder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 14:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The H1 was great. You don't see them often because they're $100k+ trucks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 14:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm. My Jeep YJ rides like absolute shit and is a death trap.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 14:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly the first gen Ford Ranger. Had a beautiful '85 and I loved it, even though it was the most unreliable POS ever. The Vulcan V6 is absolute trash and blew gaskets left and right. The 2.3 4 banger was a much better (and Mazda) engine. I don't think it's possible to find one with the original V6 engine. Everyone swapped 302s into them because it was so simple.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 14:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uhh what? Ford has been doing phenomenal the past decade in pretty much every aspect. Truck? F-series. Hot Hatch? Focus RS/ST. Supercar? GT. Muscle Car? Mustang.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 14:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Charger? Challenger? Hellcat? Demon?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 20:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 14:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to FCA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 03:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As opposed to starving while waiting in bread lines.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 20:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say do it. Build quality is fantastic and it's just an amazing pistol. My dad traded in his Ruger P90 for it and couldn't be happier.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 18:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Nice. My dad just bought a .45 version and it's amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 13:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RX7/8?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 13:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the same reason slow car fast is (sometimes) better than fast car fast.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 00:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to college in Akron and can confirm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 14:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's not purely escort, so I don't think it counts. Even with the update, the first point is still a complete bitch to take.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 13:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why fight capitalism though?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it actually looks better than a normal 2002 F-150. Those things were ugly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Legal in Ohio at the very least as long as it passes emissions testing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like it. It needs paint, but it actually looks good otherwise  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poor YJ didn't deserve that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah probably. But this also mainly happened in the middle of December in Missouri when it was snowy, cold, windy, and we had no cold weather gear, so the top was somewhat nice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just with the canvas top(sometimes no top) and all we were transporting was people. You'd definitely be crushed in a roll over.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still don't understand why this is wrong. We did this in LMTVs all the time in the Army.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that a samurai behinf it? Poor thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm. Might be time to pick up a second one of these  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 12:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's canon again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 12:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's more than alluded to. There's an episode in season 3 I think where Satine is about to be kidnapped and they pretty much confess their love. Obi wan even say he'd even have left the Jedi order has she asked  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> B stands for Blade. It's explained in Star Wars Rebels </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stock leafs, but yes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good times were had blowing those up in JC2. It was more fun to destroy them in Mercenaries 2 though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks like a great place to take a a drive. It would be awesome to explore the old rail line. (Given you have a 4x4) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much how it worked for my Company as well. Although it was sometimes assigned as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But 7.62. So an AR-10  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My OSUT switched roadguards every day, sometimes multiple times a day. I didn't realize it was a semi permanent position at some places. This was at FLW in 2015 btw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *boop* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Riigghhhtttt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm wondering why they needed to replace the bed given they were fiberglass. At least on earlier models.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for new shocks. Any suggestions or tips? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, my YJ has the stock shocks that came with it from the factory 22 years ago and are all completely shot. Ride quality is absolutely horrible and I can't stand it anymore.  

My Jeep is stock other than a 3" body lift and 33"s and I seem to be in the market for new shocks. 

I was thinking either

 [These from Quadratrac](https://www.quadratec.com/p/quadratec/maximum-duty-nitro-80-shock-kit-87-95-jeep-wrangler-yj)

or

[These from Quadratrac](https://www.quadratec.com/p/quadratec/maximum-duty-hydro-70-shock-kit-87-95-jeep-wrangler-yj)

Any other options? These seem pretty good for the price based on reviews. I don't do any major offroading other than some trails and my YJ is my daily driver to and from school and work (about 30 min both ways). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. It's mostly dirt trails. There really aren't any obstacles except for a branch or some dips </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/meirl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking a YJ that was converted to front coils, which isn't uncommon. Those rear leafs look exactly like the ones on my YJ. And the frame is the exact same shape.

Also, I don't know of anyone who would convert a TJ to leafs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's a 22 year old Jeep. I don't want to break anything, although that still happens way to often, which is why I'm a bit puzzled.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. Unless 5 mph is too fast.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, YJs are already the ugly duckling of jeeps and this trim just accentuates that. Personally I love it. I wish I could have found one, but ended up with my plain ol' 95 instead. 

I have a wierd taste in cars though (i.e the AMC Pacer or Ford Pinto is a dream vehicle for me). I love ugly '80s cars.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everytime I got off-road something breaks! Last time it was my diff cover, oil pan gasket, radiator, and gas tank skid plate (still functional but cracked). All because I bottomed out. It was just a trail too, nothing remotely major. What do? It's a 1995 YJ btw. It's in great shape (except some minor tub rust) so I don't get it. My brother has a '95 in way worse shape and it never has these issues. 

I'm really starting to think of selling it just because I can't deal with then repair costs so often (even if I don't go off-road).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A hose. 100% serious. Once a year I take all my seats and carpeting out, park on a hill (previous owner beckoned over the drain plugs :P) and spray the crap out of the inside. Then I let it drain and dry and rebedline any areas that need it and reinstall everything. 

This may or may not works quite so we'll with more modern Jeep's.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still do it occasionally if I don't want to use up what little phone data I have. Well, what I actually do is screenshot Google maps, but same principle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Works fine on my note 4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially with Swype. It's so much quicker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm slogging through it. Its fault lies in the fact that most if the characters I really don't care about and don't contribute at all to the overall story hat much. It's all side characters. I'm barely managing to read a chapter a night.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha. Yes it is. Hudson represent! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get outta here Jar-Jar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh God. I'm reading AFFC right now and the Dorne scenes are just awful. Not to mention the whole book is a slog so far.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't even use it because I lost the plastic bolt that holds the wiper motor to the windshield frame, so it bangs around the opening in the frame. It's getting fixed soon courtesy of a fellow /r/jeep er who is sending me the part. I couldn't be more grateful to him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously. A lot of girls I talk to are obsessed over the fact that I have a Jeep. They all want to ride in it  They're chick magnets I swear.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Went for a nice Sunday drive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dang I was hoping it was the same truck. I've been trying to find it again ever since I sold it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You live in Ohio by any chance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the crap these things do, it would likely break almost immediately.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohio actually has some pretty great infrastructure. Cleveland has some fantastic bridges from the 20's and 30's that are still great. The problem is the road surface. It's always being repaired due to the constant freeze/thaw cycle that absolutely destroys the road surface (especially in NE Ohio, where we get the lake effect). I just wish they would stop salting the roads in the winter.

We also don't really have any trains (other than freight), but that is more due to a lack of need.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 02:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. They're all long gone or in private junkyards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It comes with the entire wiper motor assembly, but I can't afford to buy it for just the one part.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do realize you're on a satire sub dedicated to American nationalism right? 

Also 'Murica! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1995 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that feel. Almost 200 hours this season and 175 of them are playing Mercy, just because noone wants to heal.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm going out of my mind trying to find a part for my YJ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So recently I was driving during a thunderstorm and my windshield wiper arm flew off. Ok, no big deal, stopped the Jeep and picked up the arm and wiper, said I'll put it back on later and went on my way. 

Well as it turns out the reason it flew off is because the cheap plastic bolt/clamp thing that holds the wiper motor to the windshield frame snapped and fell off somewhere. 

I am going out of my mind trying to find a replacement part. They just don't exist it seems. Doesn't anyone know where I can find the part? I'll upload pics in a minute to show what I mean. 

Thanks.

Edit: Here are the images, apologies for the shit quality.

http://imgur.com/a/h5ook </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love that book. I still read it occasionally.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it useful for Overwatch when I'm spraying fire with Bastion, Orisa or D.Va,etc. it's pretty useless otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the input! The hair basically evolved from my time in the Army and I just kept letting the top grow out. I just don't know where to start in terms of hair I guess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah been putting on weight and lifting. I was dealing with anorexia for the past few years so it been hard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah, sorry. I completely forgot. Also thanks. I was slightly confused as to why people were replying me as banned </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stupidly sold this and bought my current vehicle which is a Jeep YJ. I would trade my YJ for another Ranger without a second though. I miss it so much. It had the horrid 2.8l V6 and auto transmission but this truck had so much character. I loved it to death, but never realized it until I sold it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Old 1985 Ford Ranger, Serenity. I miss her dearly. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not sure how I look, Opinions? [20/M] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  https://imgur.com/gallery/HOltK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link to the sale post?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buy it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not just FCA. Even AMC Jeeps did this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My YJ has this and has some pretty minor rust on the body but I recently replaced the hinges and the bare metal underneath was spotless. Guess I just got lucky.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 14:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely a joke. I know someone with a modded and lifted X-Terra that threw a GT-R badge on as a joke.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 14:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually like it. It's a no fucks given car. I had a Ranger like it and it was fun as hell since it was cheap to fix and parts were aplenty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 14:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not certain but I think that's a Jeep Wrangler YJ frame, or something very similar. That's pretty neat actually, since I bet the donor YJ was completely rusted out (they tend to do that).l, and this is a cheap and pretty cool swap.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 14:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's exactly what's happening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 14:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 00:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello! NE Ohio here also!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/shittytechnicals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's pretty impressive from a stock truck actually, no less a Chevy Pleasantly surprised. Someone's gonna try some stupid Trophy/Baja crap with it and destroy it most likely though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see France on the right either  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Columbus is pretty great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of my 1985 Rangers weird red interior </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man. After watching the Clone Wars cartoon, his death hits a lot harder. He was such a cool dude.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 13:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> USB OTG adapter? Like $5 + tape </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of MoH. Looks very promising.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless it's a Tacoma </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An actual wagon too!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds familiar. People are usually pretty good about this at concerts. I was at a ADTR/Blink-182/AAR concert over the summer and we had a circle pit going and everyone was helping each other back up. There were a few broken noses and fingers though. It was a blast.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait. What?! I'm from NE Ohio too and I never realized that wasn't normal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey everybody! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm back! I've had to take a break from the community for various personal reasons, but I think I'm back now. Just wanted to pop in and say hi, since I'm still technically a mod, even though I've neglected it. How have you all been?

[](/Bjshake) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's beautiful. We need more helicopters with pusher rotors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only thing in the interior that gives it away is the seat belt buckles. I honestly thought it was a 60s car until I read the title. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try vintagejapaneseautos.com. They're legit and take care of a lot of the paperwork. All their cars are legal too since they are 25+ years old and therefore not subject to EPA or DoT regulations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously. I thought it was some old car from the '60s but then went back and read the title and was shocked that it was built in 1991. Fantastic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 12:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a tangent line in there somewhere where it does count </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 14:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They used one of these when constructing the patio at my parents house. Very cool.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 13:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely a K5 Blazer with a Camaro body  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 17:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yes the Ford Focus(Fusion?) The epitome of good cars.


/s if it wasn't obvious enough 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
