<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject758</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 08:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mother always refers to this hot sauce as the sad hot sauce because of the face. Good with dumplings and noodles! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 09:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My boyfriend was that half Asian teen selling trinkets to strangers in a Safeway parking lot. Thanks for sharing your story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A year ago I had your hair color and I miss it dearly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 06:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i am here if you need me. you aren't alone in this, and i know it could be devastating when your partner isn't there to comfort you while you're going through this and living with your diagnoses. please know that it isn't your fault if people don't understand you or your illness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 09:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> white hood white hood, oh k k k  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zoloft really made my hair fall out and feel dry, my skin was yellowing as well. Sometimes I felt like I could manage my anxiety while on it but I'd end up feeling physically sick/malaise throughout the whole day. In the end, it didn't work out for me for like 4 months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember hiking that trail last year and twisting my ankle. Saw a lot of salamanders though. Cool shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 04:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> out of curiosity did you go to nightlife a week or two ago? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 07:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey girl hmu!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nutritional Yeast Infection </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 09:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have the same taste in music!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 07:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just saw this guy in San Francisco. No joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 08:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unpopular opinion but the KVD liquid lipsticks are super drying on my lips... seriously, WTF </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 20:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wish we could get an AMA from her </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 09:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like you're the perfect cross between Arya and Siri from the Witcher. I don't really have any good tips for makeup tho  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 19:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of the above, same.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 23:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> holy fuck. My sisters friend is unaccounted for and went to the venue yesterday, it breaks my heart and I do wonder how the fire was started. From what it seems, it had a lot of flammable objects and it was severely lacking in safety measures. I wasn't there and I can't accuse this guy because who the fuck knows who really happened. My heart hurts  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 10:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Picking my nose and scratching my wedgie in public. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 01:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got2Be texturizing hair pomade is something that I use that smells very STRONGLY of vanilla and marshmallows. Seriously, look it up and try it for yourself. It's good on different types of hair as well, I have layered medium length to short hair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 18:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was actually really good. I used a 6lb pork butt instead of an 8-10 lb one and could have easily fed 7-8 people. For the brown sugar and salt glaze, I added in a teaspoon of apple cider vinegar so that it would stick to the meat better. my family and I are looking forward to leftovers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 04:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Making this right now and it's almost done, man I'm excited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
