<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1637</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 15:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it'll be an excellent card in the matchup, but it won't exactly win on its own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 15:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 15:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems good, but not on its own. 3 damage won't kill Nissa or Gideon, so you need another creature swinging. It's less helpful late game because Sylvan Advocate, but it's tricky early game to have a creature to swing with AND delirium. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 06:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Declaration is much better as far as creature removal goes. I'd still keep Firecraft, since you're running Goblin Dark Dwellers, but drop it to 1-2 copies.

2. Thought-Knot seer! It's an incredible card, a 4/4 for 4 that also exiles their best card. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 23:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on mobile so I can't do a full write-up, but here are a few notes:

1. You aren't doing Nahiri because of budget, but the rest of the deck is pretty expensive. If you can afford Nahiri she's really incredible in this deck.

2. Cut Sin Prodder. It's nowhere near as good as it looks. The extra card never goes in your hand, and the damage it deals isn't worth the lack of impact on the board state.

3. Wasteland Strangler is a great card if you have any exile removal. Speaking of which, Declaration in Stone should be a 4-of.

4. Drana is a good card, but it doesn't really feel at home here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 00:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This could help make [[Thing in the Ice]] shells viable. Ability to throw down Thing turn 3 and still have mana to counter removal is not insignificant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 20:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh boy, more great bant cards. Yay... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 10:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's an overly optimistic assessment. Thalia is good, and it'll be a huge help for White humans in the matchup, but it's not going to single-handedly force Tokens to do anything more than add more removal, which White is still king of.  As for Decimator, I'm very uncertain about how impactful it's going to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 10:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'll be excellent in the mirror. And unless B/R/U get some serious boosts, GW Tokens is going to continue to be THE deck in Standard. I'd say it's a sideboard card for the mirror. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 22:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woo new land for my [[Alhammarret's Archive]] deck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 01:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right, I guess I just didn't expect the gap between the cheapest countries and the first world to be so enormous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 01:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, so Northern Irish farms don't actually produce anywhere near enough marketable goods to be successful businesses? Please correct me if I'm wrong here, but it sounds like the farmers are getting paid to work hard and accomplish nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Standard] Mono-White Archive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 20:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://tappedout.net/mtg-decks/standard-white-archive/

I'm trying to improve this deck, and I would love some criticism/advice from more experienced deckbuilders.

The heart of the deck is [[Alhammarret's Archive]], which doubles lifegain and card draw. This turns mediocre cards like [[Healing Hands]] into incredible value. 

The deck is mono-white to maximize the value from [[Prism Ring]], which gives some massive lifegain over the course of the game.

I'm not really sure about a win condition yet. I'm currently mainboarding 4 [[Sunscorch Regent]] as the win con, but I've also experimented with [[Myth Realized]] and [[Linvala, the Preserver]].

My removal comes in the form of [[Declaration in Stone]] and [[Stasis Snare]], with [[Planar Outburst]] as a sweeper.

Other builds I've considered are:

1. A more creature-based version, including playsets of [[Cleric of the Forward Order]], [[Bygone Bishop]] and [[Serene Steward]].

2. A [[Felidar Sovereign]] shell, with [[Center Soul]] to keep it safe from removal.

3. A [[Myth Realized]] shell, with minimal creatures and much more removal.


I'd appreciate any advice that you could offer! I'm very excited about this brew and I think it's shaping up to be a fun, FNM-competitive deck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 20:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, this is a major part of the problem: nobody cares who their MEP is. This applies everywhere in Europe, not just Britain. Nigel Farage, who opposed the entire concept of the EU, managed to gain and keep the position of MEP with minimal effort. 

And so he argues, not unjustly, that the European Parliament is undemocratic because only a minuscule portion of the European population actually votes in the elections.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 16:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doubt it's Standard playable, but it'll be very welcome for Zombie EDH players. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 11:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woo more [[Fevered Visions]] fodder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 08:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm kind of disappointed in the sorting ceremony. The background we have on Ilivermony's sorting tells us explicitly that many students are offered membership in more than one house. It would have been nice if I could be offered 2 houses instead of just 1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 03:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like this flag, but it's giving me Bant Company flashbacks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 03:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need more good spirits! Specifically good 2-drops with decent ETB effects that aren't Rattlechains. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 00:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> heh heh heh [[Priest of the Blood Rite]] this could be fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 23:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh boy, an answer to Always Watching Ojutai... and it's white. Great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 23:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a vastly superior version of General Tazri, and it's not even legendary. I'm not optimistic about the color balance in this set. It seems like either White gets several OP cards (i.e. color imbalance) or every color gets several OP cards (i.e. general power creep). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 17:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's not forget the Lifelink part. That's a hell of a clock for 4 mana. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 15:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you, players on /r/spikes of all places should understand mirror match of the best deck in Standard. That said, there's no fault in complaining about it being a stale format. However skill-intensive the game is, if it's mostly the same game every time you play it gets boring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 04:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is... is that a giant churro with ice cream? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 01:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The mods must be crazy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 02:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> .556 weapons would be nice. We got December's Child in Far Harbor, but I'd really like to see a base weapon that uses .556 ammo other than the disgustingly bulky assault rifle.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 21:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is Insolent Red. It's not exactly tier 1, but boy is it fun. It's a like a mono-red vampires deck, but with funstuff like Skin Invasion and Infectious Bloodlust. Here's my 5-minute decklist: http://tappedout.net/mtg-decks/31-05-16-insolent-red/

and here's the article mtggoldfish wrote on it: http://www.mtggoldfish.com/articles/budget-magic-45-13-tix-standard-insolent-red

Actually, on second thought, just ignore my list and read the article. That's closer to the list I'm actually playing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone get the feeling that Western Civilization is, as a whole, just really bored? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 10:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 10:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right? Like, Ireland's flag is just a tricolor. Scotland's flag is just a white X on a blue field. Honestly not all that interesting. But put together we're seeing some fantastic flag designs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 07:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not until I can get Jeremus as a companion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 00:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Celtic League anybody? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 00:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially spirits imo. It's close to being a tier 2/1.5 aggro-control deck, but it needs one or two more tempo cards to be viable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 10:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Celtic League. Invite Brittany and Wales. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 01:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is /r/fullcommunism not satire? I thought it was circlejerk/satire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 08:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I haven't bought Fates yet. Which versions allow me to grind supports? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 07:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly this is probably worse than Reality Smasher unless the flip condition is achievable before turn 5. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 23:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm actually not a fan of Stardew Valley's characters honestly. They were well-written but I didn't find any of them appealing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 07:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It feels GREAT when you can ult Nahiri with 2 Stranglers in the graveyard, which makes the play:

Nahiri Ult-Swift Warkite-Wasteland Strangler from the graveyard--3/-3 a creature- swing with Warkite and Strangler- pass turn, Warkite and Strangler go into hand- cast Warkite- bring ANOTHER Strangler from the graveyard- -3/-3 a creature- swing with Strangler-pass turn, Strangler returns to hand

After 2 turns, you get a 4/4 Flier, 2 Strangler ETB effects and 2 copies of Strangler from your graveyard to your hand.

It's not competitively optimal, sure, but it feelsgoodman.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 04:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously [[Linvala, the Preserver]]. But a favorite of mine for Mardu Nahiri is [[Swift Warkite]]. It allows you to bring back a [[Wasteland Strangler]] from the graveyard and use its ETB effect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 20:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was cruel, that's certain. But Ramsay was also cunning, intelligent and talented. He terrified us. There was always something... off, about Ramsay. But that was all part of his toying subtlety. And Iwan did a PHENOMENAL job of showing us every tiny detail of Ramsay's personality.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 22:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What *exactly* are these changes you made to r/all? If you really want to communicate with the users, if you really want transparency, then you ought to give an explanation of what the changes you made actually ate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 19:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FUN FACT New York has some of the cleanest tap water in the country. It's pretty much the least dirty thing about Manhattan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 19:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mage can be great in some ways. I did the sneaky Illusion-Conjuring mage and it was a blast. Sneak up on a group, silently enrage one of them, then watch the carnage unfold.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 19:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on the DLC. With the Season Pass, I'm getting content below the market value but taking the risk that it might not be good. It's a gamble to buy before reviews and gameplay videos come out. If there is additional DLC, I wouldn't feel slighted by the invalidation of my Season Pass, but I would have to carefully consider before purchasing at full price. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 13:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jade Empire. It's like Kotor, but in China. Favourite Bioware game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 01:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mostly starting from scratch... I've got 2 Tireless Trackers and 1 Nahiri, but that's pretty much it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 22:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for a tier-1 (or borderline tier-2) deck that is NOT White Humans. My budget is about $50. I'm tinkering with a budget UG Tentacles decklist, as well as the UR Fliers list. I really like everything, but my favorite archetype is probably aggro-control. What competitive decks fit that best? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 01:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This card could make Kiora actually playable in standard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 22:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> White Humans. It's cheap, it's simple, it's competitive. You can get creative, there are several different ways to build it, but it ends up being a very good deck to get into the format with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 10:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The evidence presented at the Grand Jury clearly showed support for Wilson's story, in which he responded reasonably to at least the threat of violence. The opposing story had numerous flaws, was impossible on several different counts, and ultimately contradicted itself to be considered anything more than a pack of flat out lies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 04:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Periodic table, because of freshman chemistry. No, I'm not kidding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 04:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Furthermore, when tyshawn shoots dequan, tyshawn goes to jail while black victims of police violence struggle to have their case go to trial

Part of the argument is that Tyshawn often *doesn't* go to jail, because majority-black areas are systematically underpoliced. Dangerous criminals roam free in low-income, majority-black areas because police are too afraid to venture near them. 

And it's precisely because of the racial backlash that officers get when policing black-majority neighborhoods. Remember Darren Wilson's shooting of Michael Brown? That was, in hindsight, entirely justified on Wilson's part. Unavoidably so. And yet Wilson "resigned" (no severance pay) and will never be a police officer again, because of the response by black-power movements. 

*This* is what people mean when they talk about black-on-black crime being a bigger problem than police violence. A paranoia of police officers perpetuated by black-power movements is making it harder and harder for the law to keep order in black neighborhoods. And that's allowing dangerous career criminals to terrorize these communities. Children in these areas are brought up seeing nothing but crime, knowing no life but that of gangs and ghettos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 21:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is good stuff!

I had a budget Mardu control deck that looked a lot like this. The Nahiri-Fetch-finisher was Swift Warkite, which felt real good with a Strangler or two in the yard. 

(Fetch Warkite-Warkite etb bring back Strangler-Strangler etb to kill an enemy creature-both return to hand-cast Warkite again-Warkite etb to bring another Strangler. End result: Two Strangler ETB effects, one 4/4 flier, and two more Stranglers in the hand. Feelsgoodman)

I was also using Topplegeist, since Delirium is pretty easy with the +2 and you don't have to spend mana like for Displacer. And I'm strongly of the opinion that Hallowed Moonlight should be MB for this meta, since it exiles creatures from Company AND can be used to delay token-producers for a turn.

In addition, I really dig the Oath of Chandra-Angelic Purge interaction for this deck. Sacrificing an Enchantment helps delirium, and exiling their cards helps Strangler. Plus, if not for the sacrificial "downside" Angelic Purge would be insanely good removal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 05:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just played against myself on tappedout against a few popular decks. I understand that it's not the best way to test accurately, so I'm wondering what the metagame consensus is for the deck, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 04:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first deck I made in this meta was a Mardu control shell for Nahiri. It was garbage, bc I suck at brewing, but I'd be really interested to see what you've done with it. Did you run Wasteland Strangler? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does Sylvan Advocate's +2/+2 stack? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 20:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Say, if I have 2 [[Sylvan Advocate]] and 6 lands. Each advocate says that under these conditions, "Sylvan Advocate... gets +2/+2". So do both of their buffs impact both of them, giving me 2 Advocates with +4/+4 each? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 07:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only manages 40 acres though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Standard] UW Spirits primer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 09:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to tune my UW Spirits list and looking for good resources. I haven't been able to find any thorough primers on the deck though. Any resources are good, but a fully fleshed-out primer would be ideal. Has anyone found anything? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 08:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Normally I agree, but Midsummer in particular is a grammatical labyrinth. It's hard to deliver the lines meaningfully without some inspiration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your favourite performances of Bottom in Midsummer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 05:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just cast as this role and I adore the character. Looking for a little inspiration from the greats to help me out. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 12:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not run [[Pieces of the Puzzle]] here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 08:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he's genuine then I hate him and his character. That's why I hope he isn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 07:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be so great if the High Sparrow was just more relatable. Right now he's a pretentious asswad on his high horse. If we knew that he had goals other than "fuck over the Lannisters," if we knew his win-condition, we might like him more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 04:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh fuck you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 04:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think he just wants personal power. Why would he? He doesn't do anything with it. He doesn't live in the lap of luxury, he doesn't get glory, he seems to genuinely want what's best for the people. Which I hate, fuck the people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 04:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to see his endgame. He's so deliciously evil but I hate him right now because he just fucks over everyone I like and I have no idea why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 04:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Brotherhood without Banners attacking Frey supply lines? Edmure Tully prisoner of the Freys? Sounds like Lady Stoneheart is coming back! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 04:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ikr they couldn't wait one episode between melodramatic Daenerys speeches? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 03:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BENJEN FUCKING STARK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 00:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Standard, I like UW Spirits and RUG Cluestorm. In Modern I like Izzet Blitz. 

Generally, I'm a big fan of stupid janky combo decks that actually work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 20:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about blinking, specifically Essence Flux </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 20:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If my opponent casts [[Ultimate Price]] on my [[Bygone Bishop]], and I respond by casting [[Essence Flux]] on it, is my creature still targeted or does it survive? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 20:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Despite your downvotes, I agree. Petersen is more charismatic, he'll do better in debates than Johnson. I'm holding out hope that he wins, but it concerns me that everyone just assumes Johnson will get the nomination.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 08:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Money is fungible, if ppfa is getting money from the government and is providing abortions then the government is funding abortions through ppfa. Arguing against that shows a fundamental misunderstanding of how money works.

And ppfa is trash. There are hundreds of organizations that can provide better care without abortion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 07:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything about then is blatantly leftist. I listen to them for non political shows sometimes, and even then they often manage to sneak in some bullshit that implies that the leftist view is the only acceptable one. Public funding for them is almost as bad as for Planned Parenthood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 04:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. Petersen would do much better at representing the Libertarian position during debates.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 20:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've tried building a Memories Milldeck too. I'd recommend including white for [[Bygone Bishop]], [[Bound by Moonsilver]] and [[Angelic Purge]]. Note, Memories triggers whenever you sac a clue for*any* reason. That makes Purge and Moonsilver premium removal that also help you mill.

Also consider [[Forgotten Creation]]. It makes the Tutelage clock extremely fast, and it can lock in a pinch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 19:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you think about running 1-2 [[Embermaw Helion]]? It doubles your cluegrid damage and gives you a trample body for [[Confront the Unknown]]. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 05:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The easiest and most budget tier 1 deck is white humans. But you can get a good tier 2 deck for around 20-30 bucks, easy. I'd recommend looking at UW Spirits as a cheap jumping off point. You can build a playable one for like $20, then just start playing. The more you play, the better you know both your deck and the others in the format.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 04:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone explain the Hodor warging thing? Bran was in the past, then he warged into Hodor from the past? Then he warged into past Hodor from present Hodor? Whose body is Bran in right now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 12:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woah, woah, woah, hold on. You're claiming that *Marxist* historians value government inaction? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 11:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a tough call. I've never been really good at perfecting the sideboard but I'd consider putting the negates in there for walker matchups.

That said, if you flip Thing then you have nothing between 7 damage and their planeswalker. Plus, Stormchaser is a fast flying bruiser in here, and there aren't too many good flying/reach creatures in the meta right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 03:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swap negate. It's less effective at disruption, but against control it does a great job speeding up the clock and protecting your TitI, since it's two spells for one card and protects for 2 turns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 17:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you considered [[Center Soul]], in either side or main? It casts 2 spells for 1 card, and protects TitI. I've been running it in Jeskai Visions and it's had good results. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 00:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad you're feeling better! Take this opportunity of energy and enthusiasm to take care of yourself. Make an appointment with a therapist. If you have bipolar depression it can be hard to think about the bad times during the good, but this is a great chance for you to set yourself on the path to recovery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 23:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm with you on maindeck Hallowed Moonlight, it's a 2-mana answer to tokens and coco with a cantrip. Anyone in white should be running it.

On racing aggro, would you recommend tempo (Hydrolash, Engulf the Shores) or life gain (Lantern Scout, Apothecary Geist)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 23:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly I haven't really playtested it, I just kind of assumed that a blink/bounce deck wouldn't want it. I ought to pick up a few copies anyways so maybe I'll give it a try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 21:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3. I run a lot of counterspells and blinking, so I always leave mana for negate when facing control. 

4. Hallowed Moonlight, unfortunately, is unplayable in my current build. I've got too much blinking for value.

Thanks for the tips!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 20:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Standard] I'm building my first real standard deck, UW Spirit tribal, and I'd like some sideboard advice. The deck is very much a tempo-based aggro-control one. 

1. What should I side in against A human aggro? Lifegain to outrace them feels like the best bet.

2. Always Watching? The card is nuts, but I'm unsure about putting it in maindeck. How many copies?

3. What are the worst matchups for a flier-heavy aggro-control deck? 

4. Just in general, how do I build an effective sideboard? Any tips would be appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 18:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> me too thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 08:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steampunk India here we come! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 02:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait is this seriously how it works? What medications do they use? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 01:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh, do you mean "Don't read spoilers" or "don't read the rest of this post, it's got spoilers?" I'm pretty sure it's the former but I want to be sure... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 20:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is Pokemon Super Mystery Dungeon? I liked the pokemon mystery dungeon games and I'm wondering if this new one is worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 05:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No sprinklers, that's a Stardew Valley thing only. You can spend Princess Points to add another area of farmland to your farm, but you should only do that if you're already using all the space you have access to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 03:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this is kind of a vague question, but what are some good 3ds games that have come out recently? I just got back from uni for the summer, haven't touched my 3ds in half a year and I want some suggestions for new games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 03:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grinding combat is a waste of time that early in the game. Focus on training other skills to level up. Expand your farm, complete requests, craft weapons/armor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 23:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The "European Colonization of Americas" statistic is pure propoganda. I'm sorry, but there's no other way to put it. The total population of the pre-Colombian Americas is highly disputed, and it would take a very high estimate and a very negative view of colonization to reach 138 million. 

In addition, characterizing the series of events as a "war" is enormously dangerous. It implicitly splits these events into a conflict with 2 sides, European and Native American. Never mind that the European powers were fighting each other most of the time. This strikes me as dangerously tribalistic and unrealistic, viewing history through a lens of "conflict between ethnic groups" rather than the more reasonable "conflict between states." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 03:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> me too thanks
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 21:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Playing a sneaky-shooty survival game, it's Deliverer and my tricked-out pipe bolt-action pistol. Early on I found one with a supressor mod already attached, and since I'm going the luck/Idiot Savant path for experience I don't have Gun Nut. So it was my early game silent weapon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 12:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like there is no "myself." I've been acting for so long I don't think there's anything genuine left, just a hollow shell that's good at pretending to be a person. 

If I opened up to my friends, I wouldn't be a tragic, tortured genius who just needs to learn to love himself. I would be a boring, apathetic escapist who doesn't want to do anything but play video games all day. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 04:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly who gives a shit? There are so few "trans" people that we can judge whether they're mentally ill, physically uncomfortable or just special snowflakes on a case-by-case basis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 22:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good. I look forward to hearing him speak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 18:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dropped $20 yesterday. The day before, I dropped my school id and had to pay $20 to replace it. No matter how careful I am, how slow I go, I'm still clumsy and forgetful. I can't function like this, and there's no way to get better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 22:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh right. Lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 21:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, how does she dodge ultimate price? She isn't hexproof. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 22:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her voice is, yeah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 23:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lets not ignore the fact that **your companions can come to Far Harbor with you.** Nick and Piper, at least. That's a huge departure from the Bethesda trend of self-contained DLC storylines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 23:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally the first thing I thought of. If Far Harbor doesn't have some heavy Rapture references I'll be disappointed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 23:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bring us the girl, wipe away the debt... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 17:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course self mill has its uses, I'm not denying that it would be an advantage in a well-built deck. But if you're going through 3 cards a turn instead of 1, just surviving ~18 turns becomes a win condition for your opponent. 

And that's assuming you only use the +1 once. Use it twice and you've got guaranteed Delirium, [[Graveblade Marauder]] swinging for 10-20, massive [[Diregraf Colossus]] and other good combos. But if your opponent can stall you out, then you rapidly approach the bottom of your deck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 10:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A planeswalker whose +1 gives you a detrimental emblem. I thought of this for a new Tibalt and it's an interesting design space. For example,

+1: you get an emblem with "at the beginning of your upkeep, put the top two cards of your library into your graveyard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 10:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Magic Trick

1UBR

Reveal the top card of your library, then shuffle your library. At the beginning of the next end step, reveal the top card of your library. If it is the same as the first card, take an extra turn after this one. Exile Magic Trick.

*Is this your card?* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 10:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Move aside, Mizzix. We've got a new top-tier Izzet commander. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 10:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can [[Sigarda, Heron's Grace]] fit in a GW tokens deck in Standard? Is there a fit for her in any standard-competitive deck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 06:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how "wall" has been used as a weapon twice already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 05:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm almost a single-issue voter, with that issue being abortion (pro-life). I'm supporting Governor Johnson because he wants the government out of the abortion industry. Before even bringing my own views into it, it's clearly ludicrous that the entire country is paying taxes to support a practice that fully HALF believe to be *literally infanticide*. 

Once government funding of PPFA and groups like it has stopped, THEN we can talk about how abortion is murder.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 20:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> West/East AJ and New Hall West/East are the nicest and newest dorms on campus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 02:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right. In hindsight, I think I mentioned it just because it was a rare 5drop. I'd replace it with Briarbridge Patrol or Epitaph Golem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 00:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WG

Declaration in Stone, Angelic Purge, Expose Evil, Moorland Drifter x2, Angelic Purge, Dauntless Cathar, Paranoid Parish-blade, Militant Inquisitor, Inspiring Captain.

Loam Dryad, Lambholt Pacifist, Obsessive Skinner, Quilled Wolf, Rabid Bite, Byway Courier x2, Intrepid Provisioner, Sage of Ancient Lore, Kessig Dire-swine.

Splash black for the Gitgud Frog, add 2x Warped Landscape for delirium/swamp fetching.

Add True-faith censer and I think you've got a solid GW pool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 08:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frankly, one of the most underrated benefits of Brain is that it gets around tricky mana costs. Tragic Arrogance, for example, costs WW3, which might be hard to get unless you're running white heavily. With Brain, you can resolve it without a single white mana source in your deck.

I haven't tested yet, but I'm working on a 4-color Brain deck, topping out at Part the Waterveil and Seasons Past. I think it's promising, so maybe tinker around with other colors for a bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 00:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She really puts the "mass" in "Massachusetts." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 17:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you considered Forgotten Creation? It's a decent blocker and a massive Tutelage enabler. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 20:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Geralf/Jace vs Gisa/Lili, the necrowar to end all necrowars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 22:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah W humans is fast and powerful, I have no doubt they will continue to be relevant in the meta. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
