<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject758</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 00:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's possibly something neurological as well and I'm looking into it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 23:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds like a good idea. I don't have a TV/consoles in my appt but I can dl some games on the laptop or something. Maybe I should read. Sigh.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> disassociation from PTSD, co dependency, I am feeling so alone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 09:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a 20 year old woman, with very few friends, a boyfriend who I am overly attached to, and several mental issues. 

A couple weeks ago, I was sexually assaulted outside of a concert venue- one that I didn't attend. I was waiting for my boyfriend to come out, and he never picked up his phone. He was too high/drunk/whatever. There are certain parts I don't remember, however this guy bit my lip and tried to get me to come home with him. He pushed me against a fire hydrant and left some gnarly bruises on my thigh. I am angry still, at my boyfriend- but it isn't his fault at all. The concert was supposed to end an hour earlier and I was at the wrong place, wrong time.

 I currently don't have a job, and a relative of mine is financially supporting me. Anyways, I left the culinary industry as a below mediocre cook and I'm planning to go to school during the fall for my degree. Right now, I can't even hold down a simple job because my mind is killing me.

As of right now, my PTSD is really fucking with me. I am blacking out often, and I don't remember doing or saying certain things- that I do. I find things placed in odd places and I hurt myself and I don't remember when or how. My boyfriend says it isn't me, when I sometimes talk to him..or other people. I hear voices, and I panic when I go outside, I can't really rely on my family. There are so many things that trigger me when I go outside.

 I have the apartment to myself for 1 week because my eldest sister and her boyfriend are on a trip to NY. My psych isn't here either. I really need support, or distractions. I don't know why I'm blacking out and I'm reliant on my 21 year old boyfriend who's willing to go therapy with me in a couple weeks, but he really doesn't understand. No one does, to be honest.

I've been having a lot of sex every time I see him. I haven't had a proper period in 5 months (I suffer from an ED but I'm at a normal weight and I'm not thin in my eyes). I'm really stressed. I can't help but to push him away even though I don't want him to go away. I'm on a low dose of Wellbutrin, btw.

TLDR; I feel so alone and I just want someone to be there.. :/

edit: i was diagnosed with PTSD before the incident I just mentioned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 22:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's something I need to definitely look into and try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 20:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really gonna try to seek some assistance somehow. I wish I could really find people who are experiencing the same thing/similar things as I am. Wish I could camp or chill with friends to get away from all the BS. Thanks for replying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 03:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm down, but I'm in SF and this post is a bit old.. ah.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 10:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i was trying to walk home from work and this shit was going on.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-22 13:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> reading this made my stomach twist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> please help me I am feeling so sick? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 05:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i've been smoking cigarettes for a long time..about 4 years. I'm 20 now, I went on a date with this boy yesterday and we smoked so much till we got sick. A pack and a half together, and one pack was one of those packs were those popping menthol packs. anyways i can't even sit up straight now, i have a fever, and i just took my patch off.
 
i work as a line cook, full time, as a 5 foot 2 girl.. it's really physically tiring and i don't even know how to feel better for work tomorrow. i feel so nauseated and i want to vomit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-12 08:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck on your recovery. You can do this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 03:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From age 15 till now (20) I've been there several times. 
I feel safe but at the same time too safe. When I leave the hospital, it's overwhelming because I'm faced with all my problems and these people again. I struggle with PTSD, BPD, anxiety, depression, an eating disorder. Everyday is a struggle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 12:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who's that Pokemon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
