<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6681</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 06:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also grew up in a place where there wasn't unlimited food. But recently I bought a /ton/ of triggering foods only to throw it all down the garbage shoot before I could even eat it. On one hand I felt proud that I didn't give in.... but I felt so guilty for wasting that food (and the money). 

Ive also been in restaurants, ordered food, had one bite, then got it "to go" so I could throw it out while walking down the street. Eating disorders are weird.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 22:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sticking to my 23:1 IF , 500 calories diet for a while.

Breakfast: Skipped

Lunch: Banana (105), Oranges (130), Tofu (240), Lettuce (10)

Dinner: Skipped

Total: 485 calories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 04:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, now that my 7 day fast is over I am going back to restricting. Yesterday I had a "non restricting" day when I came off the fast, so I obviously maintained alot of water weight. I am going to watch it for the next couple days... hopefully I don't go crazy from this weight fluctuation.  It's nearly 6-8 pounds worth. I didn't even eat that much food. LKJHFDLHSAKJFAHELWKJFHAEJLK

Breakfast: Skipped

Lunch: 2 Bananas (210), orange (65) and almond milk (110)

Dinner: Skipped 

Total: 385 calories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 19:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today, Monday September 26 2016 @1pm , marks the 7th day of my fast. I officially havent ate any food for a week. Today, like usual, I am going to break my fast with raw vegetables like Lettuce,Cucumbers, Bananas, Oranges,etc. For the sake of my sanity, I will not count calories today. 

I lost 13 pounds in total, but I will definitely gain some water weight once food enters my digestive system again. I am hoping this will only be around 3 to 5 pounds though, so I still have some sort of loss.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 21:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been drinking plain water, with the occasional diet coke for Sodium and Caffeine. (:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 20:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today is the 6th day of my fast. I plan to break my fast tomorrow, which will make seven days. I am already dreaming of what I will eat lol. 


Breakfast: Skipped

Lunch: Skipped

Dinner: Skipped

Total: 0 Calories
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 19:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just finished up my 5th day of my fast. I feel pretty exhausted but I have nothing to do until Tuesday. I think I can at least make it a week... maybe more.


breakfast: Skipped

lunch: Skipped

dinner: Skipped

total: 0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 20:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently 4 days into my fast! Let's gooooooooo~

Breakfast: Skipped

Lunch: Skipped

Dinner: Skipped

Total: 0 calories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 21:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello! And welcome(:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 19:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. Happened more times than I would like to admit.
( I don't really "binge" per say, but sometimes my rational brain just convinces me to eat enough food to cancel out the deficit of calories. ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
