<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9229</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 19:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> KO2s everytime for me. Decent on road and off road and cheap too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not in my district. Has to be a picture ID. I've seen people get turned away for not having one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohio has voter ID laws. Or at least they ask for ID when you vote based on my experience.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None of my past 3 vehicles have had airbags of any kind. I don't care too much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah. Hellcats don't hurt people. It's the Mustangs leaving Cars   Coffee that do that /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mac10?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey it's Cleveland!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 03:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OBS is best truck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 02:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice. I got two '95s. Ones a Rio Grande and the other is just a base model but in much better shape. Gotta keep those old Yjs on the road.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 00:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never seen a white YJ hard top. Cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do they jump to immediately attacking capitalism every time their system is criticized? Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to boop them the way they are already moving. It adds to the momentum.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 03:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've gotten that in my YJ too :(
Also from a JKU.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 03:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks cold.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 02:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got em for $100 on Craigslist. I think quadratrac sells them too but they're like $400-500 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 23:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yarr matey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 23:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't choose them. They came with the Jeep when I bought it. They're not bad though. Although they are a pain to keep clean.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. I adjusted both, since I replaced both anyways. Still have the problem. It's been driving me nuts trying to figure out what's wrong. The washers will work for now at least.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I vacationed there a few years ago. Absolutely beautiful place (and Jeep). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a bad deal, but it's not great either. That's more what I would expect a later year TJ to go for as well. I wouldn't pass if everything seems good though, maybe try and talk the price down a little.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finally got my new hinges and door parts this week and got my half doors all put together and ready for spring. Now I don't have to use my ugly (and somewhat rusty) red full doors. Somehow I managed to stop it from rusting from all the salt and crap here in Ohio this winter also.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finally got my YJ (kinda) cleaned up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a hinge problem. I just replaced my old rusty hinges with new stainless steel ones yesterday and adjusted them every which way and it has the same issue. This problem has me stumped because the passenger side is perfectly adjusted and works great, but the driver side doesn't. I currently have it shimmed with washers between the upper and lower doors on the bolt, and that somewhat fixed it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yeah, those are similar to mine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no space, but they hit the side of the hard top when I close the doors. My hinges are adjusted all the way up as well. Right now I just have bolts acting as pins holding the uppers onto the door, there is nothing for them to screw into.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't even do that in my YJ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do I need some sort of spacer between my hard upper doors and the lower doors on a YJ? The doors don't seem to fit right even after adjusting the hinges. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 03:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chopper is in Rogue One too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 01:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually kinda like it other than the stupid sticker on the diffuser. It's a bit too ricey and the Lamborghini doors are dumb, but other than that it's not too bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 00:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ford's 2.8l/2.9l/3.0l Vulcan V6. Most commonly found in first generation Ford Rangers and Bronco IIs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 22:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I've never seen one like it before. TIL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 22:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I have a 2" lift and 31"s and get about 20-22 depending. This is with the 2.5l as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 22:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah jeez. Try finding hard uppers and half doora for a YJ if you think finding TJ ones are hard. They just don't exist. I was lucky and scored a set for $100. I have never seen another set.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 19:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't mean anything. If you have loans to pay off, and you can work more hours in order to be able to meet the minimum loan payment, than you should. You took the loans in the first place. I see no issue with working more to pay them off. Refusing just makes you sound lazy and enttled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 14:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha not isn't. Why is it broken? People regularly work 60+ hour weeks all over the world. Noone ever has said life is easy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 04:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That the frame is fucked. If so, avoid it at all costs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 04:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not in the US sadly :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 03:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 02:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention that you still wear a climbing harness while in it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 02:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like Leonard Wood to me, but it's probably not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 00:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's nothing wrong with JKUs. It's the American equivalent of the Defender 110 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> U wot M8. I'm a Sombra main but Tracer was literally the first character put into the game. And she's fun as hell to play as.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shut your mouth. Pineapple on pizza is delicious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love those, they were very useful. It's kinda similar in concept to how a lot of utes have beds where the sides fold down. Much easier to access things in the bed that way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing the weird door on the bed of the F150. Which actually looks like it would be pretty useful and looks very well done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maul looks pretty normal though, doesn't he? He just tattooed himself red instead of the normal yellow of the Dathomir, didn't he?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quick! Look. For Sombra clues! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yet they still find some of them, so I hope you are one. You seem proud of your evasion and it's absolutely disgusting. You say you won't work more than 40 hours a week and that your wife refused jobs offering $12-14/hour. You have absolutely no reason to evade your loans. You are just lazy and entitled.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is correct. I used to work at a donut shop as a fry cook. Cake donuts come out of a dropper directly into the fryer and don't have the "dough hole". Regular donuts are cut out and then allowed to rise (we put ours in a hot box) and then fried.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to work at a donut shop as a fry cook and yes, they do, or at least ours did. There is a big roller machine you feed dough into and it cuts out the donut shape (or rather a octogon with a hole in the middle). The machine also cuts out a hole in the middle which is either used as donut holes or remixed into more dough for donuts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It was a livestream, so maybe not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope they find you. Thanks for screwing everyone else over.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 14:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because we know we are right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 01:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sawzall solves all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 18:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The whole car is gaudy and overdone IMO. It's a great car, but I think it looks pretty awful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 18:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are we going back to the 80's now? Haha. Anyone else remember the all red interiors on everything in the mid 80's. I love it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 17:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh. Kinda. Mines all leaf springs and is very barebones compared to a JKU. It's closer to a CJ7 than a JKU (or even a TJ for that matter). They're all Jeep's but there's a pretty big difference between YJs and JKUs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 17:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That must weight a ton if its steel. I wish we got those things in the US (the truck, not the bumper).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 17:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. They're excellent off road as well, while still retaining that "luxury" status. Obviously you're not going to go rock crawling in one, but they're pretty decent. I wanted to buy one before I bought my Jeep, but got talked out of it, since they're not know for reliability. Also I had wanted something manual, and I couldn't find one in the US that was, which leads me to believe we never got manual ones in the US.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 15:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Headlights are actually pretty cool. They make the truck look much more modern. Probably much more useful as well. It's a Ford, but gives off a newer Chevy/GMC 1500 vibe. I love it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 15:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love those classic Range Rovers. So cool.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 15:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This makes me wish I had a XJ instead of my YJ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 15:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  What's the deal with the bumper on the middle one? That's massive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 15:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's very true. It does look excellent. I'll reserve judgement until we have more solid reviews though.  Let's just hope it doesn't  suffer the same problems that are so common with other Chrysler vehicles.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 15:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not offended at all, I just thought you were confusing the various militias with the National Guard. I don't disagree that National Guard soldiers are often subpar to Active Duty ones, but very often, National Guard soldiers are ex-active duty ones and many have seen more combat experience than a lot of active duty soldiers. 

We've come a long long way as an Army since Vietnam and Kent State.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 14:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No they don't. But as we saw in Vietnam and Afghanistan, you don't need anywhere near the power of the US military to defeat it in asymetrical warfare.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 14:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The National Guard has Special Forces and an Air Force as well. It's not really much different from the regular army. They still have tanks, jets, drones, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 14:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The National Guard is still part of the Army just FYI. They go to the same training (at least for BCT and AIT). They're just part time (with a few exceptions, such as the National Guard's Special Forces, and various maintenance positions). They are still professional soldiers, and can still deploy to Iraq, Afghanistan, etc.  

You may be thinking of individual state militias which *are not* part of the Army/National Guard (or DoD for that matter). They usually fall under the oversight of the state governments or are non-governmental entities entirely. These a militias are the ones full of the "dudes who just like to dress in camo once a month". 

Source: Former US Army National Guard  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 00:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. It's very stupidly planned. It right next to campus too, so it's not like it gets a lot of traffic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 21:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup me too. Can never be too prepared.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 21:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Newer Chrysler isn't any better. Very poor QC and often build quality as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. It's all about aerodynamics. For example, my Jeep's is about 2 mph. Bugs. Bugs everywhere. And rocks. :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohio would be split NE Ohio to Columbus is now North Ohio and the rest is now South Ohio. The two areas are pretty different demographic wise (also urban vs rural), so I think this would work pretty well actually.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it's your belt? My YJ had the most godawful clicking until I did the scheduled maintenance at 130k miles and replaced the belt.  I didn't know a belt could be so loud.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 18:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Parked next to two JKUs the other day on campus. I'm one of the only  YJs there, which is a bit disappointing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of these things is not like the other </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 18:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 18:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Broadway is already wide enough to be a two lane road. They can probably get away with new lights and painting new lines because it's never congested as it is currently.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 02:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speaking of which, do we know what form Kanan and/or Ezra uses? I don't think it's ever been defined.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's still junk just because FCA.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 03:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks very similar, but I didn't think they made 4-door versions until later. I think they only had 2 and 3 doors until the third(fourth?) gen. It looks like a GM model though(so maybe it is Opel?). That front end just screams late 60's-70's GM to me. You might be right though. 

Edit: I think it's a third generation  Dodge/Plymouth/whateverthefuckGM Colt. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 03:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why the newest vehicle I've ever owned was made in '97. Older vehicles are just better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 02:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it is?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 23:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I think the last year the 4runner had a solid axel was 1987. Same with their pickups IIRC.Toyota made the switch pretty early for some reason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 21:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4runner is still IFS. Only SUV with a solid front axel currently sold in the US is the Jeep Wrangler </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 21:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats why I quit playing comp halfway through this season. I got sick of the toxicity around anything Sombra. I just want to have fun :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the best, right after hacking Rein and making his shield goes down, since he immediately becomes the target of literally everyone on the enemy team </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends. If I hack a Genji, I can usually take him out by myself without help. If I hack Rein, it's usually pretty obvious since his barrier goes down. If it's not a character I can take on by myself, I usually get on my mic and call it out to my team though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like it only because it means I have to play other heroes more often if Sombra is already taken.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is true in my ~100 hours of Sombra experience . It's annoying. I think it can also happen with Rein's shield as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah really. I don't play comp anymore because it's way to toxic. I quit halfway through this season. I play to have fun and getting bitched at nonstop is no fun, so I play quickplay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like Bad Religion by Bad Religion on Bad Religion? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Extra excersie is always beneficial barring you have a medical condition such as anorexia, high blood pressure, low heart rate, etc  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 17:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't use the entire military for stuff like this. Legality aside, it would destroy recruitment. Noone would want to join. Military life is shitty enough as it is. This is why the Army Corps of Engineers exists. For people who want to do this sort of stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 03:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first instinct was to think that it was a rip off of Kronos from Star Trek.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 19:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I know. But now my only rifle is my Saiga in 7.62x39 which really isn't worth it to reload since surplus is so cheap.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 17:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely this. I owned 4 or 5 Lee-Enfields at one point but didn't shoot any of them reguarly because .303 is too expensive to justify.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 02:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/prequelmemes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 00:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 18:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interested in the contact info! I'm in NE Ohio so that's not too far from me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 02:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will always think this car is gaudy and hideous. It looks like something Widowmaker would drive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 02:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't a new GT though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Judging from the state of my squadrons 182s. Absolutely not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been a member for 8-9 years. You'll definitely get some opportunities, probably for 172s or 182s since they are the most common. Someone from a sister squadron even got to fly a Air Force C-130, which was a bit terrifying knowing a 15 year old was piloting it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh nice! I've only flown the 182s in  my wing sadly. That being said, I'm not a pilot, so I'll take what I get.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 13:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CAP 182? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. '95 YJ 4-banger. Black with red doors. Currently at UofAkron in Ohio  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 20:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> F-150 based on personal research and a quick Google search.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 02:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't look abandoned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 02:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't in the US either. At least not anymore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 19:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched SW:Rebels. I may be fine. Probably </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 14:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can believe taxation is theft and also believe it is a necessary evil. Same as war. It's murder, but it is sometimes necessary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they actually knew anything about guns, that's what they would try to do. They just see and AR-15 and say "OMG, scary black gun!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 17:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my car? Everywhere. Leaks literally everywhere.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 17:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless your car doesn't have ABS. Then you're fucked. 

Source: My Jeep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they used to be part of a series. It used to go Explorer, Expedition, Excursion as a somewhat SUV equivalent to the F150, F250, and F350 respectively.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah. People will just buy F-series trucks even if they'll never use the bed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 00:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Safety regulations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because their body kits look like riced out shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 01:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coffee, Monster and nicotine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 01:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds like you date shitty people
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 01:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 4cyl is fine. I own two '95 Yjs and both are 4 cylinders. Watch for rust. That's about it. '95 was the only year the body was galvanized, so they tend to be the least rusty. They aren't comfortable to drive, so keep that in mind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
