<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8986</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 20:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, I see. Have you considered going to a doctor to see if there's anything else going on, and why that's happening? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 18:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Natural is does not always mean better 

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Appeal_to_nature

Also, why are you asking for low fiber? If you've just started eating higher fiber food, it can take a month or even 2 to get used to digesting high fiber foods. Unless it's because of an illness you have, I'd stick to it and see if it goes away. Your body has to get used to new foods. Also, with increased fiber intake you have to increase water, too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 18:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I worked at a restaurant in LA that was vegan friendly (so they had daiya, gardein, etc) and no one was vegan or vegetarian, not even the owner. A lot of green washing. They even separated the trash and recycling into multiple compartments on the floor, but at the end of the night it went into the same dumpster. Worst job I'd ever have (not because of green washing but they treated me terribly). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-02 18:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of Reddit is male, though? At least from a survey I remember a few years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-02 17:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From a design POV, I think the magnifying glass works better. It's simple and people know what it is very easily, but might not understand a microscope.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-02 17:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also realize that the host might not be as well versed on the menu and how to change the ingredients around as the waitress. That usually isn't part of the hosts job, and a lot of times hosts are new workers that are in training to become the waitress. It's possible she wasn't questioned about making something vegan, whereas the waitress might have been. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-02 06:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at raw food recipes. Lots of fruits and veggies. Use cronometer.com, as they track how much water comes from your food.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 18:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think so! I don't shop too often but they have a couple of bags listed on their website, but full price. I live near urban so I walked in when they had for sale signs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 08:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm an art major and all I can think of is [ballerinas](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Edgar_Degas). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 07:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. Only buy if there's a sale though. This was a few months back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 06:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got a Matt and Nat bag at urban outfitters for $15. 40% off clearance is the greatest. Check them out if you haven't! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 20:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try using nutritional yeast and salt. Sooo good. Makes it kind of cheesey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-28 21:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Miso is soy! Unless it's digested differently because it's fermented? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-28 17:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went for a week a couple years ago, and again this winter, I'd love to know, too! I was specifically only in Hilo. There's tons of fruits that were amazing to find, and very cheaply at the farmers market (6 papayas for $2!). There's a natural grocery store I went to, which I think was Island Naturals Market. I just did a yelp search, and Sweet Cane Cafe looks good. Listed as vegetarian, not vegan, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 07:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, buffalo cauliflower has been a weekly staple for me probably a year now. Although I use a recipe that's simplified with no spices. Not against spices but franks is so flavorful, I don't know if I need more spices.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 05:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you tried buffalo cauliflower? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 00:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, and here's another based on tomatoes:

http://www.tomatosushi.com/#what-is-tomato-sushi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 00:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the one I was talking about: 

http://thursdayswithwanda.com/2014/06/26/vegan-tuna-salmon-uni/

Although I have no idea if it's any good, or realistic at all! I would probably go into it thinking its another type of sushi as opposed to a fish replacement, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-26 18:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just saw a blog post of sushi made from slowly roasted watermelon. Sounds soo good and strange! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-26 18:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ingredient is usually fish sauce, and sometimes shrimp paste, but it could be made with just soy sauce instead. So both of those ingredients aren't necessary, it doesn't hurt to ask. Fresh kimchi is just kimchi that's 1-2 days old and hasn't started the fermentation process, but the ingredients shouldn't be any different.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-26 17:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An easy way to find places is getting a mobile wifi device (if you have a smartphone). Soo worth it! I've always stayed at airbnbs that specifically rent out mobile wifis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-26 17:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look into vegan and vegetarian lifters! There's a few out there. If you like to cook, it definitely helps but there's tons of protein sources outside of animal products! Tofu, tempeh, seitan, beans (black bean burgers are great).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-26 03:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loved the sign for onion! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-25 19:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate it when people post pics of abused animals because the reason I'm vegan is so theres less of it in the world. I will unfollow people that post that because if I want to learn more about it, I want to do it on my own terms and not as a surprise post. I don't think people should be forced to see these images, omni or vegan, unless they're consenting to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 04:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 8 applied to me, and was why I was omni for a while. I had to learn how to eat anything, including foods that were phobias. I needed to take any amount of restriction out of what I decided to eat. It was important for me to go through this, since restriction and denying food easily led to relapses. I eventually healed and am vegan, though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 07:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know about TJs but the brand I bought had a version that was 5 grain (including rice and barley and stuff like that, I think) and a version that was all soy. So it isn't always filled, but sold as a multigrain option. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 06:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does your rice cooker have a brown rice option? If not, cook it twice. Brown rice usually takes my rice cooker about an hour, double the amount of time as white. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 18:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I go to Berkeley but my friend from UCLA swiped me in and their dining hall was gorgeous and amazing!! Nicer than Berkeley's. It felt like an actual restaurant than a cafeteria. I went to the Asian themed one, I forget the name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 18:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try padmapper or craigslist. Most people commute. Look at west la/palms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 17:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be great if he went vegan! He eats vegetarian at home, and was better at stopping red meat consumption when we decided that a year ago. He also grew up vegetarian and was vegetarian for a few years as an adult.

Unfortunately, I doubt it'd change much if I stopped paying for eating out because of subconscious gender roles and all that junk (I'm F, he's M). Although we've been going to lots of vegan restaurants where I pay for it so he can have a better experience.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 17:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He would've gone shopping himself because he's better at picking out fruits than i am. He's great at finding crisp apples, it's amazing.

There is a difference in consumption, though, because he's a procrastinating shopper and it would've taken time for him to buy it. So it's possible that he waited a few days (especially with more [vegan] food in the house). Meaning, he could've eaten 1 package of cottage cheese for the week instead of 2. That reduces dairy consumption. 

Plus, our relationship is stable enough where it didn't cause any strain (like I stated in the original post). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 16:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in a similar situation. He pays the rent and I do groceries (although during the school year, we're long distance for another year so we both handle our own bills). I also cook waaay more often so it makes more sense that the kitchen is better suited for me. Your suggestion of finding veg options is good but I haven't heard of a good one for cottage cheese. Unfortunately, he still wants milk, yogurt, and cheese, and isn't that much into soy milk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 06:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want to try again, try kale chips. Use salt and nutritional yeast to top it. They become super light and crispy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> how do you split groceries with non-vegan SOs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 05:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind of a specific question. I'm newly vegan, and my SO isn't (although he doesn't purchase any meat while doing groceries). I'm newly vegan so my grocery habits have changed a little (obviously). While I was shopping, I asked if he wanted anything and he asked for cottage cheese. I couldn't buy it for him because I just didn't want to spend my money on that. Is it ok that I just told him to buy it on his own? There was no big argument over this so it didn't cause a strain. I was just wondering what others did in this situation. Is what I did typical or picky? Both?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 11:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an unfortunate side of meeting new people but I prefer it to people who decide to share unsolicited very personal info about themselves. An example being like when I had just met my old roommate, and her mom says to the landlord "she has a different last name than me because my husband was very abusive etc"... It's uncomfortable. There's a spectrum of personal details with how intimately you know someone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 10:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah! I live so close and didn't know about it. Also don't have $45 to spare so I'd agree with you on pricing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 10:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could look into performance anxiety medication, I think one is propranolol. I don't have experience with it but Xanax can cause euphoria and such which you won't get with the former. Also, if you take a low enough dose of Xanax, and stay at that dose, you shouldn't become addicted. I doubt the dr gave you a high dose either since it's hard to function properly at high doses. You can always try it, and know it isn't for you and stop any time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 19:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much! :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 18:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! It doesn't affect me much, but my SO is an athlete (not body builder but prefers strength training) who tries to eat as much protein as possible (but has mostly given up meat). The info is super helpful! I would love it if you had links to sources/studies.

I'm new to veganism and have spent lots of time lurking on fitness subreddits so I'm still more familiar that the more strength training you do, the higher protein you need. They recommend more protein intake if you plateau, for example.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 17:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oils are good when you're only eating 1400 calories. Coming from someone who underate, they're a godsend because you can hide it in stuff you make instead of having to eat more. 

Also, OP, make sure he's counting all of his calories correctly. It's possible that he added extra oil when he was cooking but it's really easy to forget to add that when counting calories.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 17:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be careful with feeding a wide variety of foods as pets can learn how to be picky! If they don't like a certain food, they may not eat it until they get the food that they like. For instance, I take care of a cat (not mine) who is given raw food and kibble, yet the kibble is yummier for her (in the way fast food is yummy for humans I'm guessing). So, she stopped eating the raw food which is much healthier. When I took care of her, I stopped giving her the kibble all together and she eventually ate the raw. It's a lot to think about but most recipes I see with feeding animals whole foods blend or mush it all so they can't eat around it. I wouldn't assume variety affects dogs like they do humans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 17:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since you might know, how is TVP? Also, any downsides you know about using pea protein in protein shakes? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 17:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a sage cafe in culver city which is nice (I think yelp reviews said it's nicer than the other one? Haven't been to the other one yet). 

I just went to Stuff I Eat in inglewood that was really great! Vegan soul food :) 

OP: Los Angeles is huge! Plan out your route well, as traffic can be a real bitch and you can easily spend 1.5 hours just to get from one side of the city to the other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 17:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this guy especially because I'm Japanese and he has great recipes for my palette, and for some common things I eat. His videos are so lovely to watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 19:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously... One of the reasons I live the way I do is so I can see less animal cruelty. I think what helped me the most was cute piglet videos on YouTube, anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 06:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It said vegan cheese. Depends on the recipe... just made one thats based on cashews and nutritional yeast. Sounds healthy enough for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 21:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was Beyonc? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 05:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love those. In terms of vegan resources, I like some of what Unnatural Vegan on YouTube talks about, but of course you have to find out what is and isn't applicable and good science. She doesn't claim to be educated in science or anything but it's refreshing to hear her talk about the "natural" vegans who feel so awesome and whatnot. I really hate that there isn't more science-based stuff on veganism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 11:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good to know! I never really used those features but I just remember seeing some of the more specific options asking for payment, so I wasn't sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 04:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you aren't opposed to OkCupid, I *think* you can search by people's diets (probably have to pay).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 03:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not my experience today driving on PCH near the 10. Goddamn beachgoers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 18:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't read either of those so I can't compare. The book doesn't talk about animal treatment much, if that's something you're interested in, but a lot about how capitalism is ruining human rights and diets.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 06:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could that be kind of like vegan version of pork and beans (the sweet kind from the canned section)? I'm just trying to imagine the flavor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 06:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about the vegan version of what they recommended? Like instead of a milkshake or ice cream, use the soy alternative (or whatever you usually eat). I remember healing pretty quickly and I did all 4 of my wisdom teeth at once too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 04:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep... Read Fast Food Nation in my sociology class. It's so bad. My first reaction is to feel upset at how someone could work at a slaughterhouse, but they don't want to either. The people that make horrible decisions (let's say, size of cages or whatever) often are sanitized from the whole experience. The treatment of both humans and animals are really bad in slaughterhouses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 21:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been watching vegan cooking videos on youtube, and the same thing happens (for those specific videos!). I got an ad for bacon, and another for outback steakhouse. What the hell? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 09:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about reducing types of animals, such as cutting out red meat first?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 10:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you know it isn't just leftover of the mask? Seems to be the same color... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 12:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it's very "little" (with caffeine and alcohol...) but it's so good- tiramisu! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 12:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I make something like this and pour Annie's goddess dressing on... Soo good. Sometimes some black beans or roasted garbanzo beans on top, too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 11:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is red toner and red dye very different? What would be the pro to using the toner?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool. So would you mix a diluted mauve (purple+red/pink?) over bleached pale yellow? Or tone first? Also on the topic of oxidizing, if you can answer... when I get a bottle of toner I end up using only half of the bottle. Will the bottle that has opened (but closed lid) oxidize quickly as well? Or only after mixed with developer?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would I get this color hair I keep seeing in Japan? (ash blonde, slightly pink/grey undertones?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 14:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm traveling in Japan right now and I keep seeing this type of hair color. It's a very ash blonde, but there's a sort of pinkiness. Almost a grey-silver-pink. Some photos of what I'm looking for:

[\[1\]](https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/aa/aa/ee/aaaaee5c8a6921470e6bc8df6c3be82e.jpg) [\[2\]](https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/236x/a9/bb/9e/a9bb9e4d3e8943517e51d045417976d9.jpg)

(I know these are different colors, but I can't really find the specific color nor do I need a specific color). 

I'm pretty platinum blonde right now (from dark hair). What products would I use? I usually tone Wella in T-18. My guess right now is leave in Wella T-14 toner for too long, maybe 35-40 mins (dangerous?), with a very very diluted (more diluted than pastel hair) cool pink and maybe Ion in Titanium. 

Also, I'm really used to having colors in my hair so I don't really care if I go too purple or pink or whatever. I'm wondering if there's a specific product I can get in the US for this color, too. 

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 03:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! We're going to Haneda. 12 hours total between check out and the actual flight. We might go to a love hotel for some rest. Thanks for the link! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 03:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By accompanied, do you mean it's co-ed? Looking to kill about 9 hours before check out and my flight departure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 23:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe Violet's ugliest dress? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 06:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to buy the phones as an upfront cost, and then each device per month is a base rate of $6. Then you add the minutes, text, and data of however much you (and whoever you add) use.

Example of two devices would be:

One time payment of each device (your example of $170) x 2

Monthly payment of $6 per device (so $12 for two devices, etc). If you don't use your phone at all, lets say you're traveling, it'll be $12 total. Say you texted, called, and used data, you'd follow this:

https://ting.com/rates

It's much simpler than I described, I think. I switched about a year ago and love them. Not for power users, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 07:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here... I still get nervous, but kind of regular test-taking kind of nervous. I'm pretty good at it, though. People tell me I don't seem nervous. 

I'll have a panic attack before going to a party, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When would I use a protein treatment when I bleach and tone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 06:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the aphogee 2 step protein treatment. I understand it's best to use it before using dye, would toner be the same? I'm doing my roots right now. Bleach, protein, toner (with 20 vol dev), condition? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 00:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say make half the amount and refrigerate the rest. Frozen cream cheese sounds like it'd change the texture of it all, although I don't know how it'll reheat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 19:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I just went to an ENT doc and they asked me questions like how long I've had it, but no tests. Kinda sucks but oh well!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 17:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No idea what causes mine. I'd love to know though! I don't think I'd go under any medical procedure unless it was something simple like nasal spray or something. Or if it benefitted me in other ways (like cured my allergies or something?) But if it was invasive like cochlear implants, I don't think so. I think the thing that is the hardest with me is knowing when food goes bad, and I can't smell if something I'm cooking is burning. Those are the only "everyday" challenges. Otherwise it doesn't really affect me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 08:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every single thing you've written describes me, down to the congenital anosmia. Crazy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 01:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You get to sign up for half of your classes, so I'd recommend it. Otherwise, I think it's delayed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm traveling. What foods will last in the fridge, pre-cut for a couple of weeks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 21:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to make it easy for who takes care of my beardie. What foods should I give in advance? I'm thinking collard greens, zucchini, carrots, mixed in a container. Would that last a couple of weeks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 09:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess, but psychologists don't need MDs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 09:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Psychological?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 05:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what works while sharing my apartment while I'm away. I don't really care if my roommate's side is messy because I can easily disconnect myself from the mess. I guess that's what I should bring back home. 

My parents have always had separate bedrooms while I was growing up so it's totally understandable! And those rich people who have their own houses that live next to each other... I wonder if it's similar issues they had haha.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 04:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've been together for 6, lived together for 4, and it's still difficult. What I've been trying to do is to help by example. Not sure if it works. I get lazier when I'm at home too, though. The place back home is a much bigger space (3bed2.5bath) vs 1bed1bath. But I guess I knew this going into the relationship... his last place was really horrible. I remember finding knives on the ground in the kitchen... and he had a dog! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 00:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's so many things that add up, I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 23:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. His car's interior right now is black with red stitching. Fancy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 21:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same. I don't really like wearing my favorite color (sea foam/mint). It's too bright for me, as I usually wear neutrals. Same with the SO- he likes red but mostly wears black and neutrals. I don't think I knew his favorite color until probably 3 years in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clean while I'm away at school, but I get back to being messy once I'm back home </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 09:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've noticed this during my breaks at school, and summer's coming up. I'm perfectly clean while I'm in my apartment during the year. Then, when I go back home to my fiance, I have much less motivation to improve. During the year, I don't let dishes pile up, and am looking for ways to improve my surroundings. Right now I'm feeling this, about how I can't wait to get home and paint and clean out the pantry, etc. But when I actually get there, I just sit at home and be lazy. My fiance's behaviors don't help as he's much messier than I am (when he visits my apt during the year, things get messier). How do I work around that? Any reasons you guys can think of why this keeps happening?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 00:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eating out is expensive. Already discussed above how it's restaurant-rich, but not really grocery store rich. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 23:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Berkeley. Super white.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 23:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably about a little over a mile, but there's tons of stops because I live right next to campus. I could walk it but I'd rather not walk a mile with heavy bags. It's really not bad, but I live near Oakland which I've heard have parts that are actual food deserts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 20:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know the law, but it would make sense if it was related to your job. Like getting a DUI when your job is being a truck driver or taxi driver. I think boxing and domestic violence can be paired up similarly, but I don't know anything about the sport (or any sports, really).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 19:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They still aren't in walking distance from me, but a 20 min bus ride is tolerable as opposed to an hour. I just live in a college town where people aren't as expected to cook much. But also not a food desert at all, because theres tons of restaurants. Food deserts tend to be poor areas, whereas where I live isn't poor, just too many kids with money to spend on eating out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 11:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm from an urban part of California and it's much more expensive, like $4 for a dozen eggs (everywhere- trader joes, Safeway...). I also don't have a car so I'm limited in where to get my groceries because I don't want to bus an hour just to save a few dollars. So no ethnic markets or anything :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 18:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I put up that a space in my apt was available because I don't want to come back to Berkeley over the summer just to look for a roommate. I'm happy that people are looking now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 18:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on what your money is worth to you. The reason it's so popular is because it's only $10 a semester for students.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 06:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the other hand, there are tons of computers at school to use. If you have a smartphone to check email often, I think the rest should be fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 06:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it similar to TVP?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 06:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought this was going to be a funny pun :(

Looks yummy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 02:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on the style of art you're doing, but I've seen using a palette knife of a light color as a highlight work really well. If the rest of the painting is very smooth, though, it might not work out. The key would be to not blend, but to just lay the paint down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 21:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have fresh eggs, [tamago kake gohan](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tamago_kake_gohan) is the best yummy/lazy food. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
