<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3132</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Merry Christmas! A few questions regarding the holidays of an IB student </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 20:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are you guys celebrating the merry days of December? Travelling? Studying? A mix of the two? 

What about presents? What are you asking for from the man in red? Something related to your study? 

Happy Holidays! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 19:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out /r/gainit

That sub really helped me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 06:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best squid I've ever had was in Naples! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 08:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a savior! Thank you very much. We will definitely contact the students down at SAE Dubai. 

Renting is also a primary option for us. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Help] Small high school band recording </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 11:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there, r/Dubai

I am a guitarist in a three piece punk band based in Dubai. We are in our final year of school here and would like to record a short acoustic album of covers of songs we feel define us and our lives, to this point, in Dubai.

Our only problem is: lack of equipment. We are good on guitars, amps, an audio interface... but not microphone. 

We would like to know if there is anyone on this sub who wants to work with us to record this short cover album? Or if anyone has a microphone that we could borrow/rent?

Thanks in advance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 07:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, thanks for the reply. At this point, I will probably keep at the 2700 for this upcoming week and then when exams strike, go to maintenance. Would it still be wise, if I have time, to work out on perhaps the weekend if I have time (clear mind etc)? Thanks again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 07:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck on your exams! 
Unfortunately, I will be completing, on average, 2 exams in a day for 2 consecutive weeks. The only days where I will be able to wake up at 6, eat, study, gym, return home- are the weekends. 

Eating for me is no problem. I will probably end up cutting to maintenance cals and see how I go from there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Help] School exams and gaining </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 08:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, in 1 weeks time I start exams. These are extremely important for my predicted grades which will get sent to whatever uni I apply to. 
Problem is, I am worried about time in the gym interfering with my study. I know that I can simply stop for the two weeks but I am worried about fat gain as I am on 2700 cal a day as a female 16 year old. I also want to note that there is no real possible way I will be able to be working out in the 2 weeks as travel time to the gym on top of workout time will be shite.

Is there any way that I can decrease caloric intake for the 2 weeks and not work out? Or what other options do I have to keep as much strength as I have built and minimise fat gain?

I am planning on beginning a new program following the exams as I will be in holidays and can focus on gym. This will hopefully be a power lifting and conditioning program. 

Thanks in advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 11:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy has a point! I'm in for a chat and for the meetup! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 11:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much! Have you got any tips regarding how to manage my eating without getting too pedantic about it? As a student, I don't have the time to really sit down and think about what I am going to eat and when, and then log that into MFP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Help] How should I split my macros in a day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 05:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello all,

I am a recovering anorexic and am seeing a dietitian. I am 16, female, 167cm, 50kg (pretty sure). For the past 3 months I have been following a weight gain program strictly eating clean foods. This includes: chicken breast, lean beef, kangaroo, oats, brown rice, sweet potato, apples, bananas, peanut butter, nuts, wpi and lots of veg (broccoli, brussels etc). This, according to my dietitian is a total of 2700 cal. I have been gaining weight and I have been getting stronger. 

I am also doing a beginners power-lifting routine from the liftbigeatbig website 3 days a week. I also walk my dog every night.

Recently, he has suggested that I use myfitnesspal and attempt to eat intuitively, though stick to macros that he gives me. This is quite daunting for me considering the last time I used MFP, I was purposely attempting to lose weight at less than 1000 cal in a day. After I finish my upcoming exams, I am willing to give this IIFYM-esque approach a go. However, I am not sure how I would split the macros throughout the day. Do I try eat more carbs at certain times of the day, or more fats, or more protein? I want to have consistent energy throughout my school day and balanced hormonal levels. 

Would any of you suggest using myfitnesspal or should I just ask my dietitian to keep me on a diet/schedule of eating so I don't have to think about it.

I really wanna make them sweet gains bros, thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 11:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there! Another teen here :) How about you post a teenager meetup? Maybe it will spark the attention of some others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 05:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Erm.. Breakfast was oats, protein powder, frozen strawberries, walnuts and peanut butter as a shake
Snack was apple, banana, nuts
Lunch was chicken, sweet potato and broccoli
Afternoon snack was same as breakfast
Dinner was chicken, rice, veggies, spinach, avocado
More nuts. yeeeee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 05:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Started PLing 1st of October.


167cm (5'5 I think), 110lbs, 16 years old


Squat 121.2


Bench 66


Dead 165.2


Any tips? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 06:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 19:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Went as Lara Croft(ish) for Halloween, then got this guy's number. SCORE
 http://imgur.com/nNYw6aK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 07:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [There Is - Box Car Racer](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6K02NBPd7G8)

I have always enjoyed this live version of There Is. I know it isn't AVA but Tom performed it at an AVA concert (I think).

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 06:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THANK YOU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Advice] Don't know how to move ahead w/ Halloween party kiss </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 16:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello comrades!

I am extremely happy and giddy and my emotions are crazy out of control because I HAD MY FIRST KISS LAST NIGHT. We didn't make out but, oh well (later ;) ) Oh... the joys of Halloween! 

But... I have no idea how to move forward. I really like this guy and he said last night that he really likes me too. We have been texting but it seems kind of like small talk... What do I talk about? Help! Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 06:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, it wasn't available at the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 14 Meals for $38 -Meal Prepping in Dubai </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 09:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 14:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where is this located? Thanks for the tip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 16:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Portraits are an interesting one to discuss. Especially since they are presented as "extremely accurate and detailed pieces of art". Thanks for the input. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 16:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting, what you said regarding the naked warriors. I never considered how artists could merely be attempting to appeal to whoever is viewing (in that case, purchasing) their art. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 15:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the insight. I also find that in these 'pieces of art', whether they are battle scenes or photographs, the artist purposely creates emphasis on something they want to draw attention to and downplays the role of other variables within the art. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
