<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6210</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm such a mess </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 05:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a big wreck now. I binged and purged 3 times yesterday and twice today. It's getting out of control right now. I don't know what to do anymore. I feel like absolute garbage. I keep telling myself that today will be different but I always end up binging and purging. I need this to stop. I can't keep going like this. I just want to starve myself

Edit: I know I keep posting about my troubles with binging lately. I just don't know where else to turn to. Sorry if all my posts are annoying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 21:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's totally why I want to be skeletal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 20:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty much addicted to electrolyte drinks. They really help, especially after binging and purging </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 17:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I binged 4 times yesterday and purged 3 times. That's the most I've done in years, I feel like absolute shit too. 

Try to get some electrolytes, because purging really fucks them up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 04:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cocoa (147)

Lunch: Egg whites with partially skim mozzarella and Sriracha (120), celery, red pepper and cucumber (25)

Then shit hit the fan. I had my first appointment with my dietician today. I found out my weight was higher than I thought. It obviously triggered a b/p session because ed logic. I got Starbucks venti hot chocolate, 2 cookies (600!!!!). Purged. Giant bowl of oatmeal, purged. Whole bag of chips, purged. I feel like absolute shit. I'm still eating because I'm disgusting, but I won't purge again. I ate most of my binge foods, so I won't go grocery shopping until my safe foods run out. Sorry this turned into a super long post. I'm a huge mess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 03:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to, but I have a feeling there isn't enough people in this sub. I doubt anyone from my city is on here

Edit: I forgot to say where I lived, I'm in the great Canadian prairies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 21:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry that you feel like this. I'm kind of going through the same thing. I don't really have any advice to give you. One piece of advice I have is to put a heating pad or hot water bottle on your stomach, it will help with the bloating and pain of binging </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 17:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love to watch cooking shows and I have a tumblr with a bunch of recipes that I would never eat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 16:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to be a doctor in a field related to bones too! I just love skeletons </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 04:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is me these days. I hate it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 03:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm at 42 hours, I was hoping to go longer, but I think I have to break it. I feel super guilty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Emotions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 02:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have alexithymia, which means I can't identify emotions. Both in myself and other people. Most of the time it's fine because I'm numb. But lately I've been feeling emotions, but I don't really know what they are. I don't know how to handle them. I have no idea how articulate what I'm feeling most of the time.

I think this is triggering my binging and I hate it. I'm 41 hours into a fast and I feel a binge coming on, but I think I can push through it. 

Any advice? I hate feeling like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 02:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Peppermint white chocolate tea (5)

Lunch: Vegetable bouillon (15), ephedrine and diet coke

Dinner: Vitamin water zero (0)

Snacks: mio sport (0)

I'm 41 hours into my first fast and I can feel a binge coming on. I'm drinking vitamin water zero right now and watching Netflix. But it's only 7pm, I don't know if I'll be able to last until bed time

Edit: I ended up binging and purging. Fml, I don't know why I can't stop binging! I don't know what to do anymore, I've tried everything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 19:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fasting today too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 16:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fasting today too. I also fasted yesterday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 15:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the uncertainty of the future is triggering me to binge, but idk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 02:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm an omnivore, but with my restriction I usually don't end up eating meat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 01:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: White chocolate peppermint tea (5)

Lunch Diet coke with ephedrine (0)

Dinner: Vegetable bouillon (15)

Snacks: Mio sport (0)

Total: 20 calories

Since nothing is helping me to stop binging, I've decided to try a liquid fast. I have no idea how long I'll go, I'm hoping at least 2 days.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 00:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'm worried about him too. Hopefully he's alright </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 22:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that's what I'm going to try. I also have a friend who's going to come visit a few evenings, hopefully that will help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Change in routine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 20:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a huge creature of habit. I love my routine and it freaks me out when I have to change it. 

I have to change my routine for the next 2 weeks and I'm really worried. My mom is on a 2 week trip. Since I'm not mentally/physically healthy enough to be to left alone my brother is staying with me. 

Normally I'm home alone from 8 am to 5 pm, when my mom is at work. But my brother works the evening shift, so I'll be home alone from 3 pm to 11 pm. 

I'm really worried that it'll increase my binging because I'm usually an evening binger and if I'm alone all evening I might binge more often. 

I hate changes in my routine, I'm so worried about the next 2 weeks.

I also started a fast because my binging is out of control. Hopefully this will restart my self control around food and help me restrict and lose weight. I have no idea how long I'll go, hopefully as long as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 17:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, me too! Good luck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 17:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fasting today too because I've been binging too much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 17:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is super inspiring, even though I'm a girl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 05:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get pretty stinky burps too, but not as horrible as my farts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tmi, binge farts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 04:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is kind of tmi (sorry), but when I binge I get really bad gas and it's super stinky. Like the worst smelling farts ever and the smell stays for a really long time. I was wondering if anyone else had that happen to them after a binge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 04:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry about it. I broke my new years resolution on the first day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 03:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can relate to this so much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 03:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I probably do, haha. I'm also a big hypochondriac </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 02:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American apparel and Aritizia carry very small sizes, but it's super expensive. I usually buy my jeans from the gap because they seem to make pretty small jeans there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 02:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cocoa (147)

Lunch: Egg whites with partially skim mozzarella and sriracha (120), celery, red bell pepper and cucumber (25)

Dinner: Vegetable broth with soya sauce and shirataki noodles (31)

Snacks: diet coke (0) and mio sport (0)

Total: 323 calories

I did my first EC stack today, hopefully it will help me stop binging and help me lose weight. I'm using pseudoephedrine, hopefully it works as well as ephedrine. If anyone knows the difference between the 2, I'd love to know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 00:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You shouldn't feel bad! You went so long without purging, you should be proud of that. Everyone slips up sometimes, it's nothing to feel bad about </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 18:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My ass looks like 2 deflated balloons </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 17:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's because of a lack of waste in your body and because your intestines aren't working as hard. They are a muscle and they lose strength if you don't work them enough.

I will take a stool softener to help things move along, or if I haven't pooped in a week I'll take a laxative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 17:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate my ass now. It's flat and saggy, I have really bad anorexia ass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 09:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a weird fantasy that I have cancer. I like to imagine and plan what I would do if I got diagnosed. 

I actually wanted to tell people I had cancer when I dropped out of school this semester because of my ed, but my mom wouldn't let me. 

I'm really fucked up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 06:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of it yes, but most of it no. I usually binge on foods that I eat everyday or my mom's food. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 05:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I binged reallllllyyyyy badly today. Peanut buttter (almost half a jar), cookies, chips, bread, popcorn, oatmeal, cheese, ice cream, candy. So just a bunch of super high cal food. Urg I am disgusting. I'm taking laxatives soon to flush this disgusting food out of me.

One good thing is that I think I'm sick of peanut butter now. PB is usually a binge trigger for me. So if I'm sick of it maybe I won't be triggered to binge as much. 

I am so goddamn sick of binging. I'm at my last straw, I've decided to start doing EC stacks. Hopefully it'll stop my binges. I need to lose these last few pounds quickly and binging isn't helping at all!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 23:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I do, but I need to buy more wool, but I don't have enough money </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need to stop binging! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 22:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep binging these days. I don't know why. I think it's partially because of depression and boredom, but I need to stop this. I binged so badly today. Cheese, bread, about half a jar of peanut butter, chocolate, cookies. Urg, I am so disgusting. I'm definitely taking a laxative today to get rid of this. 

I just bought some binge food, I want to eat it, but I feel so sick already. I don't know what to do with it.

I'm definitely starting an EC stack tomorrow. I'm going to try to go a week without binging, this post is my way to put that goal out in the world which will hopefully keep me accountable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 18:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I could go to school. I had to drop out because of this.

I spend my days laying around my house, which is really depressing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 16:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so depressed, as per usual. I have no motivation to do anything. I barely have an attention span anymore. I try to start a new series, but after 3 or 4 episodes I'm bored and start something new, and the cycle repeats. I don't know what to do with myself anymore. 

I wish I could sleep more, I get 8 hours a night, but I want to sleep more because it's less time living in my boring hell-hole of a life.

I'm just so sick of this

Edit: urg, I really want to binge right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 04:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You pretty much described me. The last sentence of the first paragraph is 100% me these days. 

My life is so boring, I just lay around my house doing nothing. Thank god I don't binge everyday, but I binge too much for my liking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 02:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Simply egg whites (60)

Lunch: Simply egg whites with partially skim mozzarella and sriracha (120), celery, red bell pepper and cucumber (25)

Dinner: Tortilla pizza (144)

Snacks: Rice cake with 1 1/2 tbsp light peanut butter (155), diet coke (0) and mio sport (0)

Total: 504 calories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 01:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm definitely a big stoner. I don't really have any advice to give you because I don't get the munchies.

Try to get low cal snacks, drink lots of calorie free drinks.

I wish I could help you out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 23:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's an app called IMQuit, it looks pretty good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 23:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love spicy food. I have garlic hot sauce that I put on almost every meal (except breakfast), but I'm almost out and they don't sell it at my grocery store </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 22:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to get a nice concave stomach, but that stopped lately. I think it's because I'm binging more though. Now my stomach always sticks out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 21:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I measure my arms and thighs with my hands everyday. My fingers overlap a little less than an inch at the thickest part of my thighs right now. 

I also use a tape measurer once a week.

I like counting my ribs.

My pants are all too big now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 20:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really bloated lately. I never have a flat stomach anymore, even after I poop. It's really weird.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Experiences in recovery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 04:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, as many of you have probably seen in some of my posts, I'm going into treatment soon. I'm going into an inpatient program for about 8 weeks, then outpatient for a while

I was wondering what people's experience in recovery has been like. I would love to hear how it went for you. If anyone has any advice as well I'd love to hear it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 02:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like today will be a binge day for me too... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 01:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know how you feel. I can't seem to go a few days without binging these days </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 00:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's 84lbs, it was my weight when I was 12, before I hit puberty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
