<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5711</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 00:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no cake for me thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-17 06:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how did it save your life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-17 00:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they claim I'm getting cancer 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-17 00:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i mean when i actually drink soda i only drink diet and my family gets so mad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't care if you say Diet Coke is bad for me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-17 00:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have heard it all diet soda will make you sick.

diet coke will do this or that 

frankly i don't care i am NOT drinking soda filled with calories and sugar 

not fucking happening </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TITP have Fatorexic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-16 23:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i found something interesting 

Fatorexic
opposite of anorexic; People who are in reality heavy, fat, overweight etc. but see themselves as very thin or underweight, boney etc.
An exmaple of a fatorexic: a heavier person squeezing into pants 4 sizes too small and thinking they look like hot shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TITP Definition </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 22:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i am trying to explain to my wife what fat logic means and oppression and all those terms mean could you give me a good definition for them all:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British columbia hates pets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 07:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i just moved to bc have been looking EVERYWHERE for an apartment 
i have 2 dogs 

it seems like every place in all of bc hated pets every single place i have seen 200+ is NO PETS 

wtf is wrong with this province  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 01:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats not unpopular for people who keep in shape but VERY unpopular for fatties with no self control  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 22:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i don't think it should be taken down.

anything that is posted on the internet is fair game unless everyone forgot how the internet works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 22:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> look at them teeth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 05:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> considering im a nutritionist i fully believe that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quiting smoking is fucking easy just do it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 04:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i smoked for 5 years almost a pack a day 
and almost a year ago i quit smoking because my partners father died of lung cancer  i didn't crave them i didn't get moody i just moved on with my life 

my sister has only been smoking for 3 years and smokes the same as i did and she says she just cant quit ( smoked with both her pregnancies) 

my mother smokes has been for about 15 years had to buy oxygen because she cant breath ( she's only 38) then fucking stop smoking its really not that hard just have some discipline 

god its not that hard  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-12 01:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> holy fucking shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-12 01:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i don't think  pregnancy is any reason to let your self go 

and that looks like a 2-3 month old baby so  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I fucking hate guitars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 02:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i think they sound like shit unless mixed in with other music.

my mother plays professionally and every time she has to practice i cringe and almost have to leave the house good god its annoying. 

then she gets offended because she thinks i hate her singing or she's a bad player thats not true but to me the sound of the cords is like nails on a chalk bored for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 02:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how what how do you poop??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-10 22:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> only children are superior to those with siblings 

and i am only having one child. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-10 05:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have said it before and i will say it again 
i don't have fat people i hate their excuse their denial and their refusal to change but expect others to change for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-10 05:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is your mother something called a Truther or call people sheeple  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google is not a DR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-10 01:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> google is not a doctor and Youtube is NOT a news site 

yes goodgle is great but it can not diagnose you and it can not do lab work 

and youtube is not a news site yes very good but not everything on there is real 

and on the google thing my mom hasn't been to a doctor in years and has decided she has a rare form of leukaemia and is finding alternative medicines to try 

she got this all from google and she says that she will never go to a doctor because they don't know what they are talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 23:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm related to gene wilder he was married to my aunt gilda radner 

:) just thought it was cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 00:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> um gross
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 04:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we have a lot of problems she is always telling me to shut up because i make her annoyed , gives me the finger, tells me that i shouldn't feel cold because she's warm , tells me i am acting like a child when i cry ( even over my friend losing her son) thats not the worst of it but i think 99% of the time i deserve it i mean i do make her upset.
but she has NEVER hit me so  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 04:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> get over yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Me [20F] with my [31 F] privacy in marriage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 03:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Side: 20 year old female i have a lot of depression and the only way i have ever been able to relax is writing in a journal. It makes me happy and calm but my wife says that i should not keep anything from her, that is could be deceitful and will read it when I'm not around
i just want 1 thing that is just mine
so question is is it ok for a married person to have some privacy (journal) from the other


---   
**tl;dr** i want to have 1 little thing to my self  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Privacy in marriages </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 03:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Imgur username. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 05:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 05:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you made my life  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 05:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> let me just pack my bag you can have the house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 05:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what I'm just saying we DO have an obesity epidemic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 05:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i actually really want the eat less shirt 

who cares it apples to like half of the USA  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 05:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you should post this to /r/childfree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 05:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm getting my masters in nutritional health  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 05:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes you are right but i am anorexic with a BMI of 16.2 and have many friends with anorexia we always push for recover we don't want to see are friends sick  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 05:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they really do but at the same time they are NO worse then TITP but pro ana really encourages doctors and recovery  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 05:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i don't know how its possible and they co-sleep as well so how they found time i will never know 

they also said that they were using condoms and birth control  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 01:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> actually there are to many children in foster care from teen moms 
there actually are not enough privet adoptions for newborns.

and its not discouraged anymore teen pregnancy now is just another thing that happened i think in my school over 70% of the girls were pregnant people don't care anymore.

then i think that everyone from 10-21 should have to have mandatory birth control  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 01:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i actually want the Eat less shirt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 01:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i was really nervous to talk to a councillor so i wrote a letter and handed it to her it had my name on it she called me down a about an hour later and by then i knew she understood and she could direct the conversation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teen Pregnancy should be illegal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 00:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i know thats crazy but i have teen moms in my close family.

My mom was a teen 2X 17 and 18 

my sister was and is a teen  17 and 18

aunt 16 and 18 

Plus more family members.

and to be completely honest teens can not raise children.
My mother was a terrible parent, My sister got pregnant 2 weeks after giving birth to her first one and she cant make eggs and refuses to cook. 
Aunt never finished grade school 

in fact I'm the only girl in my family who even graduated high school.

teens should not be allowed to be pregnant i think that every single one that has children should have to give it up for adoption. Then should have a fine.

i might just be mean because i come from the teen pregnancy capital of canada.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 00:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hi i think i could help your life sounds very similar to mine 

only I'm 20 and a girl is there anyway you could talk to a guidance councillor or a principle that you trust i know it sounds very ya ya what ever but really its true they will 

if you need to talk I'm only a few clicks away :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 08:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> im in a wheelchair you ass hat and i use voice recognition software to type for me

it is still brand new to it and i need to train it so thanks for pointing that out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 07:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i would like to try to change but only because i know its wrong to feel this way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 07:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NASTY  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
