<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8657</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to eat regularly when I can't exercise due to physical limitation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 03:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't eat regularly enough. I never have any energy as a result of it, but I have a hard time convincing myself to eat on a regular basis, because when I do, I gain weight. I'm already overweight, I don't want to become obese. I have a bad lower back that prevents me from doing as much exercising as I would like. I'm feeling really stuck. Anyone have experience with something similar, and/or have advice on what I can do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Research Article: Defining Purging Disorder in Practice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 03:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of our readers suggested [this article](http://eatingdisordersreview.com/nl/nl_edr_19_3_1.html) by a Professor at University of Iowa, Iowa City, might be helpful to some of you. It distinguishes between Purging Disorder and other forms of eating disorders </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My Eating Disorder Therapist Has An Eating Disorder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 02:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a crazy scenario. So my therapist and I are tight. Like more than therapist-patient tight. I've actually worked in her office SPECIALIZING IN eating disorders despite the fact that I've had an eleven-year eating disorder. I'm good in this population, no denying it. The thing is my therapist has had a past of ED's (honestly at this point most therapist's who specialize in ED's have had one at some point) but she has clearly relapsed. Emaciated and so very triggering. And unfortunately my coworkers at the time confirmed it. She's getting worse.

How am I supposed to take the advice of my therapist about treatment when she's the one who needs to be in there herself? Because we're so close, do I just bring it up? That might ruin the bond we have. But I feel it has the potential to be destructive and I give her excuses because she's had my back for this job and stuff. I'm lost. Any advice is welcome.

Please notify /u/hellofriendsitsme when you respond </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Can you still have an ED if it looks nothing like the textbooks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 04:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a 21 year old university student who has had a lifelong struggle with food. Things really started to go downhill in high school, but never enough to do anything about it. Then when I moved away to university, especially after 1st year when I had to start cooking for myself, things fell apart even more.

I think about food all the time, but not in a good way. I skip meals, then eat a lot. I seem to either restrict, or go completely the other way and eat bad food and often lots of it. I'm very overweight, and trust me, this isn't my opinion. I've always been overweight, but I've ballooned since starting university.

My problem is, a very close friend of mine is recovering AN. Her case is quite "textbook". But my... whatever it is doesn't seem to match anything. But I feel that this is fallen into ED territory. But some meals, and even as much as a day, I can be pretty fine and not have the thoughts. Does that negate a possible ED? I feel like to be able to recover I need to own whatever this is, but I'm worried if I use the term ED, they won't believe me, take me seriously. Especially since I'm good at hiding it, and not even remotely skinny. I told my mom when I first asked for financial support to start therapy two years ago, and she outright denied what I said, even as I was sobbing to her after getting the courage to tell her.

Sorry, that was really wrong, I'm just super conflicted and having a lot of trouble. I need to start to do something, as if I continue on this path my weight gain will be incredibly harmful to my health, but I feel like I can't go forward if I don't figure out what I'm up against.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: BED Recovery and Substance Abuse - How do I fight two battles at once? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 04:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've tried to keep this as short as possible as per the sidebar guidelines, so I apologize if this is a wall of text because there is some history, but here we go: I've been seeing a therapist for the last year and she referred me to a psychiatrist, who diagnosed me with BED. I've finally come to the point of acceptance and am gathering all the information, tools and support I need to recover. I'm going to continue seeing my therapist, requested an appointment with a dietitian, and I am waiting for a group BED class that my insurance covers but will not start until the middle of June. Walking out of the psychiatrists office, I felt like I've been ignoring a problem that has been staring me at the face for so many years, and I cannot stand to wait another day to start recovering.

I feel confident and motivated to start this process and I think I have all I need to overcome this. But there is one issue that I see repeatedly mentioned but with no explanation about how to handle this while recovering from BED: co-occurring substance abuse.

Last year when I settled into a new comfortable job and home, I made a conscience decision to "get healthy." I quit smoking cigarettes after 10 years of being a smoker. I wouldn't say I'm completely "smoke-free" since I smoke socially now and again. I'm satisfied it's not an every day thing anymore. Then there is marijuana, which I have been using almost daily for the last 8 years. When I quit smoking cigarettes, of course my marijuana intake went up because I just "had to smoke something." Whether it's marijuana or tobacco, I know I'm addicted to smoking. It's worth noting I'm not much of a drinker. I do drink socially when invited to, but the truth is that I'm a tank so when I do drink, it inevitably leads to binging. This happens only about once or twice a month, if at all.

What I've discovered is that my BED and my substance abuse are interrelated in that I believe I've been using food and substances to mask my emotions or other underlying issues. But when it comes to recovery, I find myself in a dilemma and I find myself swaying between two approaches and I cannot figure out which one is right for me. The dilemma is this: I'm thinking of going sober all at once so I can fully address my BED, but I've found that in the past, where I address "one at a time" then use of the other substances or binging increases.

Many say "don't quit too many vices at once," and to take them on one at a time. I've been doing that with tobacco in my efforts to "get healthy" and when I quit smoking tobacco, I gained weight because I was binging more. Thus, quitting substances will exacerbate the binging. On the other hand, I don't think I can fully address my BED without quitting marijuana because marijuana doesn't make me binge, but it makes me lazy and reduces my awareness. Quitting drinking I know I can do since I don't do it much anyway. This all leads me to question whether going completely sober (no smoking anything or drinking) is the answer so that I can recover from BED with full awareness, but this is exactly what is commonly advised against.

My question for you fine people of Reddit is if anyone has gone through and eating disorder and substance abuse, whether it's drinking or smoking? How did you handle it? Did you tackle the substance abuse first or the ED? Did you do both at the same time? Did you go completely sober? What kind of treatment did you seek? What was/wasn't helpful?

Please, I will appreciate any and all light shed on this issue since I feel like I've dug myself into a hole. I believe I can make it out, I would just like some insight/encouragement before the next time I see my therapist.

Thank you and much love 3
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request; want to lose weight but fear relapse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 04:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So recently I've been working out more and I love the effect it's had on my life - I'm happier, more productive, crazy sex drive, etc. Another great effect is that I'm losing weight naturally; I'm almost close to the weight I was at when I was suffering from anorexia/BED a few years ago.

My concern is that I want to keep losing weight. I like how I feel in my body and feel like I would be happier at a slightly lower number (I'm well within the healthy BMI range now, nothing scary). But I'm afraid going lower will trigger old disordered habits.

Has anyone done this successfully? Is it even possible to avoid old habits when doing this? I don't want to trigger myself but... I want to be leaner and in prime shape. Any advice is welcome :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Had disordered eating for 8 years, recovered but now want to lose weight without slipping back into disordered thoughts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 04:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello all. This is my first time posting, just recently found this subreddit and thought it would be a perfect place to ask about this.

I was anorexic for about 8 years, from middle school until my early 20s. It got to a point where I wouldn't eat for a few days at a time, especially when I started living alone where no one could track my eating. I started fainting somewhat frequently and that's when I realized that I was doing some major damage to my body. The turning point for me was not eating for a few days and then going to a pool party where I was in the Texas sun for hours. On my way home, I fainted while driving and ended up totaling my car on the freeway. Thankfully no one was hurt, but it was a huge wake up call that I needed to change my relationship to food.

I finally recovered after a big move to another city and a boyfriend who loved me dearly and helped me see the error of denying myself food. I gained quite a bit of weight while I was with him but was still a somewhat healthy size. Once we broke up, I went on a binge of emotional eating and drinking almost every night and that really caused me to gain a lot of weight. Eventually I gained so much that I realized I really needed to make a change

I started by just eating healthier with a healthy weight loss calorie count,  but I started getting back to disordered eating as I would only eat about half of what would be a healthy weight loss diet. It slowly devolved into a more and more restrictive calorie intake. I feel some sort of satisfaction from eating less than I had the day before.

My question is how do I get into a diet regime to safely lose weight without beginning to restrict myself in an unhealthy way? I really thought that I had overcome the eating disorder but once i start to track calories, it's really difficult to not go back to the old ways of thinking of slowly eating less and less.

I'm not sure if therapy is the only way to solve this or if there are things that I can do on my own to help guide me into a sustainable eating plan. Thanks in advance for any suggestions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I believe my sister is suffering from BED/EDNOS. How can I get her help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 04:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My sister binges on large quantities of food more than once a day. She's been doing this for quite a while, 2 years I'd say at the least. She's skin and bones, yet she eats to the point of being so bloated she looks pregnant. Then, once she is able to feel like she can move again, all she does is walk on the treadmill. Her health is in a severe decline, with her hair falling out. I also believe she doesn't menstruate, at least normally, and she's told me she wears a diaper because she can't control when she goes to the bathroom sometimes. She's incredibly frail. She has poor body image and depressive thoughts. I believe this all started when he ex cheated on her, though she had underlying issues before that. She also experiences Celiac and potentially other dietary issues. She sees doctors on occasion but never mental health professionals to my knowledge. She'll say she wants help, yet refuses to see anyone, sometimes cancelling appointment after appointment with her doctors. Basically, I feel like someone in her situation would be seeing doctors frequently to get it figured out, not once every few weeks.

TL;DR: I believe my sister has severe BED/EDNOS. How do I get her the help I need without upsetting her or putting her in a space where she feels like my family and I are "out to get her"? Please help.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Bikini Bartender Recovering from an Eating Disorder - Desperately Need Advice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 04:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am in my early 20s and have recently "recovered" from Bulimia. I say "recovered" because I have not purged since my initial decision to stop about 3 months ago. I have had a full blown out eating disorder since my late teens, but can think of occasions as young as middle school where I showed ED tendencies. I still remember the first time that I ever purged, I was a sophomore in high school. I had been fasting, going into my fourth day, and couldn't take it anymore. I ended up eating more than half of what was in the fridge. Afterwards, I felt so disgusted with myself that I curled down on to the title floor of the kitchen and just started balling my eyes out. The combination of dry heaving, hiccups, and a full stomach made me throw up. Afterwards, I decided that this would be my solution for managing my weight.

This was a very effective way for me to stay "skinny". Mostly because I purged everything like keeping it down would poison me. Although I looked fine on the outside, I always felt like crap. Whether it was because I'd plan my life around my binges (which always managed to inconvenience me), or because I was constantly tired and dehydrated from purging, or because I couldn't go out for dinner with friends who were unaware because I had lost all idea of what a normal person ate like. The reasons why I felt like crap where endless.

Finally, I decided to end this way of living once and for all. The only thing I was gaining from this disorder was the fact that I wasn't gaining weight. The cons finally outweighed that one pro. It has been three months now, and I feel much healthier.

I'm still very early in the recovering phase, so I was wondering if anyone could answer me a few questions.

When does the weight fluctuation stop?

Also, how do you explain the fluctuation of weight and take the sometimes hard criticism of others noticing weight gain?

I went from a small to a small-medium. I know that I am not overweight, but thicker than I was before. It's so difficult for me to hear people make comments about my weight gain, even jokingly, because for a normal person this wouldn't be so harsh. Also, I am a bikini bartender, so the slightest loss/gain in weight goes noticed by the staff   regular customers.

Any advice anyone could give me would be so much appreciated, I really feel like I'm all alone on this.

Also, how do you explain the fluctuation of weight and take the sometimes hard criticism of others noticing weight gain?

I went from a small to a small-medium. I know that I am not overweight, but thicker than I was before. It's so difficult for me to hear people make comments about my weight gain, even jokingly, because for a normal person this wouldn't be so harsh. Also, I am a bikini bartender, so the slightest loss/gain in weight goes noticed by the staff   regular customers.

Any advice anyone could give me would be so much appreciated, I really feel like I'm all alone on this.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Bikini Bartender Recovering from an Eating Disorder - Desperately Need Advice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 04:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am in my early 20s and have recently "recovered" from Bulimia. I say "recovered" because I have not purged since my initial decision to stop about 3 months ago. I have had a full blown out eating disorder since my late teens, but can think of occasions as young as middle school where I showed ED tendencies. I still remember the first time that I ever purged, I was a sophomore in high school. I had been fasting, going into my fourth day, and couldn't take it anymore. I ended up eating more than half of what was in the fridge. Afterwards, I felt so disgusted with myself that I curled down on to the title floor of the kitchen and just started balling my eyes out. The combination of dry heaving, hiccups, and a full stomach made me throw up. Afterwards, I decided that this would be my solution for managing my weight.

This was a very effective way for me to stay "skinny". Mostly because I purged everything like keeping it down would poison me. Although I looked fine on the outside, I always felt like crap. Whether it was because I'd plan my life around my binges (which always managed to inconvenience me), or because I was constantly tired and dehydrated from purging, or because I couldn't go out for dinner with friends who were unaware because I had lost all idea of what a normal person ate like. The reasons why I felt like crap where endless.

Finally, I decided to end this way of living once and for all. The only thing I was gaining from this disorder was the fact that I wasn't gaining weight. The cons finally outweighed that one pro. It has been three months now, and I feel much healthier.

I'm still very early in the recovering phase, so I was wondering if anyone could answer me a few questions.

When does the weight fluctuation stop?

Also, how do you explain the fluctuation of weight and take the sometimes hard criticism of others noticing weight gain?

I went from a small to a small-medium. I know that I am not overweight, but thicker than I was before. It's so difficult for me to hear people make comments about my weight gain, even jokingly, because for a normal person this wouldn't be so harsh. Also, I am a bikini bartender, so the slightest loss/gain in weight goes noticed by the staff   regular customers.

Any advice anyone could give me would be so much appreciated, I really feel like I'm all alone on this.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I need help, ED coming back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 04:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a 21 year old male who has struggled on and off with Bulimia since my mid teens, and with drug and alcohol abuse. I am currently in recovery (with occasional slips, I'm not perfect) from my addiction to drugs and alcohol, but I'm afraid that my bulimia is coming back. My drugs of choice were mainly stimulants, MDMA, Meth, DXM, Adderall, etc. Now that I'm abstaining, I've noticed that I have started binge eating. At first I thought it was just withdrawal, but it's been a couple months and I still struggle with knowing when to stop eating, and with massive cravings for certain foods. One of the reasons I liked stimulants so much was they kept me from having an appetite, kept me thin. At first I was just binge eating, but in the last couple weeks I've started to purge. Not all the time, only once or twice every couple days - but I know myself, and I know it's going to snowball. I don't want to deal with Bulimia again, it's something I'm very ashamed of and secretive about. I have that thought that because I'm a male I "shouldn't" struggle with this. No one knows about my secret habit, and I'm awful at asking for help, because I'm afraid people will just think I'm looking for attention. I want help though, and I thought the internet might be a good place to ask for it because of it's inherent anonymity. Sorry for the TL;DR, just had to get this off my chest. So... yeah. That's my story, I guess.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Are my thoughts unhealthy? Scared that I might develop an eating disorder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 02:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realised that I'd lost a bit of weight when I stepped on the scales at home in January - going from a borderline underweight/slightly-healthy weight to underweight. I put it down to eating healthier at home. From that day, I started weighing myself multiple times a day and calculating my BMI everyday because I wanted to see the numbers go lower. And I'd calculate how much I needed to weigh to become more underweight.

Then I went to study abroad and I haven't been able to weigh myself anymore because I don't have scales, and due to several work deadlines I was distracted from my weight. I didn't really realise that I was quite skinny until some people asked me if I had lost weight. Then I actually looked at my body and noticed I had in fact lost weight. I felt proud of myself for unintentionally losing weight because I've never been happy with my body, even though people say I'm slim. I think that weight loss was down to stress - because I got a lot of other stress induced symptoms during that time.

However their comments and the weight loss has just made me want to continue losing weight because I still feel fat, even though people say I'm not. And now that I'm less stressed, I'm scared to put on weight again. I did binge-eat twice but then felt guilty so since then I've been counting calories and limiting my calorie intake to a level which I thought was safe for weight loss - but according the recommended calorie intake chart on the sidebar of this subreddit, I'm vastly undereating (even though I don't feel really hungry). I really don't want to eat more calories though. When I eat anything remotely unhealthy or when I eat until I feel full then I feel guilty, and I've started to enjoy the feeling of being hungry because it means that I'm losing weight. This past weekend I spent hours looking at food recipes, I don't even know why.

I'm going to visit my boyfriend for two weeks and I know we'll end up cooking/eating foods which are so unhealthy. I feel conflicted because half of me wants to eat the food that I used to enjoy and love eating but the other half of me doesn't want to put on any weight.

I think my thoughts relating to food and weight loss have become unhealthy, is this true? I don't know what to do, and if they continue will it lead to an eating disorder?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Personal and confidential information (concerns about housemate) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 02:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am very concerned about my housemate. He and I both started a degree in Spain last year, its just the two of us living together. He has developed pretty serious Bulimia. The situation is difficult because neither of us speak great Spanish and live in a fairly isolated group of foreign postgrads.

We became good friends pretty quickly, close enough that I have been able to talk to him about it a bit, but that generally just results in him being sneakier when he does his vomiting. I feel like action needs to be taken because the guy has become seriously weak (still goes running all the time despite having no energy), basically doesn't sleep and has already failed 5/6 subjects. On the other hand I can't make him see somebody or take action in some other way. I feel like the school / his family need to know but he has also cut himself up once pretty badly and I am not 100% sure that me telling the school or family wouldn't result in serious self harm.

What the hell do I do? I feel particularly responsible because the whole thing seemed to get a lot worse because I started excising a lot and taking my diet more seriously. I think he has developed some sort of gay infatuation with me and wanted to "keep up", I know that sounds very self absorbed but its my opinion when trying to be as impartial as possible. I bring it up only because it effects the way I am able to talk to him without eliciting extreme emotional reactions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Should I ask my guidance counselor? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 12:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My request mentions a time when there was a senior meeting at my school, and there was a woman there that said she can assist us in problems with our home lives and relationships, but I don't know her name or job title. I wanted to ask my guidance counselor if she knew who the lady was, and if someone here has spoken to a person like that and if eating disorders is something I can talk about with that lady, like if that counts. Is she called a school therapist do you think?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: What's wrong with me? Is it bulimia? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 12:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every now and then (once a week or so) I'll eat to the point where I get overwhelmingly nauseous and then I'll deliberately induce vomiting. On rare occasions, I'll actually go to multiple restaurants in one day and eat in between visits to each restaurant. I'm slightly overweight and I am self-conscious about it, but it's not why I do it really.

The problem is, I absolutely cannot stop eating certain foods I feel are unhealthy. I've tried to avoid them, but I always come back to the foods that give me the greatest comfort in the short term. Then I end up feeling really ashamed, but I rarely actually induce vomiting. Only when I feel nauseous do I do that, but that happens frequently do to just the sheer amount of food I eat. The problem is, I feel really good after I vomit. Like, really really good. But yes, I do eat to the point where I'm ashamed of myself very frequently.

I'm seeing my therapist this Thursday. Is this something worth bringing up with them?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Mom micromanaging my what I eat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 21:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I'm recovered but I still have a hesitate towards food. I don't count my calories I just eat whenever I'm hungry. My mother who wasn't very supportive during my recovery because of my ''weight loss success''. She is suddenly extremely overbearing with making sure I eat enough. 

She monitors what I eat; she counts how much calories, Sodium, Protein, Calcium I eat. I know she has good intentions, but it makes me feel very overwhelmed and stressed out. since I am not comfortable with getting into counting what I eat territory. She feels like she's helping me but it makes me feel closer to relapsing. I've told her but she ignores me and seems to think she's doing the right thing. 

What do I do?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Success Story: BED recovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 21:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having struggled with BED and EDNOS since I was around eight years of age, I feel your pain. Here's what's helped me in my road to recovery: Reading material: "Life without ED" by Jenni Schaefer "Food: The Good Girls Drug", "Full" by Kati Simpkins, and a Cognitive Behavioral Therapy Workbook (used after having gone through CBT with a therapist). Other helpful things: finding something else to occupy your anxious thoughts. When I first decided to go into treatment, I had my roommate teach me how to knit. I knew that my anxiety and my ED would be screaming at me, so I figured if I had something to do with my hands that didn't involve giving into ED, I might be able to not binge as frequently. I also found a therapist that specialized in disordered eating. She's helped me to use tools like food logging, and working on body positivity with myself. Instagram, oddly enough, has also been a huge help. I started going on there to find others who were going through recovery in order to get ideas as far as healthy eating habits, healthy foods that help with wrangling BED (serving sizes, pre-prepared,etc), and with a positive outlook for recovery.
I think the hardest part with having an eating disorder, for me, has been being honest with myself and others on how I'm doing. ED makes things so hard to perceive sometimes, so I've learned to practice more translucency with how much my ED affects my daily life. If I hold myself accountable for how it influences me, and share my struggle with others, I hope that in time that vulnerability will help me to see that I'm going to get past this, I'm going to be fully recovered someday, and that in the meantime, I just have to take every day as it comes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I don't have an unhealthy relationship with food but have begun purging when I'm upset. Should I see a professional? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 17:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am in the normal weight range for my age (early 20's) and have a healthy relationship with food. A year and a half ago, a very close friend took his life. Since then, I often find myself making myself sick on purpose when I feel particularly upset. 

The sadness is often about my friend, but could be as little as a stranger being rude to me on the street. Right after my friend passed, I would make myself sick at least a couple times a week. Purging makes me feel better. 

Now it only happens two or three times a month, but lately it's been increasing again. Not sure if this qualifies as an eating disorder or how I should approach it. I don't have depression or anxiety, but I do tend to get upset easily. Is this something I should talk to a professional about, or is it okay to just leave it be and assume it will go away on its own?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: recently noticing that my therapist who I'm seeing for anorexia is sickly thin looking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 00:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started seeing my therapist about 4 months ago; I had started having some issues with restricting again. One of her specialties is eating disorders. Recently it's been getting warmer where I live, and in the past few weeks she has been wearing things that have made me notice how extremely skinny she is. Like not normal skinny; I've been to Ed treatment in the past so I've seen a lot of sick people, and now that I pay more attention it honestly seems like she may be having Ed issues of her own. Should I even try to bring this up? Or should I just find a new therapist? I feel like it's such a touchy thing to bring up. Not to mention she has made comments hinting at the fact that she has had her own issues with an eating disorder in the past. Any advice helps!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: People with eating disorders: what families and friends can realistically do to help you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 22:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Short background: Im concerned about a male friend. He a colleague from the university, we had classes together for a year but we only talked a couple of times so were not really close. I noticed he lost loads of weight and looks really bad now. This plus many other ED-typical symptoms. A little bit about me: I too suffered from ED (AN). Im recovered as much as its possible, Ive been eating normally for years, no major relapses.

I really want to talk to him. The problem is, I dont know what to say to him to not do any harm. I remember that when I was at my worst, on one hand I really wanted someone to come and talk to me and offer me their support. On the other hand, whenever anyone cared, I rejected them. Actually, rejecting people was giving me a huge satisfaction. It made me feel strong, because I had the feeling I didnt need anyone, that I was above feelings and emotions, that I could control them. And then, I restricted my diet even more. Moreover, I couldnt stop thinking they only care when you lose weight, otherwise they never give a sh*t, you should go on with the diet, or it means that you lost weight, youre doing well, youre closer to your goal, you should go on. 

Later on, when my AN got more serious, after talking to someone concerned, I would allow myself to eat more than usually, which then would almost immediately lead to panic, shame, self-disgust, self-hatred, exercising more to burn the additional calories, more self-hatred and eventual decision to avoid the person who threw me off my inner balance. Because in the end, any form of interest was too overwhelming for me to handle, so I perceived it as a threat.

I dont really know what to do so for now I stay away. On every single site about ED they say that you should offer support to the sick person. But honestly, how do you do it? I cannot come up with a single sentence that wouldnt have backfired if I had heard it during my ED period. I recovered only when I, myself, made the decision that I dont want to live this way. Until that point, every single help offer, support, or concern led only to further diet restriction and isolation.

So: what, from your perspective, a third person can realistically do or say that will not make things worse (i.e. wont lead to hostility, isolation, even more restrictive dieting)?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five Strategies for Managing Eating Disorder Thoughts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 21:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I am worried about my friend - what should I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 21:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am worried about my friend. He only eats when he realizes he's hungry, and sometimes he doesn't even realize it. 

Yesterday, he ate normally and he's not concerned about his weight or his body image, so I do not think he is anorexic. 

He just doesn't eat enough, and when he does, he avoids certain textures. Could he possibly have ARFID? I've looked into it, but I'm just not sure because it doesn't seem like he actively avoids food (just when he isn't hungry).

Should I be concerned? Is there anything I can do?

edit: The user of this post has asked you to please respond to them directly: /u/Zubat_Breeder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Should I be concerned about my friend? She has a history of restrictive eating and is in mourning of her father. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 17:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My best friends father passed away around 2 months ago. It was very sudden, a heart attack; he was young. My friend was obviously really upset. 

1 month after, she told me she was going to be vegan. This came out of NOWHERE. she hasn't ever expressed any interest in the idea. 

She also she kept this a secret until i figured it out and asked. 

She has a slight history with restrictive eating and bad body image - should i be concerned?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Good friend is most likely slipping into an ED, and I'm not sure how to best support them or how serious it is </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 03:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm writing about a close friend of mine who used to be overweight and always had confidence issues about their body. Over the summer they started to undereat with the goal of reaching a normal body weight.

Around December this started to pay-off and they reached a healthy body weight, however, that's where they started to continue counting calories. Supposedly due to a very controlling mother that would force food onto them.

This trend has continued over the past few months, and right now they are underweight and up until last week were still justifying undereating with a plethora of reasons. However, recently, due to a few social eating days they started severely restricting their calorie intake and started to complain about ED related maladies.

Ever since last week I've been trying to support them, by talking about it, and being judgment free. However, recent days have made me extremely worried, and since I'm close to them this is affecting me and making rational thought and being supportive difficult. Which is why my question is two-fold:

What are methods for detaching from being worried and being able to be supportive while they do not wish to acknowledge they have a problem at all? For unrelated reasons they will probably see a psychologist soon, and I have some hope that this might get the ball rolling. but I'm not sure whether they will be really open to the psychologist on account of being ashamed.

When it comes to physical health, how dangerous is their current state? I only recently started to read into EDs and I have no idea what the impact of restricting while being borderline underweight does. More specifically, is this a point where immediate medical attention is necessary? If not, what are indicators that they are at that point?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Potential eating disorder, hostile to recovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 18:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After experiencing drastic weight loss from a depressive episode, I noticed that over the months, I developed an intense fixation on my eating - what I've been eating and how I've been eating. I started obsessively listing down the food I ate daily and being hyperaware of my portions. I also started designating almost completely arbitrary "bad" and "good" labels to the food I encounter, and punished myself in my head for eating the "bad" ones. For a period too, I couldn't stop counting calories. Some days it gets really bad and tiring for me to think that I end up crying or wanting to cry in the middle of doing something unrelated. Apart from the huge amounts of guilt, I feel like I've lost control of my body, and it makes me think like I don't know my body anymore. I am aware that these are alarming signs and I should probably consult a therapist, but at the same time, I have been eating regularly now, and have been experiencing those symptoms "less" now, so I think I've been recovering, and am not sick enough to warrant a checkup.

However, I've noticed I'm also hostile and afraid of what I think is entailed by recovery - increasing my frequency of eating, potentially increasing portions, the "healthy" weight gain. I eat with more ease now, but I still have bouts of guilt and fixation, and I still get extremely afraid of weight gain and sometimes even get frustrated at myself for wanting to get better. Help?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Lost medical assistance. Don't know what to do </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 17:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I purged again last night. It'd been a long time since last. I saw some pictures in /r/cosplay and realized that my body will never look right. I hate it. I hate it. I hate it.

I haven't been able to meet with my eating disorder therapist in a while because I lost medical assistance. It's typical for people who are on disability to lose it. I'm on medicare which covers much less.

So I'm kind of just here. With a terribad headache my eating disorder screaming in my ear that happy or sad thin is better. Eat shit feel like shit.

All sorts of... I'unno. Propaganda. I hate my eating disorder. I want help. I want a community where I can talk about feeling trapped in a skin that's wrong. I. I can't control so much of my life right now. Food is all I have. And I feel really bad whenever I listen to it. It sucks but it's all I've got.

Can anyone offer advice on what I can do?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I'm an extremely picky eater and I can't help it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 17:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For as long as I can remember, I have been the pickiest eater. There are only certain foods that I like, mainly my mothers cooking and a few other things but for the most part I feel disgusted when I attempt to eat anything else. I don't like 90% of meats, I don't like vegetables and I don't like any fish, there isn't really much else for me to eat. I really don't like being picky with my food and I would like to try new things but as soon as I eat them I just feel completely disgusted. Is there anything I can do?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My friend is killing himself </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 14:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello friends. My friend has severe Aspergers, this makes it hard to reach him. He just doesn't get how dangerous it is. He has lost a significant amount of weight in a short time. What he considers enough for a day is barely a breakfast. Now he's at a high risk underweight that is tearing me apart. He's not suffering from a classic ED, he just doesn't care. I'm quite sure he wants to die but doesn't get it himself. He says there's nothing emotionally wrong with him because he's unaware of his feelings. He has been diagnosed with depression and is now on antidepressants. I'm sure it won't do any good but it's something.

He's been going down a bad spiral the past months, self harm that is escalating and loosing more and more weight. I'm his only friend, the only one he talks to and i am tearing my hair out trying to explain the dangers. 

Please, help me to explain the dangers to him of not eating and underweight. Sites that are legit with good information. Studies, references, explanations, anatomic changes.
 If i can't make him understand, he will die and it's scaring so much.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: When will my period come back? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 19:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still workout a lot but have gained weight in recovery over the past 6 months. I am still gaining weight by eating a sufficient number of calories a day to do so. I workout because even before my ED I was very active. I had my last period at 5 pounds below my current weight, and it has not returned. I'm confused because I am definitely eating enough for my activity because I am still gaining weight. I went to my doctor and they gave me 10 days of birth control but it still didn't come back. Does anyone have any advice?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> REQUEST: Any information comparing Anorexia Nervosa to Body Dysmorphia? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 19:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

I'm interested in learning more about the fundamental differences between AN and BDD. I know in a lot of cases there are some really identifiable differences, but there are some instances where it might be more tricky. Does anyone know of any information/studies that highlight the key similarities and/or differences?

Thanks!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Help me help my girlfriend. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 23:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend of two months has been suffering from Anorexia Nervosa for the past year and a half. At one point she was forced into therapy but she told me she lied about being better. She says she doesnt want to get better but she's getting worse and im terrified for her. I care for her deeply and i cant watch her waste away. She refuses to seek proffesional help as she says she doesnt want to get better. How can i support her? How can i help her break free?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How do I get my husband to be supportive and understanding? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 23:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just confessed to my husband that I have an eating disorder. I've never told anyone in my life. Today, he asked if pizza was okay for dinner for the kids, knowing full well that that is definitely a trigger for binging. I've tried to explain to him that I need help and do not have self control. I was barely starting to recover and relapsed last week and ate an entire pizza. I don't know what to do. When I told him that he didn't understand how hard it is, he just took it personal like I was blaming him. I need his support, how do I help him understand?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How do I start eating again and not become nauseous or vomit? [emetophobia] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 23:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been a dangerously long time, over a month, since I've eaten normally, I'm desperate to start again and recover and be normal but I'm so, so scared of the eating making me sick, just having a small amount of food in a stomach that's not used to it. Nobody's told me how I need to do this besides eat little, gentle foods often- but for how long? How do I know what won't make me sick? The doctors just brush me off and I'm so frustrated right now.

It came on because of my fear of being sick (really bad emetophobia), gastrointestinal issues and I've recently learnt I have a cyst on my ovary. It's become its own problem - I binge ate pretty badly before, no purging, I was massively obese and couldn't control myself. I've lost a lot of weight, not healthily. I've asked many doctors, my gastro and nobody really tells me what to do. I'm frustrated, tired and I feel like I've seen many doctors. I can't afford private counselling so I'm on the NHS waiting list. Any advice? Even a few coins of bananas were terrifying to get down, I'm still scared they'll come back up.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Hypnosis, yay or nay? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 22:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anyone tried hypnotherapy for treating their eating disorder? How was the experience? Do you feel like it helped you?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I'm stuck! suggestions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 21:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been dealing with Binge Eating Disorder for many years, and had some good recovery work after spending 3 months in a rehab facility. I am starting to break down a lot more lately and going back to old habits. My therapist is so swamped with clients that I don't get to see her as often as I need.

I wrote sticky notes all over my house telling me to spend at least half an hour a night working on recovery (Journaling, reading, reviewing work from Rehab, etc.). However I am a king of distraction and never end up doing any of it. My therapist thinks its my brain fighting back not wanting to change out of fear or something.

Do anyone else have these issues and have any suggestions? Its very frustrating as due to myself being military if I don't get this under control I will loose my job and with the debt racked up from spending $400-$600 a month extra on binges I will loose everything if I loose my job. I tried to use that alone as motivation but it causes more stress and anxiety I binge more...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Asking mom if we could have less "binge foods" in house </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 10:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all -- the title gives the background more or less. I've been struggling with BN, and there are particular foods (nutella is the devil) that for the time being are rather dangerous for me. I am in the process of seeking professional help (which is proving to be quite a pain, hence "process"), and when I mention to my mother that it would be helpful if certain things were either not in house, or at least somewhere hidden from me, it would be easier to control binge-purge cycles, she grumbles that I am trying to "control her life", more or less hijacking her autonomy to have what foods in the cupboard and wants, and that I should just talk to a shrink. Working on that one, thank you. Nothing I try to do on my own is acknowledged as even partial progress (which I understand is no substitute for professional help, but I realize I'll have plenty of 'homework' to do in any treatment plan I pursue either way).

I feel horribly guilty and selfish for asking her to revolve things around me, and I wish from the core of my being I could just ignore those "trigger foods" if I can't enjoy them in moderation, and most of the time I'll just push them to the back of the pantry and avert my eyes, but in times of weakness... shit. Just this nasty cycle of "well, I'll just have one, maybe one more..." followed by god knows how many one-mores, followed by self loathing and subsequent frantic exercise.

How do I convince her that I have no manipulative ulterior motives, I just want to get my damn bulimia under control? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to deal with my mom's critical comments? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 09:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have struggled with restricting, over-exercising, bingeing, and purging for the past 10-15 years. My weight has fluctuated between being severely underweight to being at the high end of normal during this time. Most of my family is supportive, but my mother sometimes just does not have a filter. I love her to death, but she will often just say whatever comes to mindeven if it is overly critical or downright rude. This wasn't a big problem for me until the last year or so when we started to live in the same city. Now that we see each other fairly often, her comments are really starting to get at me. I have confronted her about it on numerous occasions, but she still doesn't get how much it bothers me.

Right now I am picking myself up from my latest relapse into anorexia and she constantly makes crude comments critcizing on my low weight and appearance.

My concern is that these comments will impede my progress as I start to gain much-needed weight over the next couple of months, especially because last time I gained weight, my mom was (for lack of a better term) a complete asshole about it, making similar comments except about how I was fat.

Have any suggestions on how to talk about this with her so she actually gets how hurtful her comments are? Or should I just accept that this is how she is, deal with it, and try to move on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Had an important photo taken and I look fat in it. How do I cope with this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 03:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A little bit of background (trying to make this as non-ranty as possible): I've been at a 'healthy' weight for a little under two years now, and part of my process was to not weigh myself. I let it get too far though, and when I realized I was getting too big, I found out that I'm now at the higher 'healthy' end of my BMI.

There's nothing wrong with being at the high end of my healthy BMI. It's just that I seriously have a lot of fat in places I don't like to see it (limbs, stomach, and the worst - my face). It's been wearing me down, more than I'd like to accept, but I figured I could tackle this the healthy way with diet and exercise, and I trusted myself to not get carried away. However, I've been doing this for over a month now and have hardly lost any weight and I'm getting really discouraged.

Please note I'm just trying to get to a healthier weight, I will not go below a healthy BMI, but this situation is making it really hard to not go about this in an unhealthy way which is why I'm asking for help...

I had to take a passport photo for my new work ID today, and I almost cried right on the spot wen I saw it. I have a double chin, clear as day - it's not in my head. When I came home I bawled my eyes out, and I still am honestly... all I can think about now is reverting back to my old ways... I'm trying to remember the hell that I went through, but all of that feels like nothing compared to when I look at this picture and I see the double chin. It's making me sick to my stomach.

I don't usually see the double chin in the mirror, but only if everything is perfect (my posture/the way I hold my head, the lighting, etc.) and besides, this photo is important as it's something I'm going to have to look at nearly every single day, and so will random customers. I'm so ashamed and embarrassed. I just want to be at a healthy weight where I actually look healthy and in shape, but it's always been either too much or too little.

I want to stick to my diet and exercise, but it's really hard to stop myself from saying, 'just skip eating altogether, you know this will work and you can be happy with how you look again'. I don't want to fall back into that, it's just really hard to find the right perspective here... any ideas?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Supporting my girlfriend who refuses to see her ED as a problem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 03:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend has struggled for 6 years with BN, and used to receive help from a therapist. Then it stopped when her therapist moved to a different state, and she was devastated when she could no longer contact or have therapy sessions with them. They were the only person she could fully open up with. So after they left the state, she relapsed and just continued purging and not eating. She's expressed so much to me about how much she hates herself, and how little her self worth is, and I do my best to listen to her, and tell her how much I appreciate her company. I somewhat understand this, as I had just recently recovered from severe major depressive disorder. After I had been encouraging her and being positive, she was starting to eat more regularly, and purge less, to the point where she hasn't purged (all but one time that I'm aware of) since our relationship started. Recently, she discovered my most recent ex (who suffered from extreme AN) had started modeling and saw how skinny she was. So now my gf see's this as a competition, and has made a goal to get skinnier than her. It's gotten so downhill since she discovered my ex. It's wearing me down, and I know that it shouldn't, and that I need to take care of myself before I can take care of her. All I want is to encourage and support her, but she either doesn't think she needs help, or that she's incurable. I used to refer to support guides on Reddit and other sites for what I could be doing more or better, but now I'm starting to feel like none of it is working and I feel stuck. I don't know what to do, but I want to support my gf so bad. What can I do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: One toe still in ED? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 04:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A little background: I've been in recovery for almost 6 years now, have gone through various programs and therapists, and am also diagnosed with depression and anxiety. At the beginning of recovery, I did the Maudsley family therapy while I was still in high school, which helped a lot. I had a lot of issues though with lying, throwing food away secretly, etc at school while my parents and family therapist had no idea. I fessed up to them at some point, and a few times my therapist described me as in recovery but "keeping one toe in the eating disorder", and I feel like that accurately describes my entire recovery so far. Since I'm above 18 now, we can't do family anymore and I feel like my parents are sick of having to watch me all the time (and I hated it and it caused so much friction between us), I'm a healthy weight (as far as I know), but I know I never quite reached my goal weight and I'm still restricting compared to the meal plan I had when I was seeing therapists and nutritionists. I feel like I'm constantly in a limbo between wanting to recover and then using ED to deal with my anxiety, etc. 

How do you guys commit completely to recovery? How do you stop lying to yourself and your family? How do you make yourself stick to your meal plan even though everything is "fine" physically and you're eating "regularly", but the thoughts and urges are just as bad as ever? I'm okay at, say, passive activities like not buying too many shoes for example, but since eating is such an active thing that we (esp us with ED) really have to force ourselves to do, how do you guys get yourselves to do it? I hate that the rest of my life is going to have to be like this, and I know it would be easier if I could just commit entirely to recovery, but for some reason I just can't. It's so hard ):
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to get over physical side effects of eating disorder? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 20:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I struggle with an EDNOS that I developed as a side effect of an anxiety disorder in high school. I have the disorder under control now, but I still suffer from the horrible eating patterns. I find it very difficult to eat full meals on my own because I do not know what to make (often I will end up making a ton of food and waste half of it), and I find it difficult to eat foods that have a lot of flavour/require a lot of chewing. I really want to put the weight that I lost back on but I don't know how to do so on this kind of diet because it lacks protein.

I was wondering if anyone knows of an app or service that could produce a meal plan for me? (I live alone so I do not have a roommate that I could ask to prepare food for me.) As well any tips on how to ease my body into eating normal meals again? My biggest aversion to eating is that while I am hungry, my body feels like it is full even after ingesting very little food and it feels uncomfortable if I try to make myself eat anymore. It can take me hours to eat a whole meal because of this.

Thanks in advance.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Horribly trapped </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 20:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, r/eatingdisorders. I'm a 20 year old female college student in her last semester of undergrad. I recently had to move back in with my mom for this last semester for financial reasons, and the ED I've been struggling with for maybe about a year or so has gone from an unhealthy quirk with potential to go wrong if left unchecked, to something much more all-consuming (pun-intended?). Bulimia is probably the best descriptor. Normally, throughout the school/work week, I tend to be rather restrictive -- not excessively so, but probably enough to raise a doctor's eyebrows. I have an insane schedule -- 17 credit hours and two small part-time jobs. From Monday through Thursday I leave the house at around 7-8am and don't walk back in the door until around 9 or 10pm. Friday is more 9-5ish, and I tend to spend weekends 10a-2p on schoolwork as well.

Basically, I have no life. But the problem is, whenever I have ANY freetime (spring break, weekends I don't have much schoolwork, if I'm sick, etc.) I have these horrible binge-purge cycles, and my binges are almost always on sweets. I'll try to vomit up what I can, but then I'll run over to the gym (even in my insane schedule I'm still in the gym about an hour everyday, sometimes more) and work out for hours, sometimes trying to overcompensate so I there's hope for a caloric deficit. Of course, this gets time consuming and I'll get behind on my work -- and with this time, if I were to spend it "non-productively" I could have maybe done something enjoyable, maybe breaking this isolation which I'm sure plays a role perpetuating this nasty cycle. Despite how exhausting my normal schedule is, being on the go constantly means that I can't binge, and I tend to do whatever I can to avoid being idle -- which is effective (I use that term loosely) most of the time.

There's also lots of family problems going on -- as always, really -- that I don't want to spend too much time going into. My mom's a guilt-tripper, my dad and I are estranged -- and as much as I wish I could have a relationship with him, it's probably for the best. My sister is mentally handicapped, and we've never really been close. I try to bond with her, but she's a brick wall. I have a boyfriend whom I see about twice a week and is really my only salient social interaction and support at the moment, and he urges me to get help. I agree with him. I have a therapist which I've been seeing for a while and have built a good rapport with, but because of my schedule, I can't get an appointment in. I tried to go into the school psych services hoping I'd be able to pop in during the occasional spare hours I have between classes, but there's a massive waiting list and the intake lady told me, quite bluntly, that they won't be able to see me before I graduate in April, handed me a card with a 24-hour hotline, and told me to take care.

I feel lost, isolated, strained, and horribly, horribly trapped. I hate living back with my mom again; I feel like I've reverted to my childhood, and the memories are painful. She wants me out because my bulimia is too emotionally burdensome for her, but I don't know where I'd go. Maybe my boyfriend? I'm wondering if I could ask my boss if I could cut back my hours to see a shrink, but I tend to work evenings after typical "business hours" anyway. Further still, I have so little money as it stands. If I had any chance in moving out, cutting my work hours would crush it. I don't think my mom will actually kick me out, she tends to be "all talk," but I need to get my ED under control regardless. I can't keep deluding myself that I can kick it on my own without professional help

Can anyone offer advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Renfrew In Philly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 02:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am almost thirty and I am in (almost) full relapse from my ED. I have the full spectrum of ED since age twelve, but at age twenty-seven I started getting into restriction, compulsive exercise, orthorexia, so on. In March 2014, I entered treatment here in Buffalo. As soon as I got out, things were shaky. I tried my best to fight through, but from January 2015 to now, I can say that I am really not doing well. I know that I am medically a healthy weight, but I still haven't had a period since June 2014, I struggle with eating and resting from exercise. I decided that maybe I need help that my counselor can't give me. In December, I looked into Sol Stone in Elmira, NY. While doing a screening with one of the counselors at Sol Stone, she assessed that because the treatment center that I went to was a weight restorative model that may have heightened my anxieties about food and weight as well as all the numbers that go with it. However, I wasn't able to go to Sol Stone due to financial reasons. My older brother with whom I am close recently moved to Philly. I am supposed to go check out Renfrew on April 4th. Has anyone else been to any of the Renfrew locations? I need some honest feedback. I need to know that I making the right decision.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Do I have an eating disorder? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 03:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I eat a very small amount of food almost everyday. Sometimes I push myself not to eat because I'm not hungry enough or I'll go to sleep hungry to save for more calories the next day. I'm always dizzy, I get up from lying down and I have to hold onto something to balance me for a few seconds. I constantly think about calories burning and weight loss. My hands or whole body feels shaky. Every once in a while I'll get a weird twitching vibration feeling in my stomach. It'll go off and on all day. I don't know if I'm hungry or not anymore. My stomach doesn't feel hungry until I start eating. My family thinks I'm doing it on purpose and a part of me is but I don't know how to stop. I know this isn't good, but is it an eating disorder? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trying to avoid knowing my weight as part of recovery, until today. What the heck do I do now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 03:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in hospital earlier today for dental surgery, and I wanted to be knocked out for it, so of course they needed to know my weight for that so I wasn't given too much of the sleeping stuff. I mentioned to the nurses as I was admitted that I can't/don't want to know my weight as I'm in recovery from AN, and if I know my weight my recovery is going to go down the drain. They were very kind and accommodating for such an odd request and I'm incredibly grateful to them.

Then the anesthetist comes along. I mention to him that the weight I put on my form was an estimate as I cannot know my weight, and the nurses had an accurate reading so he should refer to that. He then proceeds to throw all that out the window, not listen and tell me my weight anyway, right after I said I can't know it. Great.

I'm home now, and my mouth is hella numb so I can't feel any of that, but I'm feeling like crap because I know my weight now, and I feel like a disgusting piece of lard. I'm nearly in tears and I don't know what to do because I can't stop focusing on anything but that number. I've tried so hard for the past three years since I got out of hospital for AN to recover, f*** I was even getting to a point where I could look at myself in the mirror and not see a disgraceful sack of s**t staring back at me, and now it feels like it was all for nothing. I don't know what to do.

How do I deal with this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I'm going to lose my job either way. Feeling hopeless. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 02:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I left my previous job to attend residential treatment last summer and started a new position in November. Since then, I've relapsed to the point that I've had to call in sick or leave work early, in addition to seeking urgent medical treatment. 

Today, I went in for evaluation at a PHP center and was told that I have to go back to residential before they'll accept me due to my current severity. Because FMLA laws require a year of employment, my current position is not protected. 

I'm running out of money and time.

I don't want to uproot my whole life again, but it seems inevitable. Can anyone offer advice?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to help a friend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 02:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, I am close friends with a girl I believe has issues with eating. Her sister was like that too, and she looks very thin for her weight. Could you please provide me with some resources to encourage her to be more healthy? Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: HELP. Medication (Paxil) weight gain triggering another relapse? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 00:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For background information, I have been struggling with my eating disorder for roughly five years now rather cyclically. I am 19/F. 

Around January of 2015 I began relapsing into old habits, and in June of 2015 stopped menstruating. This was very scary for me, as the last time I stopped menstruating I later came very close to dying and it was traumatic and awful. I reached out for help from my family doctor in October of 2015. Now, I had been going through a very stressful period from late august to when I met with my doctor. She had me fill out a questionnaire sheet about how I was feeling (like have you had suicidal thoughts? how sad are you? type thing) and diagnosed me with depression. 

In 20/20 hindsight, I have always been a little introspective and shy, and keep in mind that at this time I was incredibly stressed out, upset, and emotional. She diagnosed me within minutes and prescribed 20mg daily of Peroxetine HCL (paxil) and told me that it would help me feel better and improve my concentration. She told me NONE of the possible long term negative side effects of the drug. She told me that I would feel a little worse and experience negative side effects for a week (such as depression, not being able to sleep, etc) before I started to feel better. I trusted this doctor, and didn't know much about the drug, and consulted with my mom who told me she had taken SSRI's before in the past and they worked for her. I trusted this doctor because I had taken a joint counselling session with her and a psychologist to talk about my eating issues before this diagnosis because I was reaching out for help and recovery, which is important because she understood and had full knowledge of the extent of my issues surrounding food, weight gain, and control. I took the medication from October 2015 to March 10th 2016. 

On this medication I have felt lethargic, sad and/or emotionless, and my concentration has been worse but I trusted my doctor and my mom who both told me it would make me feel better and to stay on it, and tried to get me to up the dose. I have also been steadily gaining weight during this same period of time. A LARGE amount of weight over which I have had no control. I have not changed my eating or exercise habits only to make them MORE restrictive to counteract this bizarre weight gain. I have been exercising every day and making my body sore and tired, and decreasing my calorie intake. But also I've begun using behaviors again (chewing and spitting), which was an embarrassing habit I had managed to quit for over a year before I started taking Paxil. My appetite increased but this did not lead to me consuming more food, because of my use of behaviors. This was very awful and time consuming and shattered my confidence and self esteem). 

Still however, on March 7th I had my first appointment at the doctor to discuss recovery (I had put it off for a long time - I don't know if anyone else has had this but it was just to be weighed, have blood work done, and discuss putting together a support team). At this point in time I was distraught and had NO desire to go through recovery or follow through, but I had made myself accountable to my mom. I was weighed at the appointment and the doctor told me my weight (I'm not sure if she should have done this or not?) and I was on the low-ish end of the healthy BMI range for me and my doctor was ecstatic but I didn't know how to take this because of the weight I gained  since I first came in to see her. 

It is good to be at a healthy weight but I did NOT get here on my own terms, I had NO control over it, and it has DESTROYED my desire to recover. All I can think about is losing the weight. 

I quit my medication because I read that Paxil can make you gain weight. I quit cold turkey (weaned for like 2 days) and am on day 5 of withdrawals. They feel awful but I was just so panicked to get it out of my system. I've been living in my own personal hell for all this time of losing absolute control of my body and just steadily gaining weight, which is unhealthy but my ONLY coping mechanism and something that is VERY hard for me to relinquish and what I was seeking help for. I spent Christmas starving myself because I was so afraid of weight gain, I didn't get to enjoy any of the foods I love and I hurt my Grandmother's feelings because I was so afraid. 

I know it's good to be healthy, but this is NOT how I wanted to get here and it has been a major setback. I know that once I get this drug out of my system I'm going to resort back to my old ways and suffer a major relapse to lose this weight and I'm terrified. I'm mad at my doctor for putting me on this specific drug because it seems to be the worst for weight gain after I trusted her and I feel betrayed, and I'm mad at my mom for breaking my trust and telling me that SSRI's worked for her when she told me today that she NEVER EVEN FOLLOWED THROUGH ON TAKING THEM because she was afraid of the bad side effects. I feel hurt and insecure and my suicidal ideation peaked before I went off the drug. I have never felt worse than this in my entire life. I went to the doctor trying to recover once and for all and now all that strength and courage is completely gone and I'm scared that I won't get to that point ever again. 

Does anyone have any advice for trying to fight this off? Has anyone tried Paxil and maybe I'm just crazy? I don't know what to do right now, and feel completely hopeless. I don't think I will be going back on any medication.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Trying to understand her after a break up, please help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 00:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could really use help here. 

I was in a long term, very serious, 4 year relationship that was heading towards marriage (we were both post grad). We were always in varying degrees long distance and there were questions about whether she could get a job were I was after grad school (I had an inflexible job situation), and some other issues causing some conflict, but overall smooth sailing. But really the last two years she changed, in a real way, from the person I fell in love with that really checked all the boxes, to a very high strung, high maintenance, stressed generally unhappy person. It was like varying degrees of close to insanity, like a constant morning routine of what she ate and did, if it got screwed up the day was screwed up, just the list went on and on. I tried to talk to her about it because I had no idea what was going on, and on a certain level I thought well maybe this is who she really is and that is something you eventually find out about people when you've known them long enough. And with the distance, the job issue, and then who she "turned into," I couldn't do it anymore. 

So, we fought, broke up, it was nasty, said a bunch of things that can't be unsaid to each other, etc. etc., we still loved each other but realize it stopped working etc. etc.. This approach was "working" for me and I was moving forward somewhat, but she finally came out and told me recently that she was struggling with a full blown eating disorder of the restriction kind for really the last two years of our relationship. She said everything I had said to her in the post-break up nasty discussions about how I felt like I was walking on eggshells around her and how I thought her many quirks were bordering on insanity suddenly made sense to her because a relative she had went through the same disorder and she felt the same way around that person. She basically said the breakup was rock bottom for her, she's getting help through therapy, and honestly she seems like a changed or at least changing person now that we've resumed contact somewhat.

So in nutshell, I thought I had wildly misjudged her for my first two years with her and got roped into dating the most high maintenance, inflexible person, and I broke up with her largely over that. Instead, I find out how she was behaving (according to her) was for a completely different reason, let alone a mental illness. A real lightbulb moment that could have solved a ton of our problems, if I had found out about it, say, any time over the last two years of us dating. I knew something was up, but didn't know it was that bad. So on one hand I'm really pissed she never told me about this, but also really angry at myself for not figuring out she was going through this essentially alone and I couldn't find a way to help her. Like what if I had forced the discussion on the personality part, and maybe the real "cause" would have finally come out by coincidence? I kick myself over it. But at least she's in therapy now, and I genuinely hope she gets better for her own sake.

The question is (finally), we've started to toy around with the idea of trying to figure this out. The distance/jobs is something that's solvable. But how do you know someone has really changed mentally? The last thing I want is to get back into this, find out she is still like how she was, and break up again like a walking stereotype of a couple that got back together with an ex. Mainly I have a hard time trusting that everything I was struggling with about her was fully due to the eating disorder. I kind of remember how she was when we first started dating and that's the person I fell in love with, but the overwhelming memories are of how she became for the second half of it/why we broke up. And on her front, well I broke her heart, she really regrets not telling me about all this but also she lost her trust in me now because I drove this wedge in between us with the breakup, and I fully understand her being skittish now. .....it's a mess. Advice?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I am a bit confused and would like some input. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 13:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not really sure how to start this one off so I'll get right to the important part. I saw a mention of a 'pro' eating disorder subreddit elsewhere, and I went out of sheer morbid curiosity. Some things started clicking in my head that are really bothering me. I've always struggled with body image, and at one point I looked like some of those horrific "inspiration" photos they pass around. I saw a lot of myself in that subreddit and I don't really like it. I just moved and I won't have insurance for a while, so if there's anything you can recommend to me while I iron that out please let me know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Need advice from those who have experienced ED or loved ones who have experienced it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 12:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a friend of a friend (acquaintance, really) who I don't know very well but I'm concerned that she may have an ED. She appears to have lost an unhealthy amount of weight but my only context for this is Facebook posts. I wanted to see if it was possible to post a copy of what I would like to send to her, as a message that I am concerned and support her. This is touchy because I don't know her well but I am very concerned for her health. I want to make sure my message doesn't come off wrong. 

I thought posting it here to see what others thought would be a good avenue to make sure I don't upset her further or offend her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Questions about BED: Where do I start? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 12:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My therapist and I recently discussed Binge Eating Disorder after she noticed I put on a lot of weight. I recently got a full time desk job, so I have no time to exercise and I'm not getting exercise at work. I suffer from Borderline Personality Disorder, and we on medication for a period of time a year ago. It worked well, and helped a lot. I was able to enact a strict regimen of calorie counting and exercising to lose weight. Once off my medication, I began binge eating again.

Some history would be my family gets angry if you leave food on the plate. My mom will serve me, harass me if I don't finish it, then constantly verbally abuse me about being fat. She will not allow you to serve yourself. My dad doesn't do anything to help. All of my grandparents have diabetes, so I'm not trying to lose weight to look good. Really, I have a lot of risk factors that I need to avoid now. Other than diabetes, heart problems and issues with circulation are in my family. Because of this and how judgmental my mom is, I binge. I binge at odd hours, usually. I have literally set my alarm to 2am so I can wake up and binge. And then after I sit in my bed and cry. I really hate myself. 

When I spoke to my therapist she said to look at Binge Eating Disorder. My mother won't help me, I don't know what to do, but I know this isn't healthy. It's not even about my figure, anymore. It's about the fear of early diabetes. I need resources, help. Please, I'm really lost and I have no one to turn to.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Roommate potentially has an eating disorder -- need advice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 14:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, here's the post we're looking for advice on:

TL;DR roommate is stealing food, hardly ever eats around us, supposedly has intense allergies but would have reacted to the ingredients in the food she's stolen. 

I'm currently living in a house with 4 other girls, and food has been going missing since January. It's always things that are high in fat or calories, like chocolate, pitas, cereal, and birthday cake. We always write our names on our things so everyone knows who it belongs to. We've always pointed out when things go missing, so everyone else in the house knows that we're noticing.

Recently, one of my roommates (we'll call her Allison) who lived with "Stephanie" last year told me that this happened then, too. Allison and the third roommate had worked out that it was probably Stephanie who was stealing the food last year, but they didn't have any proof. They had spoken to Stephanie about it, and mentioned that all signs pointed to her, but she denied it even though she couldn't provide another explanation. 

Everything was fine this year until we signed the lease for next year, and then things started going missing again. The missing birthday cake was the last straw, so Allison went into Stephanie's room while Stephanie was out, and found several wrappers in her garbage can. They all had writing on them, clearly indicating that they were Allison's and not to take them. 

Stephanie hasn't come home yet, so we're trying to figure out what to do. The thing is though, Stephanie had been updating us on her health throughout the year, and she told us that she's allergic to a number of things and absolutely can't eat them without experiencing pain. All of the things found in her garbage can contain those ingredients she's "allergic" to. 

During the day, she eats very little, and almost never when anyone else is around to witness. What we do see her eat fits with the allergies she told us she has, but the amount we see her eat is so low it's obviously not healthy/doesn't sound possible. 

It seems like Stephanie might be binging or sleep eating or something. It seems more conscious though, because she always covers her tracks. We love living with her, and she doesn't seem like the type to purposely steal food and then easily lie to us about it. It seems more like she's unable to help herself from taking things. 

Obviously, we're upset about the missing food, but mostly we just want to help her if we can. 

So far, Allison has kept the wrappers she found in Stephanie's garbage can as proof, but we don't really know what else to do from here. It doesn't seem feasible to get Stephanie's family involved. 

Can anyone offer suggestions on how to handle this?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I don't know where to go from here </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 19:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After a breakup in November, I had started restricting because I just had no appetite and became underweight. I was sexually assaulted in December and relapsed pretty heavily the end of that month into bulimia because we had a bad storm and for a few days I couldn't run and started having panic attacks at work and it was the only thing that helped settle the anxiety. I've since then become quite underweight but able to maintain my weight within a few lbs of this the last month. I've been seeing my doctor throughout and also started therapy. Primarily my relapse has been anxiety/trauma induced not body image. I know I look and am very sick but I can't seem to control the anxiety and panic attacks any other way. Medications only work for the anxiety by putting me to sleep essentially. We've considered antidepressants but in the past they have made me suicidal while on them and it's a risk I'm not willing I take right now. Inpatient has been offered several times and while I am willing to work outpatient I will not do inpatient. I myself am a nurse, disagree with the models typically used and available at facilities near me, and do not think the environment would help me for several reasons.

I am so tired of waking up everyday, throwing up, repeating because I feel so physically weak from throwing up that I can't not eat again, which continues until I take medication to make me fall asleep. When I asleep I either have nightmares about what happened and even sometimes more cruelly very good dreams where I am back with my ex and things are normal again. I wake up hopeless and anxious. Sometimes the only thing I look forward to is knowing I can get rid of the feelings by just simply binging and purging but I feel so tired and worn out these days. I had a previous trip planned to Europe which I was hoping would cheer me up and maybe break the habit but things have just as bad here. I know why I feel like how I do but the things causing me stress I have no control over- I can't make the police work faster, I can't make the DA want to prosecute my case, and the idea that nothing will happen to them while I'm a mess of a person slowly killing myself trying to feel some relief makes me unable to function I'm so anxious. I can't keep doing this. I'm trying my best in therapy but I'm so mentally uncomfortable I can't help myself. I love my family and I know they're worried and I want to get better but I'm at capacity. I can't fix this one, I feel like what I need is closure on my case and it's the one thing no one can give me. 

Has anyone been able to bounce back from similar? Can anyone offer advice?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Is this an eating disorder? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 19:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel silly asking this as I don't want to undermine issues others may have which is why I shy away from seeking answers.

All my life, I have been OBSESSED with my figure. I literally live off of the phrase "oh my god! you're a stick!". I don't purge after meals, I don't refuse to eat meals, but I grow anxious after eating meals and find myself only eating a little at a time. I rarely finish meals. I recently started gagging toward the end of eating meals  because the thought of food is sometimes so sickening. 

I'm a little concerned with where my mind has been subconsciously going recently. Is this of concern? What should I do?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Research: Desired resources for Depression/Mental health website. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 15:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there, My name is Parker and i am currently putting together a website with the intention of creating a hub for resources and information for treating and conquering depression and other mental illnesses. I myself have been suffering from depression for about 4 years now, and the content on the website will be largely focused on depression.

As a moderator of a mental health website, I have some questions for you:

1.What would you like to see in a mental health website?

2.Would you like to provide links and traffic for each other? (my website --- your subreddit)

3.What are some similar resources you are familiar with (other than subreddits) that would benefit reaching out to?

Thanks for your time, I look forward to hearing back! -Parker
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Supporting a loved one who doesn't want help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 15:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello! A close friend of mine who's really dear to me seems to have an eating disorder. She has every common behavioral symptom. She restricts, she obsessively exercises, she'll throw up on purpose, she feels disgusted with herself after eating, she bases her entire worth on her weight loss, she will occasionally binge eat because she can't handle the constant hunger etc. Despite all this, she is at a completely normal weight, and therefore uses that to say she doesn't have an eating disorder. This has been going on for 3 years, and she tells everyone it's a diet, and she can get away with it because of her normal weight, and the fact she used to be just barely overweight. I have tried to talk to her about this many times, and she'll either deny there's a problem, she'll dismiss it due to her normal weight, or she'll flat out tell me she doesn't care to change things. She refuses to see a professional. I don't know how to support her at all, I've struggled with other mental illnesses but never an eating disorder. As far as I know, no one else in her life talks to her about her eating habits. I would really appreciate some advice on what to do to help her, especially on bad days. Sorry if this is too long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Research: Recruiting for a study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 19:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello! My name is Evan and Im from a Harvard University research team that studies the thoughts and feelings that motivate self-harm behaviors among individuals with eating disorders, anxiety, and other related mental health issues.

We are interested in recruiting people who use this subreddit to participate in our (Institutional Review Board approved) study. This study will be completed online over the course of one month and participation is completely voluntary. People who are interested in participating will be compensated up to $50 in online gift cards to Amazon.

You can learn more about our study and complete the brief (about one minute) eligibility screener here: http://projects.iq.harvard.edu/smartphonestudy/study-ad#

Please feel free to private message me at /u/HarvardPhoneStudy if you have any questions. Thank you so much for your consideration!

Note: This is a [repost of this original](https://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/3tpfs3/research_recruiting_for_a_study/). Although I don't track referral community (for privacy reasons), I received an uptick in responses around the time I posted on /r/EatingDisorders. So, it seems like there was a lot of interest in your community. Thanks to all who responded last time. We've received in excess of 500 responses from people who are interested, and we're hoping to get enough responses so that we can publish in 4-6 months
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: how to overcome Night Eating Syndrome (NES) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 17:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Lads,

I am suffering from NES for a very long time (years already), but I didnt took it serious until i started gaining some fat cause I am getting in my very late 20nies and my metabolism is I guess getting slower and slower.

I wake up 5-6 times a week (almost every day) around 4am and I go straight to eat something. I do not feel hunger but I have to eat something and most of the time sweets. Its not a huge amount. 

I think its related to my mouth being dry or something so lately i go to bed with a glass of water near me. But I still do it, like I can drink the glass and then after 1-2 hours I wake up again to get something to eat. 

Some other things to note are:

Cause I am aware of my sweet intake @ night, and I know its gonna happen, i try to minimize the sweet intake during the day like almost to 0. 

BMI charts put me slightly above the normal range, and I feel out of shape.

Can anyone offer any suggestions to overcome the NES?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Medication effecting appetite </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 17:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've recently started taking medications that drastically effect my appetite to where I wait till late in the day to eat, and even if I feel hungry I resist eating, as I have difficulty motivating myself to eat. As a result, I have been eating very little. I have had a problem overeating and binge eating my whole life. How do you become inspired by food again? I love cooking but I just don't have that spark with these meds. (I cannot stop taking the meds because it has improved my life so much)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Restrictive medical diet makes my binging worse. What can I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 04:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been trying to stop binging for over a year and realized that my restrictive medical diet makes me binge even more because I have to avoid some foods.  The foods and ingredients I have to avoid are very common. Just the fact that I can't have these things makes the urges build and build until I find myself stuck in a binging frenzy until I get physically sick from them. 

I realize that being able to eat anything in moderation would probably help and would help me change my perspective on "good" and "bad" foods but that doesn't seem doable. I have found substitutes for very few things which makes it even more difficult. It puts me in a very "black and white" position. 

Is there anything I can do to help my situation?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My Wife </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 00:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife in anorexic. She admits as much to me in moments of candor. She doesn't want to get help. She continues to tell me she wants to lose weight, even as I tell her that her cheeks look hollow. She is significantly underweight, She gets mad at me for trying to bring her food. She runs 2 to 3 times a day. When we go out to dinner she immediately takes laxatives when we get home. I know she loves cheese so I keep it around the house, last night she threw all the cheese I had bought in the trash in front of me while yelling at me, accusing me of trying to make her fat. Then later in the night I noticed she wasn't in bed so I went to the kitchen. She was bent over the counter, a box of crackers torn open in front of her, her head in her hands crying. She turned to look at me and with tears coming down her face said "I'm so hungry." I took out some salami and bread and had her eat a few pieces then carried her back to bed. It broke my heart. 

I don't know what to do. I thought I could post in your thread to learn about what she is going through and how best to help her. I love her more than anything. I can't risk pushing her away, but I can't stand by and watch her destroy her health. I'm mostly a lurker on reddit. Occasionally I chime in with a sarcastic comment. This is the first time I actually need help. I need to learn about what I can do and what she is going through. Please tell me I am in the right place.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Obsessive Thinking About What HE'S Eating </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 15:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't been obsessive about an eating disorder for three years, started for the first time ten years ago. It comes up every now and then I suppose but I just constantly work on it, and having a positive body image and focusing on strength.. but for some reason when my boyfriend can skip meals. It makes me jealous. I over reacted today when I asked him if he ate anything while I was gone (I had breakfast with him) And he didn't eat. We ate at 9:30 in the morning, and he hadn't eaten again until I made him pizza at 9PM. I always ask him to eat. I especially don't like eating when he doesn't eat. I feel disgusting (to the point where I get ridiculously upset at myself for even feeling gross about such a thing) when I eat more than him in a day. It is completely unfair to him as well. I told him I feel this way but I guess I'm just looking to converse with someone who has the same kinda thinking as I do, someone who's gone thru an ED or obsessive eating or something.. I ate breakfast and lunch and a snack and then pizza with him then got mad at myself and purged for the first time in six months. I don't know how to make it better. I know how to help myself, but I don't know what to do now. This is the first time I've really acknowledged it. I don't know if it's a trigger or what. I told him I feel jealous of him. I think about eating a lot (should I eat, what I'm eating, when I should eat it, how specific foods affect me :( I don't know what is with me. I used to know it was half anorexia, half binge and purge. Now I have no clue. 

Can anyone offer advice?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Books/resources for SO? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 00:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I'm new here so I apologize if this has been asked before and I just didn't see it.

I am, unfortunately, relapsing with an ED after about 6-7 years of being okay and a maintaining a normal weight. I used to be really underweight, then I bounced between normal and high-ish weights, and now I find myself quickly dropping the pounds due to old behaviors such as restricting, overexercising, etc.

I did not receive professional help the first time around. This time, however, is a lot different. I am older, I'm tired of ED consuming my entire life, and I have a wonderful partner who is totally supportive and is encouraging me to get help. I feel just terrible that he has to put up with my issues and I know deep down it worries him. 

I also know that he doesn't completely understand my eating disorder and he said he wants to learn more about it. Can anyone recommend a good book or other resources that are geared towards people who are living with someone with an ED? 

Thank you :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: ED or emotional anxst / overreacting? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 00:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, it has in the past week occurred to me that I may have some form of an ED. I suddenly realized I have had a pattern through my life of gaining lots of weight, followed by intensively working it off again. Whenever I stop exercising, it's always on the assumption I'll start again when I start feeling fat again.

At my worst point a couple of years ago I became super obsessed with losing all my body fat and would do 4-5 10km runs a week plus cycling, weights, walking etc. By the end I was down to like a really low body fat and starting to like my body a bit but hated my face, bc it was so thin and bony. So I stopped all exercise and began gaining weight again. As I did so, I started liking my face more but hating my body! Now a year and a half later I feel fat again and have been binging as a way to force myself to start another exercise phase.

Pls tell me I'm not imagining this or overreacting. I'm just surprised I never noticed this as a problem before. Is this an eating disorder? Can anyone offer advice on what I can do?

I'm 32yo trans female and more self esteem issues than you can poke a stick at.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Follow up: First 24 hours without purging! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 23:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been bulimic/anorexic for 12 years, and the past 24 hours have been the most "purge and restrict free" day I have experienced since I was 14. A personal victory for me but I wanted to thank you guys. A user encouraged that I start attending ED Anonymous meetings and they have really helped pave the way for my recovery. It never too late to ask for help. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I started restricting and purging and it is getting worse due to intrusive thoughts. How do I get out of this cycle? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 01:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like a failure when I eat. Food makes me feel disgusting. I feel powerful and good about myself when I don't eat. I just feel this need to hurt and punish myself. I don't care about about being "pretty", I just want to be as small as possible. I feel like it's not enough, I want to just disappear. 

For the past six weeks, Ive been restricting my calories significantly below what someone my weight/height should be consuming, but I haven't been fasting. It wasn't intentional at first, the first week or so, I was just too busy to eat and I felt like I was riding high on an incredible wave and it all came crashing down when I did eat. 

I have a lot of anxiety about weight and I am terrified of becoming fat or gaining weight of any kind. I started purging recently, I've purged daily for the past three days. 

In the beginning of high school, as a cross country runner, I did struggle with disordered eating and was obsessed with food and exercise. I've always hated my body and have never felt thin enough. It's not even that I want to be pretty, I just want to be small. I just want to hurt myself. I hate my body so bad, I want out of it. I don't know if this is truly an eating disorder or if it's just....I don't know. 

Ive also been having constant intrusive memories about childhood sexual abuse that I endured and it makes me feel even more disgusted with myself and makes me want to destroy myself. I feel like a monster.

**What can I do to stop hurting myself?**

**Where can I look for help?**

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I lost a lot of weight from an ED and sometimes gain weight when still undereating, can my metabolism recover if my eating does? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 01:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to be very overweight, but at the age of 14-ish I lost much of it through walking a silly amount daily and sadly by starvation. Now I've been slightly underweight (not dangerously though) since then, I'm 18 now. My metabolism is still ruined and I haven't had a normal diet since before I lost weight. I eat about one time a day, max 2, and it's almost never a full meal. I'm clearly starving my body still BUT I'm struggling not to gain on this amount. Since my metabolism and body is so messed up, and has been for such a long period of time, is there any way of getting a good metabolism without gaining all of my fat back? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> #I am not Ed - Eating Disorders Awareness Week campaign </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 21:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My name is Cindy Glover. Im working on a marketing campaign focused on Eating Disorder recovery in conjunction with the national awareness week coming up Feb. 21-27.

The projects theme is life is better on the other side and the title is I am not Ed. For so many people suffering from an ED, its their entire identity. We want to show some of the great things that happen when an eating disorder no longer defines who you are.

This project is personal to me because I suffered with bulimia from the age of 15-23 and was hospitalized three times. I'm now a happy, healthy 45-year-old mother of two.

Were hoping to get people to post photos of themselves holding a card that says #IamnotEd, with a caption incorporating the three sentences below.

I am not Ed

I am _________________ (a mother, an athlete, a confident woman, )

When I let go of ________________ (obsessing about weight, bingeing and purging, being ashamed of my body)

I was able to _____________ (go swimming for the first time in years, have a healthy relationship, eat with other people, create two amazing kids,)

The inspiration is a blend of the Humans of New York photo series, and the #BringBackOurGirls campaign.

To kick it off, we'd like at least 20 photos and captions from people willing to make a statement about how life is better on the other side of recovery. With that as a foundation, hopefully it can spread across social media with people all over the country contributing (possibly including celebrities).

Do you think any of your members would like to participate? They do not have to give their names.

If possible, we'd like them to post on social media and/or email me at cindy@frac.tl. We'll be building an "I Am Not Ed" landing page, and I'll share the link as soon as we have it up and running. 

Many thanks, --Cindy Glover
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Experience with ED Rehabilitation Centers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 09:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi,

I have been unsuccessful treating my BED with therapy, medication, or anything. I've been seeing doctors out the wazoo for years. But, I continue to gain weight, even if I stall for a while. I have begun going to OA, but it also isn't really helping.

Does anybody here have experience with inpatient or outpatient rehab centers for EDs? I am to the point where I might die in the next 5 years if I don't completely rework my life from the bottom up. I'm thinking the best place to do that is in rehab, treating it just like life threatening drug addiction. I have been overeating to the point where I have uncontrolled diabetes, high BP, high cholesterol, and more recently bad reflux and swelling of the feet. 

Any help would be greatly appreciated! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Could this be a relapse? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 09:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For three or four years I have thought of myself as recovered. I've been diagnosed with both anorexia and bulimia at different times, but I've really been alright for years. At a stable low but healthy weight without any intentional restricting or purging.

Here's the problem, I'm a performer/athlete. In recent months I have greatly increased my training. I also moved across the country and my lifestyle changed completely (for one thing, I know longer have a boyfriend cooking for me). I know I haven't lost weight, but I'm worried that I'm not eating enough. At the same time I'm terrified of eating more. But I am beginning to feel like I did when I was sick. I'm getting dizzy and my period (which has never been truly regular) might be MIA. 

I'm definitely not intentionally restricting, I avoid any cardio training because I hate it and know it's not healthy for me. But I'm worried that my reluctance to eat more might be a relapse, and I'm not sure what to do about it. Any thoughts or suggestions? Any tips to avoid relapse? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Has anyone ever told someone else about your eating disorder without your permission? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 09:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anyone close to you ever told someone else about your eating disorder without your permission? How do you feel about someone telling someone else about your ED? If it's never happened, how do you think you'd feel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Not sure if I had an eating disorder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 13:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Between the ages of 11-12 to 16 I had an odd relationship with food. I wouldn't have classified myself as anorexic or bulimic because I didn't check all the symptoms boxes and have never wanted to lose weight. I am naturally very thin and have a small build, I used to eat fairly well as a child but was always quite little. Fast metabolism and genetics I suppose. My obsession at the time was rather to gain weight because I hated the way my body looked (hence why I can't classify myself as anorexic as the thought process is the complete opposite). However I rarely wanted to have people see me eat in school. My mom would pack me lunches and I would either never eat them and hide them or would wait until I got home and either throw them away or consume them while hiding out in my room. I also never ate breakfast at the time. I ate a decent amount of food at dinner or on weekends when my family was there but that was about it. I still have moments where I have an odd relationship with food as I do not eat when something bothers me and can go on for days like this. 

Is this an eating disorder? Does anyone have any advice for me?

Additional information, if it can be of any help: I have had suicidal thoughts since the age of 12 and have been struggling with depression. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I am relapsing, nobody knows about my ED, I feel out of control. What now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 00:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wrote a bunch more here but it all seemed stupid. I thought I had kicked my ED but in the last 6 months my bulimia has come back in full force. My "binges" aren't severe, but they have been brought on by my desire to lose weight, as since treatment I gained some weight. I can't control my eating, then retroactively assert control through purging. I am scared. I went to a counselor 6 months ago, after my first purge, but haven't been able to bring it up. My ED has been 100% in secret and I'm having trouble coming clean for my own sake. Help me please.

What can I do to get help if nobody knows about my ED and I am scared to tell anyone?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Participants needed for mothers in Recovery from Eating disorders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 10:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you in recovery from and Eating Disorder (Anorexia, Bulimia, Binge Eating Disorder, Eating Disorder Not otherwise Specified, etc)?

Do you have a history of disordered eating?

And are you a mother of a child a child between the ages of 5-18?

Would you like to earn a $25 Amazon gift card by sharing your story about your journey of motherhood in relation to recovery?

 Must be in recovery from an eating disorder.

 Must have at least one child between the ages of 5-18

 Must be at least 18 years of age

Participants will partake in a video/audio recorded interview for approximately 1  hours in person or through Skype. If you are interested in being interviewed about your experience please contact Heather Austin-Robillard. There will be a brief phone interview to determine eligibility.

Heather.austin@ttu.edu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Helping a close friend with purging </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 10:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all, I'm coming here looking for some advice. A very dear friend of mine has been struggling with bulimia / purging for quite some time. Recently, my friend has opened up to me about it, and it's extensiveness and how it's been affecting their life. I've tried to be available for them; being very open to listen and try to suggest potential solutions to the problem, but I'm afraid it doesn't help.

I'm not really sure where to go from here. I know a lot of solving the problem is trying to get the person to want to change, or speak to someone. Unfortunately, my friend doesn't want to speak to anyone about this. What can I do? What should I do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Questionable therapist approach to ED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 10:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a long history of dieting/binging, calorie counting, the whole lot. My biggest problem is binge eating (no purging). I consider myself educated on causes of BED, but recovery seems daunting, as if I'll never have a relationship with food that's "normal" like everyone else, even if the binging stops. 

I understand that BED is often caused by dieting, your animal brain trying to refeed your body, etc. I also have read "Brain Over Binge" and am aware of intuitive eating. I do not binge often anymore; I had my first one in about a year last week (in the past they were 1-4 binges per week), so I decided to go see a therapist to prevent it from escalating further.

In the past, I saw one therapist who told me re: BED "it's okay if you binge; just do it on fruits and veggies!" I never went back. Another was always 10 mins late to every appt and fought me saying "You don't need to diet, you look great. I don't get it." These were self-proclaimed ED specialists. 

Enter now, as I wearily enter a new therapists office who specializes in ED's in hopes of some help. During our appt, she asked me about family history of course. I had a tumultuous childhood (addictive parent suicide attempts, divorce, etc), but I consider myself strong and independent as a result. I've made my peace with my childhood and do the best I can as an adult to make healthy decisions and am successful in most areas of my life. 

Long story short, this therapist insists that my binging is related to my childhood and my narcissistic mother, and states that once I "fix" those problems in my life that the binging will magically go away. What I feel like she doesn't understand is I have already come to peace with my past, and though I can't "fix" my mom I try to maintain a healthy relationship with her. My problem is my years-long obsession with getting the body I want and have felt like I deserve, and wanting to just accept my body for what it is and see food normally. 

I guess my question is; should I listen to my therapist? Should I seek out someone new? I guess I'm just tired of people trying to pin all of my problems on my childhood, instead of taking a different perspective. All I want is to be at total peace with my body, to end the diet/binge cycle, and to have a healthy relationship with food.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: concerned I may be headed toward an eating disorder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 13:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always been an impulsive/compulsive overeater (thanks ADHD) and I was pretty average weight until last year when I moved away for university (2014) and I had no one around to keep a sense of structure in my life. This year I've been on track with healthy eating, but I've also come to develop a fear of calories. I check calories on labels every time I eat and I have established fairly low limits of "acceptable size", above which is too much and I likely won't finish it out of guilt/disgust with myself. This behavior, which I've recognized is sort of restricting, alternates with mindless binging. In fact, the restrictive periods come about after binging because I've begun to see it as a way to "make up for it". I only recently read about "non-purging" bulimia and my habits sound scarily similar to it. I think I'm slightly overweight, but I feel like every bit of fat is amplified in my eyes and if I wear clothes that hug my body too tightly I usually feel like I'm bursting at the seams. I am almost certain that I'm not as big as I perceive myself to be. I don't really know what to do because I want to lose weight but in a healthy way, and I don't want my parents to worry about me. Can anyone offer advice?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Extreme fatigue on rest days, worried my eating is disordered </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 12:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I'm a young man and I've had some problems with being underweight and gaining weight for the past 2 years or so. I've been noticing some things that make me think I might have some type of ED. I'm sorry if this post is too long or has some mistakes.

Several months ago I managed to gain enough weight to get have a healthy BMI rating, but I had some issues about feeling like I gained too much fat and not enough muscle, so I did some dumb stuff and lost too much weight, putting me back into the underweight category. I've been underweight again since around October or September, and telling myself that I'm trying to gain weight despite not eating enough calories. 

I guess I'm afraid that I'll gain too much fat so I keep my calorie surplus a bit low, and I have a lot of trouble eating enough on non-lifting days so I calorie cycle (eat extra surplus on lifting days and around maintenance on rest) but I'm thinking that it's not enough to help me gain weight since I've stayed about the same weight since October. I'm just so afraid that I'll gain fat even though when I compare pictures of myself at a healthy weight, I had pretty low body fat and more muscle than I have now, so I mostly lost muscle weight.

For the past week I've had severe fatigue on my rest days, where I have hardly any energy after going on my daily walks despite still eating meals. I have very low appetite and feel a bit depressed and hollow, not as bad as I have before but I feel like I wouldn't mind just ceasing to exist to stop the stress of dealing with everything. I started to realize that I share a lot of symptoms for anorexia and bulimia listed online, but I don't know if that's just coincidence and I don't want to self-diagnose. Reading those symptoms just makes me feel even worse, like everything I've done to try to get in shape has been a waste and it makes me feel terrible. I really just want to be in healthy shape and be able to function normally, and do athletic things I love to do without so much stress.

I just know that something is wrong with me, but I don't know what I can do. I live with my mother and I'm afraid to tell her about all of this, because I don't want to cause more stress and feel like such a failure for being a bad son. I know that I have to tell her how I feel, but really don't know when or how I should. And I don't know if I should be worried about feeling so fatigued and low, or if it's just a coincidence type of thing.

I'd like to hear any advice or insight anybody has that might help, thank you for reading and I'm sorry if I took too much of your free time.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Boyfriend likes my "chubby cheeks", he doesnt know it makes me feel fat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 12:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So my boyfriend thinks I have really cute cheeks, and wants me to pinch them cause yeah he thinks its adorable. He doesnt know it triggers me a lot, and that i used to stand in front of the mirror when i was younger, pinching my cheeks to emphasize how fat i thought i was. 

How do i tell him without hurting him?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Seeing hot girls triggers me a lot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 12:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes my boyfriend shows me pictures of hot girls from his insta, its a long story. Anyways, just seeing hot girls trigger me so so much. After he showed me three pictures ive purged twice and i cant get the self hatred and urge to starve myself out of my system. He wont repeat showing me pics like that again though, he connected the dots and being really really hard on himself for it, even though i didnt want him to find out. 

How can i stop the racing thoughts of comparing myself to everyone, it hurts so so much and its hurting my boyfriend that i'm so fragile
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Is my eating disorder shifting shapes or am I getting better? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 01:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would really like some insight, if possible. I don't know what's happening with my body and mind at the moment. I used to suffer from Bulimia. I haven't purged in weeks now though, but I still binge. So I decided to tackle that part of the whole issue. I've cut out several foods that I used to binge on and now I have nightmare of losing control, of waking up and having eaten all those foods, of being back to stuffing my face with no control over what or how much I eat. It's terrifying. Every morning I wake up convinced I failed at yet another part of life and I'm back to that out-of-control sad little monster. Also my list of things I'm 'not allowed to eat' because otherwise they would trigger me to binge, is getting longer and longer, I get more and more fearful around food and have panic attacks when I just see something in a store. Or if a friend offers me something... I'm scared that I will forget that I'm not eating these things anymore and then relapse. When I eat I usually eat the same things that don't make me panic, but there are maybe five things on my 'safe' list, which can't be healthy either.

Is this a normal part of the whole process of stopping the binging? Or is my eating disorder just changing to something different? Do the nightmares and night sweats ever go away? Is there a way to speed up this part of the recovery? I really can't deal with it and I don't know what to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: books about food addiction/binge eating disorder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 16:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I've learned more about food addiction and binge eating disorder I feel like it could be an explanation for what I'm going through. Does anyone know of books I can get that explain things well?

I see a therapist regularly about other things and I wouldn't be opposed to talking with him about it but I'd like to do some of my own research first
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Coping with weight gain during recovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 15:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the majority of my teen years, I have struggled really badly with anorexia. I'm currently 2 years into recovery, and I am at the heaviest I have ever been. I'm the same weight I was when I was 13, (I'm 18 now, and I stopped growing at age 13,) which is about a pound overweight, but those that I confide in swear to me that I am not the same size I was then. I don't understand how that's possible, and I am convinced that everyone is lying to me. I was doing really well with the mental part of recovery, but for the past few weeks, my weight has been the only thing I can think about. This is causing me to have full days where I just completely break down. I cry for hours on end, and I feel so overwhelmed. I feel so sad and angry and out of control. I lash out on my fiance when he tries to help because the only thing that makes sense is that he and everyone else is lying to me, and that just makes me feel even worse.

I was hoping that someone might have some advice on coping with this? It's become an almost daily occurrence, and I need to find some way to get this under control.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: What to do with friends that doesn't revolve around binge/unhealthy eating? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 15:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been struggling with an eating disorder for the last little bit and I've been making so much progress. I'm very proud of myself. However, I tend to slide back into my bingeing (and then later as a result, restricting) ways every time social gatherings happen. I feel as if most of our social interactions at least in the society I am from revolve around getting together to eat and drink, especially in university. But I really struggle with eating, especially in social situations. Does anyone have any suggestions for what I could do with friends that isn't about eating, especially for low income university kids in dorm rooms? or any tips on how they've overcome similar situations in their own lives?? Thanks so much!!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Is ED IOP considered rehab? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 12:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is ED intensive outpatient program considered rehab because it is in a treatment center?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Questions about orthorexia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 12:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am very health conscious, there are a lot of foods I refuse to eat. I've always considered being healthy to be a good thing. How can a diet like mine be unhealthy? Then recently one of my friends told me she thinks I'm orthorexic, that the fact I wouldn't even eat (for example) one piece of chocolate might be physically healthy but mentally that's not healthy at all. 

I don't see how a healthy diet can be an eating disorder, like what makes a diet healthy and what makes it orthorexia, where is that line? On top of that, while I am at a healthy weight, I can't deny that I've always been terrified of being overweight and I've always been very upset if I gain any weight, probably to an unhealthy extent. I've always been a lot more comfortable with myself when I'm thinner than average, and I might sometimes skip meals or be a little too preoccupied with what I eat. This has been going on for as long as I can remember, since a long time before I started cutting certain unhealthy foods from my diet. 

If I do have orthorexia, is that totally separate from my other issues with my weight and body image, or could my possibly unhealthily healthy diet just be a part of a bigger problem? When I started eating more healthily, I genuinely was just trying to be healthier, it wasn't about weight loss, so I'm inclined to think it's not a problem, that my diet right now is fine. I've always managed to maintain a healthy weight, so I've always figured I must be healthy, but my friend bringing up orthorexia has made me think about all of this a little more and I don't know if I should be concerned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Trouble with Parents </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 12:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all. I've been struggling with something lately, and I was hoping I could get some input from the community. Just as background, I'm recovering from AN. I've been doing really well on the recovery front, my eating has been totally solid and I've been sticking to the plan that my nutritionist cooked up. I'm practically weight restored and I am no longer experiencing the mind-boggling levels of hunger that I once did. However, and this is the problem, I can't convince my parents that I'm full. 

Whenever I express that I am no longer hungry, even when I eat a completely reasonable and healthy amount, my dad or mom will just say "No. Eat more." I've been pushing myself past fullness for them, and I just feel a little uncomfortable with this situation. 

Any tips for confronting them and building back their trust for my fullness cues? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Do I Dare (non-blind weighing)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 21:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I relapsed hard about a year ago. I have dealt with multiple deaths and did a thirty day yoga challenge that was really triggering. I also manage a boutique and have been struggling to find another gig. 

My partner and my counselor have been blind weighing me. But I am having trouble with eating and I don't trust them about my weight. I feel like I am being lied to. Not fun. I also am starting to question if the weight-restorative model was the right way to go. I did a day treatment program from March 2014 to May 2014 where we were given a model to measure and count calories that were consumed in a certain amount of hours. It felt like as soon as I walked out of there, shit started to fall apart. 

I recently did a free screening with someone from a different treatment center in Elmira, NY who told me that seeing the number of calories while being weighed without knowing what is up heightened anxieties that I had about eating and my size. 

I feel like I don't know what is real and it is allowing my ED-voice to fill in the blanks. 

Does anyone have experience with non-blind weighing (learning their weight)? What should I do? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How can I and my family help my 16yr old sister with her Anorexia? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 12:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My little sister started showing eating behavioral changes around 2 years ago. No matter how much my mother, I (her 24 yr old brother), or our sister and father help out she has maintained an anorexic diet and has been distancing herself emotionally from us. Every day it's like there's a dark cloud above her and it extends to the rest of us. We love her and do so much (make sure to wait until she comes home from school to eat a snack and then dinner together; my mom (a pediatrician amusingly enough) has been taking her to a nutritionist, psychiatrist specializing in adolescents with eating disorders, and my sister's own pediatrician, but not much has changed in these two years. 

We've even had interventions where we all sat together, told her how much we love and care about her, and how much she's damaging herself. 

The mood of the household is so much different now than it was a few years ago, and it saddens me. I want my little sister to be the happy, bubbly girl she used to be. 

I'm a med student and I know and have seen in rounds the damage anorexia can produce. It's horrible, and not something I want my sister to experience. The long-term effects may be permanent and it just kills me to think that she may already have damaged herself to that extent. 

How can I and my family help her? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I have relapsed and I am scared. How can I conquer the fear of weight gain? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 18:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About 2 years ago I entered treatment for my eating disorder. At the time I was restricting and at a low body weight but my disorder has been around for almost a decade and started as bulimia. 

When I left treatment I was in a better place but looking back I'm not sure how "recovered" I really was. My weight dropped slightly after leaving treatment but remained steady. However in the past few months I've dropped down to my lowest weight. The restriction wasn't intentional at first, I was taking meds that killed my appetite. I'm trying to lower/stop the meds but I'm so scared of gaining weight and feeling hungry. 

I feel like I've wasted my time in treatment and I'm back to square one. I'm seeing a nutritionist, therapist and psychiatrist but I'm worried if I don't gain weight I'll end up back in treatment. 

How can I conquer the fear gaining weight so scary, how do I get rid of this forever? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Weight Redistribution in/after Recovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 15:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it is common for fat to accumulate in the midsection when a patient is being weight restored, but at what point does the weight "redistribute"? I have a friend who is experiencing this, and I keep telling her it will "even out", but I am starting to doubt that it will. She is heavier than before she became anorexic, but "looks fatter" than people of the same height and weight who weigh less than her. I am (obviously) very supportive and do not point this out, but I am scared she might relapse if it does not even out soon. To get to the point: Do some people maintain an uneven fat distribution after recovery? If not, how does the body determine when to stop putting it all on the stomach area? Thankyou. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: "Medically" Anorexic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 15:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please let me know if this is the right spot. Sorry for the tangent. This is new and confusing for me. If posted, please keep me anonymous. Thank you for any and all help/ guidance

Long story short(ish), I've been trying to lose weight in a healthy way because I was overweight, I began to lose the weight, then the weight started coming off very quickly, I reached my goal weight, and the weight still kept coming off. Within months I ended up being underweight with a fast metabolism and next to no appetite. It turns out that when 2 of my medications are combined they act as diet pills, and when you add the third it's apparently a "super" diet pill. No one warned me of this. So now I'm on high doses of heavy medications (that I need. They're the only ones I've had success with) and no food in my stomach. Bad combo.

Here's the other problem. According to my doctor, my body is physically and mentally showing the signs of anorexia due to starvation (brain fog, exhaustion, weak, feeling faint, black outs upon standing, thinning hair, hypoglycemia was a prior issue, heart rate issues, the list goes on). I started drinking boost and I'm trying to eat small meals throughout the day but food is just so unappealing to me. I will get a stomachache just at the thought of eating a lot of the time. This includes when I'm hungry. I'll be starved, finally find something that's appealing, eat 4 bites, still be hungry but my stomach won't let me eat more. It feels like a mental and physical block. I don't know how I got to this point because I've always loved food. 

Any advice beyond "see a doctor" (I'm what keeps doctors in business...) and "just force it" (I can't afford to force it, get sick, and end up dehydrated on top of everything else) is welcome.

edit:
The op /u/8plur8 has asked that you pm them when you reply. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I'm not sure how I should talk to my friend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 15:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a friend who is very strict about only eating healthily, she's a vegetarian (mostly vegan) and she doesn't eat anything with added sugar, so basically she lives off fruit, vegetables, and nuts. Some days (not often) she does have smoothies for breakfast or lunch but mostly she doesn't eat anything for breakfast or lunch. She says she eats plenty of food when she gets home in the late afternoon/evening, but I don't know if she's telling the truth about that or not, and she does eat dinner, I know she usually cooks for her family, but other than that I don't see how she can be eating a healthy amount every day with the amount of meals she skips and the fact she usually doesn't start eating until I think about 3 or 4pm.

She really doesn't like people talking to her about her health (we've been friends for a long time and something else unrelated happened before and she got really upset when anyone tried to talk to her about it) so now I don't want to bring this up with her and end up making her angry or completely unwilling to talk about it, but I'm really starting to worry, she does look like she's lost some weight over the last few months and she was fairly thin before that.

So basically I just want to know if it's at all normal for someone to just not eat until late afternoon every day, and I want advice on how I could talk to her about this without risking making the situation worse.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I've got 99 problems... and they all make my appetite issues worse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 15:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a LOT going on (grad student and life is hectic), and I already had poor eating habits prior to all of this. I guess you might call it UNintentional intermittent fasting. I have always had some preferences as far as texture and temperature (warm is always more appetizing).

I have anxiety/depression, and that (previously) untreated caused some more food weirdness for me. My empty stomach turns on me now, the nausea much worse than the original dull ache, Ive even thrown up a few times from not eating (body, no, stop). I had previously been self medicating with mj which helped the nausea as well as my appetite (not to mention the anxiety and depression and mood), but sadly that was not a long term sustainable option. I decided to seek formal treatment for my anxiety/depression, and cycling through the meds has been a disappointing cycle, one helped a lot but absolutely killed my sex drive and sleeping habits, one made me sleepy constantly, some didnt work, etc. Im now on another handful of the stuff, and when I started one of the meds (welbutrin) it sort of amplified these feelings and habits a little. Appetite definitely dropped, it got easier to forget I hadnt eaten, less lust for food in general, more nausea (thats hard to gauge on a timeline). I also recently quit the mj, so that is in play as well. 

I am sensitive to the dosages so my Rx's are all kids sized, so lowering them isnt really an option. I know I can ask to switch again, but the welbutrin is my "work horse" med, plus I already have another SNRI to try, and this is all happening as the next semester of grad school and clinical start... tomorrow. Plus psychiatrist is booked 10 weeks out anyways. Switching meds is a little traumatic for me, the taper up/down process for some of these is maddening (brain zaps and MORE APPETITE PROBLEMS YAY) so Im not very inclined to ask to switch yet.

So here I am writing this, 6am and I havent slept yet, although I have a rumbly tummy and food looks/smells absolutely nauseating right now. Boyfriends get nervous when they see me eat so little, so I try to shove some down to make nice since they made me food or are worried etc, but its hard. I try eating even when Im not hungry but should be, to try to retrain those hunger hormones, but it hasnt been something I can manage to do with any sort of success or continuity because I feel just as pukey trying to force myself to eat and its a really strange mental experience, not sure i can explain it.

TLDR Medications, anxiety, depression, quitting mj, and a record of poor eating habits are about to hit me like a truck. Riding that trainwreck into a fresh semester of grad school. Need to learn to regulate eating somehow in a way that doesnt mean me feeling ill from undereating or eating when my stomach/nose/brain turns food against me. 

Looking for ideas and support on how to deal with this.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I am a very fussy eater. How can I get help with this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 20:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have always been a fussy eater and I've went to many doctors are they've been literally no help, i want to try different foods etc, but i can't bring myself to do it.

It ruins night outs and everything really for me and i need to break it. 

How can I begin getting help with this?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How can I stay on track with recovery/weight restoration while I am very busy with school? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 20:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am in recovery from AN and need to restore a significant amount of weight. I am eating a sizable meal plan to accomplish this, but now that I'm back at college after the winter break I'm finding it really difficult to keep on track. It's so easy to restrict when I have classes to distract me. 

Furthermore I find it really hard to eat when no one else around me seems to be eating. Obviously everyone eats according to their own hunger cues   schedules but so often I feel like I'm the only one eating and it makes me feel terribly guilty. On top of everything, i'm finding it hard to pack the volume of food I need! 

Weight restoration requires a LOT of food and I often feel like i'm hauling around half a grocery store in my backpack. 

How can I help aid my weight restoration process while balancing a full course load at school? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How can I help my friend who has bulimia? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 20:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello

I know someone with Bulimia and from the looks of her teeth she has been having that from a teenage years.

She is a very sweet person.

I don't know if I did wrong but I told her that I knew about her disorder and didn't judge her for it and offered my support.

She didn't deny anything (apparently she previously denied it to someone else)

She told me some personal things about herself.

I told her that if she needs anything or support with anything that I would be there.

But I did it a bit spontaneously and I have to admit I don't really know if I should start to slowly present the idea to go to a consultation about her condition if she opens up a bit more about it.

Any constructive advice would be welcomed and greatly appreciated. How can I help?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I have a hard time eating and I am noticing negative effects. My doctor is not helping. How do I get help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 04:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've struggled with food since I was 15, from what I can recall. I am 22 now and have noticed some long term affects, I just need advice.

I don't know if I'd classify myself as anorexic, as I don't know how much of my behaviour is learned or is stemming from something wrong with me. I've never been a big eater, and I often will get halfway through a normal portion and feel sick - hell sometimes it's two bites in. For example at 1:30pm last Friday I hadnt eaten anything in almost a full day. When I finally took my break I could feel my stomach turning and myself feeling that "I've gone too long without food feeling", I bought subway and got two bites into it before feeling sick and nauseated. 

Since Wednesday (it was Friday as I wrote this) I have only had a few very small portions. I've been doing this for years, but it's not that I don't want to eat. It's more of a every time I eat I feel worse inside than I felt before eating. There are times where i want to eat but just "don't have the time to". I put it off until I notice it has started to affect my cognitive ability.

I've told a lot of this to my doctor and her response was "well I think you are just eating the wrong things" when I let her know that my appetite is very low she just says "well you look healthy, all your lab tests are fine" and brushes me off. I recently tested hypothyroid - she did not bother looking into WHY I am hypo, just focused on giving me a pill a day to fix it.

There are days where I'll wake up and cook my boyfriend a full breakfast... I'll eat much less, not a full meal. I just loose interest, and often feel ill after just that. Sure some days I forgo more nutritious food for convenient snacks out of just an inner want. But the majority of the time I just don't want to eat anything.

I've struggled with loosing weight all my life, and the majority of it would come from "junk" food and not much nutritious food. But it's to the point where I view all food as the same nutritionally. The reason I think this way could be because no matter what I eat I feel sick.

Anyway, I'm just looking for advice as to how I can break myself out of this habit and maybe some ways that you all have dealt with similar situations with loved ones / yourselves. Any help, is greatly appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Thinking about getting help for restriction, but nervous and not sure how to start. Advice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 04:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been struggling with restricting for several months now (since July) and have lost a fair amount of weight. I have had trouble with this in the past, too (senior year of high school, 10 years ago) but handled it on my own. I have been thinking about getting help but am not sure how to ask.

I have considered going to a therapist - I'm sure they would be kind to me but the idea of talking about food just seems too embarrassing. I am thinking about talking to my primary care doctor but I would have to talk to the secretary on the phone and say what the appointment was for, also I would have to talk to the nurse before I see the doctor herself. Also, what exactly would I say to my doctor if/when I talked to her?

Have you found a way to benefit from therapy? How do I bring this up, and how can I get help while managing my fear of talking about certain things?

I think I need help but I am really not sure what to do so any advice would be so appreciated! :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Tried to help my friend by telling her mother, now both of them are in denial and my friend won't speak to me. What do I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 04:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After submitting multiple posts and consulting multiple people who have successfully recovered asking what I could do to help my severely bulimic best friend, I finally told her mother. My friend told me something that particularly alarmed me, so I sent a LONG Facebook message explaining what was going on. 

The next day, my friend told me that her mom had asked if what I said was true, she had said no, and that was that. So I followed up with screenshots that proved I wasn't making it up. Nothing. They're both in denial. Not only is my friend (who is over 18) not getting help, now she's not talking to me because I violated her trust. On top of that, one of her other friends messaged me to tell me that I'm a bad friend and that I'm making everything worse. 

I hate this. I hate it so much. I always said I'd rather lose her to anger than to bulimia, but I figured once I told someone she'd finally get the help she needed and things would be okay. I was wrong. Everyone told me there were no easy solutions, but as it turns out, there are no solutions at all. 

Can anyone offer me some encouragement or advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Thought I had anorexia but now I don't really know what this is. Please help identify what I have? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 10:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 18, at the end of spring last year I started clearly getting an eating disorder. Thought it was anorexia for a long time and maybe it is but I feel like it isn't so yeah.. 

* I've gone from a pretty healthy weight to very very thin in about half a year because of it  
* food disgusts me most of the time and I can't be around people who are eating (not in a misophonic way) because I just hate being around food  
* this is the MAIN symptom that makes it scream "not anorexia!!" To me.. The #1 reason I don't eat. I have this HUGE paranoia about getting a stomach ache when I eat. It never happens, in fact spicy is my favorite kind of food. But I am scared to eat because the thought going through my head is "you're gonna get a stomach ache don't do it don't eat" and like I said I never get them. Sometimes my paranoia gets so bad about it that I think I have a stomach ache for real when I don't.  

This makes eating really hard, I'd love some advice on what the hell this is... Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Relapsed into anorexic behaviour after long period and kids </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 10:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a middle aged female who has a history of anorexia and bulimia. When I became pregnant the first I was able to kick it. I was OK for 13 years after that. I was overweight for many years and then I started dieting. Extremely restricted diet... Extreme exercise. Of course people were complimentary. Then it got out of hand.

My kids started to notice I wasn't eating. (my husband really is clueless at this point.... He's just happy I'm skinny again) So for the kids sake I try to eat... But i can't. I do eat but I have to purge right away.

I'm scared.... I am so embarrassed to tell anyone. Can anyone suggest a next move for me?

So now it's a year.... And my kids are so proud of me for. the loosing weight....but I'm a fake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My girlfriend doesn't like to eat - does she need help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 17:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend likes all types of foods and will eat with me for some meals. When we do eat together, sometimes she will say comments like "This is the first thing I've eaten today" and it concerns me.

Other times, especially during breakfast (which she rarely eats) she will take two bits of her meal and then say she doesn't feel good and can't eat anymore. I've asked her if she could have some sort of allergy or celiacs but she says no. She just feels nauseous after she eats any food.

I don't know if she's anorexic or if she just really doesn't like food a bunch! She is very, very thin.

Its hard to tell what to do or whether or not she needs help. I don't know if she is healthy or not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Eating Disorder? Depression, and anxiety. Who can help me at this point? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 17:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello! Im an 18yr old gal struggling a bit, I previously was diagnosed with EDNOS, mild depression, and GAD when I was 15, worked really hard to build a normal relationship with food, be healthy, and love myself. 

Everything had been going really well until completely unexpectedly my boyfriend who I still am very in love with broke up with me. He was a big part of my ED support, always made me food since he lived with me, and made me enjoy going on dinner dates! 

But since the break up my mental illness has gotten out of control, i'm very anxious, depressed, and having suicidal thoughts (which i will not act on) for the first time in my life. 

I have not been able to eat. I have no interest in food what so ever. Im not actively trying to be thin like I was when I was really struggling with my ED, but I am now at my lowest weight ever and don't know how to help myself. I've tried snacking lots and drinking supplements. 

Its just too hard to gain weight when i have absolutely no will or interest to eat. I'm on an antidepressant and feel seeing a therapist (again) won't be very helpful, I know all about my problems and why I am depressed and anxious and what it stems from and everything. 

Do I go to an ED treatment facility? Who can help me at this point? Because my GP sure doesn't know what to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How can I stop binging? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 17:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't stop binging. It's like clockwork. I binge after a week of conforming to diet and eating healthfully. I promise to never to binge again and hit my macros for a week. I binge once more. Rinse, repeat. Every fucking week. 

Its so easy to resolve to not binge while I'm eating healthfully but then I enter some state of mind and I can not stop eating. In the past, I purged after with exercise, restricting the next day, or sometimes throwing up, but lately I've given up. I'm so sick of it. 

I started my cut in September to lose a small amount of weight. Simple, right? Instead, I've succeeded at gaining more weight. I think I should stop tracking calories but MFP has become my obsession in a way, using it provides me with comfort and stability. I could use some guidance. (16F btw) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Worried I'm developing a problem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 18:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since I was young I have had a lot of anxiety around food and body image. I have used myfitnesspal for years which both calms my anxiety and feeds my fixation. Whenever I have gained weight I have crash-dieted it off and then gone back to maintaining. However, the goal weight that I like to maintain is at the high end of the healthy range (I like having muscles) so I haven't felt in danger of bad health effects from my food issues.

Lately though, I've been going through a tough time with a breakup, bad injury, school stress and some weight gain. I also accidentally found a proana forum online (I'm not kidding about accidental. It was linked in a circlejerk Reddit thread!). Since then I have been checking proana sites hundreds of times a day. I'm eating less than ever before and my usual weight is starting to strike me as fat. All of this is having a negative effect on my other goals, especially finishing my dissertation. I want to stop reading those sites and go back to my (somewhat) more healthy eating habits and goals. But the proana forums are so welcoming, eating little and losing weight quickly are satisfying, and I feel so sad and stressed that it's hard to turn my back on these things!

Any ideas? I already go to a therapist for anxiety and depression, but I'm usually pretty cagey with him about food, and in the past whenever I've brought up food issues he has said the most unhelpful things. I'm also deeply ashamed of all of this so it's hard to talk to anyone about it. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Anxiety Induced Anorexia Problem with Dizziness/Slurred Speech </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 15:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My eating disorder stems from anxiety. I cross posted this in /r/anxiety but I wanted to post it here because I really do think it's something with where my body was when I was at my most anxious/lowest weight.

For about 3 or 4 years, I've been having regular (as in, hourly) short "bursts" of dizziness and slurred speech. My fingers and sometimes my toes/feet will often sort of clamp up uncontrollably as well, like I'm not in control of my actual nerves. These bursts last about 3/4 seconds, and usually happen when I stand up or when I'm walking. It's quite similar to a headrush from standing up too fast, but with the slurred speech and weird finger cramping added in.

The last 3/4 years when this started happening have been the worst (in terms of anxiety) I've experienced. Some people close to me died which I didn't deal well with and I just completely lost my appetite for a few months. I pretty much became scared to eat because my anxiety stems from a fear of vomiting and I thought that eating anything would cause me to vomit. I was quite underweight at one point but I gained what I needed to this year and am now in the healthy weight range. I now get enough protein and water. I never get ill or get headaches. As I said, things were terrible, and I hardly left my house, but this last week I finally managed to go to the doctor to get a full blood test done and he said I wasn't deficient in anything and that all my organs were fine. This surprised me because I thought I might be dehydrated or anemic at least, or diabetic at worst.

Does anyone have any ideas about what it might be? I can't be certain, but it does happen when I think about it. I don't know if this is because I feel it coming on and then I think about it, or if I think about it and then it happens, like some kind of tick. If anyone has any ideas I'd really appreciate it because it's happening quite a lot and I feel like a fucking idiot when I'm slurring and almost stumbling over if I try to keep walking.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What can I expect in inpatient treatment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 05:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because my relative has guardianship, I am being forced to go into inpatient treatment for anorexia even though I am 18. I am not told where nor exactly what date. I'm not ready to recover right now, so I'm very nervous about it. 

My main questions are:

How much weight will I be expected to gain? Will it just be up to the normal weight threshhold? 

Do I have the right to refuse to eat? If so, to what extent can I refuse to eat? 

If I adhere to dietary restrictions by choice, will they cater to that? 

How strict are they about exercise? 

Will I be allowed to have my phone? 

What was your experience like? Did you want to go, and did it help?

Thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
