<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3094</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jump rope for HIIT? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 23:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy Sunday!  
  
I've been lifting for a while as well as doing HIIT cardio three to four times a week on either the elliptical or the treadmill. I thought I'd see if any of you guys have used jump rope as a successful HIIT alternative. I despise running, and the elliptical is just boring to me. Thoughts/suggestions/successful routines?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 15:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have struggled with anorexia since I was 15 years old, and though I am technically recovered, it is still a constant struggle.  
  
I have a two year old daughter, and though this may not be typical, I was more at peace with my body during pregnancy than I have ever been, before or after. When struggling with an ED, it's so easy to be angry at your body for not doing the things you want it to do. Pregnancy made me proud of my body. Not of what it looked like, but what it was doing for me and for my daughter. I felt strong. Of course, I had bad days, but for the most part I was just overwhelmed with respect for my body. It also was so much easier for me to eat what I needed. Not easy, but easier. Because it wasn't for me. It was for her. What I did struggle with was post-pregnancy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 22:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know a lot of people are saying, "just do it", but it's true. I fell out of lifting for a short time and [this](http://www.muscleforlife.com/shut-up-and-train/) article SERIOUSLY kicked me back into high gear. If you ever want to get into lifting and training, I'd highly recommend his book "Thinner, Leaner, Stronger" as well. He does a great job at motivating, and he does a TON of research. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 21:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A stomach virus hit me at about ten last night, and I've spent most of my time since then on my bathroom floor. I have managed recently to migrate to my bed, and Netflix is keeping me occupied. I just want some egg drop soup, man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 01:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mike Matthews also does this. He reads an insane amount of papers and studies.  
  
www.muscleforlife.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 01:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mike Matthews  
  
www.muscleforlife.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
