<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1113</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 13:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I'm apparently on the "high" end of the spectrum which is pure bullshit because autism isn't a binary of low and high functioning, it's a spectrum, hense the name! But I do have problems with stimuli and instead of disrepecting or ridculing the person, we should try and make the world better or less stressful. It is not their fault that the world is sometimes too much to handle, they didn't do anything to be that way so we should try and understand that person and give them ways to cope with those problems.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 13:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been around autistics, I am autistic and some of my best friends are. The kids you saw there, the reason they screamed when they were touched is because sometimes for autistics being touched physically hurts and people have boundaries that need to be respected. Also grown men playing with crayons is not part of having autism and could be a different disability. Have you ever had depression? I'm curious because I have both autism and depression and depression is so much worse than autism. Depression is for the most part life long, you can learn ways to cope with depression and take medication but depression is to do with how your brain is wired and that is life long.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 03:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I self censored the word because I really don't like that and I know a lot of people like it either. It's an awful word. How is autism an undesirable medical condition? Autistic people are actually very talented and intelligent, we just have difficulties in things that come natural to neurotypicals
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 02:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it is a neuro developmental disorder, it can't be cured. To cure someone with autism is taking away their personality and what makes them unique. A huge part of the autistic community don't want to be cured. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 01:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like this is an unpopular opinion among autistic people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 00:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except Autism isn't a disease like AIDS etc and how am I r*tarded for thinking that autistic people deserve to be treated with respect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
