<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1499</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 05:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How I wonder would have he wrote that letter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 05:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please tell me how the hell would you comprise a microwave without having physical access to it, and turn it into a flippen camera? (Sorry if this is coming across as aggressive) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While to Zanarkand is definitely the most recognized, how is FFX otherworld? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Downloaded a mod for skyrim, was surrounded by 30+ ebony played bandits who proceeded to turn me into a poisoned hedgehog, the mod was worth it. I was lv ~220  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless you are a distributor of illegal content the Law enforcement usually sends a cease and desist letter and nothing more than that, but by non-violent I meant more drug possession and etc, and do you have sting operations? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 04:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Internal injuries sometimes take time to surface  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 03:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you might enjoy this https://www.reddit.com/r/yesyesyesno </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much practical control would the mayors office possess ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much practical control would the mayors office possess ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much practical control would the mayors office possess ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if the police are more likely to catch you doing something non-violent illegal how likely are they to prosecute you and what sentence are you likely to receive? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if the police are more likely to catch you doing something non-violent illegal how likely are they to prosecute you and what sentence are you likely to receive? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing is I view police will act cool to you as long as they don't think you are a criminal. I had a friend who unwittingly stumbled onto a sting operation that ended with the cops busting down the doors, tearing apart carpets in the apartment, screaming and yelling profanities into her face saying she is guilty and all that, pressuring her to confess all the illegal things she has ever done. When I got the details my opinion of police plummeted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here you go this should help you. https://www.reddit.com/r/small_business_ideas/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even Hawaii? I had a relative who went skydiving and they picked them up in a pick up truck had them in the bed after the fall...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 09:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do all states bar people in trailer if in motion? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 09:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If false or true
  Short circuit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 08:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say CA is a big state and hard to lump together, hell even in the same city there is I-80 where people are more or less courteous, safe, reasonable and then a few miles over in BUS I-80 and people drive to kill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 08:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here you go, the advice they is fairly good with sections on how to rephrase things to a higher level https://www.reddit.com/r/resumes/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 08:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a happy sibling, but seriously I recommend you check out /r/legaladvice  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find myself being able to communicate on a low-mid level with Ukrainians despite not knowing a word of it. (I speak Russian) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically in the short term that does increase your risk for a heart attack by a good amount but... I can't say if smoking and running is worse than stationary smoking in the long run. (Random pun) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like a bad way to die, held down and slowly stabbed to death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump was campaigning for the bill, as a president he has much more power or influence than any member of the senate or congress. He bears the biggest share of responsibility and accountability for the bill, whether the president cares or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Companies, academics, NSA, Google, Telacoms, schools, and people who like to be well informed "stalk" people by reading papers and posts by others. It's how communication works my dear friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Short bills and laws will come up short when enforced </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the president does have a veto so ultimately he can block it if he so cares </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to make a quip that he is also addicted to junk news but I feel that would offend some people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was about to make a whole reconciliation prompt and all but I checked /u/drdeth666 post history bc he has a weird name and... pretty sure he is nothing more than a troll. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did not know the last part, before I made ghouls defensively waiting for the enemy to *ahem* dig their own grave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only if well farmed (but then it's the ADC who becomes the support) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell yeah with a vayne adc, no way she can miss her e now!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Azir was the buggiest champ of all times </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makes me miss when Azir was not so horrible  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh played sacred stones at least 6 times and never noticed that part </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 09:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Explain to this plebeian  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 09:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ai, but we kill each other less. Minus a few "backwards" nations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 09:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few were crazy, let's put nuclear land mines in Germany? Train cats to be spies? Though I don't get what was so crazy about the British subs cutting the wires. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 09:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you certain it wasn't due to lack of information or that information that a single bomb destroyed a city was hard to believe and they needed confirmation? The infrastructure in Japan at that time was ruined so Information probably didn't travel that fast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 09:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Care it was not at least a million casualties, that were inflated figures </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 08:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very well written, somewhat surprised not to see the victor bot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 08:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Writers were probably northern  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 08:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 03:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "These men have not wronged us..."

"I understand the need to hold one's life dear, but to hold is so far above others"

Most of weigraf 

And it just goes on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 03:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It made me hate him more because I recognized his rhetorical strategies to manipulate the general populace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 21:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ai such as Napoleonic conflict I don't think genocide was in there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 09:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flee flee flee I accidentally (well I tried to kill him) pissed off the dinosaur! And he is chasing me across the freaken map! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 09:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The game has a gradual learning curl but many of the features you learn are not absolutely necessary but very nice. Particularly the Gambits system where you can automate some decisions like cast cure on an ally below 40% hp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really enjoyed the Gambit system of XII </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heard many stories how how to smuggle bibles in the military, prison terms being served, beatings being administered, economic pressure, during the USSR, while it comes from only a Christian perspective I assume it wouldn't have been different for Muslim (things that occurred recently on Chechen lands comes to mind) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A particular event by military vs civilians would be the rape of Berlin by solviet soldiers, considered in retaliation to German treatment of Russians. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slavs were considered around the same level as Jews by the Nazis so... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~40% of solviet POWs held by Germans survived

~63% of Germans POWs held by solviets survived 

~65% of American POWs held by Japan survived 

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Prisoner_of_war </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The eastern front as a whole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of a comic that made humor of this rule. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lead statistics are quite similar around the globe suggesting a very real correlation between lead and crime. While potentially we can reproduce this to confirm, it would be unethical to expose anyone to lead just to confirm statistics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The article is quite well written  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I am expecting only = $900 I don't want to lose that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine is liability only, so when I called them they told me I have to settle it with infinity insurance  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [CA, Sacramento] should I start repairs on my vehicle if the claim is still not closed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [CA] last December I had gotten involved in a 10 car accident on a free-way my car is still drivable despite damages such as the trunk won't close and the frame needs to be bent. Insurance I am dealing with is infinitely insurance, estimated the value of the vehicle to be at 5k while repairs would be 7k according to estimates, so insurance wants to buy my vehicle. 

 The person at fault only had 10,000 dollar liability, and across 9 cars, 2 of which were totaled, there is no way I can expect 5 k from insurance. I want to start repairs however I want to know if I start repairs will I still be reimbursed out of whatever of the 10k the insurance allotted to me. I had my vehicle estimated both by a third party and the insurance auto shop. I am afraid if I repair my vehicle they will say "what damage?" And I will get nothing. Please help.

The claim is still open and from the insurance representative I get the feeling it will not be closed for a while, and the insurance only want to pay out after all parties involved come to an agreement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 07:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ai it's a shame, but most would accept killing a few to save the lives of many, or in this case solidify political power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 07:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crime and punishment as mystery?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 07:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crime and punishment as mystery?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 07:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds so familiar. Is it the one with angles vs demons? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't say I know of any specific edicts attached to not every women having a husband but I do think greater emphasis was placed on gender equality in the USSR than under the previous regime. Anecdotally my grandmother spoke of how in her youth she had assembled weapons such as rifles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a lot of honored public figures covered in dirt and muck that is all too often swept under the rug. Both in their time and in the histories that follow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The children could have been propped up with a regent fighting in their name, I think they were killed to prevent that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't deadliest warrior do something like this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 10:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It made it funnier, you were not expecting it all and just stopped for sec like "huh?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 10:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey it got better, last time I saw it it would activate itself creating a giant loop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 10:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's up with all the down votes in this sub... I thought this was a nice place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 10:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could /u/MR-GRN be referring to how many organic foods do not get injected with preservatives? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 10:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I specially farmed knights and black mages to feed to my superior characters. (For the black knight) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 09:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He most likely will </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 09:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That always going to be a grey area, I can see a child being raised to open doors for ladies and etc but growing up to be sexist thinking women are weaker and should be under a man's protection  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 08:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zac, Rammus (vs AD), karthus, kat, veigar, xerath, jayce, Azir (but he is gutted at the moment), are fairly interesting champs to play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 08:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do a duo of either Karthus top or ww top. Depends on the enemy pick and if I am one of the first picks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 08:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much do you hate poppy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Social planners can be more efficient, I would attribute the poor economics to the aforementioned political climate and corruption. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 10:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly wood if the person in question provided me an extension cord for my electric chain saw chop up that tree (or at least the parts used for firewood) for no cost... though at the moment my chain snapped.

If anything it's not hard to take the tree apart yourself, I would estimate a large oak tree an amateur to a chain saw could do it in a day or 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 10:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I chuckled at UBER thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 09:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are these things economically viable? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 09:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good manners on the reload? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 09:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you were beating a dead horse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 09:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... if they introduce something similar to the MAV of BF3, it could be heaven or it could be hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 09:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that he has your info I think you should delete this message, you know don't post private information. PM instead otherwise a random troll could mess with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 09:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should take away the reduced damage when squad spawning </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 08:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just browsing and encountered /u/dogfck in /r/gaming, I can't tell if he is serious or joking with the random things he posts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 08:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What... well Hadrian's wall begs to differ.

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hadrian's_Wall </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 07:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some one just do the math to stop em </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 23:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure big pharma makes more. But if you disagree with all this vote for/against your congressional representative and senator. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 20:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 20:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 20:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I should have thought more on it, I posted related only to the US but OP wanted beyond that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 11:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrong subreddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [CA] asking for further reference, do most health Insurance plans cover ambulance calls/rides? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 11:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if it is is it still better to be driven to a hospital by friends/family in semi-threading conditions? I.e. Non-fatal stab wound from a kitchen knife. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 11:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First time playing terraria during a blood moon. Wandering outside oh the moon is different... huh more zombies than usual... okay WAY more enemies... welp going to find a safe place to die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 10:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somehow managed to suppress the urge to shout and link to the Spanish Inquisition  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 10:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ! What... I  I thought he was in a good place. I tried him as support and it's just so hard to kill him, and top lane against almost any comp I can do well (screw teemo, Quinn, anyone ranged) because he just heals everything back up but if I am losing I quickly toggle w for blood price. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 09:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Originally there were 13 states and many thought all what would happen is each state would just get bigger but after much compromise they managed to agree on a system to add more states and on how to define a state. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 09:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's capital punishment for the professional forger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey if someone points an antique firearm at me I will still raise my hands </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
