<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1563</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 07:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> implying theres a difference </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 03:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> perfect for /r/anitjokes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 03:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i thought you meant the animated series at first </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont need any more reasons for that. I need more reasons not to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It gave me cancer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone just got put on a list </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How the fuck is my mechanic going to tell me that i need new brake pads? i have an A+ in all of my classes...smh so patronizing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh fuck this shit. kill me now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He obviously wasn't resetting, why not just fight him? Black knights arent THAT hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats the difference between cats and dogs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 04:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (cats - dogs) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 04:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She just said thank you. and i said you're welcome. i felt dumb but i probably wont see her for a long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 00:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In most cases I'd say that could be a little rude. Would be better to say that instead of your welcome when someone thanks you for coming to their spouses funeral. Just did that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 00:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cough torrenting cough. skipping classes cough cough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 00:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my problem is that i buy a bunch of games, but i become so infatuated with one that i dont even start the other ones. I'm on my fifth playthrough and 3rd character for dark souls. Still haven't started on the witcher 3, doom, or tomb raider yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 22:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I was frustrated working on my PhD so I made a new etching for my laptop." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 22:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its still confusing. "I was angry at my PhD so I made a new etching for my laptop" is a pretty weird sentence. i didnt get it either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 22:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an American, I get very confused with British colloquial language. I didn't understand the title at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kids are highly malleable and change interests all the time. Until they are old enough to really understand their decisions fully, they need guidance.  That even goes with highschoolers. I think it would be better to push your kids in a general direction and if they feel strongly that they dont wanna take that path, then talk with them and help direct them towards something that they'll like and will be able to make a career out of. I'm not sure what youre talking about putting up walls. All i'm saying is that its more socially acceptable for guys to be into computer stuff than girls, and maybe we should treat a girls interest in that kinda stuff the same as boys. And in general, we should encourage all kids to get into STEM fields. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 15:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what in the fuck is hannouka? Is that some kind of Jewish anime? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 15:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if(sex==gender)

return true;

else

{

return false;

cout"SHITLORD!";

}         </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 15:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spoken like someone with a lot of privilege. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 15:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly, it needs to come from the social level. Girls need to be encouraged by parents to get into STEM fields. Other girls and boys should not be making fun of girls for being into computers, science, math, engineering, etc. It's cool, and they'll have great careers pursuing those kinds of fields. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 13:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to spite these people I hope next year they pick ted nugent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Walk out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 04:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd imagine four kings would be a bitch, as would manus. I can't imagine any other bosses being difficult using this tactic. I've been doing an intelligence build, only leveling attunement as my other skill. Just because I hit 40 int, i only now started adding to vitality and endurance. I've had a ridiculously easy time with every boss so far. I can't see how a couple less attunement slots and a little bit less vitality and endurance would make the game that much harder. Plus you could always use Darkmoon Seance ring for extra attunement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 03:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was and had </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 02:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Intelligence for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's worse than being tortured, raped and killed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 04:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watching your only child suffer horribly and die slowly from terminal brain cancer and then being tortured, raped and killed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Skyrim and fallout do not belong here at all. Love the games, but the stories weren't that great. Gameplay and fun quests is what makes them fun, not storytelling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brady is definitely the best qb of all time but let's not get ridiculous here. They were getting beat and Brady led the best comeback ever. I don't think for a second he was playing around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 15:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't vote for Trump, but it's not like he was running against a respectable candidate. Obviously still stupid to vote for him, but damn what an awful choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 12:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay. Yeah I can definitely see how that can be annoying. It seems like the person is not being genuine and also on big decisions its likely that you've already went through the logical points of your choices. I confess though I am highly guilty of this. I am absolutely awful at being emotionally supportive so pretty much all of my advice is like this. I have a very hard time empathizing with people and letting my emotions loose. The best thing you can probably do is just tell that friend that you've already gone through the facts and logical arguments behind your decision, but you wanna hear their feelings on it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 22:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So if I'm understanding correctly, you don't want to be given "logical" advice, you want the person to tell you how they intuitively feel about your decision? If you ask a friend about which school you want to go to, you don't want them just to tell you logical reasons to choose one school over the other, but you want them to give kind of a gut instinct type of response, given that they know you pretty well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 03:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. I have a bad habit of debating online and wasting time better spent doing something else so I think so I really wanna spend time arguing or should I just delete my comment and move on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 03:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well said </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 02:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah all the time. There's a lot of nuance to similar words, so it's nice to know which word would be better in a situation . I also find that there's a lot of words that I know he meaning of, but I can't really define them well. Looking up the definition gives me a deeper understanding and appreciation for the word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 02:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you give an example? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 01:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd imagine this is common. When do you ever need to stop on a ladder? Most times you wanna get the hell down that ladder and book it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 01:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh please sneaking is easy to level quickly. In 208 days you could even level restoration, block and speech. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably English. That way I don't have to learn another one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 19:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that , could make sense in terms of his insecurity. The execution of that scene was just so bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 14:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really wouldn't have looked that dumb if he was moving around  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 04:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is dead may never die </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 04:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Around extremely extroverted people I feel very uncomfortable and my introverted nature really shows. Around just average people I'm fine. Around other very introverted people I can have meaningful conversations if we share a common interest. If there's nothing not to go on, I'd rather talk to an extrovert who will keep conversations going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 04:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What absolutely kills me is that Anakin doesn't even try to think of a way out of it. Obi wan says he has the high ground and all of the sudden it's checkmate. Anakin could try and force throw something at him to give him a window of time to jump onto even ground. He could maybe make the platform he's on move. Maybe he could look for an alternate way out of the situation )maybe other platforms or something. Or you know, just fucking wait and try to psyche out Obi Wan. Not jump right away when he's expecting it. God I fucking hate he prequels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 22:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Centrist...kek </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 15:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spoken like a true wagecuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 02:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or you can stick up for yourself  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 02:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is kinda gross to me. Seems so fake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 02:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "That might have he opposite effect of being really fucking entertaining." he commented as he ate a bowl of ice cream. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 02:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A bank would be an awful place to keep a pony </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 20:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kek  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 19:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not my job  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those too. I just hate having to watch a half hour worth of cutscenes to introduce a game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 15:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Close minded hands down. There's nothing more frustrating not me than a person who just dismissing any views or beliefs they don't like, without any real reason besides they're different. In my experience boils down to the person being too afraid to think their world view is wrong and/or extreme arrogance combined with ignorance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 15:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the corral is close, I'll put it there. Sometimes it's a walk across the parking lot to put it away. In that case, I'm not doing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 15:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At first it was an impossible task. Now I can do it with my eyes closed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 14:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> During the gwynodlin fight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 04:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvote this to the top </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 04:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He died doing what he was best at, shitting all over everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 04:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't this kinda patronizing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 04:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theoretically then, would but be possible for a person to propel themselves in space by farting? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 04:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not just make our flag the constitution? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 01:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It probably would have done the same to me but I'm really stubborn and spiteful when it comes to video games so instead I stay up all hours of the night determined to win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 01:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've beaten the bed of chaos but I'm just wondering if doing it that way instead of trying to do it all in one go and getting killed is so you don't lose humanity and souls.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 22:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh okay I've never done an SL1 run. I still have different builds I wanna try before I do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 17:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another easy way to save solaire is just to ignore his quest line until you get the sunlight maggot. Then you can talk to him at undead burg, anor Londo etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 16:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the purpose of quitting? So you don't lose souls and humanity? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 16:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it so odd how different players struggle with different bosses but have an easy time with others. I never had a problem with Gwyn, and I've done a few different builds. However, I get absolutely rekt by four kings time and time again, yet I see comments all the time saying how four kings are the easiest boss. I don't even parry against Gwyn, I just dodge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 02:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eating their own. I love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 20:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cultures can never be wrong. In some cultures, women are treated like dirt and do not have the rights that men have. Who am I to judge? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 20:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is waifu  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet 4chan loves Trump. Explain that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's kind of ironic to be okay with giving objects gender, but not people, seeing as how objects do not have genders but people do. What an odd time we live in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 04:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After having a phone with shit battery life for so long, I can say that battery life is probably the most important feature in a phone for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 17:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're friendly I'm sure they don't hate you. Yes it's a pain but I hate the customer who is never satisfied more than the customer who wants something difficult to slice. Had a lady ask for roast beef cut super thin, almost shaved and then when I gave it to her she complained it was falling a part and started huffing and puffing. I wanted to throw it at her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 16:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suggested it but they said to just use the slicer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 16:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Key word, BOTH. I have no issue with pro criticizing the lies of the Trump administration. In fact, I highly encourage it. I was no supporter of trump. What drives me absolutely nuts is the people who will not acknowledge the lies of the Obama administration and/or cannot acknowledge the lies spread by those on the left of the spectrum. People are acting like this is the first time our government has ever lied to us. Same goes with the media. Everyone loves to bash conservative outlets for being heavily biased and filled with misinformation, but they don't wanna acknowledge the fact that Slate, Vox, HuffPo, Buzzfeed and even CNN and MSNBC, etc. are heavily biased and some I would even say not reputable at all. It really does go both way. I would love for those on either side of the spectrum have a shred of honesty when talking about these things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 16:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd get fired too, but if you're sneaky nobody will know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 15:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really think so unless the person selling it to you literally owns the deli. Even then I'd probably say no. .1 is a fair amount over though. My rule of thumb is to keep it within .05.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 15:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say more people ask for it by the pound. I do get a fair amount who ask for a certain number of slices though. I agree with you it makes more sense in slices as someone buying it. It's also nice as the person slicing because then you don't need to worry about weight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 15:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've actually never tried it. It smears all over the slicer though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 15:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stringy fat and sipping wet blood soaked meat everywhere. Such a pain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 14:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I speak for the deli I work for, and by the looks of the comments most deli workers agree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 14:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually they want it in thick slices. I'm guess it's more convenient for them that way idk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 13:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man I hate that too. 1/2 pound shaved? No problem. 1 pound? Okay. More than that, you just condemned me to 15 minutes of agony. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 03:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Work in a deli. Honestly no, we don't give a shit. You could get a slice of ham and it doesn't bother us. Having us slice you up some liverwurst right before close is likely to piss us off though.  Shit takes forever to clean off the slicer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 02:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh okay. I know I looked it up when I fought them but I was unsure which resin it was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 02:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think of Smashing Pumpkins. Despite all my rage, I am still just Nicholas Cage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 02:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ice cream is so much better cold </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoops yeah I meant charcoal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two hand your weapon. Run as close to them as possible and swing away, killing each one before the next spawns. Gold pine resin will help a lot. Just run away as fast as you can when you see one spinning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chael didn't even try to pull his arm off. I'm not saying there was no physical exertion or that Chael wasn't being choked at all, but clearly he wasn't trying to get Tito off of him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 02:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty convinced that it was rigged. My first thought wasn't that they were signaling to each other when I watched. I just noticed it looked fake. Looking at the Clip though it definitely seems like there was at least one time where it looked like Tito deliberately taped he side of Chael. I don't really care to try and pursue that point though. I just saw Chael Sonnen get a guillotine on Tito and barely even squeeze. Then he easily gave up his back and tapped to his chin being squeezed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You honestly thought that was not at all staged? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate these kinds of people because I have a hard enough time just summoning people who will actually help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Danger lol. You could see them tapping eachother to give some sort of signal. Chael tapped out with Tito's arm around his chin. This whole thing was rigged   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 17:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tito has always been a better wrestler than Chael. Definitely not rigged /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 17:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think what bothers me more than the cringeworthiness is that it's not believable. Why would the teachers go along with all of this before knowing for sure that he could afford to pay their tuition? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 17:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the internet, yes it does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 05:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah, whoops. Forgot /s for serious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 00:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes and the quality of SNL is much greater than it's ever been in all of SNL history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
