<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3247</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 06:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I don't have a degree in economics, but I found this to reasonably explain how the Fed's TARP reduces real wage and employment growth: http://seekingalpha.com/amp/article/985461-how-quantitative-easing-causes-unemployment-and-reduces-growth

 nbsp;

I don't have a degree in economics, but I found [this to reasonably explain how the Fed's TARP reduces real wage and employment growth](http://seekingalpha.com/amp/article/985461-how-quantitative-easing-causes-unemployment-and-reduces-growth)

Try this next time. Your formatting was wrong. See my source for how to fix it.

Have a good day/night! 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 06:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  (USDA labeling requirments)[https://www.google.com/url?sa=t source=web rct=j url=https://www.fsis.usda.gov/OPPDE/larc/Policies/Labeling_Policy_Book_082005.pdf ved=0ahUKEwiekJz6tbTSAhUs5IMKHfP5DNYQFggaMAA usg=AFQjCNH2Tof9_ysErjwhxzTiaFqXJZlHDw sig2=4dIDvC_GoDnVgLB7Z93-kw]

 nbsp;

[USDA labeling requirments](https://www.google.com/url?sa=t source=web rct=j url=https://www.fsis.usda.gov/OPPDE/larc/Policies/Labeling_Policy_Book_082005.pdf ved=0ahUKEwiekJz6tbTSAhUs5IMKHfP5DNYQFggaMAA usg=AFQjCNH2Tof9_ysErjwhxzTiaFqXJZlHDw sig2=4dIDvC_GoDnVgLB7Z93-kw)

Your formatting was wrong. See my source for how to fix it. 

Thanks for the link, and have a good day/night.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 02:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really need more people to write some bad penis facts. 

Sometimes it's as hard and draining as my ex boyfriend, which reminds me! 

Did you know that guys call peeing draining the lizard? Why do guys talk about their penis like it's cold blooded? I've never encourtered a cold penis. But a few guys have said it needs warming up. 

I firmly believe men think their penis is constantly cold and needs a warm place to put it. 

We all know this is a bad penis fact that men spread, and sometimes it works.  

This r/BadPenisFacts is mostly true according to our sources.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I do my best!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you know that a man learns from an early age that his penis is magical? 

He truly believes that if he tugs   rubs on it often and long enough his wishes and dreams will come true. That it will be so big and hard it will make all women walk with wobbly knees after they have sex with it. 

I've only known one man, who, while we were in University had a few of my female friends make a mould of his penis. His wishes have come true. 

This fact brought to you by r/badpenisfacts ! 

Some of it is true, some not!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
The tapestry goes deep, just follow the threads. And little paw prints from rabbits,cats and chitinous cruciforms. And bread crumbs......... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 02:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, there are *bread crumbs* in the photo caption on imgur. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> STAPH! 

Ass 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, it sure seems that way at times! 

Civility is lost, along with basic empathy and kindness. 

This is why I'm a mod. I want to bring some of that back, and hopefully I will, to an extent. But remember, rules are rules, and I tend to live by them and the spirit. 

The world is not a kind place, but that doesn't mean I have to be as unkind as others. 

Nice to meet you :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 14:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't care, he can tag me. I'm always willing to read and learn. I might not respond, but I'll most certainly read the thread. 

FYI - I'm more independent than left. 

The world has problems, yes, but be someone willing to learn and make a difference in a constructive way. Don't tear people down, lift them up. 

Cheers - I need coffee.... bleh. 

Gabbi  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 14:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think its for all versions? But PC has it better. *PCs are the best*. 

I still don't understand why Xbox has dashboard stuff, but can't buy it yet. :( Maybe next update? 

I'm also hopeful we will get 4k support with the release of Scorpio. 4k on my 55 inch TV will be nice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 03:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are other ships besides the ASP? /s 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 02:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's see where he takes us this time..... 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 21:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [You're welcome!](http://33.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_m4jtbw9L161rnc2zr.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elite Dangerous - Hutton Orbital (XBox One) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SCP-1 is not part of this. 

You all know who ***we*** are and how ***we*** [operate.](http://i.imgur.com/eFXHIeS.jpg)


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that three Soviet Warships sailed into San Diego Harbor and docked along side U.S. Navy vessels on August 1st, 1990. marking the first such military visit to the West Coast in more than a century. The last time this happened was in 1863. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 16:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rum Ham?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 01:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's okay by me. :)

Mods might feel otherwise....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 00:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Naughty :) But that's ok!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two leather cords, that go around the neck, forming a loop to hold up the corset, which is not part of her skirt. 

The leg part is for mobility. If you've ever seen a woman run in a dress or long skirt we pull the sides up, or at least one side, so we don't trip over it. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 02:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Men are not alone in experiencing the discomfort of unrelieved vasocongestion. Women's genitals also become engorged with blood during sexual arousal and, like their male counterparts, women can experience pelvic heaviness and aching if they do not reach orgasm."

Women can suffer from it also, but I've never heard of a woman pressuring a man to help her with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 01:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although it is rare, [Blue Balls](http://health.howstuffworks.com/sexual-health/male-reproductive-system/blue-balls-dictionary.htm) has a "grain of truth in the myth". 

Men have used the Blue Balls excuse to make women feel pressure/guilt into having sex.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 21:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you know that men lose blood pressure each time they have an erection! They become light headed and have the following issues:

 nbsp;

1) They can't stand up in class when they are called by their teachers. This usually happens between the ages of 12-20!

 nbsp;

2) After sex all the blood rushes back into their bodies from their penis. This causes a huge pressure difference and they end up falling asleep!

 nbsp;

3) If they don't masturbate, the blood pressure in the rest of their bodies causes problems. They end up a little "off" and complain of "Blue Balls". This is because the blood is not going to their hardon and instead is pooling in the balls, causing them to turn blue in colour. 

 nbsp;


This fact brought to you by r/BadPenisFacts! 

 nbsp;

Feel free to contribute! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 02:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it's always running out, and the modules are hard to find. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 21:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I paid $160ish? 

The controller was allowed for several other flight games. I think it now goes for $89 (flight stick only) to $130 (Full bundle) on Amazon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have that flight stick also. It's a simple USB flight stick and there is no reason we should *not* be able to use it with Ace Combat 7. It was used for 6 and other games. No excuses. 

Plus .. yeah... Elite Dangerous! 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [twitch](http://www.reactiongifs.com/r/hdch.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 01:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Fraternal Twins are even more weird.](http://vignette3.wikia.nocookie.net/itsalwayssunny/images/b/b5/Dennis_and_Dee.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20120212034105) One looks like a bird!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Massive Attack - The Spoils ft. Hope Sandoval [Trip-Hop] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 23:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I'll definitely hold out for V2 now! 

(That monitor though... so nice!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 11:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you like the Surface Studio? I've been debating buying one soon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 16:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ultimate Kingpin did this to Ultimate Spider-Man.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 06:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that makes sense. I've seen some places do that lately if they had a family restroom. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 06:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [ You might enjoy this video - Obama   Bourdain in Hanoi Vietnam. Yes, they had beers!](https://youtu.be/2kztetjZKpM) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 04:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too expensive to do that large of a overhaul. Just be sensible and leave things as they are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 03:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because some people who were born with a "pee pee" now have a "slit".  And some people born with a "slit" now have a "pee pee". And! Some people have both! Some are men with no bottom surgery, and some are women with no bottom surgery! 

Just let them go pee and wash their hands. Seems the sensible thing to do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 06:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Uninvited](https://youtu.be/uvgi7P97lu0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 21:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can get out of that place! What methods do they (Docs) recommend when you plateau like this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 20:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> May I please have a link also? 

Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 16:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [They pay rent!](https://i.imgur.com/TnOaNdQh.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Virginia Broadband Deployment Act would kill municipal broadband deployment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 21:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Found in the wild! I knew it was true!] "I dunno man, every time I have sex with a different girl my dick gets a little smaller" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 20:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 20:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/BadPenisFacts  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> THC - The Podcast. Not what you think, but then again maybe it is? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 03:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 21:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I bet they are worth every penny to the talented pilots who fly them, and more to the passengers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 20:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much do planes like this cost? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 01:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Uhhhhhh](https://i.imgur.com/1ejrHCG.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Misogynatomy]"Nobody would care, lesbian sex is completely meaningless. Is it even sex?? It's like high school kids having a make out session and fingering each other. They can't hit a home run, 3rd base is as far as it can go." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 19:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 20:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd wait for the cooling off period (mute) and then ask a Senior Mod. 

I just joined and have no knowledge and no authority to speak on the issue. 

Have a good weekend, get off Reddit for a bit and relax.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 19:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, 

I honestly don't know, as I just joined their mod team and I don't know who reported you. I'd suggest asking one of the Senior Mods to lift the ban after a certain amount of time has passed. 

Best of luck. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chile's Navy Releases Groundbreaking UFO Video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 05:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 02:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm all for things like limitless power and food for all. It will be interesting in how we arrive there. Kinda sad that I won't live to see it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 01:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm! Currently living in Ga and it has been various degrees of muggy lately. But we are "supposed" to be receiving 2-4 inches of snow on Saturday, the 7th. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 01:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really great on the Sci-Fi Dystopia angle. Chris Pratt has some great lines about why he left earth. I watched it last night and the line I quoted started running through my head. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 00:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me either. 

Have you seen *Passengers* yet?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 00:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.... 

Are you Amish?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With advances in AI and Robotics in the past decade I keep thinking of this line from Insurrection. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 23:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Our technological abilities are not apparent because we have chosen not to employ them in our daily lives. We believe when you create a machine to do the work of a man, you take something away from the man." - SOJEF - Star Trek: Insurrection </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 15:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I really liked this one](https://www.reddit.com/r/FedExcellent/comments/47t0jc/i_deal_with_these_guys_daily/d0ff9kz/). 

Because it shows a lot of kindness on the redditors part.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 05:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/9M9H9E9/ /u/subject3247 

https://www.reddit.com/r/9M9H9E9/comments/5jy495/r9m9h9e9_best_of_2016_nomination_thread/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 04:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our [Artwork Wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/9M9H9E9/wiki/art) is incredible and I love that we had so many people participate! 

Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 04:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "Mother Horse Eyes - Reddit's Strangest New Phenomenon" An Introduction to The Interface Series [Video](https://youtu.be/_7e5pBfGi4I) by u/pickel5857 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 23:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u/_9mother9horse9eyes9 .....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Understanding the Carbon Bubble </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 23:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 19:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The High Striker - </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 18:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
The penis does indeed *strive* to hit the Cervix

It empowers the penis with magical hardness and that each time a woman squeals from having the cervix hit the penis becomes like a "fucking diamond"  and typically the man wants the world to know about his accomplishment. 

As we have been informed - "Eventually the penis loses all self-control. It grows harder each time and begins to stay hard, never becoming flacid. He said men secretly call this sexual move ["The High Striker"](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/High_striker). Successful  "Strikers" have to tuck their perma-hard-on in between their belts. They can one day fuck their own belly buttons." (I have no idea how fucking a belly button works, but he said "A hole is a hole, and twenty dollars is twenty dollars.)

This fact brought to you by r/BadPenisFacts

 nbsp; 

______________________________________________________________________________________

 nbsp;

Kinda dispels the "Grow Vs Show" thing. Our researchers will have to investigate this issue soon. If you have information feel free to share it in the Sub.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 04:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Each time a penis hits the Cervix it losses at least 3mm in length. So, eventually they can't hit it anymore but don't understand *why*. 

This fact brought to you by r/BadPenisFacts! Feel free to steal it, because we need contributions! 

E- I was corrected. Please see my comment below. 

Sigh... 

A male friend actually sent me a text and corrected me... 

The penis does indeed *strive* to hit the Cervix. He said it empowers the penis with magical hardness and that each time a woman squeals it makes it become like a "fucking diamond" that he wants the world to know about. He said - "Eventually the penis loses all self-control. It grows harder each time and begins to stay hard, never becoming flacid. He said men secretly call this sexual move ["The High Striker"](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/High_striker). Successful  "Strikers" have to tuck their perma-hard-on in between their belts. They can one day fuck their own belly buttons." (I have no idea how fucking a belly button works, but he said "A hole is a hole, and twenty dollars is twenty dollars.)

This fact brought to you by r/BadPenisFacts .... sorry we got the other one wrong y'all. 

Kinda dispels the "Grow Vs Show" thing. Our researchers will have to investigate this issue soon. If you have information feel free to share it in the Sub.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 07:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My family doesn't want me around because I transitioned.  I don't impose on my few friends, so I stay home and play video games and watch movies.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 16:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tip a percentage, same as if I was at Fabiano's on the square.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 16:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right! I was going there for just that reason....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 14:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ditto..... 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 06:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have photos of that on my phone. They were filming [Logan Lucky](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt5439796/) in Hudsons.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 01:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the sticky,  then The Interface Series. 

Be careful to not lose yourself. 

Eye is watching you now... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stranger Things filming in Douglasville Ga </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 01:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stranger Things filming in my home town! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 01:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 00:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks to the lovely u/josikins

She might enjoy The Rabbit Hole.... 

Be Careful of the Flesh though.... it likes to tickle, and consume ... 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 23:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a ...collective of sorts ... 


Explore young one ... enjoy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 23:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks to the lovely u/josikins

She might enjoy The Rabbit Hole.... 

Be Careful of the Flesh though.... it likes to tickle, and consume ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSYCHONAUTWIKI.ORG </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 23:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 23:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks to the lovely  u/josikins who would undoubtedly fit in here...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSYCHONAUTWIKI.ORG </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 23:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 18:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why, yes, yes they are sexy....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 18:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey! Congrats on transition! We wish you all the best and thanks for being a role model! 3 

Happy Holidays/Merry Christmas! 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> *GRaPhIC* ViCiouS PitBuLL AtTacks HeLpLeSS BaBy! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 19:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 21:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The G-spot exists. It's just that each time a penis hits it a few things happen.

1) An Angel gets her wings.

2) The Penis loses some sensitivity due to hitting it.

3) The Penis itself learns to avoid hitting it and slowly shares this information with other peni via telepathy in men's restroom. This is why men don't like to make small talk in the bathroom. The words are lies!

This information brought to you by r/BadPenisFacts 

The only true part is the G-spot is real, and an Angel does get her wings.


 nbsp;
_____________

 nbsp;

Edit - Thanks for the Gold kind stranger! Feel free to join us on r/BadPenisFacts and contribute (you can even steal this post!)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 21:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chad had a 12' cock once upon a time. The more he used it the smaller it became, until eventually he was no longer a Chad. 

This fact brought to you by r/BadPenisFacts  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 07:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely more of a r/BadPenisFacts....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 22:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been a long time since I saw one of these beauties! Almost bought one on eBay years and years ago. That S H fee though....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 06:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're totally going to steal that idea we've been talking about, aren'tcha? 

Swear..... you owe me a Spinach Florentine dinner at Scalini's now u/_9MOTHER9HORSE9EYES9. In the private booth. 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 05:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out r/BadPenisFacts ...those are funny too.....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 05:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, this definitely belongs in r/BadPenisFacts! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 21:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! 

Did I tell you the one about hairy palms?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 07:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turn about is fair play

I imagine there will be lots of butthurt once the sub is known...if it is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 06:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh .. total overlap! Go for it! 

I should put that in the sidebar! I'm working on the CSS now and watching Scrubs :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 01:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 01:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear Penis's are like candycanes! The more you lick and suck them the smaller they eventually become.
 It's a fact.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 23:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ...and r/BadPenisFacts is born.... have fun!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a Bad Penis Fact </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 22:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here are a few examples of "Bad Penis Facts"

 nbsp;


____________________________________________

 nbsp;



["Sexual promiscuity weakens the muscles of the penis, and this leads to erectile dysfunction. Males would do well to save themselves for nice gals instead of getting hard for every cheerleader who looks in their direction.
....
See? I can make up random bullshit, too."](https://www.reddit.com/r/badwomensanatomy/comments/5howku/til_on_fb_that_the_more_sex_a_woman_has_the_more/db1w2di/) by the lovely u/cactless_tunt!


 nbsp;

["The penis and the vagina are like a pencil and a sharpener, if it gets stuck into every sharpener out there there will be nothing left.
..Wow, that was easy.'](https://www.reddit.com/r/badwomensanatomy/comments/5howku/til_on_fb_that_the_more_sex_a_woman_has_the_more/db1y4n4/) by the lovely u/Feinyan!

 nbsp;

["Every time a dude has sex, the top most layer of skin cells rubs off the penis and wedges in the vagina. As time goes on, the vagina becomes tighter and tighter, while the penis works it's way down to a stub.
True fact!'](https://www.reddit.com/r/badwomensanatomy/comments/5howku/til_on_fb_that_the_more_sex_a_woman_has_the_more/db2e2ck/) by the lovely u/Kovitlac! (this is actually a fact!) 

_____________________________________________________

 nbsp;

So, now that you have the right idea, go ahead and make up some Bad Penis Facts! This includes things about guys with one ball too!

 nbsp;

___________________________________________

 nbsp;


Remember ... **EVERYTHING HERE IS IN JEST! We really just want to amuse ourselves and promote good sexual health and knowledge! Our anatomies are *nothing* to be ashamed of, and I for one encourage real discussions between everyone!**  


This sub is less than an *hour* old at this point... give us time to grow, kinda like some peni...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Welcome to Bad Penis Facts! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 22:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sub was created after reading a [thread on](https://www.reddit.com/r/badwomensanatomy/comments/5howku/til_on_fb_that_the_more_sex_a_woman_has_the_more/db1xopu/) r/badwomensanatomy and it's so we can amuse ourselves! 

If the sub takes off I'll start working on the CSS and I am more than willing to read any ideas! 

Have fun! 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 22:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...and r/BadPenisFacts is born.... have fun! 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 18:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't give them ideas! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 19:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Better Link](https://youtu.be/GGgiGtJk7MA) because I'm an expert linker.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 17:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah... termites are the worst! 

The windows are all intact, with screens on some. The foundation looks great from the outside. No holes in the roof in the photo. 

I'd really love to see the inside. I bet it has a lot of beautiful hardwoods!

I wonder how much a house like this would cost to build in today's economy?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 15:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great! I showed your photo to my stylist/friend at the 1 year no-cut mark and told her "Hair Goals!" she only gave me the smallest of trims!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 15:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the exception of the porch it seems very "healthy" in the photo. Would love to see the inside. 

I knew a couple who restored a house similar to this, but sadly it burnt down in the 90s. Just a open field now. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 15:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you cut your hair? 

Also, great makeup, especially the eyeliner! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 22:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're the editor? 

Oh, that's right.... I'm MHE and Karen.... I forgot. 

Goes to pet Angelica .......  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 03:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How you doin'?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 04:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's still not a bad looking guy. Downright handsome! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 04:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIP in Pieces.....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 02:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you sooo much! 

Just know he is working really hard at it and I believe it will surpass what was initially written here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 20:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *swoons again*

I swear I love old fashion so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 20:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has pockets! 

*swoon*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 4TH DIMENSION - TESSERACT, 4TH DIMENSION MADE EASY - CARL SAGAN - For The Children </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 12:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There has never been a greater chance of a President revealing that there are UFOs and Aliens. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 10:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 05:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, next year. It's currently filming here in Atlanta and we see them around town a lot. Check out r/Atlanta and you can see a recent photo. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 04:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, throw some stuff in the private chat and see what folks like.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 03:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you all decide on the Wiki Names so I can get to work on that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 01:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Me to u/_9mother9horse9eyes9 at times](https://youtu.be/NukF3NXJqrU?t=11s) 

I really need to make this a gif.... 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WE THE PEOPLE.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 00:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> YOU DONT GET ME HIGH ANYMORE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 00:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Honestly - MHE is working on the rewrite. And it's Incredible! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 23:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to let everyone know - Things are going good. The rewrite is "slogging" along as my friend ( u/_9mother9horse9eyes9 ) told me. There have been a few hiccups for both of us. We might spend too much time talking about pizza toppings and opening up a Cobbler's Shop in a little Maine Square, but he is working very hard. 

I promise this - If you are a fan of the Series, the rewrite is going to be incredible. At least from what I have read so far. 

If you have general questions I am beginning to cycle through a lot of vacation days starting tomorrow and only on Emergency Call. 

But tonight it's pizza with my girlfriends.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 23:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Urgh....I've seen that before, along with accelerating with foot on brake (brake lights).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A friend from Paulding County shared this today. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 23:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 20:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Hah](http://33.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_m4jtbw9L161rnc2zr.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 20:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Children, we all know what Mother does with her Flesh! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DOOM 3 BFG VR Gameplay on HTC Vive with roomscale and motion controller ... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 06:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
