<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3859</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-29 07:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Don't think you've lost anything yet. I see the eye gettin a bit muddy though, I would avoid overworking any areas with the colorful design you have going on, and it might be cool to see that incorporated more to the form of what your drawing. Not just in a flat way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-27 17:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-27 17:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Punjab, India </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My meditation spot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-27 06:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-25 07:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wowzers in my trowzers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-25 00:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah like I said man, your the artist you don't have to listen to anyone, or even give two shits about what anyone thinks. Some will like it, some will hate it. Your not here to please others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-25 00:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think its something you should go back an work on, its more of something you learn from and can use in future work. And sitting at something for long periods of time can sometimes drag your work down. Take breaks and come back to it with a fresh perspective and you will see what parts need work and what is already working for the piece. Good luck  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-24 21:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel its almost two different pieces of art, the girl and the drips. Even the drips on the shirt take away from the form of the figure. Of course its your own art you don't have to listen to what anyone says but I think it could have been more successful if the drips were more carefully placed. Maybe change of sizes too, if they all are huge then it doesn't really have an impact  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 23:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't even under contract . It was about 69.99 the first 6 months and then I knew it would go up, it was 79.99 and then they started charging me 83.99 sometimes a bit more for no reason, it was bull </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 07:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You deserve more upvotes, this thread is blowing my mind and I'm learning at the same time. Thank you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 22:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FF7 ahh what a special game  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 10:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine too, fuck what others say </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 03:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the wisdom  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> hey guys, anyone know a good internet provider? I'm fuckin sick of Comcast </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 01:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comcast has been ripping me off for too long, increasing the bill by like 3$ a month, I'm not sure about Verizon either. Are there any other options? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 01:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if its been said yet but "it is what it is".
What the fuck else is it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 17:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The concert was such a blur. I didn't realize how amazing it was until I watched the videos over an over. This song gave me the chills. I'm gonna upload the rest of the songs when I get time. I'm glad you were able to see it live too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> hey guys I was at the first show of the tour, this was my favorite recording: leave out all the rest/shadow of the day/iridescent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-13 17:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Making my childhood happy as an adult </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-13 02:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-12 10:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was mindblowing,I'm uploading some videos at the moment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-09 20:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very true and such an easy fix-_-  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-04 18:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you and of course, I've been practicing non stop since I got it(about 3 days ago). What do you see that can be improved?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-04 04:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing, really responsive an everything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-04 04:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Captured my baby with my new Canon T4I </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-04 00:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-03 23:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used nightmode for this, I don't know much about cameras yet either but practice a lot an mess with the settings, esp shutter speed and aperture </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-03 23:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha thanks , can't get enough of it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Capturing my baby with my new Canon T4i  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-03 19:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-08 21:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the real orientation is the submission, its reflected because I took the pic with me in it with a webcam , explains the crappy quality too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-08 02:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh and DA   its been years since i updated it but it should have a lot of work up still,   its the same username as my reddit account </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-08 02:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't used my DA account in years and haven't been really updating my blog and website, been too busy. Facebook is easiest to update from my phone so that has all my art on it but here you go anyway.

www.noodos.blogspot.com  there is a lot of work on here you can scroll to previous pages too

and my unofficial website 

www.ramandips.moonfruit.com

it loads a little slow but click paintings or drawings at the top

Im working on building a legit online portfolio with high res images at the moment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-07 08:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used my dad's face as a reference and my own hand 

thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-06 22:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahaha I come back every summer so I don't feel that bad. Just got home from india a few weeks ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-06 21:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-06 21:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah actually he was my influence for this, amazing painter that man, I have about 10 calenders and just used them to come up with ideas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-06 21:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah good sir, Im sitting in the U.S but thought I would do something for back home;] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-06 20:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, it feels great making something worth looking at. I spend months on pieces and they haven't been as successfull as this. Did this in one night actually,

here is scale  http://imgur.com/XWL7w </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Painted this the other night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-06 20:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey r/India, just wanted to show you something I finished the other night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-06 20:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IDAP of a Guru in Oils </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-06 20:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My first religious painting, Oils </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-06 20:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-29 07:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Acrylics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-28 20:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I thought it was funny, apparently so did 600+ others. People here just like to bitch a lot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-28 19:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make me happy long time  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-26 02:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :( I hope you feel better. Remember the good times an try to smile.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-25 22:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone told me it was a brown recluse an I freaked the fuck out, it looks just like it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MY GOD, Looks like I'm never stepping into my basement again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-25 20:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-25 02:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sounds like just an ignorant hater babbling  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-24 05:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When did the v6 ever beat the v8? I have a 2011 GT and have fried plenty of 2011 v6s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-21 15:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha they were so cheap, about 20 rupees each. That's a dollar, it was in India. Can't wait to use em  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I managed to pick up a couple souvenirs in the Himalayas  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-21 14:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-17 10:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats beautiful sir, I'm about to graduate college and am in the same boat. Torn between the money and what i love. great stuff, you need more upvotes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-12 09:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol why would you come live here? most people try an get out of here. hopefully its not for too long. The corruption is unbearable. I'm only visiting but damn my relatives here flip shit everyday telling me not to bring  home a white girl. good luck, and be strong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-11 07:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> great work, angle of the face is a little off though, sorry dont mean to be a nazi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-09 08:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :] thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-09 05:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/d1Bjl

here you go sir </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My attempt to capture emotion in acrylics  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-08 19:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I painted my aunt taking care of her disabled son </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-08 19:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IDAP of my aunt caring for her disabled son </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-08 19:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-05 17:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you, i couldn't even get through one listen of it. they said they were going back to the roots, this is pure crap. I hope they are just trolling with this song, Burn it down is much better, even though it seems like just a dumbed down version of burning in the skies. ATS had so much more soul than this. I hope there are real songs on the album im going to the first concert in the u.s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-05 13:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is the worst thing ive ever heard, all i hear is cheap generic electronic effects,  burn it down was nothing special either but it grew on me, but this, might have to stop listening to them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found some inspiration to paint in India </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-04 19:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-17 08:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fuckin great  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My first time using 3-d(mudbox), how'd I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-11 15:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-02 09:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I'm still working on last one, it was shot incomplete :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-02 00:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) thank you, he chose the song and It just went so well with the video, I  had never heard it before </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-01 18:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, yeah i figured but still nice to show atleast someone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finished them feet  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-01 00:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend asked me to star in his commercial promoting art, what do you guys think? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-30 17:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-28 21:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes, yes i did
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-23 20:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh yeah thanks i know its not finished, the toes definitely need work, and the foot needs some cool shadows but almost there! thanks for taking the time to view this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some feet I'm working on in oils  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-23 17:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-23 03:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost every night, i sometimes even start singing. Sometimes its in the background sometimes its coming out of somethin I'm holding. One time i left one of my favorite songs playing before I slept and in my dream, everyone was playing that song off their phones and car radios and stuff, I was gettin mad that everyone stole my song. I kept yelling at them to turn it off and they all laughed, I woke up like holy fuck  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it weird that when I'm asleep, when I leave my music playing on my phone, whatever song is playing, I hear it in my dreams and start talking about it with my "projections" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-23 03:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does this happen to anyone else and is there a term for it ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-22 10:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PhotoShop lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-22 09:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh lawdy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-21 17:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need a higher quality pic, that things so fuckin wet  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-20 08:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm actually using a mirror and yes that sounds like a great idea to bend the arm thank you, Definitly not finished....still have much to do  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-20 02:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) thank you, expect a finished version up when I get it done  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-20 02:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you I will def repost once finished  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-19 22:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's interesting, some people do feel that way, but my professor said it looks like two different paintings goin on so i need to remove the brick, thanks for feedback </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-19 22:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm not done with anyyhing just yet, I need to add more shadows an highlights on the face and also was considering glazing shadows over the wall, but I'm gonna scrape it off to quiet it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-19 22:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, scraping off the bricks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-19 22:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow thanks for the advice, cools coming soon  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-19 22:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks yeah your right, I'm gonna use a brush instead of pallete knife this time to suggest,.not lay down paint  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-19 22:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I know but thanks, needed another opinion, I'm gonna scrape it off since its still wet and tone it down  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Self portrait wip. Is the brick texture too loud/distracting? considering scraping it out. What do you think reddit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-19 17:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-13 21:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, check out my unofficial site, www.Ramandips.moonfruit.com

I'm working on a better one since the sites a bit slow and image quality isn't the best. 

My blog. Www.noodos.blogspot.com  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I made this a while ago for my 2000 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-13 18:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-13 01:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Customize your character?!!!!!!  Fap Fap.. Fap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-09 21:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Started* the painting today..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Painted some feet today  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-09 17:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IDAP of Rembrandt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-05 07:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-01 09:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jin kazama, cuz he's fuckin sick. Love his demon stance, you can do so much with it, and yeah the juggles Hell yeahhhhh wall combos are pretty good too  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WTF nova, human trafficking....one of thems my neighbor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-30 02:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tastes just like it looks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-29 01:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-22 07:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jerked it while speeding, going 100 in a 50 and a cop started tryin to catch up, busted balls all over right as his blue lights caught up and i pulled over  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-22 07:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry about it man. Thanks for the info </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> painting of a man and his shadow, work in progress </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-21 22:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-21 00:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah actually.  My blog is www.noodos.blogspot.com, my unofficial website is www.Ramandips.moonfruit.com. it loads slow sometmes. Click.paintings at the top </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I walked into the kitchen at a [7] to find these babies waiting for me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-19 01:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Took this shot in d.c a few days ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-18 08:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-17 19:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry for the downvotes, we Americans don't realize that the rest of the world doesn't know about and doesnt give a flyin fuck about our tournaments </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-17 03:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vcu reppin! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-15 20:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks yeah its easily fixable but it was for fun/practice, I'm just gonna let this one dry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-15 20:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha thanks but I've seen some great stuff on here, and this is not one of my best, spent a few hours throwing on paint and moving it around with tissues :p. 

If you want to see my work 

Www.Ramandips.moonfruit.com 
Click paintings, sometimes the sites a bit slow  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-15 19:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's cool, I didn't use it as a reference or anything but it was my first favorite painting, maybe it came out subconciencly Haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-15 18:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah layers of oils :p  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-15 18:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oils  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-15 16:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks I understand, I had fun with the clouds an kinda just rushed the rest :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just finished this painting for a friend  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-15 14:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-10 17:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Op probably thinks they can link and write text at the same time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-07 17:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't say it did. I'm not worried about what point your trying to make in the slightest bit, tell someone who cares, not here for an argument.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-07 09:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's all good, I was just suggesting it, no ones gonna shove down your throat what you should be paying attention to. But you will hear the riots, haha. Good luck on midterms </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-07 08:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a commucation arts major:p  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-06 21:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should try an keep up. Vcu doing big things, making history.. why wouldn't you want to be a part of it, you DO  go here... Even if you don't care too much, you get to shit on your friends from mason, etc. Last nights game was nerve-wrecking, you would figure there's a reason all these people are excited and rushing the streets. Not just for fun, but it gives us a chance to unite and celebrate, vcu doesn't really have school spirit, but when moments like this happen  , it lifts everyones spirits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
