<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2469</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 09:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're welcome :) ... glad to be helpful :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 07:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you checked the blurring tools of youtube video creator. 
https://youtube-creators.googleblog.com/2016/02/blur-moving-objects-in-your-video-with.html
You could blur her face and it should settle everything...the thing is if you don't have her written and signed consents, you are still in a tight spot...alternatively, you could protect yourself if she wrote some sort of e-mails to you approving of posting the video, you could use the e-mail as evidence...this is a lesson to learn, when working with anyone, not just your girlfriends, always watch your back for any betrayal of the sort, like copyright claims or whatsoever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 07:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mmhh, they keep changing stuff around huh :/...where did you get that info? but in any case, I'm still positive that shorter videos will gain more attention for kick starting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 22:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're already at risk of copyright claims once you upload stuff that you didn't produce 100% ... the owner may ignore you if you don't monetise or make any profit of any sort though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Princess Allura, MikomiKisomi, Digital, 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 20:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 20:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I thought too :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 14:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Advertising is a risk to take indeed...but be careful to really select your ad well...by experience, I think an ad video should be no more than 2 min, or a 1 min trailer would be better...think about it, since your video will mention most things you are going to do it would be really advantageous for you if it goes viral...that includes, high watch time, number or views and outstanding keywords...but I guess 5 min is not that bad either...you should never compare yourself to someone else because of what I said, "fan base" is important and if you are still building it up, there is not way a video of more than 2 hour can do this...good luck :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 13:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The shorter the video, the better it is because it's the percentage of time viewed that matters the most. Always try to keep it as short as possible, at least until you made a fan base who would always watch until the very end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A lovely carrot cake tutorial, it looks tasty [56 views] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 08:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 18:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it can't hurt you then ^^ so I guess you could hope in the train for a while and then see for yourself if it suits you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 17:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you should only do it if you earn something out of it...what if all his views are fake? I'm sure some people are smart enough to avoid youtube's bot view detector...you shouldn't only look at the number of views, check the video engagement as well...if people are commenting then that means people are really watching. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 09:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not giving a review but I just want to point out that your channel trailer is too long...Try to keep it under 1 min :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 07:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you can upload as many times as you want...if you worry about your subscribers then post everyday or for ex 3 every week...In my opinion, even if you come back with a bunch of other videos, it won't change the fact that you missed these few weeks and now you need to catch up this by becoming consistent again, which will take some time before effect again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 18:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to add to that  don't use anything that lets you buy views EXCEPTED google Adwords :) ... the reasons should be obvious  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ThatReallyAkwardGirl had fun redrawing her cute character :) [61 views] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 07:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> French Pull-Apart Bread...yummy ^^ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 07:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pocahontas by Sam/PimpManFan [105 views] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 21:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Annoyed Blonde girl, watercolour, 500MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 21:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 00:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well, that was hypothetically in order to generate organic view, since you were asking where to share. I don't see any places other than what I've already mentioned, you could choose which ones work the best for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 14:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> google + , twitter, facebook (share with your families and friends), forums (search for forums that are related to your topic and interact with the community) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 11:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow...thanks for the infos, really useful...I'll see what I can do when I get back to digital... since I'll be doing traditional work for a while...but practicing real photo is also a good idea...Thanks for pointing out that practice subreddit :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 07:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're position on the camera is weird, check out some of the tips that were posted here
https://www.reddit.com/r/youtubers/comments/4s1i2y/tips_tricks_3_tips_for_better_looking_youtube/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 07:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't thought about that ... it sure sounds useful, thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 22:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I often get people to subscribe and then ask me straightforward to also subscribe to them...but I never do...it's a ridiculous act...I'm sure they won't even watch a single of my videos...so if most of your subscribers are like that, you should definitely start off a better channel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 21:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how many views per video do you have that comes from your subscribers? ... You could consider making a new channel if your subscribers don't even watch your videos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 13:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it seems to me that you are rather in urgent need of a break. Try to get some days off from work and whatever activities, go out and enjoy the sun...You need to forget about everything because your brain is crying for a break. There is no need to continue worrying about your channel if you cannot keep up the momentum in a natural way and no need to force yourself. You'll just produce crap and get even more insane when you'll look at your statistics...Go take a break and wait for the groove to come back on it's own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Get inspired from nature (by D.M. Cumbo) [53 views] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 21:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feeling hope, watercolour, 500MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 21:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I redrew my previously failed drawing, I was more careful this time [65 views] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 10:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 10:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :/ but isn't that a bit like sub for sub? and therefore they'd be inactive followers, I hope these people follow you for your content though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 10:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google +  is more efficient though, perhaps because it also belongs to google, I get exposure and followers faster on Google + ...I guess it's really a matter a company competition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 09:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just post my videos and artwork regularly, but I haven't got any phenomenal result so far...twitter and Facebook don't like youtube videos and they get less post reach...but photos, text and native videos reach more people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 21:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make schedule to finish them a little by little, for example one week, one hours everyday and stick to that schedule even if you have something else to do. If you are lazy then just reward yourself with something small and special (ex: chocolate) every time you finish a schedule time. 
If you can't finish them in the time frame or schedule you want, it's better to just forget about them otherwise they will pill up in your HEAD and obstruct your creativity, deleting them is the best way :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 22:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you are getting low exposure precisely because your content compete with larger youtubers...try out targeting smaller niches as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 19:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been uploading videos for around one year and only recently have I started to receive more organic views form channels, suggested videos and search. It's not phenomenal but at least it's getting a little bit more every month. I don't usually put any commentaries on my videos so I think that might be causing my slow growth. It has to do with how relevant and searchable are your videos. Put relevant keywords on the title, make appealing thumbnails, plan out a good video description with many keywords that people may be looking for (without going out of the topic of your video) and add annotations...you shouldn't be lacking words so you have a better chance to use those to your advantage :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 18:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> here is my second attempt to draw a child, the first one was a total failure, but I think this one turned out better. https://youtu.be/FaR0ZJzXWaU
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drawing a child (redraw), watercolour, 500MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 13:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 22:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> first off, you need to figure out if you can really do those, it's not about having talent or not, but about DOING something... and not about doing WELL but just DOING...If you show your stuff to people, they will follow you if and only if they LIKE/LOVE what you do, no matter whether you are 0% talented or 1000% talented...taste is relative to each individuals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anime Review! (OwO) Black Lagoon [51 views] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 20:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 17:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yup XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 17:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if you are doing it anyways then you have no choice but to compete with people such as Casey...you'll have to put in the keywords anyways, maybe you could try slight variations so that you can reach smaller niches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There is a difference between giving up and walking away from something that drives one insane. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 13:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 12:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't really experiment with posting time but I heard that posting time doesn't really matter, it's better to be consistent and inform your subscribers about your schedule time. You could even write it on your channel art. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 09:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ask yourself why are you doing the vlog first, and then ask yourself why would people want to follow it. Do some marketing studies, for example search for meaningful and searchable keywords...you'll have to write in such a way that people can find you so that they can DECIDE whether they want to be part of your audience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 19:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yup...exactly :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 11:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4 is priority,
3 is second priority,
but if I get 1 and 2 that would just be awesome because I'll have more of 4 and 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 11:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aren't these special animation? maybe you could hire somebody to do that for you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 11:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes, I was like aaaahhhh...also, I did the red lineart with a watercolor pencil and I didn't know (it was some random thing I bought on a flea market), so the lines disappeared and I couldn't see anything anymore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I failed this drawing but I'll show it anyways :P [182 views] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 10:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peaceful Day (digital painting by KQ4rt) [451 views] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 23:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 21:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> beautiful and inspirational :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Failed at drawing a child, watercolour, 500MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 21:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 19:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should try things out by yourself to see if it is better or not... you could stop self-promotion, however you'll have to stay active in the communities because if later you find out it's not working then you can always come back to it without having to restart from zero because people have forgotten about you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am an active artist since 2014 and I want to share my trailer with you [745 views] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 16:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 16:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well at least you learn from your mistakes and it's OK to move on...I've been searching answers to these questions for a while now and trying out different things on twitter but still I haven't come up with anything phenomenal or at least it's really going slow on the organic side...the things I usually do and often got advices on: post regularly; be nice to other people, it's OK to tweet and discuss with other people but self promotion are despised, rather just interact with them and let them feel themselves like checking out your stuff;  do some research on key words and hash tags, if it's popularity you want most, you better just search out what's popular and make content about them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 08:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 21:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks really cool...ahhh...congratulations...hope to follow your footsteps soon (wish wish wish ^^  ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I scream for an Ice cream </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 21:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 13:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats, what's your channel about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 10:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Black hair and white Azalea, watercolour, 500MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 07:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Video] How to sketch! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 08:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 11:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe it's body learning, so even if it seems you forgot, your body keeps memory of the moves, you also need to get out of drawing procrastination but it will hit you hard when you get there ... I barely drew anything since I started high-shool that was when I was 13 (you know, kids drawing...lol) and I restarted in 2014, when I was 26 ... I also picked up really fast but that's only because I took it very seriously and practiced really hard...I guess I'm just releasing whatever I missed during my long break ... lol ... also trying to keep up the momentum because I don't want to go on anymore break XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 06:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you :) ... my best wishes for your return into art, don't worry it's never too late XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 19:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no, I just asked in the general context, not really referring to any particular series </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 19:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no, what happened? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you usually react to cliffhangers? especially when the series updates really slow? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 18:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Demon, Digital Painting, 500MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 18:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anastasja A. Art Makes awesome realistic Paintings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 12:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just out of curiosity, how long did it take you to get your first link karma? how many external links did you post? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 09:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 08:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In that case I think it's better not to use those...viewers can reverse autocorrection back but it requires additional click before finding your channel. Or worst, they could confuse your channel with the others and think they are subscribed while actually they are not even though they were initially searching for you.  Also there is not enough difference between Max Gamertag and MaxGamertag for me to consider these a 2 different names and I checked that there is already a channel that has Max Gamertag as name, why do you want to choose that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sakimichan's Phoenix Girl (In my way) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 21:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 21:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My final day of drawing challenge. 
https://youtu.be/kTj4MJEhwTs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Final day of challenge (day 7): Sakimichan's Phoenix Girl (in my way) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 20:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FedoraHouse is a raising watercolour artist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 22:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shoujo Girl, Digital, 200MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 21:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Asian girl, FedoraHouse, Watercolour, 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 22:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 11:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't be afraid of self-promoting your stuff over and over again, don't stop trying, who is gonna promote you if you don't do so first?...it is blunt self-promotion that people despise, make sure you be active and engage a lot in communities and social medias you're in, and in between, post your stuff...I've been doing so for one year in a small forum on the internet, and I don't feel anyone hates it when I post my video links and so because I engage a lot with them and give feedbacks to them as well, sometimes I get them to sub, but that's the maximum achievement with self-promotion. Same thing with google+ and other social media.
As for paid promotion, better use google Adwords, it's definitely not a scam since it belongs to google, and I had the experience that they always make sure you don't pay for fraudulent clicks...when I see my report, I've remarked a huge amount of fraudulent clicks that their system detected and I was reimbursed (though they just allowed me to reuse the money for buying more ads) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 19:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> opt for the $75 and leave some room for hope :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ginger girl, Watercolour, 200MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 19:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 07:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the only way is to keep contacting people and trying. One reason they may not respond might be that your subscriber count is too low compared to theirs. It unfair because they might have probably worked really hard to get were they are. Maybe you should try out asking more people with the same number of subs or if you are really wanting sub you should ask those who have lower subs than you, you're more likely to succeed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 19:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's the question everyone asks...but no one really has a magic formula that works for everyone...guess you should focus on call to action and on improving video quality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
