<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3318</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Flight attendants of Reddit, have you ever intervened in human trafficking on a flight and saved someone? What happened? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 00:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 02:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sailor here
Many people dont realize that the weight of the chain is what keeps a ship in place not the anchor.  The anchor is to get the chain to the ocean floor.  The links are 100  200 pounds each.   The ship I was on, the anchor weighed about 3000 pounds.
The drum that is spinning is held in place by a friction brake (picture old drum brakes on a car) As a wheel is turned by the operator the friction on the drum is increased or decreased.   From what I see here the operator let the momentum of the entire thing get away from him and the brake material became too hot started smoking and lost all effectiveness. In the very beginning, if you look very closely between the spinning wheel and the rope you can see a few seconds of man turning the wheel frantically.  That smoke you see is the friction pad burning up.  I would estimate the length of the brake pad being about half the circumference of the wheel and about 6 inches wide.  The very end of the chain was connected to the ship down inside the locker.  The eye protection is on because sailors have a habit of throwing crap down the whole with the chain, usually soda cans come flying out.
I have no doubts they dragged for the chain and recovered the entire thing. 

Edit - also at the end you can see the chain is painted yellow and then painted red to warn the operator the end is near.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 01:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does electricity affect how plants/algae grow? - just asking.  I don't know a damn thing about it, but I hate to see you go through all that work for nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 01:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't EVAR let go of those speakers.  When you get a bigger place stick em in the corners of the room. (bass)  Nice!    My best to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 02:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I am actually hurting the "good" grass, however it is at an acceptable level?  Does anyone know how the poison works?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5:ELI5: How does the "Weed and Feed" I spread on my lawn know the difference between weeds and "good" grass? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 01:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why doesn't the "Weed and Feed" I spread on my lawn kill the "good" grass? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 01:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How does the "Weed and Feed" I spread on my lawn know the difference between weeds and "good" grass? Why doesn't the"good grass" die too? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 01:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 23:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not even her husband wanted her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 14:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a drink of water, listen to 2 songs, use the restroom, make a phone call, expand your vocabulary to avoid swearing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 21:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Life is not fair, and it will never be.  Deal with it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 21:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not setting up a timer.   My preference is 20 min studying 10 min. rest.  In my opinion after 20 min I need a break so I do not wander without learning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guys or Reddit, what is the most costly (money or otherwise) thing you ever did to impress a girl. Did it work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 04:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girls or Reddit, what is the most costly (money or otherwise) thing you ever did to impress a guy. Did it work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 04:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 04:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That aint nothin, once I was one-upped twice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 02:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let her see you spit in it while you are cooking it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 21:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> uuggghhhh,   Thanks.    Telling my wife to go to bed without me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 06:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We should have a drum porn site.   That is sexy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
