<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2257</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 23:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> big island of Hawaii 

You mean Maui? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 23:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> unearthly smell of waffles

FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 12:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly never thought I would read so many responses related to Chron's disease in a single AskReddit thread </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 10:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> poor doggo is gettin friend-zoned, you can just tell by the look on his face that he wants to be more than best friends </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 18:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats on the sex </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 18:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Steve Bartman reaching for ball in 2003 NLCS*

*freeze frame*

*record scratch*

'Yep, that's me, and you're probably wondering how I got there.' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 18:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all die eventually. Let me lead you into the void. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 18:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paul Blart Mall Corp: the story of Paul Blart, an exorbitantly rich CEO and his shady dealings, specifically with the new drug called 'pixie sticks,' beneath the guise of his mall company. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 08:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sub sandwiches

Further, is a chicken sandwich not placed on a bun, one exactly the same as one that would go on a burger? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 08:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but is a hoagie not a bun? Are all 'sandwiches' on a hoagie not really sandwiches? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is/isn't a hot dog a sandwich? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 08:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is a hot dog a sandwich? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 08:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 08:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Example: JewsOfDeath, you give me life. 

Compliment achieved! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 08:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, can I take a Coke Zero </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 07:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> relevant username </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 07:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well with all that static electricity buildup, those socks could be a real spark in your sex life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 07:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *And at that moment, I prayed to God, 'Oh god, please let me catch one fish.' And out of nowhere, there were 40 falling from the sky into my boat.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 22:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I swear, I swear its not syphilis! I've never had syphilis before! You're my first! I wore a condom! It has to be some sort of rash," Jason spewed as he desperately tried to rationalize his girlfriend's claim.

"Then why the hell does my pussy hurt as well then? You were my first! You are the only one who could've given me the bug!" Grace exclaimed. 

It had been one of many long days for Grace, and simply put, she was not up for yet another one of life's many sadistic kicks to her well-being.  Although the government still considered her a child, she had seen thing that many had never seen before, and would never see in  their lives.

There was the time her father beat her mother so hard into the door that the door could be picked up off of its hinges.  There was the time that her father had over-dosed on heroin, and was sent into violent convulsions, dying in front of his daughters eyes.  There was the time the house burnt down because one of the marijuana plants' grow-light sparked and started a fire.  There was the time that her mother was busted by the cops with a line of cocaine on the table and 7 new marijuana plants in the closet.  It had been a rough life.

Needless to say, it had been a rough life for Jason as well. His dad, a laid-off steel factory worker, turned to alcohol to absolve his past pains, and the absolution of his pain only caused greater pain for Jason.  Every night when he got home from the bar, a merciless beating would ensue, leaving Jason bruised and battered as he told his classmates that his clumsy ass had fell down the stairs for the seventh time in the last month.

Sure, technically they were just children, but they were each grizzled veterans of the hard life of a dying steel town, left to fend for themselves as their parents gave them pain, not support.  So there they were, arguing next to Grace's locker on the second to last day of their Sophomore year of high school, trying to figure out if their already terrible lives were about to get worse.

"God Grace, you have been the only thing good that has been in my life. There's no way I could've caused this, and if I did, I don't know if I'll be able to ever live with myself," Jason said.

"Did you ever use a dirty needle?" Grace prodded, looking for answers.

"No, baby, you know after seeing what our parents do, I'll never touch drugs or alcohol," Jason answered, with the utmost sincerity.  

Unlike many of the other kids in the town, Jason had a very real intention of escaping that God-forsaken shithole, and he realized that started with avoiding addiction and going to college.  This commitment and maturity was why Grace loved him so much, as he was a beacon of hope in a town that wallowed in its own self-loathing. Further, that was why he loved Grace so much, was because she was the only one that saw that in him and shared a similar goal.

"Did you ever clean up anyone's blood? You can get STD's through blood you know," Grace asked.

At that moment, it dawned on Jason.  For every night that his dad came home drunk and beat him up, there would be a night that he would come home passed out, and many of those times it would be the direct result of a bar fight.  Jason would have no option but to drag him out of the driveway, right where his father's old coworkers left him, and doctor him up and clean his wounds.  His father, not exactly the prime example for a clean, healthy lifestyle, was swimming with STD's from his time with the cheap hookers that he picked up next to the steel mill and brought home.

"Oh God, oh God, oh God. It was me, it was me," Jason choked out as he sobbed into his girlfriend's shoulder.

His girlfriend, overcome with grief, began crying into his shoulder as well.

"I'm so sorry, baby.  I love you more than anything in this world," Jason muttered through tears.

"I love you too, baby.  We can make it through this; we've made it through worse," Grace whispered, through her own tears.


--------------------

EDIT: Let me know what you guys think! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 20:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "And honestly, this whole profit chasing is the reason why I had to cut Jar-Jar Binks from Episode 3. Very sad really." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 08:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Creating a ton of bots on Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 08:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It had been the same daily routine for John Willard for the past 17 years: hit the snooze button twice, precisely at 6:05 and 6:14 AM, wake up at 6:23 AM, brush his teeth, eat a bowl of cereal, and then take a cocktail of pills.  The pills, a mixture of antidepressants and multivitamins, helped to combat his post-addiction depression and also tried to help his ailing heart, one tired from 10 years of Heroin addiction.  It wasn't a particularly glorious life, but all that mattered for John Willard was that he had not slept through his alarm in a heroin-induced deep slumber in the past 17 years.

John often wondered when he would be able to ween himself off of the anti-depressants. He figured that he would only need them for the five months after his rehab stint, but after several 17 years, he still found himself going to the local pharmacy every couple weeks to get his refill.

The doctors said he would need a change of occupation if he was ever to cut off his pills, but that job had been the only stable thing over that last 17 years for John Willard.  Every day, after  his morning routine, he would make the often tedious commute to Corcoran State Prison, the place that had given him his second chance, to read letters. Despite its reputation for nastiness and overall violence, John felt obligated to serve there, even if it was now the cause of his depression.

Although the letters weren't particularly good for his mental health, John sometimes took fancy in what the prisoners had to say.  Many times, it would be filled with pornographic or abhorrently violent language, showing a darker side to an already dark person.  However, the ones that John fancied showed a different kind of person, one who despite his past record of violence, showed an air of sophistication.  One person, in particular, was inmate 070969.  Because each inmate was only listed by their number, John hardly ever knew who was writing the letter, but still often recognized a certain inmate's writing style.  Inmate 070969 had been there for all 17 years of John's residency, but had just begun writing more and more of late, many of which were a drastic shift from the usual disgusting content that passed through his desk.


"My beloved," the incoming letter read, "I can only imagine a world in which I am with you. My heart aches, my body quakes, but every day I am without you.  Your letters are the only thing that keep me strong, and I do hope you will write back soon."

After an enthusiastic approval of the letter, John, for once, had something to look forward to.  Never having found love himself, he eagerly awaited the response from within the prison, hoping that it would quench the thirst for love he had harbored for the previous 65 years.  As little as it may have been, these prison love letters gave him something to hold on to. Sure enough, a response came the very next day.

"My Angel, I am with you in spirit.  You are my rock, and I only wish you could be here with me right now.  I know I may never be able to see you outside the confines of this prison, but just know that we are still together and meant for each other.  I love you."

Particularly moved once again by this outgoing letter, John Willard finally felt compelled to do something he had never done before; he wanted to speak to the writer of this latest letter.  He had never known the full identity of any of these prisoners, as he chose not to get attached to any of them.  But as these last two letters, and the countless one before them, gave him strength, he found the strength to find out who this was.

All he had to do was ask, but he just had never chosen to before.  However, this time strongly motivated by the words of an incarcerated poet, he approached the secretary with conviction.

"Hello Esperanza," John said in a gruff voice. "I was wondering if you could do an inamte lookup for me today?"

Esperanza looked up quickly, half-startled by John's presence. "Yeah, sure John.  Just give me his number and I'll tell you his name."

"090769"

As the result on the computer showed up, the same startled expression came over the secretary's face as she searched for words. "Um, I'm not sure what you were looking for, but the inmate you're looking for is Charles Manson."

"As in, THE Charles Manson?" John replied, faltering slightly.

"Yes, born November 12, 1934."

After placing so much hope into a person, John was only let down again.  Perhaps it was his old, tired, heart that couldn't handle a shock as such, or maybe it was the sheer letdown that he had placed so much faith in a ruthless murderer, but John slumped, passed out in front of the secretary's desk.

-------------------------------------------------

Let me know what you guys think! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 21:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or you'd still be alive if you had just told her no, you couldn't help. No good deed goes unpunished  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 21:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well if you are the chia seeds, did you at least start growing some dopeass green hair either time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People on Reddit who have been medically dead and gen revived, what was it like when you were dead? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 18:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 02:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sex </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 02:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just a college freshman, but being a Finance major, and looking at who else is a Finance major, I would have to say the Finance industry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 02:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, fucking rookie you lil piece of pussy ass horse shit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 02:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *every comment in this thread starts getting removed* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 02:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of the Silicon Valley(show) bit:
 
"So how does your compression algorithm differentiate itself from the others?"

"Oh, this one can change the world!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 01:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What makes you think she was crazy? The fact that she ditched her current date for a former guy that she pointed out already, or the fact that *she asked you if it was okay*? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 01:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No lie, as soon as OP called him Chad, I thought he was going to do something super douchey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 01:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And probably an analyst to clean up some other problems.

Sounds like she needs Tobias Fnke, analrapist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We need a Reddit Census to truly figure out Reddit's demographics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 01:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 01:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> buzzkill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In honor of Donald Glover's hearty endorsement, Migos - Hannah Montana (Symphony version) [Hip-Hop] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 21:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Glover calls Migos "the Beatles of our generation" at the Golden Globes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 18:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This reminds me of the thought I always had throughout high school, did the writer really mean for something this deep? Or were they simply looking for words to finish out the sentence and their reputation caused people to scrutinize every single word, even to the point that the consensus interpretation is far more advanced than he poet's intention? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 17:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBH I didn't even know that Atlanta was up for this, or that it was even a comedy in the first place. Def thought it was some sort of light-hearted drama </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Redditors who are married, at what point did you realize they were the right one: Was it love at first sight or was it gradual? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 07:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 07:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, first comment of the entire post is already hitting very hard. Great to hear your sober and your children have been a blessing though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Backwoods Redditors, what is the most redneck thing you have ever witnessed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 07:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could only use one meme for the rest of your life, what meme would you choose? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 07:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Redditors who do something that is universally shamed by contemporary society, what do you do and how do you like your job? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 07:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Older and wiser Redditors, what is your one biggest regret in life in regards to your handling of a specific situation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 07:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What is the one biggest regret you have about the kind of person you were before the age of 21? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 07:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the weirdest place you have ever woken up with no recollection of how you got there? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 07:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 07:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ironically, their romantic lives. Not everyone can go down to the drive-in theater and make out in the back of their '57 chevy convertible, pops. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 07:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cartemis would've been especially excited for his sweet sixteen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 07:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That funny, because I imagined the Planters peanut guy, with the monocle and everything  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 07:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or it could be a 'if you get the cops called on me I'll kill you and then your entire family' style ultimatum </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 01:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you experience pain in your dreams? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 01:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever considered doing something in your dreams that you could never do in real life? Like stealing a car and getting in a police chase? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 00:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a casual thing with a girl a few months ago, and then recently(a couple weeks ago) a mutual friend convinced us all that we should hang out. I was initially hesitant about going, but that mutual friend convinced me that she wouldn't be weird and it would be a fun night. 

We set off for the night with the five of us(one of my best friends(male), girl I had the casual thing with, mutual friend(female), and then another person (female). Dinner went well, with the girl I've had a history with being faith normal. There were a few awkward comments, but I think everyone just assumed they were meant to ease any tension.

Anyway, going with the plan, we went back to the hook-up girl's house to drink and just hang out. As everyone got progressively drunker, the girl I had a history with got increasingly more suggestive. First it was mentioning that we had sex. Then, after brining up the fact that my best friend spits randomly when he gets drunk, she looks me directly in the eyes and loudly says, so that everyone in the room can hear 'I don't spit.' As if that wasn't bad enough, she gets 3 feet away from my face and repeats, louder, 'Did you hear me? *I don't spit.*' from there, she started mentioning obscene details of our fling, none of which I feel comfortable explaining. Somewhere in this entire ordeal, there is a snapchat video of her sitting on my back while I helplessly look around the room.

This entire time, I was significantly less drunk than the rest, as was the one other person(female) that I mentioned earlier, and I didn't know her too well, so I generally hung by her talking to her the entire night while everyone else did the weird shit. After a little talking to her, the girl I had a thing, who hardly knew the girl I was now talking to, went up to her and told her 'If you fuck him, it would really hurt me,' despite us not having been a thing, or said a word to each other, for the prior three months.

Things escalate, the one other girl I had been talking to made plans to get picked up, and I piggy-backed on her ride home because I had to get my ass out of there. The girl I had a thing with picks up on this, and deliberately hides my hat and the other girl's coat, but I find my hat and we are on our way.

After we leave, she sends me a selfie an hour later, to which I don't respond, and then proceeds to fuck my incapacitated best friend, solely to make me jealous, as told to me by our mutual friend the next day. Also the next day, she texts the one girl I had been talking to, and tells her 'If you want to, good luck fucking him. It's tough to.'

tl;dr: let the past be the past and never think that things won't be awkward </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 00:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wear yoga pants. Girls need to appreciate this ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 00:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Film porn and all the proceeds go to charity

this. is. progress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yes, that is exactly how dreaming works. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 19:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] You are set to marry your soulmate tomorrow, and you are convinced it will be the happiest day of your life. However, that quickly changes when the doctor calls and tells you that your future life partner is HIV positive. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 17:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You are set to marry your soulmate tomorrow, and you are convinced that it will be the happiest day of your life. However, that soon changes when the doctor calls and tell you that your future life partner has HIV. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 17:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bartenders of Reddit, what is the most embarrassing thing you have ever seen a guy do/say as he is trying to hit on a girl? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 06:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girls of Reddit, what is the best pickup line you have ever heard? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 06:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girls of Reddit, what is the best way for a guy to subtly hint that he has a thing for you while still not being too overt. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 06:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 06:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dying flowers remind me of my ultimate mortality and powerlessness in regards to the ways of nature.

i'm glad they bring you happiness tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 06:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like the 'ButPooComesFromThere' also applies to your mouth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 06:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back in my day, when I got home and wanted to hang out with a friend, I had to get the school directory out, look up their name, call their house, TALK TO THEIR MOM, and then ask them if they wanted to come over! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 00:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [insert common household item] dick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 21:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, I wouldn't mind seeing that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 19:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The biggest problem in this story is that the kid in the photo is probably from San Diego and is wearing a GSW hat and a Cowboys jersey.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was weirdest and most unexplained situation you've ever found yourself in? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 07:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If two dogs and a cat were to form a rap group, what would their most natural stage name be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 07:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 07:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MWA: Mammals with Attitude

EDIT: Hit Single: FUCK THA MAILMAN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 07:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just as the cats are small in stature compared to the dogs, Eazy E was still one bad motherfucker when compared to the likes of Ice Cube and Dr. Dre. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 04:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On Election Day this year, and a native English speaker mispronounced my name, Seth. I am fully certain they were capable enough to stop any complex voter fraud schemes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 21:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go kill Adam Lanza. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 21:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Multiple bottles of laxatives, multiple bottles of epithet, a paintbrush and an easel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 21:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YouTube post:

"Time lapse of me peeling this potato"

Don't worry /r/LillyYoyoNeedGogert, I trust you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 21:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well if he is indeed a rapist murderer, at least he's a courteous rapist murderer, using condoms and all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 19:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I take ice cream from mostly children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 19:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> extremist social Darwinism ftw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 19:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> este publicacion see fantastico: cinco de siete </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 08:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/wholesomememes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 07:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, when in doubt, just remember time is some artificial number that humans came up with to try to give order to the universe. You're never too old for anything :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 07:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can totally relate, and especially in this world, it's seeming like kindness is being valued less and less, so even if you're a good hearted person, you never really get a chance to show it, because the norm is divisiveness and emotionally violent words. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 07:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being on Reddit, I feel like we're all kind of in this same boat together, to where a large majority of us, plainly stated, are just more intelligent than the average human. I understand where you're coming from, because a lot of the time I'll end up making some nerdy joke, get a few stares, and then find myself immediately diverting the awkwardness with some shallow pop culture reference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 07:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely feel the same. I have plenty of friends to where I know I'd sacrifice my reputation(or something else, just a realistic example) to take a fall for them, but I always wonder if they'd do the same for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What do you feel is one of your best qualities that you feel goes largely unnoticed by the people around you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 06:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My mother just sneezed. My dad coughed. Frightening reminders of how life is fragile and finite. Even as I am finished with my first semester of college, I cannot imagine myself fully independent from them, let alone on this earth without them. I hate sneezes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 01:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Cut me some slack, Jack! Chump don' want no help, chump don't GET da help!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Airplane, it surely is the best to quote.

And don't call me Shirley. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jefferson Davis: "The liberals are imposing all these regulations that are crushing business. Lincoln is helping! Sad!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 01:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Space bar vs. Tab </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 17:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better split up Ford vs. Chevy as well:

Explorer vs. Surburban

GT vs. well, nothing

Having a half inch penis(Mustang) vs. having a half inch penis(Camaro)

Built ford tough vs. a bunch of bullshit 'highest initial quality' awards



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 03:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In California, there is an innovative new procedure called the fourth trimester abortion. She may be catching the craze. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 02:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Color was really invented in the 1930's, as displayed in the Wizard of Oz. As a result, there was the subsequent rise of Jim Crow laws, as displayed throughout the 1940's and 1950's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 22:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just taking one for the team </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If the Italian supervolcano erupts and causes a volcanic winter, doesn't that solve global warming? Don't we want it to erupt? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 21:19:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 21:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember a documentary on the Yellowstone supervolcano scared me shitless. I was convinced I was going to be dead when I woke up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 21:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any character ever named Tiffany, there always whiny and shallow.

No offense to any tiffany's reading this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 20:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Narcos. There was 10 hours of content that I blew through in 48 hours when season 2 came out.  I rarely am even able to watch a show all the way through and usually stop watching midway through  (This was the case with Parks and Rec, The office, Peaky Blinders, The Walking Dead, and I even had to take a break from House of Cards for a while). Narcos is the only show I've ever been able to binge watch, let alone actively emerge myself into. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 20:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Space AIDS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 20:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My ex-girlfriends BDSM porn blog that featured her own naked selfies. I didn't find out about it after the fact, and I wasn't on it, but it still presented a major dark spot on my past. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 20:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Women deserve to be treated with respect and integrity. Despite the fact that I am joining a fraternity, hearing stories of any form of date rape or coercion absolutely infuriate me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 13:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did you do on May 27th through 29th, because without an answer, I'm just going to assume you had a 72 hour fuckfest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 13:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever seen a cow egg? Exactly. Cows are really good at hiding them, chickens are just the idiots that we can take advantage of and steal their eggs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Americans of Reddit, how would you describe the quintessential European? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 07:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Europeans of Reddit, how would you describe the quintessential American? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 07:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 02:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *said friend starts hysterically screaming*

"HELP ME JESUS! HELP ME JEWISH GOD! HELP ME ALLAH! HELP ME TOM CRUISE! TOM CRUISE USE YOUR WITCHCRAFT TO GET THE FIRE OFF ME!"  

*sinobii comes running in*

"PLEASE DONG LET THE INVISIBLE FIRE BURN MY FRIEND." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 21:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that you think you understand women is probably a turn off for women. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 21:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *MyAnusYourAdventure is supportive toward someone who has immense pain upon penetration* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 20:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't me, but Riff Raff followed one of my friends and then slid into her dms, asking, and I quote "WHATZ COLLEGE DO U ATTEND ?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 20:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's really pretty impressive that Kingston follows you, being that he follows fewer than 1000 people. Idk if any of the other celebrities on his list have fewer than 300k following numbers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 20:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jose Bautista follows me on twitter, probably to try to make friends because it has become increasingly apparent that no one on his team likes him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 18:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow you're really relishing in this moment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I'm listening to a football game and I move into an earlier time zone, will I have to relisten to the previous hour of the game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 18:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 18:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> U right that's a typo
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what's the worst bad omen you've ever had to start a year? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 08:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what do you hope the new memes of 2017 are going to be about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 08:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 08:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well now that we have the unparalleled knowledge about the most efficient way to move a 90 kg projectile 300 meters, I don't see how we could possibly screw this one up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 08:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually enjoyed No Man's Sky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 08:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Similarly, I worked at a frozen yogurt store that was open thru the winter, and I worked there with two of my best friends.  One night, it was just the two of them working, so one of them paid the other to put on a children's white felt cowboy hat and sunglasses(both of which were in the lost and found) and serve the next customer. The next guy who comes in was a regular, so he came in, looked at my friend, chuckled, and asked "Slow night?" 

Other than that, I spent a lot of that winter watching House of Cards. Needless to say, it was a great high school job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 08:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing. That's why you specified we're up to nothing. Stop making us feel bad about ourselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Redditors who have had a very late breakup, what was it like breaking up right before your wedding day or on your wedding day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 06:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most redneck experience you've had with anyone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 06:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After staring at my phone for an hour while sitting in the dark, I went into the bathroom and my shirt look pink in the mirror. Is this what girls see? Is the entire world pink for them? Am I turning into a girl? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 05:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what is the best way to build up Karma? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 05:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
