<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2577</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 17:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't realise it 'wasn't available in the UAE', I've been playing it for months, just like everyone else :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 16:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recharges take much longer the old you get though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 15:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Spaniard living in England I cannot tell you first how angry I am that most churro places charge around 5 (6) for about 5 churros and a little chocolate. And secondly the chocolate isn't only about half the thickness.

The one's on South Bank were both of these and it made me so angry just seeing them!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 15:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came in to ask the same thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 10:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DON'T FORGET TO BRING A TOWEL! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 09:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a decent drawer but I still got 'sorry I couldn't guess it' all 6 times.

I only had to draw: A house, a parachute, a mobile phone, a wheel, a compass and a barn.

All humans would have guessed my pictures correctly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 01:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4 years of Russian, 1 of German, 1 of English (until the end of the European war). So I'd say his Russian was probably ok but he would most likely have only understood basic orders in German and English.

I wonder once he mastered English later on in life that when he had war flashbacks whether he then understood what everyone was talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 01:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me neither, didn't even know facebook gave out the news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 01:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else forget that Obama is still the President :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 21:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never miss a train. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 20:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also available in Shoreditch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 20:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Quisieron enterrarnos, pero se les olvido que somos semillas.

Except we had the expression in Ancient Greek :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 00:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly, surely we're the most learned generation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 22:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Username checks out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 22:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's a 9th of November Truther joke :s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 22:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the priest couldn't lie :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 22:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been lied to! Porn = good karma :O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does everyone not have ad blockers in this day and age. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 17:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only the minority of Catalonians want it as they know it's pure idiocy to leave. Unfortunately like any extremist group they make a lot of noise and the media increase it ten fold.

I say this as a Northern Spaniard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 17:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to pay $80 for eye dongles to read it though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 15:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's taught me that even if you provide proof, redditors will still call you a liar and say their opinion is right over actual facts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 22:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favourite pokmon, absolute beast in gyms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 22:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you not see the news about Cameron's government censoring the internet :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 13:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Real world mouse trap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 22:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Americans were surprised with Trump's win with segregation being in their parents lifetime. Racism doesn't disappear in one generation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 19:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's be honest, as much as I love Chan, he's never delivered an Oscar worthy performance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 18:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One more to go! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mexico-US wall to be part fence - Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 17:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 15:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instantly made me feel like a teen watching chappelle's show again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 15:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would have been funny to see them as zombie because we're outsides but imagine having to play your dead friends, dunno if I could do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 11:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We also should mention the ouya's controller lag, which is kind of critical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BBC editing didn't always used to be good. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 00:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 19:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think I've ever seen a photocopier; only ever worked in paperless offices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 14:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Show me any proof that the majority of millennials voted for Trump then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 14:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How the fuck did a third of Latinos vote for Trump, that's like the Jews voting for Hitler.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 01:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to coach when I was 21/22; the first week was fine but the second week nearly all the single mums turned up looking stunning and tried to seduce me just so I would play their kids.

A few of them came up to me 1on1 and were very graphic. One kept suggesting a quickie at half time.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 01:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Londoner here, never heard of flying fig either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 01:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our President and Royal family don't get sent to gaol for massive tax dodging/illegal investments but they want to sent a kid to gaol for posting a meme. Great priorities there guys :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 00:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the horse one, hidden in plain site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 00:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every little thing he does is magic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 21:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His casino managed to lose money in a boom period. Everyone else made $$$. Casinos are like printing money. God knows how he managed to fail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 21:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's cockney, so native to London. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL - Whiplash was filmed in only 19 days, despite Damien Chazelle (director) being hospitalized after a serious car crash, who then returned to filming the next day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 01:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 21:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Lion King; I still get cut up about Mufasa even when I watch it now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 21:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the hug from Bill Cosby? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 21:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I look a lot better with contacts than glasses but when I'm presenting our quarterly finance data I wear them as it makes me look smarter and thus more trustworthy :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 21:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who says it doesn't ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 20:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure Ted Roosevelt delivered some in his time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 18:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yes, the MolotovRibbentrop Pact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 09:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Latino living in the UK it feels like the whole world is turning against me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 20:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weekly episodes is exactly why people join Netflix, to avoid that nonsense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 18:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah America, the only country in the world where I'm not in fact white but Hispanic :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 18:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do they not have online or postal voting in the USA? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 18:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah but the UK press will report standing outside polling stations and ask who people are/have voted for. It's pretty easy to 'guess' which way a part of the country has voted doing that tbf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 12:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow that's interesting; I've been doing an hour of breaststroke 4 times a week for a little while now and was planning to switch to front crawl as I thought it be tougher. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 12:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  For all intensive purposes

I believe you mean for all intents and purposes.

I'm assuming by the 89 up votes that a lot of people don't know this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 11:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not entirely true; Jesus also had five fingers in the Simpsons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 03:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I convinced my wife that the lights haven't been getting dimmer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 03:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being latino upon meeting new people, very early on they will 'joke' about latinos being lazy. Why would you think insulting my entire family would be funny :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 02:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who lives in the city there isn't anything that I could need that a phone call wouldn't fix. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 02:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fahrenheit, what is this the 1920s :D  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL - At his coronation, Peter I of Portugal had the body of his dead wife dug up and placed on a throne and demanded that his vassals kissed her hand. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 00:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 22:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm literally the only person in the world with my name (I have both a unique first name and surname (fusion of my parent's surnames)) so every day I'm setting a record for average life expectancy :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 19:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Spaniard it is always odd when I try to write a serious point on reddit and it get's laughed at because I make the odd spelling mistake. You wouldn't do that to someone when they're talking, so why do it online? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 03:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Summary for redditors.

- North Korea try to assassinate the dictator of South Korea in the 1974 but kill his wife instead
- A former policeman turned preacher/cult leader, Choi Tae-min, contacts the dictators daughter (Park Gun-hye) and says she can speak to her mother through him
- He gains unlimited influence over her and earns huge sums for access to her and the government
- The dictator is assassinated in 1979 and a military dictator takes over, thus the cult leader loses his influence and fades into the background but still has control over Park Gun Hye
- In 1990 Park Gun-hye's sister writes to the government asking them to save her sister from the grips of Choi Tae-min
- Choi Tae-min dies in 1994 and his daughter Choi Sun-sil takes over influence of Park Gun-hye
- In 1997 Park Gun Hye starts her political career and becomes an elected official in 1998
- In 2007 she runs for President but loses her parties nomination. At this point the US embassy points out to the US government about her history with the cult leader
- In 2012 she runs again and wins the Presidential election. Choi Sun-sil is in charge of producing the inauguration ceremony
- Her behaviour as President is erratic and she rarely gives press conferences. Her speeches are described as rambling and full of strange wording
- Fast forward to 2016 and there is a scandal about Choi Sun-sil's daughter getting in to a prestigious Korean university and preferential treatment despite not getting the grades or attending classes
- Choi Sun-sil and her daughter flee to Germany to get away from the scandal
- One of the major news channels find a tablet in Choi Sun-sil's former office which contains evidence that she was given confidential government files including upcoming Park Gun-hye speeches and government policies despite not holding a post in the government
- Park apologises but says that she no longer consults Choi and hasn't since the early days of her Presidency
- There is more evidence from the files and witnesses that Choi had complete influence over Park, from rewriting speeches to choosing/making her clothes for official engagements, and was doing so right up to earlier this year
- Choi has strong armed Korean conglomerates in to donating money to her 'foundations' (slush funds), threatening them that their businesses will be harmed by government decisions if they don't
- Choi apparently leads a select group of 8 advisors including a gigolo and a K-pop video director who control everything Park does and shamanistic rituals regularly take place at government buildings (speculation at the moment) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 03:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine could be a gaolable offence tbf.

 It looks innocent but he actually just took that baby hostage as a bargaining chip to get the vacuum put away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 02:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a housemate that would buy a meat pie, scoop out said pie, put a 500g block of cheddar cheese into it and microwave it. Whilst it was microwaving he'd leave out a 500g tub of Ben   Jerry's baked Alaska. Then when the pie was 'ready' he'd pour the ice-cream into the pie and swirl in into the cheese.

This he would eat in one sitting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 00:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aren't pirates just soldiers for pay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 23:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will happily pretend to be a flat earth believer if I get to go to a space station. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 23:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Legitimately had me in tears and struggling to breath :D :D :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 21:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish these videos weren't in Spanish, as it's not so funny when you know what's really being said. Always choose an obscure language. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 16:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Facebook was created when I started university and within about 2 months I didn't know anyone on campus who didn't have it.

It revolutionized having parties/meetups and this was pre-smart phone era.

Also the fact that kids and parents weren't on it meant you could truly say whatever you wanted and for many that had lived a sheltered life it was great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 15:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgot that I bought this game but haven't played it yet; will defo give it a go soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 15:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shame the drawer didn't draw the Earth [properly.](http://i.dailymail.co.uk/i/pix/2014/04/04/article-2596783-1CD3619700000578-454_964x608.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 15:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do it with a banana. That monkey's head would explode! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 19:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about the UN stop Saudi Arabia from invading them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 19:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rick James and Prince both dead, who's next in the Chappelle show curse? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 13:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The body shop since L'Oreal bought them, as they have been known to test their products on animals.

Starbucks as they're Zionists.

Apple because of their child labour.

Hugo Boss because they are Nazis. (Become big because they made and designed the nazi uniform)

IBM for helping in the holocaust.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 12:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly no-one noticed you as they too were all glued to their phones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 23:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who buys 8 bags of crisps :O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 20:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By this stage everyone would be using vegetable oil. People are farming anyone, may as well make fuel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 20:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the main reason why zombie movies always have to start with the zombie's already having taken over the world because there's no real way to explain it otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 18:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just after I'd open a new bottle mine would ask for a sip and drink 2/3 of it. She's been banned from 'having a sip' now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 03:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been interviewed a few times on tv and they always put makeup on me and when I go hang out with my friends later not once has anyone realised that I'm wearing makeup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 03:19:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still angry that I had to spend $135 on getting my table's bvh's properly aligned with its mrt's. Probably would have been cheaper to use a qvr to align it; sure it wouldn't have been perfect but I doubt 99% of people would notice the difference and it would have been a lot cheaper.

Damn my ocd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When your nose has the same HAAG as what you're sitting on. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 03:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 23:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My family had to flee because otherwise they would have been murdered. So no I wont me returning to live there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 20:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Radio app with every station in the world is where it's at. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 19:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to sign the receipt in America :s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 19:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **PENIS** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 19:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've not tipped before and I will always say I'm not tipping you because...

If I frequent a place, if when I return the waiter has in fact improved I'll tip double and tell him/her good job for the improvement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL - The world's happiest countries are also the countries that take the most antidepressants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 16:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 14:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wild strawberries. Great a shot of strawberries for 2 hours :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 14:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Room, three hours of looking at an empty room. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 14:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The shining. Just a torch shining in your face for 90 minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 14:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The silence of the lambs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 14:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Schindler's list, just a man reading his shopping list for 90 minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 10:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had that happen to me too 2 days ago!

I hatched the eggs yesterday: I need a Snorlax but got lapras, hitmonlee, scyther and eevee.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 00:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm confident that if you called someone a hungry hippo they would understand what I meant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 00:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I generally wouldn't know what that means :S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 00:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's from Aliens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 22:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not cool guys, the rule is you can only mess with someone if they still have their shoes on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 22:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the shortest woman that you've made love to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 15:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have had exactly one good boss in my entire career; sadly she passed away but honestly I would happily cut my wage in half to work for her again.

Current boss is a dick, I'm looking for another job atm but until then :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 15:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The police in America definitely aren't clean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 15:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Burma  Myanmar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
