<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1417</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 18:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watch this and can't help but think of [this scene](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7A-Km9zvFao). I started to laugh but then realised it's all quite sad really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 16:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I opened your link and read it as 'King Kong 2005 incest' and I thought, how have I not heard of this film and you're right this would be terrifying! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 15:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not one? Not even a letter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-06 18:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, she doesn't seem that hot for a model and that dude seems rather regular and...HOLY JESUS LOOK AT THAT ASS!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-06 10:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorted that for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-06 10:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh if it does then Luke's video gets seen, I don't mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-06 01:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd fuck Craster? Gross... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-06 00:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, check out the heckler video on his channel too. It's brilliant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 23:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know. My mate Luke made it and it's my favourite thing of his to date. I can't wait to see the next one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who would you bone in Game Of Thrones? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 21:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 17:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who listens to either one of these songs and thinks of doing this? Don't get me wrong this mash-up is amazing but when does that particular light bulb go off above someone's head!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 01:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-25 14:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing run, amazing try! Shameful tackling, the 5th tackler especially. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stunt man drives round the world's largest Loop The Loop! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-25 12:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Burger Bounce" by Jay Foreman   Bec Hill. This may be an advert but its cutest fucking advert I've ever seen. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-04 18:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 18:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha this is great. I honestly hate that question so much. I mean I can understand if you've no idea of how stand up works why you would ask a comedian to 'say something funny' but seriously it's like pulling teeth when you have to explain it's just not like that. I once had a girl got really angry and call me a liar because I didn't want to tell her a joke. 

I think other than 'say something funny', the next worst thing to hear is 'I bet you'll use this next time you're on stage!'.... No, no I will not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moonstone on the Amiga. Now THIS was my Skyrim! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 15:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Soak -- Blud (CHVRCHES remix) [Electro Soul/Folk] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-12 17:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-12 17:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought this was going to be a really deep and insightful piece about finding your comedic voice and essentially it's 'Talk about what you know'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-10 19:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there are two very different motifs at play there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-10 19:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you've completely missed the point. The problem isn't that Paddy Power are being disrespectful to Oscar Pistorious on the basis of being innocent until proven guilty it's that Paddy Power are being disrespectful of Reeva Steenkamp because regardless of the outcome of the trial, they are making money off the killing (being it intentional or not) of an innocent woman. 

Don't get me wrong I reckon he's guilty as they come but regardless, how a company like Paddy Power can get monetary gain from someone's death is just disgusting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-10 16:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, OK you had me going for the first half, the second half kinda threw me... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comedian tears into Paddy Power for taking bets on Oscar Pistorius trial. Hilarious but he really has a point. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-10 10:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 17:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a really creepy/great video of a Crystal Castles song played along side footage from Come and See. Worth a watch whether you've seen the film or not - http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FJtGSWUmdyc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 15:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you'll find it's when you're down and out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-05 18:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "WHAT ARE YOU DOING! WHAT ARE YOU DOING! STOP SLAPPING THAT WATER! WHAT THE FUCK ARE YOU DOING?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 15:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This series is one of the best things on YouTube. That ending had me cracking up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-18 18:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy-fucking-shit-balls YES! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lewis Watson -- 'Ghost' [indie/folk] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-17 18:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-17 15:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-11 12:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 02:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jealously and genuine mental behavior. We had a pretty intense relationship, we used to either be arguing like crazy or having sex and partying. I suppose on reflection we were both mentally immature at the time but I've never met anyone who could get to me like she could. She was insanely jealous and I have a lot of female friends so she used to get shitty about me spending time with them or even taking to another girl. It got so bad I woke up once with her on top of me, hands round my throat threatening me that she'd dreamt I cheated!

Worst part is my mates loved her, she was the prefect 'mates-girlfriend'. She partied hard with them, was funny and a good laugh but behind closed doors treated me like shit. They couldn't believe me when is explain what she was like and just told me it was in my head or not all that bad. 

I tried to break up with her and she said no. It's embarrassing as I'm a very confident guy and had no problem with women before so it's not like I should have felt trapped but I did. She emasculated me so a relationship that should have ended dragged on for another 6 months because I couldn't man up and just call it off and stick to my guns. 

When it finally happened and she left she told me "you'll never find anyone who loves you like I do" and it fucked me up for a while. Made me paranoid when with women that they were jealous or controlling and I was distant with some lovely people because I was scared to get close to someone in case they tried to control me. 

However after all that I'm now in the perfect relationship and I couldn't be happier. Seems I not only found someone who loves me more than she did but who I love more than I ever knew I could. Clich but in the long run it developed me further as a person and is part of why I'm so happy now. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 01:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit, really? I used to live near that place when I was at uni. It looked like Hogwarts and... and I just realised your name is nigger_shrimp and all the wonder has just left my post.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 10:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This series is hilarious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-28 18:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need that 'Pew' to be my text message sound! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why I Shouldn't Drink... (7 seconds) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 18:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-22 10:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of the best insults ever in this video </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 15:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone has downvoted you for asking that question. I don't understand people at times. Anyway I too like the song and would like to find out what it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 13:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly the plan :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 23:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So beautiful... Should've sent...a poet! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 18:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh come on, I'm not the borough. I wish I was... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 18:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 18:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Photoshop and making sure we had the right lighting and angle for the shot. Max (the one everyone thinks looks like Aaron Paul) is the talent one who did all the Photoshop.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 18:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that from time to time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 18:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ouch... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 17:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely never had that one before </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 17:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I literally have no idea what any of that means... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 17:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 17:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fat Mac or Not-Fat Mac? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 16:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This video series is amazing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 16:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can arrange that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 16:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, that's a new one... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 16:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trust me he knows. He works in a bar and gets told it ALL the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 15:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THANK YOU! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 14:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers PussyOnThaChainwax </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 14:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google 'the snowman' :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every year my housemates and I make a xmas card, this year I think we outdid ourselves. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 14:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-19 18:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-17 15:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the deal with that anyway?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-17 12:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the more you know... despite the shitty animation I really liked this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-16 16:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This comment is pretty redundant so don't worry about it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-13 13:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was brilliant but the Eric Lampaert and Daniel Sloss was amazing. Guess you need to know the people for it to really drive home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-13 13:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been trying to get my head round Russell Peters, I wasn't aware he's basically 'the biggest stand up in the world' until about 6 months ago. So far there's not been anything of his that made me really laugh but watching this, well again I didn't actually laugh, but it's a pleasant story that you can relate to and I guess that's popular enough... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Kill Yourself' A funny but also hugely impressive music video by two comedians. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 13:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comedian makes funny but informative video about The Cherokee and The Trail of Tears. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 16:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For those outside of the UK, I found a channel that has recent episodes of current events UK comedy show Stand Up For The Week. Thought I'd share... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-27 12:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-26 18:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been the complete wrong thing with my time on that website... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dramatic Reconstruction of YouTube Comments on One Direction's 'What Makes You Beautiful' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 18:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-17 00:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most definitely the Hawley </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cheese Whisperer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 12:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 11:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really enjoyed this. I know that doesn't bring much to the table in terms of constructive feedback but fuck it, I wanted to vocalise my pleasure. Good video, hope he liked the sketch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liam Neeson shows just how stupid Justin Beiber's lyrics are </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 11:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-04 21:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why skip the first few seconds? I think it adds to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Guest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-30 18:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-27 09:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooooookaaaay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I might be interviewing Jack Dee in a couple of days, any questions you guys would want me to ask him? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 19:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it goes ahead I'll post the interview here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-24 11:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Play that funky Tesla white boy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 17:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, I didn't initially make that link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 16:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to be a huge fan of Battlefield 1942 and used to play it at huge LAN parties, it amazes me how far gaming has come since those days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
