<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2240</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 05:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No self-hatred over here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 05:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha well thank you. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 05:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do, I'll have to dig them up. What's Rocket League? Aw, that's great! How old is your kid? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 05:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha not quite, but still very funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 05:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alone!
Also, great username! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 04:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hockey (watching and playing) and comedy (watching, writing, and performing). What about you? I guess motorcycles? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 04:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm mostly not an interesting person, y'know? I don't have fun stories and I'm not a scintillating guy. I'm a good person, just not a thrilling one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 04:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have not, but I do like NWA so how bad can it be? Let me know if you enjoy it - I certainly hope you do! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 04:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm mostly not really an interesting person, so I'd consider that boring.
I think so. Every now and again I engage in interesting things, so as long as there is at least one person who does at least one less interesting thing than I, then there is someone more boring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 04:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A nightmare on both sides. Both parties really scraped the bottom of the barrel for 2016. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 04:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope you enjoy if you do! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 03:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a book called "Chasing Shakespeares" if you're interested. I had to read it but I didn't really, which is probably why I didn't love it.

I believe he was real, but it's an interesting argument. Ever read Hamlet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 03:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An excellent question. I may bring back Shakespeare to talk to him (and see if he's even a real person: I think he is, but some speculate he was just a random guy that great writers used as an alias). I'd also wonder how he could write about today's times, if at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 03:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bring them back to today to do a job? Or to talk/hang out with them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 03:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't see it, probably won't (in theaters at least). Much like every other movie, I'll see it years later on DVD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm just a random, rather boring guy. AMA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 02:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the title says it all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 02:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! Do you know any people who would be interested also? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
