<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1271</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 17:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Bates Motel** final season proved that just like Gotham is an alternative to Batman, Bates Motel is an alternative to the Psycho film series. It wasn't perfect but it was enjoyable. [](#s "Who would've thought Dylan would be the last man standing though? I totally was expecting him to die"). Bates Motel did not try and connect its story to Psycho at all but was able tease us along the way because many thought they would.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 17:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok, I guess I will. I had a similar viewing experience with HBO's Girls for the first 2 seasons too tbh. It took me some time to figure out what that show was aiming for so it was a tedious experience at first. But Girls was visually pleasing to me and that's what made me stick with it and it went on to be one of my favorites in its later seasons. That is something The Sopranos doesn't have unfortunately, it's not visually pleasing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does The Sopranos get better or am I too late to this party? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 16:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I finished season 2 of The Sopranos not too long ago, and after 26 episodes I'm still not finding itall that engrossing. I mean, it isn't *bad* don't get me wrong, it has some of the best character writing I've seen for a TV Show and there's more comic relief that i expected (I've laughed more times than I do for these 'comedies' nowadays). But plotwise, it isn't doing much. It's a very calm and subtle show but maybe too subtle? This is a show that is recognized by many as*one of the greatest of all times* so I keep waiting for big 'wow' moments to happen that'll make me ecstatically say "holy shit this show is phenomenal!" but they never come. For what it is, it lacks excitement, there's no thrill, no suspense, it doesn't make me wonder what's going to happen next. Trying to watch more than one episode at a time would result in me tuning out of the show almost completely, so the show is not bingeable which is a drag.

From watching I can see that the brilliance of The Sopranos is in the details. What characters say, to whom, where and when... it's a build up, it's precise. I know it's a groundbreaking show, and i can appreciate that. But how does it hold up now in 2017 considering there are other well-detailedTV Serieslike GOT, The Americans, The Leftovers, Fargo, Mr. Robot etc. with more added element which makes them more enjoyable? I know The Sopranoswas probably the first TV Show to break down a lot of walls. Theyhad movie-level production values, centered around antagonistic characters, showed a main character killing people in cold blood, showed a lot of nudity etc. So yea, back when it first came out The Sopranos was probably the most daring show on TV, but I feel it lost many of those attributes with time, and now that they don't have them anymore what's left? Just an average family drama with slightly overweight, mid-age Italian mobsters talking about organized crime (which wasn't visually pleasing to me at all being such a male-dominated show).For people who watched it a long time ago and rewatch it now and still love it I can understand the nostalgic feel, but for new viewers it could be a difficult one to get into.

The truth is tho if The Sopranos didn't happen a lot of the shows we have today probably wouldn't exist.Also something I've noticed now that I've watched The Sopranos, is that Ray Donovan is quitea ripoff. Tho the premise is different the family ties look very similar.But I did enjoy the first2 seasons of Ray Donovan more than I'm enjoy Sopranos right now tho, so my conclusion is that The Sopranos did not age well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 12:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what's wrong with it being a netflix original? imo that makes it even better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
