<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2013</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should ask them if they need a safe space from the NFL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, glad to know I never need to feel guilt for all those times I insulted Republicans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I guess we know who was fittest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd argue that evolution is one of the biggest cornerstones required for a rational atheism.  If your only explanation from where all the various species of animals came from is that they all just appeared someday, it makes it a lot harder to deny the existence of a creator than if you have a theory that allows them to arise naturally through evolution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 15:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a living. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 15:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Orangutans are actually really patient with their own infants.  Even the big flanged males who'll fight each other on sight just let the babies do whatever.  No idea what they'd do with a human infant, though, and Birute Galdikas, the Jane Goodall of orangutans, mentions an orangutan casually trying to murder her by pushing over a rotting tree, so you know, who knows, but out of any wild animal, I'd probably trust an orangutan most with an infant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 13:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plus she handles hot dogs all day, so.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 13:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  but stupid people don't get to power

I'm glad to see you've woken up from your coma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 21:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Modern Corgi vs. historical corgi

That is *clearly* a datadog.  What are you trying to pull? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 02:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Basque!  The sole survivor of the original languages of Europe.  The other non-IE languages moved in later, but Basque has been there since the beginning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 23:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Trump's SEE YOU IN COURT is like if Matt Ryan had gone home and tweeted SEE YOU AT THE SUPER BOWL." - Daniel Dale </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 23:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, I don't think it'd be very unfair to say that one party hasn't been very interested in general governance for the last eight years, being willing to shut down the government and default on debt rather than work with the other party and the president. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 22:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, the old Glossu Rabban-a-roo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 21:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We hung up racist memes and angry diatribes about illegals in order to reproduce the feeling of visiting your aunt's Facebook page." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only the knowledge that rural voters can't afford to build the walls necessary keeps me from the fear that is greater than death: a life where I am forced to drink horchata. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 18:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The alphabet comes to us from the Phoenicians, so I mean, our writing system that we're using right now, via the Greeks and Romans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Tropico games do a good job of collecting weird stuff dictators did: http://forum.kalypsomedia.com/showthread.php?tid=23153

I like this one, especially: "In a stroke of genius, Nguema - President of Equatorial Guinea - had the the governor of the public bank killed and hid all the money in his jungle shed." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must suck to be attacked by the king.  Like, if you defend yourself, you probably get executed.  Just gotta take it and hope he's not gonna murder you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Intellectuals" including any random person who wore glasses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don Quixote was famous during his lifetime and immediately popular.  https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Don_Quixote#Publication </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Other contemporaries wrote about him, too, including another student Xenophon, and the playwright Aristophanes.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of curiosity, are you imagining that a civil war would be fought by random yokels using the guns in their house, rather than with stuff like jets and bombs and tanks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 05:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.  But maintaining the status quo of the SCOTUS doesn't inherently protect rights better than making it more liberal.  How does maintaining the status quo benefit you more than having Clinton appoint a justice?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sleepy-sleepy drugs and the no-ouchies drugs aren't the same drugs, so if you woke up you wouldn't necessarily be in pain.  You *might* be freaked out by being cut open, but since there are also forgetty drugs, you might not even remember it afterwards, and generally, you're drugged up enough that even if you wake up, you don't freak out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And just to be clear, you mostly care about the status quo of the SCOTUS to protect the 2nd amendment, is that correct?  Are there other rights you care about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of curiosity, what are some of these gains that Trump's expected to protect so well that Clinton would have gotten rid of?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have a source for that stuff happening?  This says no uninterred bodies have been found and that it was probably an orderly evacuation: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Akrotiri_(Santorini)#Excavations </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that guy's name?  Julius Caesar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the title I was expecting the mom to buy a dog collar or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only a *true* Sith deals in absolutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Ian, I've noticed that your last five ideas were, in order, go to Portuguese casinos, visit Italian beaches, take a Greek cruise, visit the top of the Eiffel Tower so you could, quote, "moon Hitler," and spend a week at a Brazilian steakhouse, all so you could hurt Nazi morale.  Are you using the war to take vacations?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 19:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first five pokemon all fainted on the first of the Elite Four.  Blastoise took me all the way to the end.  You were a good friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 19:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "*My* animal slaughter is somewhat less gluttonous, so I'm morally superior." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No!  Now one's going to appear!

"Hola!"

DAMNIT! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on the eggplant.  Could have been a Chinese eggplant.  Those are long and skinny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He employed a private fire department in order to buy burning houses at a discount.  You could either sell your house for a fraction of what it was worth, at which point he'd put out the fire and keep it, or you could let your house burn down and get nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 23:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  County La County

*Way* less interesting than Kill la Kill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's easier to craft a good message when you're not bound by reality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 04:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 03:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.zeldadungeon.net/wp-content/uploads/2011/12/Hyrule-Historia-Timeline-translated-Graphics.jpg  In which game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 02:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are no previous Ganons.  Ganondorf doesn't reincarnate.  He's not like Link or Zelda.  He's just the same dude game after game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 23:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you saying this based on anything from canon, or?  I can't think of any such references. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 23:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can find an old cheap Wii or Wii U you can get the Metroid Prime Trilogy pretty easily.  I think you can set up the controls to do lock-on aiming, if I'm remembering correctly, so that should help with that.  It's one of my favorite games, and there's a very heavy emphasis on exploration.  If you manage to play it, I hope you enjoy it!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 22:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you like Metroid Prime?  I mean, there are definitely enemies, but honestly, a lot of them aren't a big threat until you get to bosses, and there's a lot of exploring and finding hidden things like missile packs and upgrades.  I ask because it wasn't one of your examples but I think it's closer to what you want than the examples you gave.  Maybe not, though, you could like other stuff.  But I wanted to suggest it as a good Plan B if the lottery doesn't work out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 05:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cagot  For centuries, a group of people indistinguishable by language or ethnicity were hated by everyone around them and constantly shat on and we have no idea why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 05:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my favorite guys is Scipio's inspiration to go to Africa: Agathocles.  When Carthage was besieging Syracuse, he left with part of his army and went to Africa to threaten Carthage directly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you think would be a comment at the threshold between explicit and implicit racism, and on what side of that line do you think calling Mexican immigrants rapists falls? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 21:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Each of them are absolutely priceless.

Not in El Paso it ain't. In El Paso I got me 250 Dollars for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 21:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and steps out of her shadow as Pai Mei's favorite student

I'm gonna go ahead and guess that there's always gonna be someone he likes more than the woman who murdered him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 21:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Everyone* knows about Billy and the Clone-a-saurus, don't they? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never made this assumption.  Big galaxy, big war.  I figured there were lots of rebels who made contributions who didn't show up again.  After K2SO died, though, I assumed no one else was getting out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 18:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god, why did I become a jingle writer?  What the hell rhymes with "Caleb, the personalityless tie-filling golem?"  I'm gonna lose my job... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 18:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bid you dark greetings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 16:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Marius Jacob is pretty cool: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Marius_Jacob

In Toulon on July 3, 1899, Jacob pretended to suffer from hallucinations in order to avoid five years of reclusion. On April 19, 1900, he escaped from the asylum in Aix-en-Provence with the assistance of a male nurse and took refuge in Ste. There he organized a band of men, calling them "the workers of the night." The principles were simple: one does not kill, except to protect his life and his freedom from the police; one steals only from those considered to be social parasites - bosses, judges, soldiers, and the clergy - but never from the professions considered useful - architects, doctors, artists, etc.; finally, a percentage of the stolen money was to be invested into the anarchist cause. Jacob chose to avoid working with the idealistic anarchists and instead surrounded himself with criminals and fellow illegalists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 16:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Seriously, I'm asking, have you?  I have *zero* idea about this.  I am totally blind.  I need you to tell me: did you feel an awakening, or what?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 22:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about "How chubby are your boobs?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 21:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm wearing cargo pants right now.  ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could only ask someone three questions before deciding whether or not to marry them, what would you ask? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 21:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why run faster when you can just cripple all the other racers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 15:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  In practice, impeachment is seen as a drastic measure, reserved for shocking crimes, treasonous offenses and threats to democracy while in office.

Like lying about blowjobs, you know, threats to democracy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 23:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, he knows a corvette just escaped with the plans, and they just found a corvette, but can they confirm it's the same corvette?  They probably weren't making eye contact in hyperspace the whole trip to Tatooine.  I mean, they all look the same to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 23:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't he have a really long cable running out of the ship that was necessary for his broadcast?  Wouldn't closing the door to the spaceship probably break through that?  Or was the cable elsewhere and I'm just totally forgetting?  But I thought it went into the ship from where it was plugged in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 22:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what the fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 17:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She may be a corrupt warmonger, but she plays fair.  If we get to use a massive nuclear arsenal, it's only fair Russia gets to have one, too.  It isn't sporting otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 00:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the best way to highlight it is that when Rhode Island approved gay marriage, every single Republican in the state legislature voted for it.  Every no vote came from Democrats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 22:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shouldn't you be trying to help people prosecute all that voter fraud you personally witnessed?  I'm surprised they just told you they were illegal.  Or did you just know based on some sort of physical indicator? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 21:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's the left's fault that Republicans went and nurtured a base so receptive to fascists.  Totally our fault.  No blame left for anyone else in that scenario. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 16:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rick Perry can actually form a comprehensible sentence most of the time.  I think he's far more intelligent than Trump.  He can also take in new factual information and change his mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 05:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah, me too.  Donald Trump not considering consequences?  *So* out of character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 04:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/iamverysmart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's something you don't really care for, but love the fan community of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 22:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 01:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally loved The Onion's depiction of Obama as in love with drones.

http://www.theonion.com/article/youre-my-best-friend-says-obama-to-drone-that-appe-31594 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 23:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god I never realized this before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 22:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worth noting: that concert pianist was Paul Wittgenstein, brother of the famous philosopher Ludwig Wittgenstein.  Paul had a bunch of pieces commissioned for him after losing his arm.  He had an odd, to me, sense of ownership of the pieces, refusing to let anyone else play the works until after he died, since he had paid for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 17:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally like Empedocles.  He wanted people to think he had become a god, so he jumped into a volcano so there'd be no trace of him left.  But the volcano spat out his singed sandal, giving enough of a clue for people to put together what happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 17:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're thinking of Themistocles.  https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Themistocles#Rivalry_with_Aristides </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 14:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank goodness for the party of small government! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 14:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Well, I know the Republicans wrecked the economy for years last time, but my health insurance premiums went up, and I never noticed *that* before, so what the hell." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 14:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Annoyedly embarrassed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like you want the Austro-Hungarian Empire: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Austria-Hungary#Politics_and_government </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 17:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If only those space aliens hadn't taken control of Spicer's mouth and made him tell such blatantly obvious lies, maybe this wouldn't have happened.  Oh, how dreadful it is that there's nothing Spicer could have done to make the media trust him more! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 17:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mesozoica is supposed to be coming out soon, if you want something similar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 17:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no such thing as a free lunch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 16:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forget it, Jake.  It's Kamino. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 15:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm for taxes because I'm an adult who understands you can't go to a restaurant and eat for free.  Stuff costs money.  More stuff costs more money.  If taxes are the price of a functioning government that ensures its citizens can eat healthy food and have social equality, then that's fine with me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 15:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is clearly the public Listerine and the public toothbrushes.  What are you talking about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 23:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Tropico 5's multiplayer was ok, but it basically progressed the same way every time.

With every person you were playing with leaving before the game could end? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 06:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like a return to Tropico 4-style campaigns, with easily replayable missions. 

I'd also like game-long permanent choices.  There aren't really any exclusionary choices right now.  Building one factory doesn't prevent you from building another.  Choosing between two different missions only really affects your standing with factions, and that's easily remedied.  I'd like to have you make choices that affect your island for the duration of the mission and that lock out other choices.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 04:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4 is widely considered the best.  It's basically an upgrade of 3.  There's no real reason to get 3.  Just buy 4 and listen to 3's soundtrack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 05:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, if that's the problem, couldn't you just carve up the US into 10 regions based on population and give each one its own single payer system? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 05:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally prefer one planet, so everything can be connected.  I disliked the separate planets in Prime 3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 22:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hard to clap while I was letting him bang me but I tried my best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 22:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Discworld, judging from the octarine comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 21:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This Paul Ryan!  435 representatives enter, only him leave! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 21:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering that the last two times it made a difference we got Bush and Trump, no, liberal New England is not benefiting.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 20:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like Neil Gaiman, and they worked together on the book Good Omens if you want a bridge in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 20:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aren't they, with a few exceptions, chapterless? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 18:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Ice People? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 17:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but see, what happened is the phrase is "play it by ear," but she heard it as "play it by year," which is incorrect.  Do you get it?  Do you?  Do you get what happened? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 16:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Step 1: Possess boobs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 20:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Casual.  I only drink organic bull semen straight from the source, from a bull that I personally raise and take care of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 20:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can name him Nemo.  It means no one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SPRING BREAK! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Lord Vader, I have today's report of all recruits from across the galaxy."

"All fifteen million of them?"

"Yes, my Lord."

"Good, leave them on the table and bring me a list of every traffic accident that occurred in the Outer Rim in the last five months so I can read that, too." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A modern day Charles V. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about antlions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kuuderes are where it's at.  Inaba best girl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 05:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Missingno's got a nice body. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 22:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Defeated the Soviet Union.

Out of curiosity, do you think communism is successful enough that, without Reagan, the USSR would have thrived?  Or is communism a bad system, in which case the USSR was doomed for failure? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wear a uranium vest at all times and have taped another piece of uranium to my air bag so that in the event of a crash they fuse and hit critical mass.  Fuck everyone near me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 18:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Professor writes down "moron" next to the student's name and continues] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 18:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if the only part of this story was that more than one person has ever said the sentence "Resume it!" I would find it impossible to believe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 18:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whereas if they hadn't worn a belt, obviously an accident forceful enough to sever their fucking tits off would have left them with merely a bump on their head and three cartoon birds flying around them in circles.  *Much* safer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 18:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Now, as part of our application process, you'll have to beat Super Mario Bros." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 18:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turns out the guy was playing hentai visual novels on his 3DS with the volume all the way up and *that's* why they were commenting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 17:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your faith in your friends is yours.  Wait... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 17:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually I have to pay $200 bucks for that kinda service! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 17:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, if you want to destroy faith in republican institutions, Jar Jar's the kind of idiot I'd make sure had a high profile.  I imagine a lot of people became pro-imperial government after seeing that he was the result of a republic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 21:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bats are the monkeys of the sky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 20:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't it Nubian?  Like, Nubian starfighters and such? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 20:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For more context, rapeseed oil, aka rape oil, is now known more commonly as canola oil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 20:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read that in The Smoke Gets In Your Eyes, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 18:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Gaius, tell me again why Batman is the greatest of the future gods."

"Please, master, just let me toil in the silver mines..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 18:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those damn, slutty native children sex slaves!  Curse them!  I'd kill them if I hadn't already killed them for not finding enough gold! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 18:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You wouldn't be able to manufacture airplane parts, though, unless you're going to spend your whole life setting up a fraction of the infrastructure required.  You need to look more at stuff that the tech existed for.  You could set up a printing press pretty easily, I'd expect.  Considering its future popularity, you could probably invent chess and gain some fame that way.  Lest Darkness Fall is all about a guy who goes back to imperial Rome and tries to stop the collapse of the empire, and introduces new inventions in order to get the wealth needed.  If I recall, he introduces semaphore, alcohol distillation, double entry bookkeeping, and some other stuff, and has plans to discover the new world so he can get tobacco. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 17:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I haven't hit the pavement yet, so I can't yet judge whether jumping off this skyscraper was a good idea or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 16:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dr. Nobama </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 16:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FANG IT!  [BLOWS HORN] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If a series of movies were made portraying Donald Trump as 007, what sort of villains would he face? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 16:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 01:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is a euphemism for a sex act so filthy I can't even tell you the letters the parts involved start with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 15:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to find it, but Googling stuff like "borrowed money to avoid assassination" brings up a lot of Rothschilds assassinated JFK stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 20:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Metal Gear?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 20:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was actually a Greek politician who, when he feared assassination, went and borrowed money from all the aristocrats, who no longer wanted to kill him before he could repay them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 20:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  People dont live on dessert islands.

But what if I lived on a salad?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 20:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which they were free to change if they really, really wanted to get into banking.  It would have probably been a stupid decision, but they still refused to do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 17:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "His liver spoke German and insulted everyone but the barmaid; his gallbladder exploded into ashes when looked at; his tibia was made of balsa wood; his tonsils were filled with tiny men; his nose was the size and shape of a gorilla's foot" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 17:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You think fascist Nazis clap like some inferior negroid?  They gave him a proper Nazi salute and congratulated him on producing the next generation of Aryan supermen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 17:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he's saying that the fascist is the unnecessary part.  Like if I said I was a mammal human. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 17:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a pretty good book that you'll find interesting, I think: https://www.amazon.com/Empires-Word-Language-History-World/dp/0060935723

This one should be good, too: https://www.amazon.com/Last-Lingua-Franca-English-Return/dp/0802717713 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 17:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also felt like 5 had less, I dunno, heart?  There are a lot fewer unique advisors, and even though there are some really good lines, I don't think it was as funny as 4. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 16:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you like shitty Amazon reviews there's http://leasthelpful.tumblr.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 22:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounds like a much nerdier Ishakawa Goemon XIII. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the worst year in human history? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 21:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 21:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Niles?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 20:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use Facebook's memories to see what awful stuff you said that day so you can delete it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 18:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But for her, it was Tuesday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jews got it from the Egyptians, I believe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 78.2K tweets

Why </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Planned Parenthood prevents more abortions than every religious fundamentalist in the US combined. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
