<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3093</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 08:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fine? I'm gay   have lots of tattoos but I MADE THE CHOICE to be these things openly period </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 05:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What gay people... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 05:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's funny to me is how so many SJWs are SO about being "sex positive" and are against "kink shaming" but GOD FORBID someone has a preference that excludes them, suddenly the tables turn  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 04:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one said it can't "be a thing." It just doesn't make you a part of the gay community, which is CORRECT. A real sjw would demand a "safe space" within the lgbt community all for wishing to have sex at the right time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 04:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah you CAN in fact do whatever you want. You just can't expect to be praised, coddled or even accepted along the way. It's a choice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 04:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

Omg that flair  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 04:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm Mel, 25, from Denver but living in Brooklyn now. I moved here to study Fashion Design   am also a full time intern at a design showroom in Manhattan. I'm gay, single, love going out   feel like my life couldn't get much further from the lives of the teen moms but still somehow I've always had mad love for it hahah. I think I just enjoy watching stories so different from mine, stories that make me see there's more to everyone than meets the eye both good   bad ya know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 23:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 25, Brooklyn   my roommate actually got me hooked haha. We bond over teen mom   she convinced me to make a Reddit just for this sub. I stand by it haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 19:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope I definitely meant misogynistic... The statement is basically saying to prefer just vagina, is wrong   that one must also accept penis. It's basically forcing men on people who are not attracted to men </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 08:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> who the fuck finds out someone uses tampons   thinks "DAMN THEY COOL!" ??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 08:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #ableist
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 08:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is this mindset not seen as INCREDIBLY misogynistic? Even further, one could say it perpetuates rape culture...to guilt someone into accepting penis despite their comfort or personal preference </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 19:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I CANT http://imgur.com/iBhPaiE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 01:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can't write without being an arrogant douche bag, don't. I'm a girl with feelings, that I simply felt more conveyed to express with some alcohol. Let it go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 20:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> xtuffguyx
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 14:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 14:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh believe me... You'd feel the cringe if you woke up realizing you sent it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 02:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you so much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 00:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I was actually pleasantly surprised </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 00:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you type out a message   type the name, it sends it soooo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 00:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but the number is still attached to the contact name. Believe me-if I could permanately delete the #, I swear I would. It'd save me a lot of shame haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 00:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WOAH yes how did you know!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 00:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> iPhones don't LET you delete #s permanently...like even if you delete the #, it'll still show up when you start typing their name or something which is TERRIBLE when drunk apparently  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
