<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1137</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 15:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im from Norway, so not too much ''rednecky'' shit around here. But i went to Alaska in 2015 with my brother and my dad, and two friends from the US. We had set us up at this camping place, and i was about to go to sleep. Then this HUGE black pickup truck with exhaust pipes sticking up on each side comes up and park oposite side. Two guys come out of the truck and put their shotguns on the truck and then they take out like 10 cases full of beer and they just sit there and drink beer and fuck around with their guns, and they left the truck running the whole damn night... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 15:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I did back when i was in school, I'd go upstairs away from everyone else (or at least somewhere you can be alone), and i would put on some cool nice music in the background and i would write down simple goals. For example ''In the first 30 MIN i should have learned this'', and so on. Maybe this could help you? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 18M Tips for losing weight! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 15:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys,

Im a 18 year old guy from Norway and i really wanna lose some weight now. Im a what i would call a big guy, im 117 KG or 258LB, and im 1.89 CM tall.
I try to go to the Gym twice a week, but im not too hard when i go there i usually have a light workout. In late 2014 i was 104 KG or 229LB, and i was pretty shocked to see how much i had gained over the past 2 years. This scares me because i didnt even really notice. I have no health problems as of now and i dont have any physical issues. All i really want to do is at least get back top 104KG/229LB, and i wouldnt mind going past lower than that. But I though that would be a good goal to have. I dont really eat too much shit outside the weekends, my mom makes homemade dinners and i tend not to eat too much. My main problem is how much i Drink. I hate eating infront of my PC, so i always end up drinking soda or chocolate milk, etc. I try not to drink soda during week days but sometimes i slip. Chocolate milk and stuff like that ''feels'' not so unhealthy even though it is, and i end up drinking it more often. 
I also work in IT so getting in shape is very important since I sit still alot! :( 
Does anyone have any tips on what i should do to improve? I know i have to start out by eating and drinking properly and cut down on unhealthy drinks! :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 10:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahahahahah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 22:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you get noone to draw it for free, i advise you to check out sketchmob.com
Someone there would be able to draw this cat! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 19:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 09:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your interest :) , but i've already got an artist for this project. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 08:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhh that sucks! Hope you'll find a better job!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 22:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> uhm..... what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 06:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ye sorry forgot to include that :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 21:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey dude! My hobby is CBRN equipment collecting and thats prety fun! Learning about these pieces, making articles on them and making videos on them is really fun! I've made alot of new friend over the interent thats into the same hobby and its so fun! Im not sure if you're into that but if you'd give it a try maybe you'd like it? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 23:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats awsome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 21:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks dude! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 21:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will do :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 16:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If i manage to buy it i'll upload a video of shooting it:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 15:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks dude, think im going to buy it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help to identify this rifle! Thanks! :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 09:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 17:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah i agree with you, its definetly a Maxim but without the armor plate.
Would make sense to be a captured one! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 14:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great photo, that a Maxim 1910 they're using? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 22:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks everyone who showed interest in this! Im so happy for all the response! Thank you! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 08:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your style was actually really cool! I think it could fit well! Could you send me a mail or message me here on reddit? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 06:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Paid Request] ''Project Hinoru'' Help me draw the ultimate drawing of my character! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 00:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys!

This will be quite a big project (at least i think it might be), cause there is alot of details that i want into this drawing. 
I want a drawing that includes this:


- My character
- Background
- Extra character


The style should be Anime/Comic or both, im open actually open to any style as long as I feel like it could work, so please
hit me up with your stuff! :)


So to give you a good idea of my character ''Hinoru'' here is the whole text i made when i was getting him drawn:


Hey there!


I've had a character in my mind for so long, and i've designed this charcter over a long time, in order to become awsome! The big problem is, that i can draw at all :( 
Thats where i need your help! Anyone out there who can draw Anime characters!
 

Now to explain my characters Personality (If it matters):


His name is Hinoru. He is a quitet calm man in his 30's. He travels the world alone. He enjoys strong alcohol and smoking his pipe. Not too many people know who he is by appearance, but his name has made its way all across the world. He is said to be the strongest man in the world, but noone really knows, since no human knows how his power works. Noone who has fought him have ever lived to talk about it. 


He is not a bad person. He travels in order to destroy evil, not just your every day evil like bandits, etc. Real hell evil. Vampires, sadistic murder clans, etc. He saves small villages from evil creatures and people. He never takes credits for doing any of this, he never asks for anything in return, he simply leaves. 


Now that you have a small image of what kind of dude my character is, this might help you draw him(?). 


Now over to the appearance, i have taken inspiration from alot of my favorite characters from different shows when constructing this character in my head.
Here is a link to an Imgur album i made, wich contain all the characters i have taken inspiration from, and so it could help you draw my character:


Imgur Album Link: http://imgur.com/a/JAGzt


Now to the details:


Body shape: Hinoru is a average tall man, he is not extremely tall but he aint short either. The 3rd Kazekages body shape is pretty much perfect, but Hinoru would be more muscular.
Eyes: I always loved how the 3rd Kazekages eyes so these are pretty much perfect. (And yes the black around the eyes can be added too).
Scars: No visible.
Hair: The 3rd Kazekages hair also fits good. would be nice if it could be a bit more thick.


Clothing:
Hat: No hat.
Jacket/Coat: I love the 2nd Mizukages kimono, i would love this but with different colors. Black with white stripes.
Under Jacket/coat: Just add some simple dark grey T-shirt or something, i dont really like the 2nd Mizukages dark green sweater. 
Pants: I like the casual 4th Kazekage, his pants would probably work fine. 
Shoes/Legs: I would like Hinoru to have Luffys sandals and the ''Bandages'' stuff at the same place as the 4th kazekage has it.
Gloves: No gloves.
Scroll: I would like him to have a big scroll haning from his back like Jiraiya has. 


Weapon: I would like him to have a Bisento like Whitebeard has. Adjusted to his size ofc.


Power: His power is the same as whitebeard. 


Use the pohots from Imgur as help and ask me any question :)
Whoever does this for me will have my thanks for ever! I will make sure to spread the name of the artist so others will know how good he/she is ! :)



Now that you have gotten to ''know'' Hinoru, it might make it easier for you to draw him! :)
Now im not too sure how i want the drawing to be, so here is all the scenarios i can come up with, and you could give me your thoughts on wich one would work best! :)


1. Hinoru sitting quietly at a bar (Bar is pictured in the imgur album), he is holding a small glass in his hand and a bottle of
vodka is standing next to him on the counter. In the back is the whole bar in flames and a big part of the walls and roof is missing, and in the middle
of it all stands one of the extra characters looking at Hinoru smiling.


2. Hinoru is swingin his Bisento against the extra character, blood is dripping from his face and his clothes are torn up. Fire and stone is everywhere.
The extra character is laughing/smiling and preparing a counter attack.


3. The extra character is holding Hinoru down. Hinoru is bleeding and is tired and bleeding. The surrondings is not too important here,
but it would be nice if it was inside the bar or in the woods.


4. The extra character is hugging Hinoru, he is staring into the air with a serious look in his face.


5. Hinoru is destroying the extra character with his power. (Whitebeards Power), he is swingin his fist into the extra character, 
creating cracks in the air and destroying everything. 


Thats some of the scenarios i've thought of, maybe you can come up with a better one?


Im willing to pay for the drawing! Would love for it to be around 1920x1080 so i can have it as my wallpaper, and in a high quality so it wont look bad.

Here is the link to the Imgur album containing all the extra characters and other refrence photos: 

http://imgur.com/a/syxy8


My E-mail is: haakon-rinor@hotmail.com

Plase send me a mail or comment on this post if you are willing to do this for me! Thank you so much! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 22:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks dude, your art is cool but not what im looking for sorry :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
