<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1143</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] Reddit, 4chan, Quora, and Tumblr are now their own countries. How's life in each? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 03:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 04:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, you don't know how long it's been since I found a good multi-part story! About the continuation, have you thought about explaining how John came to the future? Or what he's going to do now? Maybe go to France? Cause being a TA forever is kinda boring ;-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 01:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PLEASE WRITE PART 3!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 13:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its called Czechia now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dimes are smaller than pennies, but worth 10 times as much. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 00:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 03:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine trying to cut your grass with this power on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 03:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He will be remembered as a good president hindered by his enemies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 03:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bern it all down! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 13:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came here to say that, you beat me to it. The Winter War was pretty cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 00:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This made me think about 'nature vs nurture'. I've always wondered what plays a bigger part in ones personality. Guess in your story nature wins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 22:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably a mistake. I don't know how much you posted, but this is the latest for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 22:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Open markets with lots of stuff, many languages, curry, butter chicken, rain forests, scammers, mud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 02:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you are shadowbanned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 21:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wormhole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] Humans finally got in touch with extraterrestrial life. When we were telling them about God and Jesus, they said: "Oh that guy? Yeah we did that. He was one of our social experiments." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 21:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 17:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And we need **more space**!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 17:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! Especially when your trying to wash the dishes and the pan won't fit in the sink!! So annoying!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 17:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks strikingly similar to the volcano in [lava](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uh4dTLJ9q9o) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How come dandelions only grow on lawns? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 17:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never see them in the wild. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bet you can't guess my favorite hue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 16:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hue Jackman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious]At what age would you consider someone less attractive if they do not have sexual experience? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 16:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 21:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Search the top of all time prompt, you won't be disappointed. There was also a book called ship of fools published on Amazon. There are many great writers here. You'll find them eventually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5:How does a school lockdown protect students? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 05:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stupid question, I know. But it's something I think about. Everyone knows about school lockdowns and how they work. If someone wanted to hurt people they could just break the doors and windows of the school and go in. Students sitting in classrooms being quiet won't do anything. Why would they choose this out of all the methods as the best one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 05:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone sees something different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 05:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He rested on a hillside, back against a tree. It's the only tree on this hill, and this is the only hill overlooking the town. The sun is setting, painting the roofs of the houses below a brilliant gold. He cupped his chin and sighed, drowning in faded memories of this place. 

"Its been so long."

"And you've never come back?"

There was a rustle of leaves, as Rachel jumped down from the tree and sat beside him.

"No. I guess I wanted to preserve my memories here as a child. If I come back here as an adult, things will change."

He was reminded of why he left in the first place. An eager, young boy, sick of the dull life in the valley, itching to go out and see the world. So he took on an apprenticeship with a merchant that traveled around the land. His mother burst into tears when he told him, begged him not to go, fearing she'll lose her last son. But his father agreed.

"He has come of age Maria, and he needs to chose his own path to walk."

On the day of departure, he walked to the top of the hill, turned and waved to his family, and never looked back.

After a few years war broke out, and he was forced to flee to a neighbouring country. Then soldiers blocked the borders, and the roads leading home.

He wandered the lands as a travelling merchant, meeting many people and hearing many tales. He was always keen to hear those that origined near his hometown.

The war had finally ended, and the borders were opened again. He had not heard from his family in a long time. He hesitated, and then convinced himself it was better not to return. His home is here now, and that place should remain a memory. He didn't admit it, but there are truths he didn't want to find out. Months pasted, then years, and he found himself forgetting about his birthplace, busying himself with his daily tasks.

Now a worn middled aged man, he decided to come back. To be more precise, Rachel decided for him.

The sky is starting to fade purple, and the first stars are coming out. The windows down below started spilling warm, yellow light.

"Don't you want to go and meet them?" 

"I don't even know if they're still there." Some truths should remain hidden, at least for now. He wasn't sure he could face them.

"Come on. We didnt come all the way out here just to go back." 

She tugged on his arm. He didn't move.

"Let's go." He stood up, but to her dismay, started walking in the opposite direction. Seeing this town peaceful, intact was enough for him. Maybe next time. 

"But.." She started to protest, then thought otherwise.  

She looked at him thoughtfully for a while, then sprinted to catch up, as their shadows melted into the twilight.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 04:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weird, I though he time traveled with his wife as their honeymoon to help his past self. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do dandelions only grow on lawns? I never see them in the wild. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 13:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3 Rules for Rulers-CPG Grey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 02:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 04:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your stories are always a pleasure to read, and so expertly crafted! I think you mastered the art of writing(short stories at least). Don't ever stop. Ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shirtless guys dance behind reporter during Hurricane Sandy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 23:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you can't look on the bright side, then I will sit with you in the dark. ---Alice in Wonderland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 04:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 23:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What grade are you teaching? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You can effectively delete your Reddit history by deleting your account and immediately registering with the same name. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 22:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 04:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted a unique name without any meaning attached to it, so I went online and searched up random names until I found one I liked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 01:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being an awesome dad, of course! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 03:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gifs that are too long... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 06:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] You hold up your brand new phone to take a selfie, but you're not there. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 17:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 17:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you control the person, or are you only a watcher inside their body? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 16:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, you're back! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 03:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can read this! Hurray for duolingo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 23:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was around the 16th century. We don't do it anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One day Canada will conquer the galaxy... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 23:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And they'll call it the *Milky Eh*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 22:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My theory is that they ran out of unique names, so they added another name slot to make sure no names repeat!

...no that's not what happened 

A child's first name used to be either a family chosen name or the name of a saint. One day a family wanted both, so they put the chosen name as the first, baptismal name in the middle, and family name last. Later people gradually replaced the baptismal name with another chosen name, and that's where we are now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 22:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, past paper is more expensive but better? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 22:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, juggling languages just seem fun, especially when you're with someone who can understand all your languages. Some languages are better at expressing emotions and feelings, there are also idioms and proverbs that cannot be translated. 

Sometimes I only know a technical term or concept in one language, and feel too lazy to translate it. Other people in this thread also mentioned secrecy, using a different language to prevent people from eavesdropping. Mostly it's just because one language is better than the other at expressing what we want to say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 22:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anglophones are the ones who call people from the Netherlands 'Dutch'. They refer to themselves as 'Netherlanders'. In old English Dutch meant 'people', or 'nation'. People from Germany and The Netherlands were referred to as 'Dutch'. It is also why Germany calls itself 'Deutschland'. I guess the name stuck after all those years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 22:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only 8% of the world's currency is physical, the remaining 92% is all digital. I'm in no ways an expert, but I don't think this will impact the economy as much as you think. Banks would run out of money, and everyone would switch to online banking. It wouldn't cause major deflation in the economy, but a lot of people would be poorer.

Also, it would contribute to global warming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 22:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Alberta and Saskatchewan produce most of Canada's oil, thus producing a lot of carbon in the process. The carbon tax limits their business profit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5:Supposedly paper made a few centuries ago had better quality than paper nowadays, is this true, and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 22:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 19:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just sleep it off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 19:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Post something worth golding </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 19:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 19:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You hungry? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is on your copypaste board right now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 19:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 19:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> one step behind... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
