<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1397</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The problem tire is not the worst tire. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 21:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Al Jazeera America will shut down April 30 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 20:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pritzker 2016: Alejandro Aravena </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 15:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pritzker Prize will be announced in three days... What are your predictions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 00:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bonus: what are your wishes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GMOs are safe. Is this because GMOs cannot be made to be unsafe, or because what is released to the public is rigorously tested and vetted for safety? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 15:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Star Wars: Phantom Menace; George Lucas: "No one can beat Titanic..." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 05:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's not often these kind of Jewish music videos actually have great lyrics - and accurate references. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 03:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Explore 30 Years of Architecture in 22 Buildings [Architizer] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 22:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 16:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Hi)[/r/AWActivity] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The fish sticks need special cooking surface </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 07:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chrome on Android - when you hit 100+ tabs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 03:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Humor] Supercell these days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 04:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This will be the biggest year at the box office ever, because of Star Wars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 00:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clock is ticking on destruction of Chicago police misconduct files </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 04:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clock is ticking on destruction of Chicago police misconduct files </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 19:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clock is ticking on destruction of Chicago police misconduct files </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 19:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [IDEA] to help with the elixir drought at th9/10, SC should get rid of paying for walls with elixir. /s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 15:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would be in line with how they are going about things here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5 how and why did the idea of being radical become passive and something that is done to the person, rather than person doing it; ie "he became radicalized/she radicalized him"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 02:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't this kind of terminology remove agency from the radical? A kind of blame shifting, or blame distancing?

Where did this come from? Why do we do this? When did this start? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [HIMB] I had always meant to share my modified 'Manley Base.' This will be the last chance before the update, so... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 01:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] [RADIO] Chicago NPR a story about data and algorithm biases. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 04:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Within the last week or so, I heard a story on NPR about how we believe big data to be objective, but they are biased as well because of the bias of the makers. 

Very similar to this story : http://www.npr.org/sections/alltechconsidered/2015/06/07/412481743/what-makes-algorithms-go-awry


I think it was an interview. 


Things mentioned: 

Chicago pothole data collection by Android phones, biased towards younger wealthiest people with smartphones.

Putting disaster efforts towards places with most twitter activity, again, biased towards younger and wealthier


Hiring algorithm based on potential employer success and likelihood of long term employment, also could be biased.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ASK] with new sheild system, could someone buy a 1 weeks sheild and then attack 50+ times without depelting their sheid? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 19:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If each attack during a sheild reduces the sheild by 3 hours, then a 1 week sheild could buy you 50+ attacks, without getting attacked, and running the personal break thing, or am I missing something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Recruiting] Reddit November/ no required trophies or level/ farming, non-competitive, non-war </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 14:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi

Seeasea from Reddit November. We are not official, but have been around a long time. 

We are a very chill clan. No war, a refuge. 

We have no requirements on level, but many are mid/advanced. 

Join us and chill, have fun and enjoy game and camaraderie. 

#QC28LGL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [IDEA] DE should be in the TH, just like the 1k gold and 1k elixir. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 02:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the TH serves as a small reservoir, it should have like 10-100 DE (whatever the exchange is), as a small bonus, just like the Gold+Elixir. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5 how can a company dilute a shareholder's equity? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 05:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can a company make a shareholder's equity smaller?

ie, in this definition: http://www.investopedia.com/terms/d/dilution.asp

it says that a company is held by 100 people with 1 share each (1% equity per person), and the company could issue 100 new shares, which would halve the equity of each of the first shares to .5%.

Where is the company getting these new shares from, if the company is already 100% held by the older shareholders? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever tried getting an abortion by stepping on some toenails? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 04:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elon Musk: model s will have 600 mile range within 2 years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-26 00:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where can I get the best sandwich in the loop? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 04:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5 how did toilet training happen before indoor plumbing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-07 03:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] In an alternate timeline, other hominid species (ie neanderthals) have survived and developed alongside humans, it is now 2015. What is going on there? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 16:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

For the 'other' any hominid, more or less developed, if it serves the story, so neandethalis,  Australopithecus, africanesis, cro-magnon, red-deer-cave, etc etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that author/neuroscientist Oliver Sacks was a cousin to Nobel Prize Laureate Robert Aumann </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-30 17:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT Request: how to stop graze eating? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 01:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm always mindlessly snacking, always mildly hungry, how to break the cycle? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Summer of Science - Anyone (With a Ham Radio License) Can Call the International Space Station </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 02:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eli5 do certain industries have across the board terrible customer service? (Ie, cable, isp, airline, etc) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 04:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some industries, such as those in title, have a reputation for terrible customer service, regardless of vendor. And are notorious for the frustrating dealings with them. 

1) Why are some industries immune to the detrimental effects of bad services, while others (retailers, manufacturers, etc) are highly sensitive to customer service reputations? What makes them unique. 

2 why are those industries not really susceptable to competition differentiating themselves through customer service (or rather why those attributes not enough to be a real, immediate threat, ie T-Mobile, southwest)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Disney may sell ESPN as a standalone service like HBO Now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-28 02:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Disney may sell ESPN as a standalone service like HBO Now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-28 02:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone laser engraved their wooden moto x ( on their own) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 19:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got a moto x (2014) bamboo back. I got it now because it's cheap new as they clear stock. 

I have access to a laser engraver and was wondering if anyone had experience with engraving the back. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Glitch] Is it a glitch, or new rules? Sniping doesn't get league bonus? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 22:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am in master's iii, and my last two snipes (lucky me) have not produced a bonus. 

I this a glitch, or a new thing like the storage spell thing?

Screen shot:http://imgur.com/AV9V6uE

Just emailed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5 what is the job hunt, rsum, and interview process like at the CEO level like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 20:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would they use reddit in Peoria? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 15:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what was your best comment/submission that just didn't get anywhere (not upvoted, and not downvoted)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 08:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've had "most downvoted" and "most upvoted" threads, but what about most ignored...



Ever have the perfect comment/submission that was great and you know Reddit would love it, too, but then it's just ignored.

You get depressed, discouraged and wracked with self-doubt (or finally realize that you had been shadowbanned for a couple of years)

And vow to do better next time. 

Please share with us, and hope that being ignored didn't happen to you again... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit is losing the war against its own users </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit is losing the war against its own users </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do members of animalia trnf to only be savory while plantae have such huge range of flavors? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 17:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All flesh seen to be an umami? type flavor. 

While plants can be sweet (fruit, sugar) sharp (horseradish, mustard) sour (citrus) bitter (many leaves) heat (pepper) cold (mint) and many more (etc etc etc. 

Thanks for your time, guys. 

I was thinking about this, I was hypothesizing that perhaps plantae needed flavor (and color and smell etc) to attract and repel pollinators and predators, while animalia were able to use motion instead of attraction, and also not repel, but leave. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Welcome back, dear leader, spez </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 01:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is up with the "James Cameron is James Cameron is James Cameron" et.? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 23:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why are some things like Richter and Decibel measured in a non-linear scale? What benefit is there? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And wouldn't a linear scale be better for everyone involved to better comprehend scales?

thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that it you eat too much popcorn, you can contract a disease called popcorn-lung. It can be fatal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 07:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5 ipv4 vs ipv6 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 06:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do they mean, what do they do. In articles about them, comments say ipv4 have no more IP addresses, but ipv6 does, but ipv4 is better...why </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Strategy] early th 9. Should I save my elixir and de for update tomorrow or spend today on other stuff? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 18:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/Yvcmj5O

Here is my base. I have just started wall grinding, and was saving up for a de drill upgrade and an aq upgrade (now is 7). 

Should I do the drill and Queen, or wait?

I have both drills at level 4, its 4mm to upgrade. Have just over 6mm

Queen is 40k to upgrade, have 42k

Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Misc] will the new update fix the lollipop graphics glitch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 19:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine: http://imgur.com/a/1vIaQ


Thread:  http://www.reddit.com/r/ClashOfClans/comments/3amdsq/glitch_have_you_guys_faced_this_bug_before/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Newds] what do you think of the new overview screen? [Screenshot from galadon sneak peek] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 16:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MISC][BASE] how would you guys fix this base? It's too good.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 01:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/wyqBqxd


Sorry if this is a weird post. I'm a full time farmer, and new to th9.

So, the issue with my base is, is that whenever I don't get sniped, and people go for my loot, they end up with 38%, which means, that not only do I lose loot, I also don't get a sheild, and I'm losing more than I can farm.

Is there anyway you would weaken the base so that I could get the sheild easier, but at the same time not make it too easy, that I invite attackers to go for loot instead of snipe.

(I would put my defense history, but I have the weird lollipop graphic glitch)


Many thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] [Music] Russian music video. circa 2007/9. Female Singer, red things floating. chorus "Moosee, moosee poosee" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 17:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> generally in the title.

Russian pop song. Singer wearing red, walking through CGI of red rings or floating things of some sort.

the only words i recall (i dont speak russian), were a chorus with the "words" 'moosee, moosee poosee.'

thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [All TV] hardhome questions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 19:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all, I have a few logistical questions about the last episode, if anyone has the time. 

1. What killed all the people so quickly? Were they older wights that just slammed through the wildlings? Or was there some power that killed them all at once (the very rapid quietening behind the gates)

2. Were the zombies these old wights, or were they recently dead wildlings (did the wildling lady know the zombie kids)

3. What was the whit walker in the hut doing. He obviously was on a mission.  Was he looking for wildling elders? The dragonglass? Jon snow? Do ww know what's up?

4. Any map of the hardhome? It's difficult to tell from the episode where things where happening in the encampment. At first I thought the hut was deep in the center of the camp, bit during the end, it's clearly before the gates. Are the gates close to shore? Is the hut close to shore? 

5. Lastly, presumably, wun wun is one elder of a tribe of giants. Are there giant wights now?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gingers have no soul. Black people have a lot of soul. It must be a melanin based spectrum. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 21:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tunnel in an abandoned building in Gary, Indiana. I did't want to live the rest of my life anyway. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 19:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TV] Pseudo-Philosophy on identity and face within the GOT universe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 00:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Generally faces are connected intimately to identity. I noticed a lot of themes on this idea throughout.

For example, the unsullied have their faces nearly completely obscured by their helmet/masks, and when they become emancipated, essentially becoming individual humans with identity, Greyworm can remove his mask.
Here the abnegation of identity through the obscuring of the face is a mark of powerlessness and enslavement.

Another, Jaqen H'Ghar, has "no face," but here the obscuring of the face is a sign of power and freedom. Here to, we see the facelessness as an abnegation of identity, as we see that Arya needs to divest herself of this identity to free herself from the limitations of it.

Other "masks" and similar themes include, the Shadowbinders of Qarth, the Faces carved in Heart Trees (and Isle of Faces), the Stranger as one of the Seven, Sons of the Harpy...etc etc.

Now I feel like an elitist GOT fan theorist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm Gonna Push the Button - Teapacks [Tipex] - 2007 [music] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 23:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [All Spoilers] I thought this was obvious, but in talking to fellow fans, it isn't: My take on what is the overarching narrative in the last season </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 06:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **SORRY, ALL SHOW SPOILERS, ONLY. NO BOOK SPOILERS, PLEASE. *"



IMO, the last season is all about setting up the real battle to come: The battle of "fire" and "ice."

The setup is simply placing the characters where they need to be for the battle. Essentially, coincidentally, half the characters end up in the same place at the same time, and the other half at the other place at the that same time.

**Arya, Tyrion, and Varys** have gone across the narrow sea to Essos. There they join the obvious leader of "fire" **daenerys** and her supporting cast, including **daario, Jorah, Selmy** and her army of unsullied and more. 

On the "ice" side, we have **Jon Snow** the most likely ice leader, most recently joined by **Stannis** and his army, **Mance** and his army, also just reached that part is **Bran** and his small group, including **Hodor**. Also **sam** and **gilly** and the rest of the remainders up north.

Meanwhile, in the middle of these, we have **cersei** who has obviously been fucked by the recent events, accompanied by **Jamie**, and their people. Further north, you have the **Boltons** including **Ramsay,** And in between them, you have **Littlefinger** and **Sansa.**

So, essentially, you have two huge factions on either side, with some stuff in the middle.

Now for some speculation: Wouldn't the biggest fuck you to cersei be, that for all her machinations, when the big war comes, its all for nothing. she will be quashed like a fly between both sides. Same for the Boltons. 

Littlefinger can go either way, either his worminess can only get him so far, or he will always remain that guy in the middle who can play all sides of the game, and always come out on top.


Also, the Tyrells are obviously going to be important this coming season, but I have no idea what they will be all about, so, I can't really speculate yet. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] video of very high end rifle manufacturing process </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 23:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a video on submitted to reddit (forntpage) of a rifle manufacturing process. it was very produced (long form ad). there was part of it being made by robots, parts by hand, and there was also a portion of a guy in a suit hammering in a light filled niche, also, the stock(?) was hand-engraved with a very intricate image/pattern.

The comments suggested that this model of rifle was heirloom kind of stuff and began at $10,000. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the Nazis billed many of the Jews for the train fare to Auschwitz </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 02:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the Nazis billed some victims for the train fare to Auschwitz. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 02:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arnold Schwarzenegger takes a bubble bath, mid-1980s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 23:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [University, writing] 20 page paper, where to begin, setup? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 04:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need to write  20 page paper (art history research). Topic is very general, mass cultural media.

I have written plenty of 8-10 page papers, never 20. How do I approach such a long paper? What kind of outline am I looking at (ie, for 8 page paper, a possible outline is: 1 page introduction, 1 page thesis intro with at least 3 points, 3-4 pages flesh thesis with a page or two per point. 1 page reiterate and test/prove thesis, 1 page conclusion) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If all the taboos were nonexistent, and paying for sex became the standard, how much would you pay for sex? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 04:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And how often would you pay for it? Etc

How would you budget for it? Ie, luxury or necessity? Etc

QuantityQuality? Etc etc.

Basically, how much is sex worth to you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FCC to reclassify ISPs as common carriers under Title II </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 22:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FCC to brand ISPs as utilities under title II </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 22:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eli5 they don't show the commercials when streaming the super bowl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 01:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd think that they would make more money doing that, and that advertisers who pay so much would want to maximize the exposure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that despite a significant muslim community, Slovakia remains the only EU country without a mosque, and actively opposed building one. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 15:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5 what is the purpose of education in USA? Job prep or well roundedness? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 03:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> High school, college, etc.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if we invent adjustable size breast implants? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 23:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Car lovers of reddit, in your opinion, which car has the nicest ass? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 15:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I don't mean stupid things like dragon fu$$$$ cars. 

I mean just a great looking car from the back side.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sorry if this question is stupid: I was wondering if we do eventually get a spaceship to travel close to the speed of light (lightsail or whatever), would sensors be able to be quick enough to avoid or neutralize any obstacles as we hurdle through space? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 05:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that in 1992 the nypd (police) rioted and rushed the mayor's office for suggesting that there be an independent civilian board to investigate police brutality. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 05:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors from non-English speaking countries, what is the equivalent of knock-knock jokes in your language? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 06:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In the days of holes and outhouses, how did toilet training work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 21:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did it happen later in life than modern times (20-36 months) because of conveniece , safety and the skills required? 

Did perhaps they train toileting but still got accompanied until a later age?

Any experts on the subject here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No spoilers] the most unrealistic aspect of GoT... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 15:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jon and Pod are experts their first time. Inconceivable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The most unrealistic aspect of GoT: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 15:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comcast, without my permission and knowledge, adds services to my account and charges me extra for it. Details inside. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 20:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While in the end, it is not as bad, and slightly more complicated than it may seem, on principle the issue is still an stands.

Basically, I live in a condo which has a cable deal with comcast and it is included in my assessments, but I do not own a tv, and when I set up the account, I only set up with internet, which is not provided by the condo, and specifically said I do not want cable, and they were ok with that, and only signed me up for internet.

After six months, the "promotional" internet rate is over (but I did not know at the time). At the same time, Comcast decides to slip in "free cable."

cable customers do not have the same internet package costs, so my "free cable" ends up costing me money. While not as much as I initially thought, it is still shocked me that they added this "free" service, without my authorization or knowledge.

I did get the charges removed, just I think its important to show that Comcast will sometimes add charges and hope you won't notice. 

chat log: http://i.imgur.com/XCQyNTW.png?5

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Other Lives - For 12 [Indie/Folk] Not a widely known band, nice melancholic sound </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 02:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [AMA Request] one of the Israeli soldiers who calls targets to leave before blowing up their houses. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 14:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Without asking about if they think they are right or wrong etc, I just want to know what it's like making those phone calls?

**My 5 Questions:**

1.  Do the recipients beg not to? Or are they in shock and say nothing? Or do they yell and swear at you?
 
2. Do they attempt to negotiate or defend themselves?

3. What do you actually say? "Evacuate the premises please" or more "were coming for you"

4. Is it difficult to be on the phone with a victim? In war usually you don't ever have direct contact with a target, here you actually speak to them on the phone. I it emotionally difficult?

5. What happens if they don't answer the phone? Do you postpone the attack? Or do it anyways?

**Public Contact Information:** If Applicable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [All show spoilers] With all the depth and dimensionality of characters, including villains, so white walkers also have it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 21:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe they're just protecting their land? Why are they killing everyone? Religion? 

It seems that everyone can unite against them, do they have any redeeming qualities? Or just evil personified?

(PS I don't mind background exposition from books unless you're giving something major away) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [S4e10] with the family in ruins... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 21:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who is heir to casterly rock? (No book spoilers, please) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are the Wright Brothers equal? Or do we lump them togther for convenience? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 19:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They seem to always be lumped together. Were they equal? Was Wilbur the genius and Orville deadweight? Was one the engineer and one the businessman/marketer?

(Bonus question, do you believe they were first, or was Gustave Whitehead or Alberto S Dumont?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sorry to bother you guys, not even sure it's the right reddit, but I was wondering if you had any ideas as to why Hyundai and KIA in their foray into the luxury market didn't crate a new brand like everyone else? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-30 06:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> KIA and Hyundai both have made luxury cars, but have an uphill battle to fight with regards to convincing customers that they are serious car makers.

So why didn't they crate a luxury marque, like all other makers. (Chevy/caddi, Ford/Lincoln, Honda/acura, Toyota/Lexus, Nissan/infinity, vw/Audi) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is not yet a stereotype of your people, but should be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 02:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there something that your group or demo all are guilty of, or do, but for some reason is not a specific stereotype? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why are lethal injection drugs so complicated. Why not just give them an overdose of ambien or morphine? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-07 05:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are lethal injection drugs so complicated. Why not just give them an overdose of ambien or morphine? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-07 03:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5 Why is internet speed more important than available bandwidth for streaming quality? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-24 16:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We always seem to be talking about speed when talking about stream quality and the ability to stream HD/4K, etc. 

It seems to me that available  bandwidth should be more important: like so:

The movies are played at real time speed already (most of the time) higher definition streaming is simply MORE information at the same time and speed. (One second of video still is one second, but more information received and displayed at that time) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It seems that many people misuse 'average life expectancy' statistic. So, what is the metric that we are really looking for when we want to know how old people would live to in a specific time/place? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 06:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A question on religious ideas in the middle ages/Renaissance. Or the seeming oblivious hypocracy of Henry VIII </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 05:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Henry VIII was convinced that he was being punished for marrying his brother's betrothed, yet he never once seemed to blame any of his other sins, such as infidelity.

Were the views of religion different in those days to that extent, or was he somewhat deluded? Or what? 

This question also applies to many other non-specific ideas that we see through those periods where devoutly religious people seem to have had different morals than we would expect, but don't seem bothered by it. Could any of you shed some light? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5, why are so many tests and other metrics not done "out of 100?" (ie, SAT are out of 800 or 2400) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 05:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Examples:

GRE score is 130-180

SAT 890-2400

ACT 1-36

Transunion Credit Score 309-839

LSAT 120-180

Why are these things not simply 0-100? Why are the numbers seemingly so random, and why is the low often well above 1?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do we compare safety of various modes of travel in units of "distance traveled"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-10 05:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When comparing say safety of airline travel vs road travel, we compare it by miles. Why is that better than any of the other units such as:

Per passenger mile

Per trip

Per hour of travel

Or any of the other possible units.

Thanks. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The best Ferraris can go from 0-60 in under 3 seconds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 01:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a recent convert from iphone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-15 18:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can senses such as sight, smell and hearing be improved through use like muscles or brainpower? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-19 03:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sorry to bother you again r/chitecture. I have a bit of a school conundrum and humbly request advice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-11 02:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Skipping the whys and other complicated parts. 

I was studying at UIC undergrad (after deciding the cost value). Half way through the semester, I discover I have a bachelors degree already (in philosophy). So I had to drop out of school.

Now, to pursue graduate degree, I only have a month to prepare to apply (gre portfolio essay letters of recommendation. Etc)

I don't know if I can hustle that quickly. That means I won't begin my masters until September 2015, and graduating 2018. 

Currently I am 26 yrs. w 2 kids. I won't even finish school by 31/32 yrs. 

My goal is basic residential architecture in small local firms. 

Would it perhaps make more sense to get, say an assoc. degree from a community college, and get some crap job but work my way up through experience and time. 

This way I'll save on degree, get working much sooner (2015), and get experience which is the real learning? (And take a few yrs longer for licensing, which I am not yet set on getting anyways)

Or jump into the masters and get a "real education". (Yes I am aware of the crap job market, but it seems that most of the students I met at uic who studied at community colleges or high school have gotten pretty good jobs already at firms, it's a risk, but maybe ok? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What differentiates a great toddler/baby book from any old baby book? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-04 01:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ie what makes goodnight moon a classic? Or any other similar book? (Everyone poops, guess how much I love you, brown bear brown bear)

What do they have that others don't? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Serious question. Can I work without any background? (Explanation inside) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-15 02:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just started my 4 year undergrad arch. 

A month after starting, I found out that I already have a bachelors (don't ask how or why; unrelated field.). 

So now I have to pull out and apply for the (3 year) masters program.(no financial aid for post ba undergrad studies). 

The deadline to apply for next year is dec. no way I can get prereqs and gres and put together a portfolio in two months. So I need to apply next year to begin the year following that. 

This means I have now close to two years before I can even begin the masters program. 

Is there any way I can intern or work at a firm (I can do bitch work if that's what it takes)? I'm afraid I don't have a good portfolio, and I have only just started to learn the programs. But I am a very quick learner and think critically and analytically and good at problem solving. Etc. (I have tools but not mechanics). Or am a lost cause?

Any advice whatsoever? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happens to insects if transported some distance? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-18 04:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When a bee is trapped in your at, and it gets some 10 miles away, lets say, can it find its way back? Or is it stuck?

Ants? Non-colony dependent insects, such as roaches? How about if you take them out of their natural region (ie by plane). 

Thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5 baking powder and baking soda. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 04:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are they? (Are they related?) What do they do? How do they work? Where do they come from? How did we find this stuff out (history)?


Thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why hasn't anyone yet made a printer with normally priced ink and no drm type restrictions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 03:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surely if it the technology is available, competition is supposed to normalize prices.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quadro or GeForce? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 04:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> School laptop? 

Spend 950 and get a top of line but with a GeForce graphics, and 5400 HDd (plus ssd cache) or spend 1250 and get a quadro and 7200 HDd. 

Probably doing rvit and maya? No? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Going to school in fall; currently working for a large electronics retailer, what equipment should I be getting for school (now that I have a discount) beyond the required? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-09 02:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will a Wacom be useful? Hard drive? iPad? 

Anything? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Retail workers of Reddit: what song has forever been ruined for you by product demos playing over and over all day and drilled into your skull? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-08 05:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request for information: Is Pratt Institute worth it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 01:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More opinion than info, i suppose. 

I have been accepted at Pratt and at Spitzer (city college). 

Both 5 year b.arch. 

Pratt is 42k a year (offer 17k a year merit and 5k financial aid a year)

City is 10-14k a year. 

I want to be an architect and work for big firms (preferably with overseas assignments - I have the languages) for 10 years or so and then move into a small local firm (my own or otherwise). 


Is the name Pratt worth the cost? (Ranked 10, city not even ranked (it is accredited) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hasidic bochur Harlem shake  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-15 22:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harlem shake -Hasidic  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-15 22:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Employees of large tech companies: Do you have up to date hardware and software? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-12 15:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most large companies tend to have dated hardware and software because it is expensive (and not entirely necessary) to replace 30,000 computers every two-three years.


Does this apply at places like amazon, Facebook, Microsoft, google, dell, intel etc etc?

Or because they are tech related, they want to ensure that tech is up to current standards all the time for all employees?

(Also, many internal enterprise software have bad GUIs that take some training to use, because it is not intended for public use. Do tech companies invest to make graphically nice, and user-friendly and intuitive? Or same old?)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If a friend disappeared, how would attempt to find him? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 21:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In response to disappear question. 

Also, relevant to my own friend. 

I had a friend who slowly faded from our circle. No one has heard from him in about two years. 

His phone was disconnected, email accounts/facebook deactivated etc. 

The only remnants is a year and half old dating profile. 

Right before disappearing, we suspected drug use. Also, he is not a US citizen, so he perhaps is avoiding the authorities. 

That is all speculation. 

While he may not want to be found, I just want to know that he is ok.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any guidance counselors for people out of high school? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 05:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I understand, counselors can take a look at your background, scores and strengths etc, and can honestly recommend schools to attend.

I am long out of school, and have a unique-ish background, and wanted to know if it is worth my time and money to apply to certain schools that may be out of my reach.



Are there any such services?

Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are respectable schools? There seems to be a dearth of information.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 05:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The list of best schools from design intelligence cost a lot, and also lists by various obfuscatory categories. 

I simply want to know if certain colleges are considered good. 

Like everyone knows MIT, Harvard and cooper are top or so. 

Everyone knows Syracuse is also.

But are Pratt parsons or spitzer?



Basically, I know most firms recruit  locally, but what schools have more national reputations?

Maybe 10-20 schools. 

Thanks

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the worst song by your favorite band/musician/singer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-11 16:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alternatively, best song from your least favorite band/singer/musician </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the chances we will see an individual trillionaire in the next 50 years? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-25 17:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In USD. Barring any collapses of the system.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why don't elevators have a cancel call/floor feature? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-20 04:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gaza complains of food shortages, yet their weapon smuggling network is clearly effective. Why aren't they smuggling food? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-16 20:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Devil's advocate: I was sitting in bed wondering what are some legitimate gripes against Obama/dems 2012? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-21 08:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not so much what *you* don't like about him, and more what do gopers dislike, and you would agree that obama was wrong


Not so much civil rights issues, and drones, as many conservatives may not be against it. 

More along the lines of Obama flipped on public financing in 08 because it was expedient at the time. Etc
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Minding the Gap in Crown Heights: Four Carribean-American High School Students' Journey to Understand the Hassids they Share Neighborhoods with [Video] [10:41] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-03 22:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [bug] I am not 100% sure if this is a RES bug, and I did not find it submitted: Moderation page; List of reddits- weird bunching of buttons [see pic] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-03 18:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - RES Version: 4.1.0
- Browser: Chrome
- Browser Version: 18
- Cookies Enabled: true
- Platform: Windows

http://i.imgur.com/trYwi.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Minding the Gap in Crown Heights: Four Carribean-American High School Students' Journey to Understand the Hassids they Share Neighborhoods with [Video] [10:41] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-03 18:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Minding the Gap in Crown Heights: Four Carribean-American High School Students' Journey to Understand the Hassids they Share Neighborhoods with [Video] [10:41] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-03 18:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does Medieval art seem to be so childish and unskilled? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-30 18:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Update: I got the Job! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-30 17:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> update to: http://redd.it/rhixx

I got the job! 

While not the specific position I was hoping for, I did get a **30% wage increase** per-hour over my previous job and then all these other goodies:

**health, dental eye insurance** for the whole family  for under 100 a month (no benefits available at all in my previous job)

Plus **overtime 1.5** (I wasn't allowed to work overtime in my previous job)

Plus **paid vacation** (not available in my previous job)

and **then some**...!

I start may 7 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukraine bomb blasts injure dozens ahead of Euro 2012 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-27 18:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukraine bomb blasts injure dozens ahead of Euro 2012 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-27 18:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Relaxing Bathroom [616x462] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-27 00:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cooper Union Will Charge Tuition for Graduate Students [x-post from NYC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-25 23:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who was the most successful investor in the Bible? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-23 18:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Bithiah](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bithiah):

She pulled a prophet from a rush on a bank. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey r/cad! Sry to bother you guys. But does anyone know any summer drafting courses in NYC? (xpost) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-23 02:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 


Basically, I'm planning to do architecture. I have been advised that perhaps the ideal route would be to learn drafting, then work at a firm to gain experience, and also to experience architecture at work, first hand. This could allow someone to get into architecture school with open eyes and grounded in reality. 


So, it's almost summer: anyone know of any classes for drafting here in NYC?

(also while I have your attention, any thoughts on taking this route to architecture?)

Thanks for your time, r/cad, 

Seeasea  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know of a good drafting/autocad summer course in NYC? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-23 01:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the education and career advice is not very popular here on rchitecture. So sry about that. 


Basically, I'm planning to do architecture. I have been advised that perhaps the ideal route would be to learn drafting, then work at a firm to gain experience, and also to experience architecture at work, first hand. This could allow someone to get into architecture school with open eyes and grounded in reality. 


So, it's almost summer: anyone know of any classes for drafting here in NYC?

(also while I have your attention, any thoughts on taking this route to architecture?)

Thanks for your time, r/chitecture. 

Seeasea  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are Queens addresses so long and weird (3-4 numbers followed by a dash and another 2 numbers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-20 17:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A: "would you pay x for y media service" questions are often posted.

B: Netflix has limited streaming library due to licensing cost.

c: I would gladly pay 100.00+ a month for access to every video or show ever (more than 10x the current cost), would you?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-18 22:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People today are paying that just for cable, on top of Hulu+ and Netflix and other subscriptions.

Imagine if you could get all that in one place?

Netflix says it is too much money for licensing each movie, but I would gladly pay ten times the current cost to add more movies to the library, and consolidate my subscriptions.

What would the studios realistically charge? And what would you realistically pay for everything?

Bonus: What about for gaming? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ikea Ad for Uppleva, all-in-one entertainment system [x-post from r/technology] [Female] [Accent] [Unintentional] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-17 17:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey, Jews of Persia, there's a big meetup in Jerusalem to rebuild the temple. Eff the Samaritans.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-01 15:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "It is as if the RNC decided to take an incredibly serious and successful argument that has the chance to produce a pathbreaking legal victory for a conservative interpretation of the Constitution, drag it through the mud, and vomit on it." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-30 20:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Dean Pelton (community) was on Friends (finale) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-29 17:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stand your Ground and the Burden of Proof </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-28 21:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Generally, the burden of proof is on the prosecution.

However, in a situation where the defendant admits to causing damage/death, should the burden of proof perhaps move to him, that he must prove that he acted in self-defense.

Basically, in order to cause damage (send to jail, get money, send to the chair) to someone, you need to prove that he is guilty. 

However, in a situation where the damage is *already* done, we move the burden of proof away from the damager, and onto the damaged.

Is this right?

Potential pitfalls: In a situation of actual self-defense, we are now placing an undue burden upon someone acting *legally* to prove it. 

I cannot wrap my head around this issue.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After two years at a soul crushing, low paying dead end job, I finally got the courage to send out a resume. 

On first attempt, I got a call back for an interview! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-28 15:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I got the call less than ten minutes after emailing my resume! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A good roundup of articles on the Healthcare SCOTUS case. (from beginner to in depth) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-26 16:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A good roundup of articles on the Healthcare SCOTUS case. (from beginner to in depth) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-26 16:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snuggles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-22 16:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Firefox, tabbed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-21 20:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flip </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-21 20:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Waves </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-21 20:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Death to the McMansion - A magic fix: Tax resources instead of income. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-21 18:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A vertically-challenged fortune-fortune teller broke out of jail... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-21 17:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is a small medium at large. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crooked Forest - Poland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-21 17:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It was reported that someone broke a hole through the fence at the nudist colony... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-21 16:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The police are looking into it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Full Length Episodes of Mr. Rogers of Neighborhood.

Mmmm.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-20 22:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we talk jobs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-20 18:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a thread that comes up often, so, sorry about that.

I am at the point in my life where I need to decide just what the **** I'm going to do with myself.

My whole life, I have dreamed of being an architect. However, as we all know, money isn't great, jobs are scarce, and the hours suck.

What related professions would allow me to enjoy this, with less schooling debt, and more job opportunities and more money.

1)
For example, I theoretically can become a carpenter/woodworker, and from there work up to contractor/develepor, each dealing heavily with building homes (also, can design furniture) , however, I am not great with my hands/physical labor.

2)
Or, looking online, there seems to be job called "building designer," basically an architect for small projects, which doesn't require much schooling (and according to salary sites, makes more money), and the truth is, that is much more what I have in mind with my fascination architecture (traditional single family homes), but the job seems to be somewhat lame/non-existent (only exists on career info sites and wikipedia, and certifying agency)

3)
Draftsman. Doesn't make much money, also not getting to actually design

Anything else that I can do? Or if I love architecture, its worth it, and will make not a lot of money, but enough to live off? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uncle Frank and the Co-defendants, "Lost in the Underground" [jazz/rock/spoken word] [2011]

He is my 80 year old (real) uncle. I think he is awesome.

The album is free to download from the page. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-19 22:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey Reddit, my 80 year old uncle has a band "Uncle Frank and the co-defendants" (jazz/rock/spoken word thing). I think he is great, let me know what you think... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-19 21:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weird Question: Why do we prefer light sodas over dark sodas when out of breath? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-16 16:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that vampire bats practice "reciprocal altruism." If one bat couldn't find food, it will beg others, and they will share. Also, if a bat is orphaned it will get "adopted" by others in the colony.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-15 22:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chabad Rabbi and Hooker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-15 18:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-15 17:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Evening Traffic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-13 17:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some interesting questions that the mandate to cover contraception raises. (not religious questions) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-06 20:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are condoms not included in the healthcare mandate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-06 20:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> contraception is not *only* a women's health issue. Additionally, condoms are highly effective at controlling the spread of STDs.

Should the insurance companies not be required to provide these free of co-pay? 

(And in the long run probably save the insurance companies money by preventing pregnancies and STDs) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yahoo typos have gone too far </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-06 19:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You Singaporean? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-01 22:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5 Why it is more "fair" for everyone to pay a proportional tax than a set amount which everyone pays equally? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-29 20:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this is a stupid question.

I fully understand why it is more fair for everyone to pay, say 10%, instead of everyone contributing a straight $1000.00. (these numbers are for illustrative purposes only).

However, I was suddenly at a loss of being able to articulate clearly *why* this is more "fair."

Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was not aware that Israelis were banned. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-22 23:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IAmA ordained Hassidic/Ultra-Orthodox Rabbi, AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-21 19:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you ever wanted to know what we do, think etc. questions, hit me.


Edit. Sry last minute, have to run. 

I will answer the rest of the qs in the morning. 

Was fun. Maybe do it again on a later date? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HI </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-17 16:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> YSK that on gmail, switching between multiple accounts is easy. Just change the URL from 0,1,2... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-16 16:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Changing accounts on gmail for me is annoying, so many steps, and usually slow.

click username, click switch account, click account to switch to. etc.

I realized that the only difference in the URLs is a number:

https://mail.google.com/mail/u/0/#inbox

https://mail.google.com/mail/u/1/#inbox

https://mail.google.com/mail/u/2/#inbox

So, just change the number in the URL, and easy. 

Even better, the end part of the URL is unnecessary, just erase it and change:

https://mail.google.com/mail/u/0

https://mail.google.com/mail/u/1

https://mail.google.com/mail/u/2

eventually, your URL predictor will figure this out, and when you go to gmail, the options will be there to go there directly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trying to come to conclusion. Is food dye safe for kids? Is there a consensus? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-10 20:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With all the freedom bills come and gone (or stayed) in the last 10 years, which one is the worst? ACTA, SOPA, NDAA, Patriot act...

AKA, if you could get rid of one SINGLE law passed in the last 10 years, which would it be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-08 21:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Extended to presidential powers and supreme court rulings and other similar things (ie guantanamo bay, torture, citizens united, TSA, etc.)

What is/will be the biggest imposition on our freedom? If you had the ability to remove one, and only one law/provision/ability passed/ since sept. 11, 2001, which one would you choose? why?


I think the torture one, this horrifies me more than any other, but not necessarily rationally. The one that currently affects me the most is TSA, so I am leaning that way.

I would like to hear what you guys have to say.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Durbin is a co-sponsor of PIPA, Kirk has not taken a stance...come on guys. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-13 19:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I called, I asked them if they have been getting calls, durbin has been getting "a couple both ways." and kirk's staffer didn't even know what it was.

Call now.

Kirk : 202-224-2854 then press 3 then press 1 to speak to someone.

Durbin : 202-224-2152

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Funny question: "nominated" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-05 19:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you need a a little cry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-26 23:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why didn't American style slavery never take hold in Western Europe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-16 18:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it kind of that they all knew it was wrong, but they didn't care as long as it wasn't visible (all in the colonies, or like today: bad labor conditions overseas doesn't seem to bother most people, as long as it isn't local).

Or is there some other factors that prevented it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Beautiful-Beautiful Home-Library. And finally, roomporn that is accessible to most people. [1984x1488] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-16 00:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> beautiful rustic-modern kitchen [721x1024] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-14 22:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I did not have sexual relations with that room [530x633] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-14 22:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Simplist Bedroom [x-post from r/RoomPorn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-14 17:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey guys? Do you think its perhaps time to move past the resolution requirement in the title? Hear me out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-14 16:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [here](http://www.reddit.com/r/earthporn/faq#Whyarewesupposedtoincludetheresolution) in the FAQ it states the following two reasons for including the resolution in the title:

* To find quality wallpapers

* So that your computer shouldn't be overtaxed by massive photos. 

And in [this quote](http://www.reddit.com/r/PornOverlords/comments/k9kte/official_vote_thread_should_we_get_rid_of_the/c2iyogh) it says the tag is for search purposes.


However, perhaps we have moved past wallpapers, and it is more high-quality photos (iregardless of resolution).

* See [here](http://www.reddit.com/r/MetaPorn/comments/jbke3/minimum_resolution_for_porn_pictures/c2askui) a moderator saying that we it is not a wallpaper network, 

*  See [here](http://www.reddit.com/r/MetaPorn/comments/jbke3/minimum_resolution_for_porn_pictures/c2jv8rv) a moderator saying how, even with a resolution req. it is mostly not usable as a wallpaper source. (but wanting to return to its original state)

* And [here](http://www.reddit.com/r/PornOverlords/comments/hd7f1/anyone_else_rage_hardcore_because_people_submit/c1uotl3) a moderator saying that the resolution is not the important thing, rather the image itself.

Additionally, in several instances ([1](http://www.reddit.com/r/MetaPorn/comments/jbke3/minimum_resolution_for_porn_pictures/), [2](http://www.reddit.com/r/PornOverlords/comments/na8u8/discussion_minimum_resolution_for_images/)) when mods wanted to establish a minimum resolution requirement, they decided against it. This partially removes the wallpaper reason.

Also, they have already have done away with the [resolution requirement](http://www.reddit.com/r/PornOverlords/comments/k9kte/official_vote_thread_should_we_get_rid_of_the/) for videos. Most of the reasons given are perfectly applicable to images just as well. The top three comments on that thread are:

 1. 1.  [I don't see how this compromises the quality of the network.](http://www.reddit.com/r/PornOverlords/comments/k9kte/official_vote_thread_should_we_get_rid_of_the/c2ijwvh) 
2. [To me, it's an unnecessary requirement and may deter users who don't know how to find the resolution from posting.](http://www.reddit.com/r/PornOverlords/comments/k9kte/official_vote_thread_should_we_get_rid_of_the/c2ik4fw)

3. [It is easier.](http://www.reddit.com/r/PornOverlords/comments/k9kte/official_vote_thread_should_we_get_rid_of_the/c2iixyh)

Finally, do you, or anyone you know, use the search by resolution function for wallpapers? Honestly, if I am savvy enough to search by resolution, I would also be savvy enough to simply find the best picture and use google image search to find a higher resolution. Also, images too large? The current issues seem to be the opposite, images too large are so rare that I don't think this would be an issue. (esp. because interactive photos are banned).

Perhaps the porn network is now established enough to move beyond this requirement? I think its users are familiar with the overall point of the network (high-quality images, no memes etc) that they would vote based on quality of the image (including resolution), and not on other  (non-porn-network) factors. 

There are downsides, however, I feel the upshot is far more worth it:

a) It makes it more accessible to users. (myself included, it is a hassle for me to get the resolution, keep tab open, hover over tab, go back to submit thing, put in the resolution, double check to make sure its correct...)

b) I am certain that much of the moderation work goes into resolution work, this would greatly reduce the workload of the mods

c) following b) it would allow the users to feel that the network is more democratic, more hands-off moderation, which seems to appeal to users (though [this](http://www.reddit.com/r/TheoryOfReddit/comments/mj0ln/active_moderation_vs_the_laissezfaire_approach_or/) syncretic submission and ensuing discussion on this topic is worth a read)


What do you guys say?


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Industrialist style Bathroom. I like. [518x640] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-14 00:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Light Kitchen [567x850] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-14 00:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Simplist Bedroom [600x836] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-14 00:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Holkham Hall Family Library [600x400] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-09 17:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jordan Staircase, Winter Palace, S. Petersburg [1024x772] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-08 22:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comfortable Luxurious Bedroom [800x536] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-08 20:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Open courtyard at an angle in an open plan home [1280x868] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-07 16:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Room with a View [1098x732] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-07 16:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am at my wits end, can you guys help? lost luggage in August on airline, they have yet to return the luggage or reimburse me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-06 22:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I flew on Royal Jordanian Airlines in August.

They lost my luggage. Fine.

I report my luggage lost at my destination airport. In that airport they contract out their luggage handling services.

They have no information. Everyday during my vacation I called them, and they told me they have no info.

When I return from my vacation, I begin the process of getting my reimbursed. They will only reimburse $20.00 per Kilo, about 1/4 the replacement value. (not an issue, my cc will cover the rest) They say that they must wait until 21 days have passed without luggage before they give up.

After 21 days, they still say "no information." 

My wife visits my home airport to check the various Lost and Founds there in person. No Luggage.

I ask the airline for reimbursement. They tell me that because I filed the original lost report with their contractor, the contractor is the only one who can authorize payment.

After much haggling, and them ignoring my emails etc. They finally conclude that they returned my luggage to me already.

This is not true. In fact, on the date that they tell me that they returned the luggage to me, I was no longer in that country.

I ask them for information regarding this alleged delivery.

They then respond after some cajoling, that my luggage is in my home airport.

I confirm with the airline's local airport liaison that it is not there, and also that the luggage never was there.

I have since not heard back from them, even after repeated phone calls and emails.

What can I do? 

(If I try to reverse the charge of my ticket on my cc, they will give me only the amount that the airline would have payed, but it would cancel out my cc insurance for replacing the rest of the money)

It seems that I cannot sue them either, because the contractor and the airline are both foreign companies. 

**TL;DR** Airline lost my luggage, no reimbursement coming. What can I do?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> amazing Minimalist Home Office facing Courtyard. [750x1011] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-06 18:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monster among the Frum: A tale of the Ultra-Orthodox community and of a boy who was kidnapped and cut to pieces by one of their own. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-05 20:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Photo of 4500+ Hassidic Rabbis at the world's largest gathering of Rabbis [2200x1090] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-05 19:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Living Room with views of the Icelandic countryside (Casa G) [880x1348] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-30 23:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Indoor infinity pool (z house, dk) [1280x667] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-28 18:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Plain white room [640x480] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-28 18:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My mail has gone extra wonky </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-23 20:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cannot be sure if it is a reddit or RES issue.

In my settings, I have "click to mark as read" 

Now, if I click on a message in order to mark it, the page from that message down starts vibrating rapidly (up and down motions).

If I reload the page, or open a another program, it stops, however, the messages remain marked as unread.

I use chrome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Barack Obama </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-23 19:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Charlie Chaplin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-23 18:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Carey Grant and Katherine Hepburn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-23 18:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hermann Goering </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-23 18:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
