<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1474</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 04:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They continually get rescued at the beach </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 04:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Vegemite on toast with butter, Vegemite worlds richest source of vitamin b, hangovers also caused by lack of b vitamins. If you are not Aussie you will hate it but trust me it works every time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 09:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you chop down below too?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 16:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All are internal bruises  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 16:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the former </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 16:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do the fuckey fuckey and you turn around </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 02:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How was working with tim Robbins in shawshank?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 15:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Innaloo serious, it is a shithole of a place too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 14:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually did this today, almost. Was on the edge in peak hour traffic coming home, stuck for almost twenty minutes, sweating hard, contemplating either shitting myself or pulling over on the freeway and hanging one out the door.

Had to loosen my pants to ease the pressure, was determined to make it home. Was slapping my self in the face trying to zen monk control my body into not realising the garbage inside me.

Finally made it home after speeding when I could. Pulled into my driveway, jumped out pants still undone, they fell down, had to bend over to pick them up which begun my arsehole telling me enough was enough! 

Sprinted to the front door as I could feel the shit coming out, fumbling with the keys I wasn't going to make it. I look around my all concert and brick courtyard for somewhere to shit. My brand new esky was there open just cleaned ready for the weekend. I disgraced that esky, I can never no matter how much I clean it, put food back in it. 100 dollars down the toilet literally  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
