<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2423</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 00:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Andy Serkis in dog face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but currently I feel they all have plot armor to an extent. King Ezekiel is another one I was thinking has plot armor. That expensive tiger of his though...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your watching TV wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also Negan, Carl, Michonne, Daryl, Maggie, Carol, Morgan. 

There's probably more that I'm forgetting too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 06:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A joke isn't a joke unless you firmly establish the proper decorum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 05:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> U need 2 instruct them and show them The Ballad of Ricky Bobby oar u fail as an instructor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 05:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only way Aquaman is getting posed is fighting his [arch enemy.](https://thebuzzkillblog.files.wordpress.com/2014/06/3488342-aquaman.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 05:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 01:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do or do not, there is not try, and you needs to shut up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 01:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun fact: There are more 11 year old on Reddit these days that weren't even around when The Office premiered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 07:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could have done without knowing there was another one of these awful reality shows out there that was big enough for SNL to lampoon it. These shows really are the bottom of the barrel on TV. I had to work on captions for a similar looking show and it was terrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 07:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one aimed at the Bible Belt demographic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 07:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is shallow, but my main gripe with Love is that I just don't buy that there are so many women that are seriously into Gus, physically and personality wise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 06:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess you could say Zendaya is *Stepping Up.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 05:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to think of it as a worse version of FXX's You're the Worst. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 04:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it picked up again in Season 5, after two hit and miss seasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 03:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He said recently that his Trump had an expiration date sometime soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 02:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how he'll end his tenure as the So Called President? I'm thinking he'll keep making appearances through the end of the season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 01:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Legion fades out... Fargo fades in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 01:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me neither, but the article I read got that information from someone involved in the show. I wish I could remember where I read it so I could link it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 01:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #I'M... CON...STIP...A...**TED!!!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 01:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read somewhere that David Haller is the only character pulled from the comics, and the rest are Hawley originals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 23:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loudermilk is a classic Hawley name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 23:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To echo those that have gone before me:

#**YOU'RE DOING IT WRONG!**

#^YOU'RE ^DOING ^IT ^WRONG!

^^YOU'RE ^^DOING ^^IT ^^WRONG!

^^^YOU'RE ^^^DOING ^^^IT ^^^WRONG!

^^^^YOUR'RE ^^^^DOING ^^^^IT ^^^^WRONG!

^^^^^YOU'RE ^^^^^DOING ^^^^^IT ^^^^^WRONG!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 23:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you managed to get through the first season you've probably got Stokholm Syndrome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 23:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude it's on FOX. The best we can hope for is that it isn't as fucking awful as Gotham is.

Matt Nix is behind it, so hopefully it's as entertaining as Burn Notice was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [QUESTION] Is there a way to import saved data from previous seasons of TWD into the new season? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 22:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just found out there's a new season of Telltale's The Walking Dead, and I was wondering if there was a way to import save data from my PS Vita to a PS4.

I don't feel like starting from scratch again, so if there isn't I'll probably wind up passing on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 03:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/stopleaving </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only ever used fast travel to find the Power Cells for the Ancient Armor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, that foliage just *screams* sex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Invincible? It's looking pretty vincible in that shot right there!

Amazing shot by the way. If I was able, I'd probably snatch up at least one of these QS Iron Men. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They need to vacuum that store. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 00:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't look safe at all. I wouldn't be surprised if people who are talented enough to make this wound up pricking themselves with those things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've probably turned off your inbox, but if by chance you see this, you should watch You're the Worst on FXX or Hulu. I think you'd like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit dude. If anyone's got a bias, it's you. I've watched all the fucking movies, and these are my own opinions. If anyone's missing the point it's YOU. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last night she sat down to watch a DVD of Alias. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 06:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's never gonna happen, I know, but I had fun making that wish list. 

If NECA made them, Mac and Dennis would come with Predators, and the rest would come with yellow Aliens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 06:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thunderjaws are nothing compared to the Rockbreakers that burrow underground. I hate those fuckers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SH Figuarts: Please make It's Always Sunny in Philadephia action figures </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 06:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mac: Comes with Asspounder 4000, beer, several hands, alt head.

Charlie: Includes bat, dead rats, several hands, bag for huffing paint/ glue, alt head with silver paint, beer.

Frank: Includes beer, gun, alt head with wig, several hands

Dennis: Includes DENNIS system, his tools, hands, alt head, beer.

Dee: Includes DVD copy of Alias, beer, hands, alt head, ostrich.

I need this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 06:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again, also, no idea what awesome or confusion technically is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 03:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just talking about the Marvel Cinematic Universe V the DCEU. This isn't including anything that isn't apart of the MCU or DCEU. So while I absolutely adore The Dark Knight trilogy, it, thankfully, has no bearing on the DCEU (MoS, BvS, Suicide Squad). 

So if I compare the first three MCU movies (Iron Man, Incredible Hulk, and Iron Man 2) versus the first three DCEU movies (Man of Steel, Batman V Superman, Suicide Squad) the Marvel movies are CLEARLY, better movies, because they make sense, they're not overly long, and they have charismatic characters.

To be honest, I'm having a little trouble tracking your train of thought because you keep bringing up The Dark Knight Trilogy as if it's related to the BvS universe, when it is in fact not. So I'm not sure if you think I have a problem with TDK trilogy, because I don't. Those are great movies, and are on a different level than the MCU movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 00:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, I'll take formulaic Marvel films that are coherent movies over the current crop of poorly conceived DC movies designed to be "different" from the Marvel stuff, but wind up turning into poor imitations.

Anyway, sorry to derail your thread. Those DCEU figures are nice, but I just can separate them from the source material. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 00:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just make the next Wolverine Laura. In a few years Dafne Keen will look old enough to pal around with the X-Men from last years film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 00:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iron Man 2 has it's problems, but at the very least it's got wildly entertaining performances by the cast. BvS had a bunch of dudes brooding, a bad script, a convoluted plot, and a bloated runtime. The worst thing I could say about Iron Man 2 is that being forced to expand the MCU handicapped what could have been a great Iron Man sequel. Thankfully they rectified that with Iron Man 3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much based on the movies being critical failures. I've seen BvS twice, the theatrical cut and extended edition, and I thought it was awful on both counts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The BvS figures included make it more like Avengers, legends of DC Comics and the cautionary tales of DC Comics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, lots of people here have been triggered by the valid rich white guy appropriating Asian culture critique, when it sounds like that's the least of the show's problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She looks Hela hot, IMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They got Cate Blanchette with the budget! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's in the credits for literally every episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 04:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it ends I won't be too bummed. Most of what I want is coming in the Rebirth JL set. My only gripe is the lack of accessories and hands. I'll also be picking up Jon Stewart, Supergirl, Nightwing and the Doomsday pack and the sidekicks pack.

Oh, and Lex and the other Wonder Woman, mostly for the accessories and hands. I'm pretty much gonna focus on the Superfamily and the Batfamily with this line.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, based on the real-time dynamic of the show's storytelling, you knew she would succeed. There needed to be a successful attack show what the terrorists were capable of, up the stakes, and move the plot forward. 

Also if they had failed, that thread would have been a bigger waste of time than it already was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are both of these the 1:12 Collective figures? If yes, it looks like they aren't in scale with each other, cuz Punisher's head looks a lot bigger than Daredevil's. Daredevil looks smaller altogether. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Interview (2014) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 07:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 05:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mary Sue has basically become a derogatory term for women in fiction who can do things competently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ggggggggggg </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 04:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the real answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 02:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, you should just dive in headfirst. Hell, why not watch the final episode of Breaking Bad before even starting the first season! It'll all make sense!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 00:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They sell SPEED WEED on the side. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 19:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of that stuff is used for crafting pouches though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 06:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So were the other kids have comic counterparts? Most of all, I wanna know if the fat kid was Storm's kid. I think he was the one that was shooting lightning out of the tips of his fingers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 06:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey man, we just wanted a Logan Megathread. Thanks for putting it up. Should have thanked you earlier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 03:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So he's crashing starships, bub? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 02:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't want to see that type of plot in the MCU anymore. I really hope they lay off that angle for a while now. Hopefully the Spider-Man films stay away from this trope.

I think that if they keep playing that particular note, it's going to result in a critical backlash, and audience fatigue.

It's really starting to bug me, and I was annoyed that Doctor Strange used that trope too. The only saving grace to it was the clever way Strange saved the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 02:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, just stirring the pot a bit, ha ha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 00:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zach Braff? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 18:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's a little man who gets off on bullying better people. Just look at how he's still trying to discredit Obama even AFTER his two terms ended. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 06:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just think it's so fucking weird that r/Marvel doesn't have a Logan Megathread up and running. 

There's so many shitposts already that basically amount to "I am broken" being the one that inspired me to create this thread, and you just know it'll get worse as the weekend goes on.

Also, if you could upvote for visibility, maybe this thread could get the mods to wake up and start a megathread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we get a Logan megathread running up in this bitch to curb all the shitposting? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 05:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 02:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually saw that in an old Hollywood Reporter article's comments section. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 23:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A bloody masterpiece.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 07:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've died like 20 times fighting the Thunderjaw/T-Rex. That thing is a beast. I'm spamming the ropemaster at it, and popping off sharpshooter arrows, and freezing it with a sling balls, but damn is it a challenge trying to beat it.

Almost did it once, but then I got killed somehow. It just happened so fast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 07:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Stay Fresh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 06:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's the NECA 1/4 scale Donny Turtle figure. I myself have been eyeing the SH Figuarts due to scale, despite not being a big fan of the turts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 06:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys sound like preteens discussing their favorite member of Latest Boyband, ha ha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 03:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Emma Stone returns, it'll be a little weird, cuz of that age gap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 03:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lock him up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 02:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CNN is still talking about the goddamn Clinton emails. WTF </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 01:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just arrived at the Thunderjaw cauldron, and I have a feeling I'm woefully underprepared for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 02:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boo! Rigged TotM! 

My idea of "Just the Boxes-- No figures" won by a landslide if you include all the people who didn't vote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good, but they could have spent a little more time defining the characters, I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "dethrone fascism"

lol right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> stop with fucking clapping </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He makes fun of people like Megan behind closed doors. SMDH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone get the front rows ponchos for when Donny reaches his climax </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he just poisoned harley davidson </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fuckin idiot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mooslims </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's with the blue ties? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pence and Ryan are eye fucking this orange cunt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought public masturbation was frowned upon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FUCK YOU, DONNY! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 02:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's set about 2 years after the 2016 US election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 02:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jolly good fun, old chap! The shenanigans I can get into, wow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 17:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was talking about it with some reporter just before the Oscars, and she was very excited about it, you could tell it was genuine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 02:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This just in: Republican's Love Getting FUCKED by Russia! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 01:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked Robot Chicken, so I had faith in the project. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 00:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cuz they got a bargain bin director. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 23:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like they'll give it one more season so they can advertise it as a final season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 23:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump is the antithesis of everything he aspires to be. That sums it all up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brie Larson refused to clap for Casey Affleck at the Oscars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 18:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Er, I think that what he's doing to his wives is full on rape. They're under duress when they say yes. They know if they say no, there will be consequences.

Dude's like the villain in Don't Breathe where he does some mental gymnastics to convince himself he isn't raping these women. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 03:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And he still looks better than OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 00:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deadpool's gun is in the wrong way on the front holster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 00:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a brown doodle. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 23:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't believe they didn't subtitle it:

#**WELCOME TO MIDDLE EARF!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 23:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So? That doesn't mean they'll translate it to the screen well.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 23:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So? That doesn't mean they'll translate it to the screen well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They haven't even started writing season 8, how in the name of FUCK are they being hyped as the best episodes ever? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotham cuz it's a piece of shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 17:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #**WELCOME TO EARF!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 17:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sooooo am I the only one thinking this clip is only here because r/the_doofus people want to show the Milo Youngboyscockolos isn't a bad guy cuz Bill Maher is being an idiot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 08:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #**NOW THIS IS PODRACING!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 07:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's better. I was beginning to think I wasn't on the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 07:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #**STOP BEING SO GOSH DARN REASONABLE!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 07:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's how I've been playing it while I'm waiting for Horizon. I'm basically not even a hacker anymore. The hacking is what makes it so easy since literally no other enemy can fight back that way against you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 07:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe for like 10- 15 bucks. sometimes it's fun to get multiple factions to try and kill you, cops, bratva, gangsters, meanies, hunters, the bike clubs.

finding invaders is fun too

THATS IT

BOOM

LATER POTATERS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 07:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cops sometimes don't show up cuz the game starts to make things disappear if you've been a bad boy. Sometimes I'm shooting things up, trying to get a decent gun fight going, and things start to disappear. Car I'm using for cover, GONE, dead civvies, GONE, cars stop spawning, killed too many cops, they stop spawning. NOW I'M IN A GHOST TOWN! Wanted level decreasing! SO IS FUN! FUN DECREASING! 

I'll go read a book after that. Books don't disappear! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 07:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that, but the game encourages doing it that way by making it a part of Marcus' character, and by making it so damn easy to complete the mission that way.

I tried not to play that way and it was still easy to go in by brute force since you could jam their coms and make the enemy spaz out long enough to blow their heads off when they're coming at you.

There is literally nothing that presents a challenge to Marcus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
