<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3605</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 07:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there anyway I could win?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 06:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, yeah working on that but my suicidal thoughts are directly tied to school stress.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is my counselor legally allowed to withhold and discourage me from learning about the Certificate of Proficiency? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to drop out of high school purely for my own good because I strongly believe that I may end up hurting myself if I don't so I talk to my counselor about it and she made it clear it was not legal to do so. I think dropping out is better than being a corpse so is she allows to withhold such information from me and actively discourage me from dropping out despite it not being safe for me to even return to school given my mental health? Could this fall under Penal Code 273a? 
I live in CA, by the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is my counselor legally allowed to withhold and discourage me from learning about the Certificate of Proficiency? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to drop out of high school purely for my own good because I strongly believe that I may end up hurting myself if I don't so I talk to my counselor about it and she made it clear it was not legal to do so. I think dropping out is better than being a corpse so is she allows to withhold such information from me and actively discourage me from dropping out despite it not being safe for me to even return to school given my mental health?

Edit: I live in CA by the way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 21:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was actually just a few days ago. On imgur there was this post of a guy on his phone with a pretty girl curled up next to him and the person posting wanted the guy to see how obvlivious he was being to the girl's feelings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 16:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I try but it's just I can hardly see her. She lives so far away. I'll try I'm just scared it won't be soon enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My best friend has given up and I don't know what to do anymore. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 07:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend has suffered a lot from a variety of things but recently she's given up. She doesn't want to go to school, take her medications, she doesn't want to do anything. The only reason she's still here is for me. What do I do?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
