<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2482</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's ok....but can only be known after-the-fact.  So, it's like...retro-knowledge.  

Whereas you could theoretically know the moments when you are the youngest human alive (not counting being a newborn without that concept of course)....there is no way to know you will be the next to die, while you are the next to die.  Only after your death can you know you were the next to die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My point is...the clickbait title is attempting to make the firearm into the cause of the problem, when in fact, the firearm was the tool that was the solution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Maybe Kellyanne was thinking of this Massacre](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uMSTIePQri0)

It's Green.  *shrug* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you 'member the Inauguration Crowd?  Yeah, Yeah, I 'member.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Using canon from a Marvel comic to attempt to prove facts from real-life.

1 Internet point for you, sir. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Additional fact: At some point in time, however briefly, you were the youngest human on Earth.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is nothing new under the sun.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 15:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump says that it doesn't matter how many, since the U.S.'s nuke are the biggest..the best..nukes in the world.  Everyone says so.  No one can beat the U.S.'s nukes.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 15:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title should be "Machete incident at Louvre."

That title is like writing about an apartment fire saying "Fire Hose soaks entire apartment".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just like when they deleted the memory of that movie from all our heads where Sinbad was a genie that granted wishes.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 20:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hacking alleged by every U.S. Intelligence agency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 20:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> William H. Harrison was only in office for 30 days before he died of Pneumonia.  So, not much time left to make it in the record books. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 17:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GDI.  Existentialism Trigger Warning needed. =( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 03:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree with your definition of "Lots of"

To me, that looks more like "A moderate portion of" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 20:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved the ending.  

[Spoiler](#s "After I finished it, and ruminated on it for awhile....I realized that it was us, the Constant Reader, that were forcing Roland to take his journey over and over again...never ending, knowing that he would have to take the journey again, with no power to say no.  Every time another Constant Reader reads that iconic first sentence and goes through the series, Roland is forced to begin his journey for the Dark Tower yet again.  Forever fated to live the same story, so long as Constant Readers keep opening his books.")

Brilliant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Congress attempts to impeach the President, and the vote fails, is there a statute of limitations before they can try it again? 

i.e. Do they have to make sure they get a passed vote before they try to impeach, or risk being stuck with him for awhile?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] If Congress attempts to impeach the President, and the vote fails, is there a statute of limitations before they can try it again? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 16:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just for visualization purposes, that 128 GB drive in your right hand has as much space as nearly 100,000 3.5" floppies.
A 3.5" floppy is 3.3 mm thick.
If you piled all the 3.5" floppies on top of each other that equaled the amount of storage in your right hand, the pile would be nearly a fifth of a mile high.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 19:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (disclaimer, I didn't read the article)
But...how is it decided what regulations are revoked, and what is the process for doing so?  Does it need to be approved by anyone other that the President?
Is this just a work-around as a way for Trump to get get rid of whatever he wants arbitrarily? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 23:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does nothing.

Source: Worked in Congressperson's office before.  The interns there don't tell the Congressperson who called unless it's important or related to anything.
At the most, your call will be included in the "Fuck, there were a lot of annoying people today." conversation on the car pool ride home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 21:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a smart dude Xeno. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 21:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rules (Geneva Convention) are basically a mutual understanding between countries to agree to be somewhat civil during war-time, when civility often goes out the window. 
An armed force often follows the Convention because they'd want to be treated the same if the situation was reversed.

...which is why President Trump's current flag waving on fighting fire with fire by making torture of detainees legal is so troubling.  One of the reasons we don't torture people is because we don't want our people to be tortured.  By legitimizing torture on detainees, he would essentially be justifying their often barbaric treatment of Americans in capture-situations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 20:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 21:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.  There is actually policy that Presidential Appointees at a certain level are *required* to submit their resignation letters.  The new administration can accept their resignation, or decline it.

This is just making a big deal out of nothing.  These people resigned before the inauguration, *like every other Presidential Appointee of their level* as required by policy and law.

It's just that "These high-level officials resigned to get away from Trump!" gets more clicks on the news sites than "Business as Usual." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Melania takes role of First Lady on the platform of stopping cyber bullying.

Her husband, the President, takes role of cyber-bullying entire neighboring country by demanding extortion money for nothing in return.

Melania, you're failing us already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 18:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Way more people watch it than that.
That's just the reported numbers watching it on t.v.  Who even does that anymore?  No one I know.
People download it...stream it...etc.  All not counted.
Not to mention the MANY people that will watch the highlights later on in YouTube videos.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 18:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grew up in Southwest FL in a very small town...walking home from middle school alone, I was "jumped" by a pretty well-known bully and his tiny entourage.  He knocked me down, straddled my chest, and was punching me in the face while I covered up with my arms.  Someone yelled that "someone is coming!" and they all ran off leaving me in the dirt.
I had no idea why he did that, even to this day.  I hated him to my core at that point.

Fast forward one and a half years.  The summer before my freshman year in high school.  My mom came into my room late at night and told me that the boy (bully) and two others were kidnapped and brought into the woods and executed.  I went to sleep happy that night...and still feel guilty to this day for the glee I felt when I thought he was killed.

Postscript:  The boy (bully) described above actually survived the execution attempt by playing dead after he was shot multiple times, and is alive today still.  The other two kids that were kidnapped were killed.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 15:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very good point, and you're very right. =) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 20:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You messed up then.  

Prime stands by their 2 day guarantee.  Any time I don't get my items by the time they say they'll deliver them, I simply message them...and once they see that they didn't meet the 2-day mark, they credit my Prime account with an extra month, as well as sometimes even refunding some of the shipping cost to the account.  

If you really aren't getting your items for 3 or 4 days, you would essentially have free Prime if you told them about it every time...and kept getting the month credit on your Prime every time it happened.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 22:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still try to instill the awe in my children that SHOULD be there, knowing they are walking around with the entirety of Human Knowledge and History at their fingertips, available at any time, and wherever they are.

But, their world has always been the way it currently is, so they don't understand how amazing current technology is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 18:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glowforge? =) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 18:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This aspect of things sucks for the parents, also...especially if your child IS independent, and off living at college without any support from you as a parent.
BECAUSE, the parents Auto Insurance will NOT drop the child from the policy while they are at college...even if a)the child is independent b)the child doesn't even have a vehicle and c) the child is living out of state with no access to the parent's vehicles.

**I use child to mean progeny, not minor (under 18) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 18:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What worse than that, is the long hold times when you call certain companies, but they break in every minute or so with "Your call is important to us, please press 1 to stay on the line with us, or do nothing and we will terminate the call and call you back when an agent is available."

So, then you can't just be on hold doing something else, you actually have to actively listen to make sure you don't miss a "Press 1" prompt, or you get hung up on.  
(Also, they DON'T call you back, fyi) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 07:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You like series'?  I got a series for ya!

41, 43, 47, 53,....1681

It is a series that increases each term by 2, then 4, 6, 8, 10, etc.....
The AWESOME things about this series, is that
EVERY term in it is PRIME, until you get to the 41st term, which is just 41^2 (1681).  How cool huh?!

(41 is my favorite number because of this series) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 20:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine is H2R38FT...because I can't be bothered to go re-enter the login credentials for out 15 devices that connect to it. =P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 20:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, what you're saying is, that some more powerful sump pumps could have saved thousands of lives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 19:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 70's was before the 80's, so no, she's OG. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 16:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MY favorite dish in keto is a half a head of cauliflower, riced.  Steam it in a gallon sized freezer bag in the microwave (just toss 1/8 cup of water in the bag, seal it, poke a few holes, and nuke for 6-7 minutes).  

Spread out riced cauli on a giant plate, salt/pepper liberally.  Put the ground beef over the top of it.  Sometime I sprinkle cheese on it, sometimes not....but it fulfills all my cravings, every time.  I just love how satiated I feel after this low cal/low carb meal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 16:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG Chris, Orange Cream?

I might need to slow down my weight loss just so I can still be on KetoChow when that comes out....lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 16:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I want to make him a really special dinner to celebrate. What are your favorite recipes that I can knock his socks off with?

Homemade whipped cream made from HWC, on you.  That would knock his socks off, and it's carb free!  ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 16:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Want a good idea of how much weight you've lost?

Go pick up a 12-pack case of soda at the grocery store.
Then, have someone stack FOUR MORE cases on top of that one.  

You're now holding FIVE cases of soda, weighing a total of 49 pounds.  Pretty damn heavy huh?  
That's how much less weight you're carrying around 24/7.  

You got this!  KCKO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 15:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear ya!

Everyone at work now knows about my weight loss, as it's very noticeable now.  At first I was telling them about what I was doing...but all the "health experts" around me constantly were telling me that I wasn't going to loss any weight by eating bacon and eggs.

Welllllll, now, I just tell everyone that my diet consists of avoiding sugar and breads.  No one seems to have a problem with that...and it lets me get away with saying no (with no weird looks) to all the office-foods that seem so prevalent.  (donuts, pastries, etc)

In my experience, it's just a lot easier to give general answers when asked "what are you doing to lose all that weight?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 15:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fantastic job!  

It's posts like this one that show the true potential in all of us when are able to KCKO!  
Great role model. =) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 02:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super impressive.  What a fantastic role model =) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 02:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look a lot like Rob McElhenney </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 21:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIP man.  Look on the bright side...at least you will save money on a slimmer coffin. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 20:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, after I washed it, it was completely neutral, and had no odor whatsoever.  I think that's exactly what it was, though.  it was just...nothing.  It never really convinced me that it was, what I was trying to replace with it.  I tried it as a rice substitute...it was just like chewing, nothing.  It even pops when you chew it.  
 Same thing as a noodle.  It got to be a chore to chew it by the end of the dish.

All that being said, some people like it...sooo..*shrug*  Give it a try, and if you like it, great, if not, oh well. =) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 17:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My experience with this stuff was less than good.  Nothing "wrong" with it, but I just felt it was more hassle than it was worth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 15:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone will probably downvote me for this, but I ate at a 70% deficit for the first 2 months, and am now at about a 66% deficit. (Haven't changed my calorie intake, just that my Basal has naturally lowered as I lost weight)

I have zero issues feeling hungry, or maintaining this.  

Essentially, I'm only doing 800 Cals a day, using three Ketochow meals made with only the powder (not using MCT or HWC), and supplementing with about 200 Calories of some sort of fish every day.  (usually a tin of Sardines, or some Smoked Trout).  I also take a multivitamin just to be safe, even though the Ketochow has that all covered.

On the rare evening that I get the munchies before bed, I'll spiralize a whole Zucchini and toss it in a bowl with salt/pepper and red wine vinegar.  It's super zesty and has always satisfied any kind of munchies I've had.

Very rarely, I'll eat three hard boiled eggs in place of one of my Ketochow meals...just when I feel like chewing something.  But, typically after a ketochow meal, I feel VERY full and satiated for many hours, until the next time it's time to drink another Ketochow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 17:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not too mention, there are probably food banks/food kitchens nearby you that you'd be able to get most of your meals from.  Also, many churches will be able to provide assistance/meals for you.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 17:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You won't be able to eat Keto on $10 for a month.  

You could go get about 45-50 ramen packs for $10 though.  That would easily get you through the month...no, it wouldn't be very healthy, at least you'd survive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 16:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great goal!!!!

I have a similar Summer goal that I'm working for...I want to be able to go swimming with my kids when we go to the water park without feeling embarrassed and self-conscious.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 03:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But...what's Table Cream? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 23:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait a minute...30 servings, for $150?!

So, $5 for a little packet of 22.5 grams (less than an ounce) of MCT and sweetener???

Wow, I'm in the wrong business.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 21:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree that their whole marketing scheme is very gimmicky.  They are advertising towards people not in ketosis...to experience ketosis instantly...what??

That being said, the product itself is 3 carbs per serving.  It's like a mini fat-bomb, but with way too many carbs.  
I didn't look at the price, but I'm betting it's way more that it's worth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 16:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never met a Russian named Gene. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 15:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Da Bears! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 22:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the best answer here.  You can order most any pizza with no sauce...and then pull the toppings off and eat them without carb contamination from the sauce. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 19:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Wegman's freezer section by the Halo Top could be an unofficial meeting place for keto'ers!  Seriously.

I hung out there for like five minutes one day, and EVERY person that stopped at the Halo Top, had a shopping cart that I immediately recognized as being pure Keto.  Meats, cheeses, and eggs...and Halo Top. Ha!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 21:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome story!

I had something similar happen to me about a month ago.  I went to visit my son at college over the weekend, and I didn't really want to talk to him about me being on keto due to a little...embarrassment?  And I didn't want to have to explain it.  We went to a local buffet place (think...fancy Golden Corral).  

They had the most AMAZING meat selection.  It was just, great.  So, I loaded up my plate with steak, chicken, fish...all the good stuff. 

We get back to the table, and he goes "Wow, got enough meat?".
Then, he gets this funny look on his face...and he says "Wait, are you doing keto?"
I said "You know what keto is?!?"

He said, yeah, tons of the athletes in his school are going keto..."everyone's doing it."

It really blew me away at how casually he knew about it.  I think that keto is out there a lot more than we think.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 21:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I eat ground beef ALL the time.

A giant plate of riced cauliflower...and top it with some seasoned ground beef, and sprinkle a little cheese over the top...reminds me of Shepards Pie.  Fills me up something fierce.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 19:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgoing Turkey this year (kids don't dig on Turkey), and making pinwheel steaks with garlic butter.  Then mashed potatoes (which I won't eat), Buttered Corn (which I won't eat), and buttered croissants (which I won't eat).

TL:DR 
I'm having Steak! =D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
