<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject366</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-09 05:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am exhibiting.  In August, I launched a new bulletproof vest company called BulletSafe.  It's going really well and 2014 SHOT Show will be my first time.  Anyone reading this is welcome to stop by our booth, number 3948 and say you saw my post on Reddit.  See you there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today I wrote this product description for work. I'm the boss so it will stay there too. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 06:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 23:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought about it, but there is nothing on the page that is NSFW.  No nudity and no profanity, so I left it off.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What should federal employees do during the government shutdown? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 23:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-21 05:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Vonnegut.  I believe he said something like 'To create a great novel, I first create a character, one that the audience falls in love with, then I make something horrible happen to them.'  Slaughterhouse Five is my favorite because in Slaughterhouse Five the character is himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-01 05:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone at the shop wear a bullet resistant vest?  Have you ever considered wearing one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-15 05:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mower Gang events are great.  They are fun and it is amazing how much work gets done.  I'll be there with my lawn tractor.  It's a Husqvarna. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-15 05:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in Birmingham where almost nothing is allowed and my kids and I shoot model rockets in the school yard.  I'm sure they would be fine at Belle Isle.  They don't make much noise anyway.  More of a woosh than anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-13 03:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work in ABS predominantly, but I like to spray coat the parts with silicone conformal coating.  It is usually used for circuit boards, but a few coats makes a nice, smooth coating.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-10 21:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd probably buy one too.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Make Love Not War with your 3D Printer - A response to the 3D printed gun by the people behind 3D printed sex toys. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-10 20:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 04:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sooner or later it happens to all of us.  The worst part is that it can ruin your self confidence for the next time.  Here is what I learned to do:

1.  Take a good look at your health.  Without good care, your body will fail you and as you get older it will fail you more and more.  Try to find a 40 year old guy that is in good shape that doesn't eat right and exercise.  You can't.  Because all of the guys that didn't take care of themselves fell away.  You need to do those things.  Sleep is important too, also stay away from drugs and booze, both bad deals. 
2.  Don't let it bother you mentally.  Your mind will mess with you.  Don't start thinking you are a viagra commercial or anything.  
3.  Next time, come equipped with some mental ammunition.  Think about something hot.  It doesn't have to be your partner, just something you can go to that will be instant.  
4.  Medications:  If you are taking any meds, see the warnings.  
5.  Relax.
Good luck to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-30 04:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is your favorite kind of muffin?  I notice that you ask a lot of people, but I didn't see your reply.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-30 04:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was surprised to find that butt plugs run the gamut from gay men to women, to couples.  Lots of people like things in their butt.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-25 23:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it when you go to a barbecue restaurant and they give you a corn muffin.  I usually eat it at the end of the meal and treat it sorta like desert.

Now I'm hungry.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-25 22:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for writing.  Here are some answers.

1.  Some people like the feeling of something in their butt.  A butt plug is designed so that once it is in, it stays in but doesn't get stuck in there.  

2.  Cock rings are used to maintain a very firm erection.  An erection is formed when the body subconsciously narrows the vessels that allow blood to escape from the penis.  As blood continues to flow into the penis with a more difficult escape route, the tissues inflate.  A cock ring restricts that flow in a similar way and causes an erection to form or to stay hard.  

3.  My answer was a vibrating cock ring, these are used because your partner will like them.  Firm erection + vibration = fun times.  

Thanks for the questions, I'm glad I could ask.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 15:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno.  I just don't see it.  Marketing dildos probably isn't something you do with a cute mascot.  Sometimes someone will create a "cute" vibrator but they usually flop, but vibrators are usually small and cute.  Dildos tend to be serious business and taken very seriously.  It is rare for them to look like anything other than a massive penis let alone something not really related like a cartoon.  

For us, we would never really show the mascot anyway, all of the photos online would be of the product itself, the packaging is rarely featured prominently.  

Keep thinking though, you've got a creative mind.  I like this saying "To get a great idea you need 100 ideas and a way to determine which one is the best". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 15:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I'm Tom Nardone.  In 1998 I started a small business after working as a business plan writer.  It is now Vibrators.com and I am running an AMA here: http://redd.it/1cz82v  

I also guest lecture on Entrepreneurship Studies as well as teaching a one night class on starting a small business.  Come on over and Ask Me Anything on my thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 15:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do I think that it will be successful?  Nope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 15:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely.  I'm good at reviewing ideas and I'm excellent at keeping secrets.  My email is tom at priveco dot com.  

I'll apologize in advance that I can be brutally honest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 15:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course.  All billing is done under our corporate name:  subject366.  Sorry I didn't mention this earlier.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 15:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think a moderate one.  (do we know each other?) I have a personal project called MakerLove.com where I publish free 3D sex toy designs for people with Makers.  I think the level of privacy that being able to print out 3D toys will offer should make it fairly successful.  The things that will hold it back are access to 3D printers (but they keep getting less expensive) and making those toys work for people.  Most women prefer vibrating toys over dildos.  I think MakerLove.com is in good shape to lead the trend though.

I've done a couple of media interviews on this topic. I'm kinda psyched about it actually.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 15:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sound rating for our quietest vibrators is called "whisper" on the site, so a quick search for that term will find you exactly what you are looking for.  We (and our customers) are quite picky about sound, so we make sure to have what you are looking for.  
http://www.vibrators.com/nsearch.html?catalog=vibrators-dot-com x=0 y=0 query=whisper
Thanks for asking.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
