<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3288</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 12:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, word in conflict is great, (still two servers online), but to my ears anything to do with MOBA is a nono. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better keep the MOBA shit of of their games. The reason people play these games are to get away from those rts killers called MOBAS.

Side note, love the fact that different national decks actually have unique units, not just reskins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to see some unique units like the Me-262 and similar jet planes and other wunderwaffe. Also I excpect a lot of unit diversion, a good combat system similar to wargame series, a report/ban function and attention to detail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 12:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That`s wierd, I`ve never run into any hackers in bo2... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 12:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, argonne map is retarded in it`s small size and 3-lane setup. Did u ever play Bfc2 VIetnam? The maps there were amazing. With even larger maps and better graphics it would be gold. Besides, there was a lot of city fighting as well, a Vietnam game would be just as varied as any other bf game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 12:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Operations mode in Vietnam would be gold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 12:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, can`t wait for Ro2 Vietnam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 12:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, I`d rather they stay to "real" history, instead of alternate history and such. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want an HBO vietnam war series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. Would have the same effect on battles as behemoth in bf1. But without any behemoths ef course. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dunno, maybe it could be limited to a commander ability, to be used every 5 minutes or so? Or maybe it could be an unlocable weapon for a pilot class, but it can only be used once every flight.
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d3JETOGrE-0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Napalm would not workt eh same way as gas grenades, they would have to be dropped by jets. No napalm stpam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I played that a lot, but too bad bc2 is more or less dead. No one plays vietnam on ps3 anymore, and according to steam only 600 people are playing the game on steam right now, and I bet they are playing vanilla mp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bf1 is a very good game. Operations might the best mode they`ve made in years. Fighting in trenches, tunnels and the jungle bush would be badass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 234 was a Reconnaissance/ jet bomber so I think they could get them in there. Since helicopters (Excepct for maybe a few german ones) are out, I bet planes will have a scout role now, and the 234 fits that role. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BF game set in Vietnam after bf1?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 13:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who would like a Bf set in Vietnam for the next bf game? With the new frsotbite engine and Dice Superb sound a Vietnam fully fledged vietnam game could be epic!
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=H4R8GDlV8rc
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DM-GZGtqmEw
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wtbh7YUL65I
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=usluSX4X1dg
OF course Fortunate son is mandatory! Just look how far bf has come, image a new Vietnam game today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 13:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ww2 or Vietnam pls! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 13:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, been a few months since I played but spent hours and hours playing with a friend 3-4 months ago. Alwasy found full servers. Just played bo1 today, and that game had 10 000 players online. Bo2 is a more recent game and has no hackers, So i bet there are even more playing that game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 13:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time i hear the bloody "Boots on the ground" shit I feel like hitting somebody. Such a lame and pointless, desperate word to use.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 13:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope they go back to the vietnam war. Or maybe even a mix of ww2 and the vietnam war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 13:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, still lots of players and no hackers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 12:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Culd anyone make a list of the most important points in the video? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 12:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bad, it was the Arado 234 that flew during the Normandy campaign. Hope we get to see it in-game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 12:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who cares about chat? I don`t know how people can actually judge a game based on politics. Screw that man. If a game is good it`s good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, I go legit or not at all. Too bad they don`t sell it anymore, could imagine a few people would be willing to buy the game now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly I never got around to buy it, and now no one sels it anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 16:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don`t know if Rhodesia is fit to be a standalone nations (even though I would play it), but if they made a coalition of Rhodesia and SA it would work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet. Wargame and Eugene deserves all the new players. Their games are amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source?
Pretty cool though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not quite in the songe of ice and fire genra but the "World of Kong: a history of skull island" is a fantastic book. Just got it today, even though I never thought I would be able to buy one. That book along with the woiaf book are some of the best there is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that is good news, wargame deserves much more praise and a bigger player base than it has now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I`m a bit concerned that the phase system will be too limiting. I`m ok with the "heavy tanks arrive after fast light tanks" mechanic, but if We can`t recruit certain units one the next face begins that would suck. Sure a lith tank would`t survive against a Tiger 2, but part of the fun in their games is those last ditch attempts were ur just send everything and anything at them. I remember my M4A5 in red dragon killing a t90 :) 15 point unit killed a 180 point unit. The ability to decide waht units u want to sendt into combat should, at least aftert phace c, bet left to the player. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only 1000 people playing right now, can`t be that many new players. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just bought the game, just hope it arrives before the 6th. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it possible to transfer a ps3 online character to ps4 without owning the game on ps4? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 13:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title says it all. I already own the game on ps4, and seeing as the last chanse to transfer my online stats is march 6, and the delivery of the game could take up to 4 days, is there any way for me to play it safe and transfer the progression even thoguh I do not own the ps4 game yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 12:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too bad we can`t but ruse in steam anymore... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 12:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They also had working, functional helicopters that could transport weapons, and even some transport helicopter prototypes. Oh and night visions goggles and guided missiles.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Focke-Achgelis_Fa_225
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fritz_X
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Flettner_Fl_282
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Zielger%C3%A4t_1229 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 12:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn`t quite understand the notes but from what I understand we will be using more of the map than in the wargames, due to the frontline systems. Can`t just hide and wait in the bushes or the towns because controll of the entire maps is what counts towards victory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 21:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that units can now surrender when encircled or flee brings a whole new mechanic to the game. Gotta watch those flanks, and if need be fall back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, they weren`t very accurate. Stil, given how large the eguen maps are it could be used as a aoe weapon. Just fire it in a general direction and hope it hits something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
