<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3535</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 06:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very true, but I meant an Archer style parody of sic-fi franchises like Mass Effect and Star Trek, similar to how Archer parodies the spy genre. I mean, the setting of a starship like the Enterprise of the Tempest would be perfect for the office comedy style of humor shown in Archer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 05:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since we're on the topic of Mass Effect Parodies, I would actually want something akin to Archer but for the Mass Effect series, or just Sci-Fi in general.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tann is associated with the benefactor to some degree. I have a feeling he's shaping up to be this trilogy's version of Udina. His not wanting to investigate Garson's murder is only adding to my theory.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lyin Ted Ryder. According to tabloids, Alec had a hand in the assassination of Jien Garson. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a side quest involving Cerberus on Kadara? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MEA Spoilers] Any thoughts/theories on the Benefactor? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 06:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the storylines I'm really interested in seeing through is the [Spoiler] (the benefactor and the hidden reason behind the launching of the Initiative). This is also the one storyline that doesn't have a clear progression and could go in any number of directions, so does anyone have any ideas as to where it goes or what it could mean with either DLC or sequels? My only fear is that Bioware doesn't try something new and the Benefactor and their faction becomes the Andromeda equivalent to Cerberus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the response. In regards to intel, I'm leaning more towards human intel, but I'm open to intel overall.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, forgot to clarify this in my OP. In terms if I would want to do post military, I want to either go into the State Department or federal Law Enforcement. In terms of career fields in the military, I'm looking at careers in intel, Law Enforcement, or Special Operations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 06:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like to think I'm the former. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 06:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another one. For example, lets say in an Andromeda sequel or some future DLC, you come across a colonist that was once a N7 operative, and maybe it can be a either a task or just relegated to dialogue, but this colonist, after learning about what you've done as Pathfinder, gives you an 'honorary' N7 designation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 05:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I forgot to put this in my OP, but my thinking was that its less like an official designation, but more like an informal seal of approval from a colonist that was a former N7 operative.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MEA Spoilers] Should Ryder get N7 designation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 05:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the more interesting things I learned recently is that a lot of the fans don't like wearing the N7 armor or the level 1 or 2 Pathfinder armor due to the fact that Ryder didn't earn the N7 designation on both sets. Given that the N7 armor and designation are definitive symbols of the ME franchise, and that Bioware probably knows about how fans feel, do you think they would or should include an option in either future Andromeda games or in DLC for Ryder to officially become an N7? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 02:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thinking about becoming a Marine Officer, but starting to have doubts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 02:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently a college sophomore and being an officer has been my dream for most of my life. For the longest time, I wanted to be commissioned in the Navy, but in recent years, I've learned a lot about the Marine Corp, and I'm thinking about visiting my local OSO, but I'm still not 100% about either. Can anyone tell me the pros and cons of being a Marine Officer verses being a Navy officer, or an officer of any branch? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thinking about becoming a Marine Officer, but having doubts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 02:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 07:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably because she was shorthanded and took what few crew members she could wake out of cryo. 

I thought about the disaster relief bit, and it makes sense for him to make the trip to Andromeda, but if your mission is discovering, pacifying, and settling new planets, you'd think you would bring someone along who's skills would lend more to that job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 04:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now, that I think about, if you put Liam in the Nomad with either Cora or Vetra, they rag on him for his tactical missteps (Cora gets noticeably irritated with him sometimes) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 04:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are fair points. I guess from my perspective, its easy to see what everyone brings to the table, but with Liam, not so much. And, maybe I missed it, but was there anything that showed off Liam's engineering skills? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 03:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that, all I'm saying other than being the glue, he doesn't bring a whole lot else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MEA Spoilers] Story wise, what's the point of Liam bieng on the Pathfinder team? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 03:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm halfway through my NG+ playthrough, and I brought Liam along with a mission, and hearing his dialogue in the Nomad, I got to wondering "Why is he here?". 

Looking at the rest of the of the crew of the Tempest, everyone there has some purpose for being there; Cora was trained by Alec Ryder and has her Alliance and her Asari Commando training (surprising, right), Vetra knows the ship, the crew and has underground connects, Drack has more combat experience than anybody on the ship, plus he's a Krogan, Jaal is the liaison to the Anagran resistance, Peebee is an expert on Remnant technology, Gil's the engineer, Suvi's the science officer, Kallo's the pilot. Liam, on the other hand, was a self admitted bad student, bad cop, and was only good what was essentially disaster relief. Compared to the others, he doesn't bring a whole lot to the table. Which leads me to ask why is a guy who contributes very little to the team on it? 

I know from a writing perspective, he's meant to be the 'straight man' in a crew full of strange characters, but i don't see a in-story reason for him to be there. And I'm not coming from a malicious place, I'm just legitimately curious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds easy enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry for the long list of questions, but I haven't had the opportunity to ask anyone about the application process for O's 

1. I've heard one of the biggest factors in getting guys to drop is the cold? Is this true, and if so, what can you do to prepare for it/build up your tolerance for the cold?

2. What are some of the daily roles and responsibilities of Officers at BUD/S? 

3. What kind of O's did you see make it through phase 1 and hell week and what kind didn't?

4. What can be done to make an O's application stand out to the selection board, specifically one coming from an OCS candidate? 

5. Can you say anything about SOAS, specifically how to prepare for it should you get selected to attend? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 05:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that sense of family is one thing the tempest crew has over the Normandy crew (I kinda of equate the Normandy to being like an office while the Tempest is like a dorm or an apartment). I hope that Bioware doesn't add to many new sqaudmates in future games, but allows them to grow and develop with our Ryders.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Kadara was meant to fill the criminal underworld niche.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have no idea how much this helps. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't it be something if we found out the Initiative settled in the Andromeda version of the Terminus systems and, like you said, there's a council of species in the greater Andromeda Galaxy fighting the Kett. Maybe in between Andromeda and the sequel, the Initiative grows more powerful due to their access and use of Remnant technology, and start to be viewed as a threat by the rest of Andromeda, maybe leading to some tense political cutscenes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. a crate to store all your old or outdated gear, similar to the cache in The Division. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they were saving the new races for the sequel when we go see the rest of Andromeda. Plus, we're getting [Spoilers](The second wave of arks coming in) 

As for space combat, Bioware seems like they're willing to take more risks in terms of gameplay, so I would like to see a mission where you use your jump jet to fight on the outside of a ship and board it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DA approval system could work really well now that crew members interact with each other more and can get into disagreements [Spoiler](as we saw with Gil and Kallo)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe an improved power wheel, and I would like to see the tactical system from from Dragon Age make its way to ME. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ME:A spoilers] Its seems kinda early to ask this, but what would you want to see in an Andromeda sequel? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, Andromeda got a lot of things right, but could use improvement in some areas. A few of the major things I would like to see done if Andromeda were to get a sequel are: 

1. A larger Inventory limit/no inventory limit at all: This became one of the biggest annoyances in my play through, especially when bringing my gear along with NG+. If there won't be an inventory increase, then I would want a storage locker or crate we can store our excess stuff in. 

2. Politics: In my opinion, Mass Effect is one of the few Sci-Fi franchises, along with Star Trek and Battlestar Galatica that can take politics and use them to enhance the overall story. Since [Spoiler] (It's been hinted at that the kett are a presence in the greater Andromeda galaxy, which we might end up exploring and that arks with the rest of the Milky Way species are one the way, with the Quarian ark having run into something on the way over to Helius) I'm hoping that we get partake in some Star Trek level politics, where we're negotiating treaties with hostile species, settling territorial disputes, etc. 

3. Your twin as a squadmate: I think this could be an interesting dynamic especially when it comes to Dialogue, moral choices (maybe your twin can have opposing views on the choices you make) 

4. Random encounters: So far, in both my playthroughs, I haven't explored any systems where there aren't planets or story missions, mainly due the fact that there isn't much to do in them besides scanning. Since we're more than likely going to be exploring the rest of the Andromeda Galaxy, I hoping to see a random encounter system where, for example, you travel to a system and you run into a group of pirates, or a hostile creature you have to outrun or fight. This could a bit of variety and uniqueness to each player's experience. 

5. The obvious stuff: Improved facial animations, improved CC, fixing the bugs, and any other problems we've encountered. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I might try that instead. I've trying to get the shade I mentioned for the last hour, and I can't get it right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't think of that. Thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] What shade of blue does the Andromeda Initiative use? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For my New Game+ walkthrough, I decided to put my Pathfinder armor in the colors of the Andromeda Initiative. The only thing I'm having trouble with is that I can't seem to get the right shade of blue (I'm using the blue found on Liam and Cora's armor as references). Can anyone help? Also, a image showing where on the color wheel would be much appreciated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 19:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not that I know of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 11:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chris Cassidy was an SDV officer who later became an astronaut.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 06:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No because ME and Star Wars are two distinctly different franchises. As for a new SW RPG being a reskined ME, I think Bioware is creative enough to take elements from their own franchises and combine them with their own unique ideas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 06:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think so. In fact, I think there's a lot a Bioware SW RPG could take from ME (the dialog wheel, Character Creator, inventory, etc.) I'm just hoping that Lucasfilm has kept Bioware on their radar and are planning on tapping them to do a KOTOR reboot or something to replace it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 05:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right, they have been for the last few years. After that, its going to be DA4, Andromeda 2 since they've already have something to work with, or even something Star Wars related.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 05:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Bioware's going to try a new IP, probably Dragon Age 4, and then Andromeda 2.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 05:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No Prob. My high school Spanish teacher told me about Art of Manliness, and its helped immeasurably through the tail end of high school and my first 2 years of college. I remember picking up Denver's book Damn Few my junior year of high school, and carried around every day for the next 2 years. It was him, Chris Cassidy, and Eric Greitens that made me want to be an officer in the teams. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 05:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we'll be getting alternate suits as DLC down the line, and Bioware will probably include squadmate customization in future Andromeda games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 05:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks. Something I just thought of is that the color scheme you see actually matches with Liam, Cora, and the overall Andromeda Initiative color scheme, which was completely accidental. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 04:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree on the helmets. I think the helmet cam makes more sense for an explorer like the Pathfinder than an antenna. Everything else about the tier 5 is awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] I'm trying a new color scheme for the Pathfinder armor, but am open to suggestions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 04:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trying a new color scheme for the Pathfinder armor, but am looking for suggestions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 04:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 03:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can either take a picture with my phone, or screenshot it on my xbox 1, though I don't know how I would post it into the comments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 03:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Much appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 03:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice. I'll give it a shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 03:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Real Pathfinders wear pink. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] Does anyone have any good color combinations for the pathfinder armor? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 03:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Initially, I stuck with the default colors, and for the majority of my time playing, I've gone between that and black,red, and white (the colors of my Shepard's armor in ME2). I'm considering a change, but can't come up with any good ideas. Suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found this podcast a while ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 03:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 02:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct me if I'm wrong, but Officers coming out of OTS can't apply to be STO, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
