<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2947</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 23:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whats your war stars? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 14:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just watched all 26 episodes, was a wild ride,  unfortunately didnt find the scene I was looking for... basically was the move when jin vs. Kariya at the end, when jin says "this can only end with one move"   he falls in the lake,  its nighttime   they're both outside, The move will guarentee kill one person or the other, the person is being taught the move, and the person who is being taught gets the kill, you can see the meat on the person when he cuts through.  Idk if u guys know the anime. But thnx anyways </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Recruiting] Fish bait #8GQCGQ9C | Th8.5   Below Lvl 12 clan Top 100 USA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 04:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rank 94 in war wins in USA according to clashofstats

- Must be respectful   follow rules

- Must Actively Donate, no ignoring requests

- Attack your townhall level in wars

- Rank is earned through war

- Be Active - Missing war attacks will get you demoted and/or kicked

If you are looking for a strong active clan   are a strong active player, why dont you stop on by! If we like what we see, we'll accept you, say mint sent you from reddit in the description. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help remembering anime show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 00:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only thing i remember about it, is:
It was on adult swim many years ago -
Only episode i remember is the master had to teach a student a move, but in doing so, one of them dies, what happens is the student cuts the master in half with his sword in the episode.

I know this is a very vague description of the show, but im hoping atleast 1 person knows the show that i'm talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 16:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Need mod confirmation or photoshopped </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 15:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you guys talking about, Jagex loves pures   Frequently rolls out Updates + balance changes for the pvp community
#nerfthedragonlongsword

Kappa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
