<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3278</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 02:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First tried it. It's definitely on the easy side of medium. The trickiest thing was some of the roofs being low which impaired me on a few jumps. I like the classic feel though. You've inspired me to make an indoor dirt level. 

Please try mine: 5C70-0000-0091-3F50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 02:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beat it first try. I must have gone the main route. It was like playing bumper cars with Bowser for the first half. I enjoyed it but it could have been longer. 

Please try mine: 5C70-0000-0091-3F50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 02:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bullet Stairs

5C70-0000-0091-3F50

I really love my newest level. It is challenging for sure but very forgiving, so you will not die much, if at all. Please try it. I'm about to start going down this thread playing levels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 02:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for trying it out. Before this game was released I knew I wanted to make one like this so I'll probably do more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 22:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beat them both. I like the look of Jungo-Jungo with all the vines. Here Nor There I took the huge shortcut with the bombs. I think I'll try it again and go for a different exit.

Please try my newest or any of mine: 5C70-0000-0091-3F50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 22:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bullet Stairs

5C70-0000-0091-3F50

I really love my newest level. It is challenging for sure but very forgiving, so you will not die much, if at all. Please try it. I'm about to start going down this thread playing levels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 11:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First try. I like how you timed the bombs throughout the level. 

Please try mine: 5C70-0000-0091-3F50  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 10:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The path I take is - off the first red cannonball to the three regular cannonballs, then make sure you bounce as high as you can to trigger the red bullets and you should be out of the there.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 10:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bullet Stairs

5C70-0000-0091-3F50

Vertical level. Please let me know if the concept makes sense to you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 03:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two new levels today: 

The Tower of Lunacy

4785-0000-008E-5f0D

Bounce on bullets and cannons in a vertical level. Just revised it so the ending is clearer. 

AND

I Ate a Bad Mushroom

5357-0000-008E-50D0

Sat down with my friend and helped him make a level. It is easy and tells the story of a mushroom dream gone wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 00:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Tower of Lunacy

89D2-0000-008C-3FCF

Made it today and I love it. Still unbeaten, but it's not that hard for someone who knows who to bounce on bullets and cannons.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 15:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just spent all night making this level because I think it is such a fun concept. It's a vertical level, so you'll need to string together bounces on bullets and cannons to move forward. There are plenty of power ups to keep it from being unforgiving.

The Tower of Lunacy

89D2-0000-008C-3FCF </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 15:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3rd tried the 10 second. It's a great idea for a level. 

Please try mine:31C8-0000-0084-847A </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 15:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost Home

Lead Mario on his way home from work. 16% completion rate. Made yesterday.

31C8-0000-0084-847A </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 14:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spaghetti Bowser - I had to trial and error my way through each section. It was hard to see what was coming, especially the flames in the 3rd area. I also figured out that I could skip to the third row by waiting for the flame rod. Really enjoyed it. I was determined to beat it. 

Please try my newest:0677-0000-0086-DF55 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 14:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a great puzzle level. You should make more of those. I had to be exact on the timing of those flares. 

Please try my level: 0677-0000-0086-DF55 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 13:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha. I took the low road. I want to try the others now.

Please try my newest: 0677-0000-0086-DF55 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 13:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the idea. Also this one is a remake of the 4th level on Super Mario Bros 3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 13:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wooah first tried it. It was crazy toward the end. It is the perfect length because I wouldn't have felt bad about retrying if I had died at Bowser.

Please try my newest level: 0677-0000-0086-DF55 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 13:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finally beat it. That was great, and I normally don't like levels with backtracking. Once I put together a mental map of the place I figured out the short route. But the spring trick had me stuck thinking for a while. A+

Please try my newest level: 0677-0000-0086-DF55 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 12:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That freaking fish haha. It struck me down a couple of times. 

Please try mine: 0677-0000-0086-DF55 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 12:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alas. I set it up as close as I could. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 11:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2nd try. The red fish got me. I liked how you had them shaped as fish.

Please try mine: 0677-0000-0086-DF55 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 11:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dream Classic

0677-0000-0086-DF55

A remake of the 4th level of Super Mario Bros. 3.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 05:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, that killed my nerves. I'm glad I first tried the maze section because it would have been hard to start over. It seems like in the very first part you pretty much have to get hit to make it up, right? In the maze those shells you need to bounce leave basically no room for error because they are coming right back at you at you've got 1 blocks worth of jumping room. It was a great feeling when it was all over though.

Please try mine: 31C8-0000-0084-847A </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 05:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beat Hey Babe. Now I'm going to have to make my own level where thwomps blow shit up. I enjoyed it.

Please try mine: 31C8-0000-0084-847A </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 05:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't get the code to work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 05:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beat it. Having never played this Mega Man 2 level I'll assume it's accurate. The toughest part is the long jump past the halfway mark, although the thwomps can get ugly too. I kept getting to Bowser Jr and going straight for the shell, then dying. Finally I decided to kill him first and it all worked out.

Please try my level: 31C8-0000-0084-847A </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 04:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, I'm the first to beat it. I figured it was going to be impossible when I saw that 8 people had already attempted. It is a weird mechanic but I'm surprised it works so well here. The little details in this game... Once I figured out the first area the rest wasn't too tough. I am so glad you put the fire flower tube in the Bowser area or I might have gotten frustrated because you have to be pretty precise to get that far.

Please try mine: 31C8-0000-0084-847A </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 04:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good one. I love vaporizing the huge enemies with a Yoshi bounce.

Please try mine: 31C8-0000-0084-847A </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 04:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost Home

31C8-0000-0084-847A

New today - A revision of a recent level of mine based on your feedback. It's a short, tricky level that should be easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 04:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was great! A good bit harder than mine. Is there a use for the Yoshi that I missed? The platforming all in all was tight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 01:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very busy beginning. I enjoyed the cave middle section the most. 

Please try mine: 31C8-0000-0084-847A </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 01:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First tried it. I thought it was a fun set up. Was there something in particular the pow block was for? 

Please try mine: 31C8-0000-0084-847A It is easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 01:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost Home

31C8-0000-0084-847A

Should be easy to complete. I was going for fun and challenging. I don't believe it is cheap at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 21:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was the first huge Mario level that relied on bouncing off the Luigi's. That was good enough for a star from me. 

Please try my newest level: 31C8-0000-0084-847A </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 21:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got stuck in the second room on my first go round because Magikoopa spawned a shell I kicked and it killed both of them. Other than that, it was a neat level. 

Please try mine: 31C8-0000-0084-847A </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 21:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First try. I made it to the end as big Mario so I just strong armed the two moles. Is there a way to get past them otherwise?

Please try my level: 31C8-0000-0084-847A </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 21:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost Home

31C8-0000-0084-847A

A revision of a recent level of mine based on your feedback. It's a short, tricky level that should be easy.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 10:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you aim to hit the goal at lowest possible point you will get by him. You can do it more reliably if you land on the last cannon and jump from there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 07:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A newly minted level - Aiming for a 10-20% completion rate. Loosely inspired by Butter Bridge 1 2 from Super Mario World. It is short and to the point, but I hope it is tricky.

Butter Pass

E3F9-0000-0081-3B05 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 14:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for trying it out. That Sumo stun there was deliberate. In most cases it keeps the player from getting the block with the other mushroom if they aren't prepared for it. And I thought the thwomp added some last minute drama... The level is short enough that I hoped people wouldn't get frustrated by these things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 13:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A newly minted level - Aiming for a 10-20% completion rate. Loosely inspired by Butter Bridge 1 2 from Super Mario World. It is short and to the point, but I hope it is tricky.

Butter Pass

E3F9-0000-0081-3B05

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 01:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stomp the Yard (Or Headbutt)

Basically lets you wreck shit with impunity. I keep replaying it myself because I like carnage. The first version of this level was super hard and barely anybody beat it, so I made a few big tweaks and it became my most popular level. 27 stars right now.

5B64-0000-004D-37E5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 11:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enjoyed it. I'm surprised it took this long for me to run into a level like that. You should make a harder version. Also I liked how you ended with a vine trip to the clouds.

Please try mine: BB3F-0000-0074-4C11 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 11:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got lost in there! But I beat it finally on the first try. I know it's sacrilege to say but I never played Kid Icarus except for maybe a minute. So I had no idea where to go.

Please try my level: BB3F-0000-0074-4C11 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 10:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beat Way to Honor. I liked the overall flow of it. Nice job.

Please try mine: BB3F-0000-0074-4C11 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 10:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not bad. I enjoyed it. Traditional.

Try my traditional level: BB3F-0000-0074-4C11 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 10:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I Came To Stomp Bombs - Wow, I beat it. I like how I had to make choices. Nothing felt cheap to me. This is one of the best multi-path levels I've played. I ended up kicking the bombs that came out of the sideways tube very carefully to open up a little hole for little Mario to edge out and jump for the flag. I know there must have been other ways but I kept getting stuck. 

Please try my Rebounding level or the easier one, Cheesy Meadows that I posted above and let me know what you think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 10:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Level Title: Rebounding

ID: 20CD-0000-0067-1605

Description of Gameplay Elements: After throwing my body at Pit of Panga: P-Break last week, I decided to create a tutorial level to teach players how to overcome it's first obstacle. You must jump, then kick a shell while in air into a spring and then bounce off the shell and over some spikes. My level helps you build up to it. Let me know if this is helpful or fun at all. I might make other tutorial levels for the seemingly impossible kaizo type challenges that aren't so impossible if you isolate them.

Video: https://youtu.be/SveqwVIOojY 

Section 1: Demonstrates bouncing over the spikes on a Bullet Bill.

Section 2: When you kick a shell into the spring, you will notice that is bounces back raised off the ground. In order to pass the wall you will have to bounce off it while it is off the ground. It helps me to have a running start.

Section 3: Similar to the Pit of Panga start but with a walkway underneath to prevent insta-death. Jump, kick the shell at the spring, bounce off it and over the spikes as the shell rebounds toward you.

Section 4: Same thing, but without training wheels.

OR

Trying something much easier:

Title: Cheesy Meadows

ID: BB3F-0000-0074-4C11

Feels like basic platforming from the old games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 09:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheesy Meadows

My girlfriend always watches me play so I made a level easy enough for her.

BB3F-0000-0074-4C11 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 01:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw crap thanks for looking for the level. That's the one I was putting up. Anyway its easy once you figure it out. Stars much appreciated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 01:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad you had mushrooms for every obstacle. I was a nice level of difficulty. I first tried it but it wasn't easy.

Please try either of these easy ones:

BB3F-0000-0074-4C11

CEC1-0000-004E-F127 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 00:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You used the effects well. It felt more like a spook house than a regular Mario level. I starred it because of the door to the buzzsaws. 

Please try either one of these easy levels:

BB3F-0000-0074-4C11

CEC1-0000-004E-F127
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 00:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Played both. Mario to Yoshi definitely had some charm. I wish I had the Bowser costume. 

Please try these two easy ones of mine: 

BB3F-0000-0074-4C11

CEC1-0000-004E-F147

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 00:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> P Switch Maze I liked, although I kept getting stuck at the only section when I need every bit of the P Switch time to scale up. I'd have to start completely over if I didn't make it. So consider revising it to have a tube with p-switches for that section.

Please try an easy one of mine: BB3F-0000-0074-4C11 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 00:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice. The sliding area was the best part. I haven't seen it set up quite like that. 

Please try mine: BB3F-0000-0074-4C11 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 00:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend always watches me play so I made her an easy level. It was meant to play like a real Mario level.

Cheesy Meadows

BB3F-0000-0074-4C11 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 01:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made a level easy enough for my girlfriend to beat. 

Cheesy Meadows

BB3F-0000-0074-4C11

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 08:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stomp the Yard (Or Headbutt)

Basically lets you wreck shit with impunity. I keep replaying it myself because I like carnage.

5B64-0000-004D-37E5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 08:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough. It's a learning experience for me. Every other level of mine was built around a concept. This one I tried going bland for practice sake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
