<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1323</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had the opposite. Once dreamed that I had a wife and I loved her very much but she died. In my dream, I was distraught when she died. When I woke up I was still sad because of "my loss" and I stayed sad for most of that day.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 12:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only answer here is a stupid one so let me try to actually respond. 

The threat varies GREATLY across different countries, even countries that just neighbour each other. Lets start with the easy ones. 

The US: Extremely low risk. The threat of a terrorist attack originates from different factors, mainly the strength of the govt., location, and demographics. The US has each of these on its side. Super strong gov., very low muslim population and a massive distance from any majority muslim country. The only thing that negates these factors is that the US is the most attractive target for most terrorist organizations. Al Qaeda. ISIS, Taliban all want to hit the US but currently they have less than a 5% chance of being successful. So I would say the chances of an American dying in a terrorist attack are ~1%.

Next is Europe: Moderate to low risk. Unlike the US, Europe only has the benefit of many powerful governments and a powerful coalition of powerful governments. Besides that, many European countries have significant Muslim populations, and Europe is bordered on the East and South by large Muslim countries. The Mediterranean Sea is the only geographic barrier between them. It doesnt help that Europes recent immigration problems heightened the threat by allowing hundreds, maybe thousands, of terrorists to stream through their bodies. And while the vast majority of the refugees or migrants are not terrorists, there will be problems with their integration into European society and these problems could lead to the radicalization of even more people. With all of these, there is a moderate risk of European people dying in attacks. This risk is moderate to low in places like France, very low in places like Germany and almost nonexistent in places like Bulgaria and Slovakia, where the terrorist organizations have very low interests in carrying out attacks. Even with these risks, most European countries have strong institutions that will help prevent and deal with any potential attacks. The police, intelligence and social agencies in these countries actually work. Notice how most of the terrorists who have carried out attacks so far were already being monitored. There are probably thousands more being monitored by European police some because they already have terrorist links, others simply because they are at risk of radicalization. And, no, the worlds greatest continent will not just wither and die because France voted for a liberal banker as president. 

Middle East: Very high. And in some places, Extremely high. When the US state and defence departments talk about thousands of terrorist attacks occurring each year, the majority of those attacks occur in the Middle East. Key countries are Syria, Yemen, Iraq, Turkey, Pakistan, and Afghanistan. All of these have large terrorist organizations carrying out daily operations both within and outside their ongoing wars. People die from terrorist attacks here every day and the issue is distinguishing acts of war, purposeful attacks on civilians (this is what constitutes a terrorist attack) and attacks by the govt. Outside these hot zones, you have countries like Lebanon, Jordan, Bahrain, Oman; where the threat is moderate to low. And Iran, UAE, Saudi Arabia, where the risk of dying in a terrorist attack is very low. Notably, if you look at the three checks I used before. The Middle East lacks all three. Few strong governments, located smack in the Middle of Islamic lands and their populations are constituted of Islamic majorities. 

The Others: High to non-existent. Some parts of Africa like Nigeria, Somalia, Mali, Libya, are extremely high risk for many of the same reasons given above for the Middle East. For places like Kenya, Egypt, the risk is moderate. Countries like the Philippines, India, are low risk. Then you have places like the Oceanic countries and Latin America, where the risk is largely non-existent. 

This all focuses on Islamic terrorism. No focus on state-sponsored terrorism or attack by non-Islamic groups.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 10:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The places where I know they have Gorillas are Rwanda, DRC, Uganda, Cameroon and (I think) the Republic of Congo. To be honest, I dont know much about the last three, but Uganda and Rwanda are pretty good. Both have a lot of wildlife, great scenery and theyre quite safe. Uganda has more attractions than Rwanda, being smack in the middle of the Great lakes region and has a couple of lakes that you could visit as well like Victoria, Kivu, Albert. I honestly dont know much about the cuisine and culture in those places though. I know Cameroon and the Republic of Congo are safe too, but I know nothing about tourism in those countries. 

Your other option, with limited time, is to choose a country with a large variety of attractions. South Africa, Kenya, Tanzania, Morocco and Algeria are all great for this, especially the first 3. With SA, Kenya and Tz, you have great wildlife, excellent beaches and natural attractions like the lakes, mountains, the rift valley etc. So you could choose one of those countries so you can enjoy a lot of different attractions at the same time. With Kenya and Tz you also have a great mix of cultures with a blend of urban western, indigenous African and Arab cultures in places like Zanzibar, Dar es Salaam, Mombasa and Lamu. 

If you want to focus on the people and culture part then Morocco, Algeria, Egypt, and Ethiopia are definitely in. They all have good cuisine, interesting cultural mixes and a lot of historical sites, especially Ethiopia and Egypt. Those four countries are, however, very light on wildlife. 

So the deciding factor is how much you want to see or what you really want to see. Different options in each of these countries and with one - two weeks you will be able to visit a lot of great places in whatever country you pick. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 08:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much time do you have? Two days, one week, three weeks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. I guess yes...

2. Going home. Only 30 mins left.

3. The last place you kept it

4. Definitely water

5. No. She's just really disorganized and never delegates.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
