<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1239</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 01:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peanut butter goes great with muenster cheese. Not sure about the chicken and rice though. Hmm... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 23:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. It's actually delicious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 23:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure it depends on the person, but if I eat anything significant before I go for a run I get cramps and feel sick. I'll usually chug a ton of water, have a natural peanut butter and banana sandwich on one folded slice of potato bread (carbs won't help much with weight lifting, but will give you some energy for things like running) with some coffee, and after maybe 30 minutes or so I'll have that digested enough to do some body-weight stuff and start running. After that I'll have real breakfast (couple eggs and some oatmeal, chug some egg whites, maybe tuna fish mixed in the oatmeal if I'm really hungry. Shoving some veggies in your eggs won't hurt either, get a variety of greens into our diet if you haven't already. Pick two that you like and alternate).

Honestly, for food suggestions, google Chris Tuttle's "Size for Seventy". Will tell you everything you should be eating to fuel workouts, $70 to buy all that food (I come in below that most of the time) and it should last you a week or two depending on how much you eat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 22:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being abused as a kid by both "parents" and treated like garbage by my school (both 90% of the students and several staff members) throughout elementary-high school, coupled with my grandfather being such an awesome father figure led to me becoming an incredibly strong-willed and compassionate person, where I proudly serve in both EMS and the military. I know exactly how much pain and cruelty is in the world and I'll be damned if I won't spend my life beating that darkness to a pulp. I may believe that Lovecraft was right and the universe is a cold, apathetic place that doesn't give a single damn about any human concerns, but it still matters to me.

When life gives you lemons, squeeze them in your eyes and give life the fucking finger. Then go out and make the world a better place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 18:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a common thing for us EMS/Military folks who see it all the time. We have to belittle it and make a joke of it in order to vent. I do indeed laugh when I see some drunk driver get ejected and fly 40 feet through the air into a semi truck on a dashcam video, but I've seen it in real life firsthand plenty of times, among other things, and have just gotten used to the horror of it. 

For someone who has no such job experience thinking it's funny, believe me, nobody hates edgy posers more than we do. If you're really so "tough" then grow some fucking balls and get your EMT card like the rest of us. You have to *earn* the right to make jokes about this sort of stuff. It's a badge of honor we take very seriously, as it speaks to what we go through so other people can be healthy and safe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 18:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lucero is my go-to band when you're any kind of down, be it the random blues or in the midst of tragedy like this. Highly relevant

"Mom"= https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VQwvOOyN1rg

also "Fistful of Tears" (which the song is really good at giving me": https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9uKe5EdQ_6Y list=PLI1hcO0XyUKkRB0amazVPfLRMkT2G_FMq index=7 

Zac Brown's "Bittersweet" is the song I listened to after my dad died: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=y3O55nG2oNM

And some more bluesy stuff, Ryan Bingham's "Southside of Heaven" is what I listen to when I get homesick:https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gF--Aw6lD2c

Stay strong, friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beyond frustrated with Civ V Worldbuilder/in game editor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 04:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cannot, for the life of me, get either of these things to work without crashing seconds later. The moment I open the ingame editor from the workshop and try to modify terrain, Civ 5 CTDs. Fine, I'll use the worldbuilder instead. Except that while I can use the initial map generation tools, and then proceed to the fine tuning portion of editing that map, I get about 10-20 seconds tops before the whole program says "Worldbuilder has stopped working"

I've tried every single method I've found online. I've tried the shortcut method, I've tried the CMD promp method. I've tried running it in offline mode, and I've tried opening the exe directly. I'm running Windows 10 with fully updated everything: Dirext X, drivers, steam, Civ, windows, etc. IS there any way I can get this thing to work for longer than 10 fucking seconds? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 09:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still not convinced my tourist trap beach town of rich step ford smilers isn't secretly run by a cult of lovecraftian nightmares slowly driving everyone to madness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 21:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you date the same girl as me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 21:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 21:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm an atheist myself so this isn't a moral issue at all for me, but in people who ARE religious, and/or who genuinely believe in an afterlife, how can you possible think remarriage is okay? If you really do believe that you will be reunited with your loved ones in an afterlife, how can you possible think it will be okay to show up with another spouse? Your heaven must be full of scorned lovers.

Again I don't have any issue with remarriage at all, but it boggles my mind when people who have convictions about an afterlife do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 03:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nails down a chalkboard. Doesn't make me cringe at all. Never got why it's so hated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 16:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I could play MW2 and CS:GO fine, those are the only two I have tried so far. I did turn down the graphics but that was to make sure I had the least lag possible online, but even before that it wasn't too bad. In fact, I don't think it had any effect at all; rather, it was simply my router. I'm playing over wi fi on a laptop, so I don't expect much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 07:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your input. I didn't have any illusions about the odds, but I appreciate you taking the time to let me know for sure. I'll wait for my desktop PC instead. I have looked into external cards for laptops but I don't think the effort to install them and such is worth the trouble. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 05:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want to know what the fuck the story is about because after three games with the same ending I have no idea why things are how they are or why I should care about the flame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 10:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was that an invitation? Like, can we all come to your house and pet your dog? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 01:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly we don't. Scientists are aware that while we on Earth have a list of conditions that support life as we understand it, and logically conclude that keeping an eye out for those conditions will increase our chances, they are also aware that anything we encounter may be (in fact most likely will be) so alien and different that we may not be able to relate to it or interact with it like we can to other human beings, even if it is "intelligent".

Only Hollywood is responsible for the idea we will meet aliens like in Star Trek or Mass Effect where they're basically humans with funny colors and appendages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 22:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The terrain they have is their only major advantage. Anyone can defend their own turf, even against the US. That doesn't mean Russia can pull off the mass invasions they wage in any seasonal FPS.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 22:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Despite what they'd like you to think, aside from its nukes, Russia is not a credible threat militarily. They talk a big talk but they've always been quite backwards.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 22:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More like people will be forever baffled that not only did North Korea actually exist (the place is something out of a black comedy film) but it was so convinced of its own arrogance that it threw rocks at the gates of hell expecting anything other than complete annihilation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 22:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Garbage. Needs more Dunkey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 04:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>       I do great Gene Simmons impressions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 00:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My concern about dying is that I hope it's a "worthy death". That can mean taking a bullet for a brother in the field, being a hero in a civilian emergency (fire, mass shooting) or dying while doing something otherwise dangerous but rewarding (mountain climbing, wilderness survival exhibition). I don't have a lot of hope for myself as a laid back civilian who chills in his house all my life until I get old and die in a hospital, and frankly, I'd rather die young than grow old, alone, and non ambulatory. 

I also don't see anything to suggest death isn't nonexistence, so after the fact I won't have the capacity to care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 10:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rebels, Rouges,   Sworn Brothers- Lucero

Pawn Shop- Brothers Osborne

Magpie and the Dandelion - Avett Brothers

The Whippoorwill - Blackberry Smoke

You get what you give - Zac Brown Band </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 03:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate that, normally a thankless job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
