<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2728</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which would you like to know most about, know the full capacity of the brain, explore 100% of the ocean, or 100% of space? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But if you agree, meet me at blockbuster, were renting rampart, then ramming eachothers farts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im high as a knife ask me anything. If this gets 1000 uptokes i wont kill myself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does it feel to make a 30 year old cry? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if yall commenters are a bunch of circle jerking divas, or if im unversally hated by everyone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like the warning that youre entering the wilderness in runescape?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Oops sorry seems my outie has slipped into your innie" 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Patrick star? You've finally come up from under your rock? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably fairly moist of up in there aswell ;). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goddamnit mom! You lied to me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im sorry i assumed the state of your belly button  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People are different heights doesnt stop the P from going in the vagee. Its called reverse cow button </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats just gross lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, i feel that. There were so many girls in highschool that people said were ugly but they werent. I mean they didnt have the best faces but if you looked past that they had some of the best bodies in the grade. Their loss, more for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Californication, thats 70s show, eastbound and down, the supranos, the office. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive been to both, and as some of them do get out of hand and dangerous, i feel that it is an important experience.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does that have to do with anything? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> shut the fuck up! shut the fuck up with that!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol wow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can definitly say that teens are being less social then before. That may be you but i know so many kids who dont even know how to carry a normal conversation. Their vocabulary is so limited to texting terms that its not even fun to talk to them. I mean im not saying all of them obviously, however a significantly larger amount than before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have so many but my favorite theiry is the theory that any thing you think can happen, either can hapoen, has happened , or will happen because the universe is infinite. So if you think, man i wish (a certsin person) wasn't alive there actually may br a universe where everything is the same except that perzin was never born, or there may not be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never look back! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is...people become less social. That was your time to meet new friends and to converse with the opposite sex. Who doesnt look forward to a good party in highschool? I mean thats what weekends were all about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk about anyone else but i graduated highschool in 2016, and from my freshman year to senior year the younger kids have changed so much. When i was in gr 9 we had so much respect for the older kids, and looked up to them and i realized as i was becominf a senior the younger kids became more disrespectful. Inalso boticed that they were dumbed down and boring because they were looking st their phones all day. We would throw parties all the time, while the younger kids bsrely threw any at all, i think its from lack of motivation like "why throw a party when theres social media". I also noticed the younger the more they used laptops, most of my frade preferred to learn with the old pencial and paper, while the younger generation all used laptops and online learning. Bottom line is im glad i was born in 1998, i mean i wish i was born sooner but at least im not born in the 2000s and im not glued to my fucking phone screen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im a good guy greg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 07:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Id go dickless for you if i didnt already for a sir michael chick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 07:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL that im a pimp and a cool!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 01:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well i thinki did ok, i had 3 people on me and got punched by someones dad eneded up breaking my nose. I did ok  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you were placed on top of a 25 foot tall and 10 foot wide cinder block with nothing but a 25 foot rope (with nothing to attatch the rope to) how would you get down? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 01:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> were beefing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
