<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3788</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 16:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got it. Good work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 16:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same. I was about two months out from starting law school. I enjoyed the process. It was nice to see the court process from an angle not many people are privy to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 16:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That/you are incredible. Do you have any sources I can read up on the history as to why so many were appointed? Thank you for your input, I really appreciate the post.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 16:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bar Chart: [Here](https://www.scribd.com/doc/139198420/BarCharts-Secured-Transactions)

A9 has a TON of information. It is important to chunk everything up correctly, even though it ties together. Learn the basics and terminology and it will come a lot easier for you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a very good idea, what a good friend you are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Res Ispa Loquitur (the thing speaks for itself). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ginsberg and Kennedy vacancies could need nominations within Trump's presidency as well. That would be an unbelievable shift in the current formation of the Court; just saying. Has any President in the past nominated three or more Justices? I know a bunch have nominated two, but 1/3 of the Court is significant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have all Ridgid power tools. I like how the batteries are interchangeable, the color (big Detroit Tigers fan), and the lifetime warranty. I did find a combo pack in CL, but that would not include the warranty. To get the warranty you have to register the tools within 90days of purchase from an authorized retailer. There are deals to be had though I found some other tools I'm considering purchasing.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He isn't a nut on the stuff. It's funny you mentioning the dovetail. My YouTube search yielded about an hour of speciality cuts and router cuts; needless to say, I was in awe. So many DIY projects came to mind as soon as I saw that first cut!    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 22:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really appreciate the input. I have seen the hand miter saws, but my father in law told me "nothing better then an electric saw," so I'm basing my bias on his words. I have no problem with a hand saw and wouldn't mind the extra work put in. Plus like you said you can find a cheaper good quality set up for a reasonable price.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 22:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not that one as in you have not tried it, or not that one period? 

My budget is fairly limits due to student loans. I was looking at the miter saw and considering doing the trim in my house rather then patching/painting. Plus the versatility speaks to the quality of what I'd be buying; I'm on the fence now. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 22:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought about a jigsaw as well, but I'm thinking my DIY will revolve around thicker wood. 

I do on the other hand absolutely know I need a reciprocating Saw...those are just f***ing sweet! Haha.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the info on the blades, that is perfect and very understandable. Those Miter Saws are all pretty expensive. I know I don't do much DIY with wood now, but I can feel once I get going I won't look back at the price. I can see the operational ease of choosing the right tool for the job. Thank you I appreciate your time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been watching YouTube and researching a bit. I am a Ridgid guy, I saw they have a circular saw, but the reviews are mixed.  

It's the: Gen5X 18Volt 7-1/4in Cordless Brushless Circular Saw. I saw considering getting this to start, any experience with it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Ort Cloud has always interested me. Does every solar system have an Ort Cloud?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Type of Saw(s) needed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time I go to HomeDepot to look/buy a saw I am offered the top of the line saw. The thing is I know nothing about saws and wood. 

Basically I want something that I can cut 2x4 and plywood, but I don't necessarily want a table saw. Is there a handheld saw I can buy that will do the trick? 

My current projects are making shelves for the interior of my closet and laundry room. Do I need a saw based on the cut I'm making? The wood I'm cutting? 

Any help would be amazing, thank you in advance. 


Edit: I went with a Ridgid Circular Saw! [Saw Photo](https://imgur.com/gallery/fj3QU)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 02:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could try, but I'm sure they have some type of verifying information. This is very interesting, could you keep us/me posted? Thank you in advance!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 22:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This photo puts my entire existence into perspective. Smh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 11:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, you have to consider that was the world headquarter for GM, Chrysler, and Ford for nearly 100 years; there are some loyal families. My wife's family had worked at Ford for nearly 70 years ( her grandfather and father) and they only drive Ford...very loyal drivers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 11:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point on the full coverage. I think that's a huge savings as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 00:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard those last forever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 23:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you on not agreeing with my original statement. 

I guess it depends on where you are located. Personally for me I am from Michigan. The ratio of American cars to foreign is easily 10:1...therefore most places that service American cars and charge extra for foreign.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 22:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With photos like this, how can people be so narrow minded? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 21:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can find a good car for $2500-$3500. I did and have put 50,000 miles on it so far. 

Edit: Buy American cars, the service and parts will be cheaper.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is almost always a heartbreaking story behind each pro.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well he needs to pick one or the other...or get a career where he can support everything and you. Poker does have a strategy but it also has a lot of luck involved.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have so much to learn. Smh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's good, it could be a lot worse. I have a friend that gambles about everything; he bet me the other day about how fast he could eat an apple. 

Just keep an eye out and protect yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem. You could even put in the contract an event that will terminate the tenancy: Y'all breaking up. 

That way it's spelled out in writing. All you would have to do is provide him with a break letter to make it final. Then if he doesn't leave you can evict him the hard way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 16:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Delusional l, yes. Love is sometimes the worst enabler. He needs help. He will start playing behind your back, on his phone, etc. Does he only gamble with poker or are there other things like sports? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 16:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, you go girl! 

Just draft up a lease agreement for an at will teneacy, that way if you break it off he isn't entitled to stay for the remaining lease period. 

I would suggest going to a local attorney to see if there are any jurisdictional loops to jump through. Find an Attorney in your area who will offer a free consultation.  

I think your price is fair too; maybe bump it to $700 + utilities, he is still saving $500/mo. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 16:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say read the small print.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 14:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's so scary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 14:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your input. For a Collector standpoint, is there a master list of sorts of titles/editions that are collectible?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 14:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have noticed that style of sale for a while now, defiantly interesting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 01:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol I agree, thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 23:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What state?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 21:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 21:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thought the same thing, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Vintage Book Lot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 20:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was doing my daily scan and came across a vintage book lot. I was negotiating with the owner and they have 123 vintage books dating as early as 1900. I'm skeptical on purchasing the lot because they want $1/per book and said they purchased the lot for $240. 

My concern is: 

(1) $1.00/per sucks--I offered $0.50 they said no. 

(2) The photo is blurry and I can't see the titles; no additional photos available. 

(3) I feel they have already combed through them. 

What's your input into this scenario?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 19:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a way John is the designer of more buildings then his father Frank.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can add my cars to this list also. Haha my wife's car has some, she says they remind her of me. I told her fill my casket up with I die.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 17:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's such a shitty feeling sometimes...smh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 17:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem. Just be careful because that Accountant has a fiduciary duty to the company and NOT you. I would take that info they give you and take it to a local attorney/CPA for a second look; find someone who gives a free consultation. 

There is no per se marketplace for closely held companies to determine value, unless they are a publicly traded company.

You are going to ask for all the correct information to determine value, however you can't purchase until your three years vest--things could be vastly different. You could gather all that information now and then gather it later to compare the progress, then use that to make your determination. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 16:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they were offering you shares as part of an ESO (Employee Stock Option) I can understand they have a vesting period. The vesting period is in place to prevent people from starting with the company, buying stock, and then leaving; the three year vesting period is there to protect and vet the employee in a way. 

The vesting period is the time you must wait until your authorized to exercise your ESO. This "option" is a choice you have whether to exercise your right or not. You can take that three (3) years to see if the company is going up or down in performance/value. Regardless of what the company is worth, you will have the right to purchase the stock for $1.00/share once your (3) years is up. 

You cannot purchase stock in the company until you are vested. 

Now, if they are giving you the option to purchase stock in the company at that rate, and then giving you a vesting period--either you are getting misinformed or have relayed the wrong info. Did you get any paperwork? Normally once you purchase stock in a company you are automatically vested in your acquisition and can freely transfer all of a portion of your stock if you choose to; there is no vesting period. 

I would have to see what information they gave you. They may be engaging in some shady dealings where they offer their employees an option to buy at $1.00 and then letting them go before they are fully vested. I don't know all the facts and don't want to jump to that conclusion, but be careful spending your money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 22:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wanna sell it? I know a buyer ;D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 02:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lawyer is going to tell you they must be reasonable in: 

(1) Scope;
(2) Duration; and 
(3) Location. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 23:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's false. Non-competes are not strictly enforceable, they must be reasonably drawn. You may have some jurisdictional differences, but from where I come from they are not flat out unenforceable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. Perfect weight/height ratio. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 18:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Top sell: Red/White/Blue Super Rare $10,000.00  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 17:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, your correct. OP cannot wait until 2017 to take these deductions. I was saying that, yes while you are technically in 2017, that doesn't matter and OP should use the expenses as deductions for their 2016 filing; not 2017. 

Disclaimer: Also not a CPA.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 15:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a similar mindset about collaborating. I dislike those individuals who take your concepts and then passes them of as their own. I tend to hold my ideas close to my chest. I know this may shelter them and prevent them from becoming something. I only have a few people I can trust that I know won't say anything and will give me honest feedback.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 15:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. I would read your contract to see whether there is a non-compete, and if so, to what extent. Also, some company contracts will restrict you from working another position if it poses a possible conflict-of-interest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 13:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Collection companies are more open to negotiate with you; but that is usually because the company has already sold you account at a discount. You could try it and see, but there is no guarantee. If you do so, do it in writing so you have written record of the discharge of the remaining balance.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 12:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I did something similar in an economic/accounting class in high school. Our teacher gave each student $5.00 and had us "invest" the money in one "investment" in our class. She had three total "investments" and they would fluctuate through the semester. The investments were (1) Stock Market--3 types of stock; (2) Real Estate; and (3) 401K/ Retirement. 

So basically the teacher allowed us to invest in what we wanted in the beginning of the class. The goal was to finish the class with $5.00 or more, then she had a scale as to the level of grade you would get for the project based on how much you have. You could pull out your money at any time but you had to keep a balance sheet of every investment, profits/losses, and a goal for the investment. 

I thought it was interesting because she made us accountable for our grade by giving us the cash and having to manage it. I also thought it was very receptive to some of the usual "tuned out" individuals because they could engage in the decision making of pulling their money in and out of growth/shrink. 

You could give them a folder with their name on it as if it was their portfolio. Inside the portfolio you will have a $5.00 bill; instructions, balance sheet, etc. If they make bad investment choices and they loose $5.00, they can choose to invest by taking out a mortgage or riding out their investments; you can see where I'm going.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 12:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it's basically just magnetic tape. It takes a long time though and the environment plays a role in degradation. Mine are all about 20-25-30 years old (wow, that's weird) and in plastic tubs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 12:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I would say there are a few things you could do:

(1) Contact the inspector and ask if they waived the past fail or the initial inspector was incorrect;

(2) Contact a local real estate attorney who gives free consultations who can tell you yes/no as to whether there is a code; 

(3) Contact the Condo Board and inquire of any of them has dealt with the code requirements you've encountered. 

I wouldn't pay them until you get a clear answer. Who knows what occurred and it's better to get to the bottom of it now, instead of later.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 02:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over sight? Same inspector? 

If it's not to code you could get a fine and then have to move it later on. You've paid the GC and you paid the interior design firm to manage the GC, you failed the initial inspection--and it wasn't fixed to comply with the initial inspection! 

This is a no brainier to me, your the boss, tell them to run the sprinkler to comply like they should have.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 01:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't do this. PERIOD.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 23:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You already did the best thing: you consulted your attorney, now let him do his job.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My understanding is yes, since the tax deadline has not passed. I'm not qualified to make that call though, call a CPA for a free consultation to double check.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have all the VHS tapes from my childhood too. I plan on teaching my kids to play them by themselves; a lot more durable then DVDs. Haha, what a father I will be!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't pay any fees. There should be no problem waking into any bank, credit union, etc. to open the account. In my opinion try a credit union, they are local banks that service the community and have favorable interest rates as opposed to national chains. 

Here is the scenario: You meet with your client, negotiate the contract, and they provide you with a down payment. Next you take that check and deposit it into your business checking account. Then you cut a check from the business account to you personally, and you have your money to deposit/cash the check at your bank. 

I don't know how your LLC is set up tax wise so I can't make a call on that. What I would say is to go meet with an attorney who will give you a free consultation; talk with them about what I said and see if your jurisdiction requires anything else. Then after you talk with an attorney, do the same thing with a CPA who will give you a free consultation for the tax implications; ask if your LLC is a "Sub S Election" which allows you to write more expenses off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was just a lot to read that's all. I do completely agree with you too. I think writing is an art form and as the vast amount of the population pushes away from knowing how to read and write coherently. I think "we" provides value when presented in the right scenario.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to an 80's themed party the other day and had to explain what a cassette tape was to a 5 year old. I basically said it was MP3 files on magic tape, haha!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If gold will be in such high demand...why sell now? Those scare-tactic ads always crack me up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your still in the 2016 tax year, even though your in 2017 technically. I would use the Start up business deduction and write those off as expenses. 

That's the extent of my knowledge, I would consult a business attorney or a cpa; whoever will give you a free consultation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe I just read all that; skip to the summary everyone!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it would be safe to assume, especially if it's paid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea it's true. It would benefit the economy significantly, both in sales and services. I think there is way to much lobbying in Washington by the big alcohol companies. We shall see, it's been interesting already--who knows what's coming in the next four years.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. Lawyer up. Find someone who offers free consultations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard that's an interesting field to get into because of the struggles between Fed/State law's; supremacy clause trumps (no pun intended). 

I'm from MI and we have medical state wide and recreational at a few small municipality levels.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because your a "partnership" and you don't have a formal entity in place, your going to be 50/50 partners. However, if you can get a Partnership Agreement together and get down in writing that he is comfortable with 60/40 or 70/30 then you will be such as defined by your Partnership Agreement. 

A Partnership Agreement is basically a contract between two people who have agreed to engage upon a business for the mutual benefit of the profits. In a typical agreement you can set out who has what duties, who has what authority, and the limits/boundaries of such. 

You don't technically need a Partnership Agreement ( check your jurisdiction) to form a Partnership; they are used to settle disputes that arise. 

If you have more questions go talk to a business attorney who offers a free consultation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well bankruptcy is a fresh start. Seeing an attorney is not a bad thing, and in bankruptcy proceedings they cost nearly nothing; there are laws as to the prices attorneys can ethically charge. 

Also, having an attorney on your side is an advantage. They will give you a different perspective and sometimes they outside positive view is what most people need. 

Sounds to me like Chapter 7 is the route you should take. CH 7 is a straight liquidation proceeding where the bankruptcy trustee will itemize your assets. The advantage for CH 7 petitioners is the fact there are several exemptions one can make which would protect certain assets you own. For example, vehicles up to X amount, homes up to X amount, clothing up to X amount, jewelry, etc. 

You can sit down with the attorney and be able to have a frank conversation with them about your struggles and they will help direct you in the best possible route. 

You should contact a bankruptcy attorney in your area that gives free consultations. Go in with an open mind and have a chat. Quality of life is something everyone should have, and with your recent hiccup, a fresh start is probably exactly what you need. 

Good luck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think your going to have a hard time finding a bank that will secure a $53,000 debt with two vehicles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's free to open a bank account, and sometimes you can find a bank account that will give you $50-$100 for opening an account with them. 

This isn't anything to do with filing, you have to file taxes for your LLC regardless. This is about protecting yourself by separating--you from the business. 

For example, you shoot a gig but your contract required X and instead you did Y. Now they take you to court for breach of contract and it's clear you breached the contract. The judge awards in the client's favor the contract price, incidental damages, and attorney fees...usually your business would be on the hook for this, but (if they have a smart attorney) during the discovery phase they would have found out your business is not separated from you and they sue you individually by "piercing the corporate veil." Now you are jointly and severally liable for the awards the judge ruled for...you see what I'm saying. 

Your going to file separate tax returns anyways, unless you took a Sub S Election (talk with your CPA) which you would be itemizing your taxes as a flow through entity. Regardless, this is about protecting you FROM your businesses liabilities. 


Plus, if you sign up with PayPal they are going to charge you on every deposit/transaction. Don't use PayPal. 

Set up a bank account where you can deposit your clients checks. Then just pay yourself as a company employee by cutting yourself a check from the company checking account, and then go deposit that shit in your personal bank account. 

It may seem like it's a hassle, but I promise you, if you ever get sued it's better to have liability against your business and not you. Protect yourself you've come this far.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 20:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 20:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Delaware is the favorite of all the states, their courts are more favorable to businesses and the law is exceedingly developed because of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 20:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You will receive nothing, because you have already received it. 

When you purchase a home you transfer title of the property at the closing. Title is a legal term that means ownership. In property law the legal document that conveys title is called a deed. There are, usually, three types of deeds: 

(1) Warranty Deed: The owner who you are purchasing from proclaims title is clear steaming from before they owned it and after they owned it. (Greatest protection)

(2) Special Warranty: Owner proclaims title is clear ONLY from the point they took title to you taking title, not before they took title. 

(3) Quit Claim Deed: Owner proclaims NOTHING, just conveys title with no guarantee they even own the property. 

When you get a bank financed loan they require you to have a Warranty deed conveyed to you. They require a warranty deed because that transfers the greatest protection on their investment. Remember both you and the bank are investing in the transaction. Now when you close on the house there are title insurance documents you sign; part of the closing cost goes to a title insurance company who verifies the title is clear. 

Once you close, you are the owner of the property and have been conveyed title at the signing. What the bank does is files a lien on the property to perfect their interest in the amount you owe them. By protecting their interest they are putting all other potential lien holders on notice that they have a perfected security interest in the property and if any other lender wants to give you a loan and take your house as collateral they will have a junior lien to the banks senior lien. Sounds super complicated but it's not, it's just there for the banks to protect their interest if you were to file bankruptcy or failure to pay. 

After you pay off the loan the bank should send you the original promissory note you signed with them, stamped canceled or paid, whatever their system is. The bank should also send you a mortgage release; this is the most important document--you should immediately go and have this recorded at the country registrar of deeds. 

The records are recorded in chronological order. When you go to sell that home one day the title insurance company will review the record and see that you took out a lien on the property and X years later you have a stamped/ certified release of that lien. If you/the bank does not record the release it will show that you still have a lien on your property and the deal could fall through. 

If you have any other questions consult a real estate attorney who will give you a free consultation. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 19:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Simply put your defeating the purpose of your LLC. 

The LLC is in place to protect you personally from business operations. I would strongly urge you to sever the connection between your business and your personal accounts. If anything were to arise you could be held personally liable for debts of your LLC by "piercing the corporate veil." Simply go to a local bank and set up a account in the business name, and only use it for business purposes; the sooner you do this the better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 19:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. You can save on shipping overall, but the Buyer will be looking for a reduction in the shipping expense as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 19:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a pearl in a clam.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 19:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could go with the new Letgo App. It's easy to sell at retail on there, and stuff usually goes quick. If you do use Letgo don't use your full name. The app pings the nearest tower using your cell phone and usually can narrow you don't pretty close to your actual location. Then, if your full name is used, you can easily do a quick google search to narrow down your actual address. 

My aunt had a guy who showed up at her house because she was selling something he really wanted; super weird, and cops told us that's how he did it. 

PM me with a list of what you have, I may be interested in some of it if your willing to ship it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 16:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Debt. There is only one way to go...forward. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 16:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries your good. I would consult a general practitioner who practices business/litigation law. What city are you in (you can PM me, I can help find one with a free consultation)?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 16:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your going to want to consult an attorney. You have a possible claim of action and if you sit on your right the statute of limitations may bar you from restitution. Go meet with an attorney who will give you a free consultation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 15:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next stop...Iceland!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 01:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a lot of shit... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty sad that we exploit 4/6 of those for our own benefit. (Not an activist of any kind, just puts it into perspective) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 00:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Consult an attorney.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 21:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Earth is round...and it rotates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 19:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can go to a local courtroom on their motion days to sit in and listen to attorneys argue their motions before the presiding judge. 

Call your local courtroom and ask for the schedule. Also, ask them if they have any interesting cases coming up and you can go sit in on the trial. 

I just sat in on a murder case that a judge I know was presiding over. Super interesting and good to listen how other professionals present/argue the law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 19:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, that's amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 19:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had people do this as well. I wouldn't go through the headache. Your only going to save a few on the sale price anyways, so why take a steep discount on the price.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 18:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My new phone background, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 18:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Way to go IS...

I hope they go there and find that they accidentally uncovered some kind of super significant ancient artifact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 18:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like: r/Flipping  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 17:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome shot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 17:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. 

People were doing this with Rolex watches. I read an article on this a long time ago, I will try and find it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 17:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. 

You have a large legal claim on your hands and if you sit on your rights you may be barred by the statute of limitations. Don't worry about legal fees, contact an attorney that will give you a free consultation. Don't contact them anymore and bring all your communications, the contract, the deed, and anything else you have to the meeting with the attorney. 

Good luck, remember the attorney will work for you and get this all squared away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 17:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. I would create the entity and up the price. Just tell them your enduring expenses and the price has risen slightly, they won't care because they will write it off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 17:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the US you can do work in-house as a compliance officer, you would be using your degree for a "JD Advantage" job.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 16:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many attorneys do transactional work. It really will depend on what type of law you choose to practice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
