<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3220</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 19:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for advices. You know, this restoration was one time shot. My first attempt. I don't have specialistic devices, especially something to do 'electrolysis bath' ;-) 
Olive oil isn't bad idea for kitchen wooden things. It's good for people, non poisonous. I'm using it not only for this knife but also in cutting desks projects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 15:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, there was the split, but it was only small crack, not very deep. I decided to leave it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 15:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great video, great sculptures. They are working pretty fast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 15:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If You like such videos there is the guy on youtube who makes such step-by-steps vids. Try to search for 'diresta'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 15:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 15:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if all cleavers have to bu such sharp... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 14:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something strange is happening. This is series of such accidents last time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 14:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Restoration of very rusty cleaver (knife) from trash - nice to watch step by step process </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 14:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 10:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are You planning to use this engine in real moving device ? This will be interesting! If You fit it in some vehicle please, post a video on redit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 10:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i guess  it's interesting.. ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 09:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks very nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 09:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the purpose of this engine ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Repairing $30 000 Damaged GIANT Tire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 09:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've made simple robot (autobot's baby ;-)) with my son. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 09:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crazy Polish rednecks making moving swimming pool from car </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 18:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 09:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can You post url for google street view ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 21:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi
I recommend You to make two simple cheeses. 
Rennet cheese (if You have rennet) like this:https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IpuPjCDCTWs
Or italian riccotta cheese (You need just vinegar and milk) like this: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IfqKV0C61lY
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 19:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some time ago, when Crimea was Ukrainian (as it should be), I was there and I found the big bridge with two pylons. This bridge was over the living houses and one of the houses was build around one pylon.
So, I guess, that in some country they don't care about living conditions at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can't believe, that this is not a fake. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 18:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 13:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> don't get me wrong, those imprefections doesn't disqualify Your good job ;-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 13:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So now I'm impressed much more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 13:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like proffesional work. Do You use some kind of pattern making that, or all was from Your head ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 11:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw that some time ago on YT.
I wonder how strong will be such junction. This bended playwood won't crac after some time ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 11:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> strange. This is really something cool but why anyone is upvoting it ?

one question - how durable it is ? I can imagine breaking connections after some time (sooner than later ;-)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 11:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it looks very nice. There was a really lot of work to do with all that painting. Good job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 11:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think You will have some support. You can glue the legs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 11:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be carefull with finishing Your projects with oil. The wood have to be almost perfectly sanded for that. Oil will reveal all imperfections and it will be devastating to see all Your work turning into something ugly during oiling.

If You want to sand, I recommend orbital sander.
First 120 or 180 then 240 and 300. After that look at the elemenst placing them against the light to see all potential imperfections.

But.. maybe You could use some stain (if You want to change the colour) and after that use the wax. Hm.. ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 10:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> great project. Maybe it isn;t the most beautiful but I like such projects where recycled elements are used.
Upvote from me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 10:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like You are doing two things wrong:
- don't use the sandpaper across the grain
- if You are cutting wood, start from the side which will be visible. Those chipping is because this piece of wood was cutted from bottom to top-from invisible part to visible part. In fact those chips were done earlier, by the saw. Sanding just reveal them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 10:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should post it to lifehack. This is real, and useful hack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 10:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very nice project. You could however use some sandpaper to mage the edges more smooth. On the photo there can be seen some imperfection on them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 08:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this video is a little bit funny but mostly strange </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oscilloscope Music - Pictures from Sound [for the electronic nerds] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 08:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A 4-bit Calculator made in cardboard and marble </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 23:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crazy russian su-27 pilot almost.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 20:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 23:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what it is so funny in this video ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 23:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I must say that this is very dynamic movie with a very proffesional like cuts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 23:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard that there is something simillar on the market like nintendo switch. I just can't remember the name of this product :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arena Security shows off his dancing skills at Amur game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 23:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Retro Shoe Cabinet - short, nice making of video [414] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 23:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
