<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1565</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 23:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I believe they matter a lot, especially in between material news flow. Not to mention how much of the market is driven by computers now, which rely much more on technicals. But I am no guru and would welcome other opinions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 13:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bingo! Trying to trade the swings is dangerous because as soon as you get on the wrong side of just one trade, you are immediately trying to correct your mistake, which brings emotion into it and often leads to more mistakes. Learned that one the hard way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 13:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking at all the charts yesterday, a surprisingly large number of stocks are sitting right on their 50day moving average, so today will be an important technical session imo. If the moving average provides support that's bullish, if not then we're heading down further. Personally, I would like to see the stocks open down, break their support just enough to scare everyone into selling only to reverse higher and close positive. For those with cash that presents a good buying opportunity and to me that would signal the bottom for now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 13:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great little town and golf course too. I am Canadian, but lived in CHCH for 7 years and used to come up to play the Kaikoura Open golf tournament a number of times. Best seafood around, but could barely stand the next day after too much piss the night before, so the golf was less than exemplary. Some of the kindest people in the world too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 11:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dammit! That's what I wanted to say. You take that back right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was gonna post something similar. On the left you have a the ultra clean diet, never smoked, probably doesn't drink, world class athlete while on the right you have t guys who have drank, smoked and injected anything they could get their hands on. At the time of this photo I wonder who was "more successful"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah....real fucked off his face in that photo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
