<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3614</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 09:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 09:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have actually. Few times. But I dont have the money to get a nice camera. On the other hand i have a nice old minolta which i would like to try but its not working and I cant find anyone near who would be able to repair it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 09:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually many people think the same since its what they know from school or art class but master quality watercolor usually comes in tubes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 09:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sure will. Thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 09:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I do. I jave an etsy shop. The link is somewhere in the comments </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 09:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theres also a song by "Foals" titled "out of the woods" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 09:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 09:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the comment. I have made etsy shop this week so theres no problem to ship to the US.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 21:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.etsy.com/shop/ContinuumWatercolors?ref=hdr_shop_menu
Here. Theres not much there yet. So if you dont find what you are looking for from the instagram just message me and i will add it there if its available.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 20:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 20:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is the best for me. The way he plays with lights and shadows is just amazing. And all the people he puts in his paintings...pure awesomness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 20:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its no mastery, to see the real mastery please google Joseph Zbukvic watercolors, that man is a genius, like for real. I am using watercolors since autumn 2015, so still learning, and trying to find whats right for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 20:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whats wrong with acid?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 20:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makes me proud, I will try to put smaller prices on smaller paintings that way it shouldnt be a problem for you in near future, in my opinion its just a pitty that the international shipping from Slovakia costs so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 20:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see no reason why not, we have etsy for that, dont we ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no problem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> for corrections of wrong sketching, I need a detailed sketch everytime, so not only to erase wrong pencil marks but also to make the rest not so visible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well on the left theres chinese white in tube. Technical pencil. Rubber and a cap from hand made bottle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two brushes. The small blue one is synthetic and the bigger one made of squirrel hair. The painting was done with just these two brushes. Than theres a black marker and in the upper right its the masking tape.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 18:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes through etsy. The link is somewhere in the thread </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 18:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no problem at all, as I said what ever works for you better, and thank you for the compliment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 18:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well for me it is easier to do it without etsy because I am not yet familiar with how it works,/dont want to sound stupid or dumb/ since i have some orders there already, and they are beeing procesed and so on. There was one guy andrew who wanted few pieces like you. He sent me and email with his request, we discused yesterday evening payment and shipping, and his paintings will be on their way tomorrow morning, while I will be waiting for etsy to end order processing. But it is up to you, which ever is better for you works for me too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 18:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do, i have opened etsy shop yesterday but there isnt much there yet, so if you dont find what youre looking for from my instag. just write me and if it is available i can put it there in no time.
https://www.etsy.com/shop/ContinuumWatercolors?ref=hdr_shop_menu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 18:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 18:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad you like it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makes me happy when my work gives someone reason to paint </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go ahead I will keep my fingers crossed for you. Hope it will go well!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much. There isnt much on etsy so if you find anything you like on my instagram just let me know. If it is available i can put it right there. Also we can discuss price shipping etc. i am open to such comunication at any time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All right will try. And dont worry about me forgeting you or this conversation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, well I have been drawing things since I can remember, I was that kind of a child that draws on everything, anytime and anywhere. But I am painting with watercolors since autumn 2015. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess we are not that different, I went actually to art school, but it was when i was about 6years old and finished it at about beeing12. Cant say I have learned anything since a corse one day a week isnt sufficient and can not teach you a thing when you have to do something completely different each course. I will try to post things regularly if they will be worth mentioning, comments like this give em really fuel into continuing painting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> your comment has made my heart all warm and happy, thank you for such a comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a lot of it is. I have made an etsy shop this week since there has been a great demand for paintings lately. All of my work can be found on instagram : https://www.instagram.com/continuum_transfunctioner/
etsy: https://www.etsy.com/shop/ContinuumWatercolors?ref=hdr_shop_menu
there isnt much on etsy yet, so if you find andything on the instagram you like and it isnt on etsy just write me an email /majercak.martin@gmail.com/ I can check the availibility and we can discuss further things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for such kind words. The thing is that I have started painting without any courses or lessons, then i have read a book about watercolors by the great Joseph Zbukvic and have purchased few videos by him and Alvaro Castagnet and only after that have I found out what I was doing wrong and what could be done better. After that I realised that it can be about someones talent but I guess its mainly about practice and knowledge of the technic and mediums you use, and since this has helped me great I guess it is only natural to pass these information on and on, since it doesnt take much to make the work look better in few little tricks. And as fellow artists we should push each other forward, give relevant critic and usefull tips. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you, hope to see nice comments when the series change :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh no i am not really, just trying to draw or paint something everyday to move forward and get step by step better, i guess thats the key to mastering anything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
