<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2519</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 12:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What you have done here is taken the last 8 years of Gandhi's life and made it seem that's all he did-you know he went on hunger strike in 1948 when India wouldn't give Pakistan any aid? This led to his assassination

Also he constantly was the head of Civil disobedience against the British and was fundamentally opposed to Muslims having to make a separate state/please don't just make sweeping generalisation if you haven't properly researched it - there is a reason Gandhi is beloved and it's not because he tested his celibacy or wanted India to return to a mediaeval style society  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 05:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah well Gandhi did a lot of good (testing his celibacy with his niece is not the greatest thing morally I'll grant that , and he was pretty racist in his younger days) thanks to his weird mixture of Christianity and Hinduism - really drove his pacifism and protest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you guys generally think about GOOD religious figures? (Who often look to their faith for guidance) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 05:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm mainly thinking of people like MLK, Jimmy Carter, Gandhi etc always has me conflicted on how I feel - I guess i just believe they are fundamentally good people anyway and maybe some positive lessons in the bible help them -idk-what does everyone else think? Do you respect them less for being religious?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maybe girls don't just want to have fun... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 05:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 05:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about listen to their problems and not bombard them with all your bullshit ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 23:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can always wear a t shirt during sex  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 20:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RFK would be proud, my favourite Attorney General  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is not a real man then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because you should be totally nice when fighting Nazi's and Imperialists... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you recommend scaling down the amount ? I use about 15 Id say but most are minor ones with some graphical ones  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long since you removed the visual ones ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skyrim SE consistently crashes - is that the price you pay for mods? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No a game breaker but crashes every hour or so - does this happen to everyone ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 02:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So how old is your aunt? I'm 21 and mine range from 48-70 - not everyone's aunt is a grandma  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 02:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude... that is so punk rock  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or Russian civil war would be cool  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 14:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assumed for most constant runners you're always going to be sore somewhere  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 04:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow thanks for sharing sorry that it was so hard for you but happy you eventually became more comfortable with your self - and of course it will be anonymous thanks again!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Map Pack 3 and 4 - where could they set the maps? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 04:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I am a history student who has done WW1 as part of my degree and was racking my brain for what could be in the map packs after the French and Russians. One campaign I think they absolutely should do is the East African one https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/East_African_Campaign_(World_War_I)

The jungle settings would be a nice touch. I also think going more towards Palestine with the British would be cool-maybe they could even do a map pack focusing on lesser know battles - Germans Vs Japanese in China perhaps? What do you guys think would be good?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi Trans community was wondering if any of you would be happy to share your experience about the moment you knew you were Trans? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 02:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm writing an article for a student publication and was wondering if you would be happy to share your experiences - and if I could share them in my piece-you can be anonymous or just use your Reddit name-thanks!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 02:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 22:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he's implying that he made Annakin out of the Force rather than fucking his dead mom  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who said Gungans couldn't be cool? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 18:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best meme I've seen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 06:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 18:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But we are gunna let Christians from those countries come to the US ? So that's not true ^  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay so if you're a right winger you might say 'we need to take less refugees and have a better vetting process for taking them in'

If you are a Trump right winger you ban all Muslims with any affiliation with those 7 countries (including people like Mo Farah) which is crazy and doesn't do much to stop terrorism.

Furthermore Saudi Arabia are not on the ban list - a country where top people in it have directly funded al-Qaeda and ISIS and most of the 9/11 hijackers were Saudi's 

So how does the ban make sense in that capacity? It's not about right or left it's about ignorance  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A ban on just Muslims coming from 7 Muslim countries - what would you call that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 04:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RVP to United has to be one of them  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 21:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can understand why people think this - whites have dominated the globe for the last 500 years - but you can still be racist to someone no matter how powerful there race is/was.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 03:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me and my girlfriend leave FaceTime on while we do other stuff that might help instead of a straight up convo  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 23:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just I hate ignorance and stupidity more than anything. And I feel if you are religious you have to be one of these things and you are believing in something that is fundamentally immoral for the time we are living in. I don't follow every law created by the Roman Empire, why should I follow loads of stuff written 4000 and 2000 years ago?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should Atheist respect other's religious beliefs? Especially if the person who believes doesn't let it make them hateful, intolerant etc ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 23:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So my parents told me I should be tolerant of other people's religious beliefs, but I general I just feel all organised religion is a cancer on the world. I find it hard to keep in how much I hate it especially when religious people talk about their faith - just been wondering how other people handle it - should I be 'respectful'? In the sense I shouldn't challenge what they belief ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As much as this game was repetitive I really loved it. Hope the DLC is a lot more linear like he last and first couple of hours  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 11:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'No reporter works for the government' while true it was still the media that led people to belief that Sadam was involved in 9/11. It's CNN or MSNBC which is the propaganda wing of corporate democrats and Fox News is the same for Republicans  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 02:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about love?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 18:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fargo, Man in the High Castle, Daredevil, Iron Fist, Defenders, Young Pope season 2 if they make it, Narcos S3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 13:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is that relevant to who is President? Those places vote for their own senators and state senates that will affect them way more  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 13:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who gives a shit are you voting for the president of the country or not ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 06:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your 20 don't worry about it most of my friends are single and it doesn't bother them at all I'm 21 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 05:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not everyone is compatible and that's just the way it goes - don't worry about it someone will like you for who you are  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 05:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah just let it go it's not the end of the world  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does shaving you beard actually make it grow back thicker and faster ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 04:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 04:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here be the witch-man... a freak of nature </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 01:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What in my opinion is wrong with Islam is two things. It hasn't had the self examination that Christianity has had since Martin Luther and later the enlightenment and its bases it's how religion around a murdering warlord.

This is why Wahhabism and the ISIS strain of Islam is way worse than fundamentalist Christianity that you see in the US and places like Africa. 

Also Muslims countries on the whole treat women like shit and the absolute belief in martyrdom is a problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 01:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Normally religion gives way to a cult of personality. Take 1960's/70's China for example, people literally spoke to a portrait of Mao in there homes three times a day confessing stuff and thanking him and saying how they were going to be better etc - sounds a lot like religion to me. North Korea is even worse for this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 01:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find most atheist can tell Trump is a bad guy and aren't blinded enough by Christianity (which Conservative Christianity in America is quite intolerant and somewhat racist) to actually think he represents them at all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 18:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could Mel Gibson become the Bill Clinton of film - 'the comeback kid' !?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did the Egyptian Pyramids survive until this day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 03:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Egypt has been the site of many wars and been conquered by many Empires. The Pyramids even survived the total wars of WW1 and 2. My question is: how is it they have managed to survive all these years? We have seen groups like Al-Qaeda, ISIS, Mao's Communist government destroy ancient sites and relics to fit in with their narrative - how come no one did something similar to the Pyramids?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 01:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dream would be able to take part in something like this one day looks so funny with that many people  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 23:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always shave me head when my beard feels like it's too long - makes it look better!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hard to argue that Stalin didn't pursue a policy or anti-semitism after the creation of Israel. Many Jews were sent to gulags for being western spies and Jews in the communist party were often purged like Slansky in Czechoslovakia  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 20:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Made its own !  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 10:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Say to your mutual friend is she keeps doing stuff like that you will tell your gf  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 05:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why the show is so good. It good easily fall into typical standard characters with Smith and Kido as 'evil' villains and Frank and Juliana a perfectly good freedom fighters.

But that's not what the show does, yeah Frank can be an asshole he's been through a lot and he just wants to live. That's what his progression is, he gives his life up for a cause and to do something for the wider resistance movement rather than just caring about himself. 

Can you tell me that at some point you didn't want the resistance to kill Juliana? At times I did - but that's the show, nothing is black and white it's all just shades of grey.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 05:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just saying 'Battle of the Bulge' is infamous for being historically inaccurate  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 21:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just meant when people reflect like really deep down-cut the bullshit and think, they realise it's bullshit even if they don't wanna really belief. I think when there is a hint of doubt it's hard to keep believing fully </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 21:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah okay so you're argument is much more 'God' focused which is definitely interesting and you're beliefs are convincing. There are just so many solid arguments for why you shouldn't believe I don't know how most of he World still do believe  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 15:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ignorance is bliss-comforting believing that you will life an eternity in heaven where there is no pain or evil - end of the day, with a little thought and self reflection-most people will realise it isn't true  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 15:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You make a great point about the Jews-Romans just about to enter the Temple? 6000 of you gather there to be saved by God. Whoops the Romans killed you all better start blaming ourselves for not being Holy enough! Really like you last point they do have an answer for everything! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 15:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's good you were never raised in it just allowed you to intellectually just say 'yep that's not true'  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 15:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it's always good to make people open their eyes to arguments against religion and make them doubt it even if you can't convert them completely  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 11:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will do that now-and yeah that's a really good point there is no way of knowing if there was one how and what form it would exist and what power it would have just because some Abrahamic texts say doesn't mean they know  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 10:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe see the light? Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Spoilers S2E12) 'Earth Angel' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 10:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 05:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bros before ho's 

Me and my friends chat absolute garbage when we are together and most I  don't repeat to my gf - but you should keep your friends over her especially since you known them for 9 years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which Blade Runner is best? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 00:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 21:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was saying that's what people often do when they criticise Islam - so they associate lack of women's rights in fundamentalist Muslim countries by labelling them all as perverts  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Probably been posted here before but Rust Cole's opinion on religion from S1 of True Detective </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 17:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 17:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In case you say something that is actually racist like all Muslims are pedophiles or perverts or support ISIS that isn't real critique of a religion  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 09:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think many people do - there is a fine line I'll grant that - but are you scared to criticise Christianity ? I'm guessing you're not but you just have to be careful with religions that are seen as containing predominantly one ethnicity or race e.g. Hinduism  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 09:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I point out in my article it could be referring to state but I really doubt that - Israel is the only country that state religion is Judaism so you could argue it is  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 08:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm my experience people who are genuinely nice don't really care what you believe, plenty of topics you can relate on with new people - I'm friends with a Christian Trump supporter (in England which is weird) but we get on still despite our differences  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 07:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks !! And I know it's been longer but my article got delayed for bullshit reasons I think it was a couple months earlier - good spot  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 07:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wrote this for a student publication FYI  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 07:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for sharing ! This is probably why it was so shocking because I was raised catholic and always learnt I be good like Jesus to earn gods favour  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 07:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But she didn't say 'Slavery is okay' and stuff she doesn't believe that stuff is right, she believes that because they were Christian they were in heaven - fucked up but I feel she is all talk  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 07:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We said the event than the act -for example we talked about the Spanish Inquisition and how they burned homosexuals, heretics, people suspected or being from Jewish or Muslim blood.

We talked about how lots of religious southern Americans believed slavery was from the bible and they were doing the lords work in Christianising Africa - and she maintained the argument that because they were Christian they were in heaven  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 06:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hitler was very conflicted about the Bible because it was Jewish in origin - it has been said the Nazi's would remove all religion eventually (seen in Man in the High Castle)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 06:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in England where pretty much every native Uni Student is an atheist-this sounds really shitty that you have to 'come out' - why don't you just say something like 'I don't think I believe in it anymore' or something not as absolute than telling them the truth.

That said I am a strong advocate of being yourself sometimes it's good not to follow the crowd and just state what you think </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 06:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh okay maybe if my friend was that extreme I definitely would distance myself from them, I agree it's all dangerous thinking that if you believe in some mythical entity whole heartedly you are absolved of all wrong doing because 'Jesus already died for our sins' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 06:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed it is! 

Yeah a lot of atheists I know would never say their beliefs to a religious person annoyingly. And yeah they definitely are. What I find a lot is 'ignorance is bliss' is a perfect saying to some up a lot of religious people. I feel a lot more people (like my friend, my mum and dad) would benefit massively from a bit of self reflection and critical analysis of what they belief - when confronted with the truth it's hard to come back as my younger sister is now finding out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 06:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like 'Jesus' (the fictional bible one based on some truth) had the right idea on how to live a morally good life, shame about most of his followers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 06:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I get that, but she genuinely is a really nice person her beliefs are just kind of warped.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 06:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes a lot of sense to why she thinks like that - evangelicals are some of the worst religious people  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 06:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I totally get the 'if you believe in him you'll go to heaven part' it's just the contradiction that fanatics, who were extremely devout, killed and butchered in his name (often ordered by the papacy) do those people really belong in heaven? It was my way to kinda make her see the concept of Christian heaven is bullshit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 06:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most evangelicals are hypocrites, like Christian Conservatives in America  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 06:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love this!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 09:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Christians saying the Old Testament is not a history of the Jewish people and Israel but actually one of the Catholic Church isn't revisionist? Despite only a minority of Jews breaking off to form Christianity ? Having a son of God and a second coming is a massive step away from the Torah and Christians had to go back and change certain lines in the OT to make it seem like they were suggesting Jesus' arrival when they weren't

I really don't see much off a difference with what Muhammad did. He was friendly with Christian and Jews. He knew their religion then obviously made himself a part of the story and created Islam  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 08:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why just Islam? Pretty sure Jews view Christians and Jesus the exact same way you view Muhammad and Islam-all religions are made up -Mormonism is particularly stupid though   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 07:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that would be pretty cool would be interesting to see the mechanics  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 07:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll make it brief - an open world game set in the America during the early 1600's playing a John smith type character - have specifics of gameplay and stuff but won't go into. Another would probably be an 1980's cop game - maybe LA Noire mixed with Lethal Weapon - again I have specifics but that's a brief summary of what I've got  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 07:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whatever I'm not a developer or even had any experience of making games don't answer not that bothered  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 07:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Post an idea then not your best  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 07:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that would be pretty goal what's the closer a game has done to that for you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Game you would love to create that has never been made ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 06:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I have two amazing ideas in my head for new IP's I'm sure I'm not alone in wanting a game over imagined to be made a reality - so what's everyone's best idea they have ever had for a new video game? 


Edit: I am not trying to steal your ideas :P  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 21:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The video game Wolfenstein the New Order did something pretty cool. Like the show it's if the Nazi's won the war (but they also conquered Asia) and you are a resistance member and one of your comrades is Jimmy Hendrix  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 21:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but specifically not just generic kill all Jews, kill all Gypsies  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 18:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure Churchill was on the Nazi kill list  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 22:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never thought about it but one set in an occupied country could work really well-thinking they could do a city like Prague or Warsaw-have curfews and have a heavy emphasis on social stealth in the day and parkour a night. Maybe have a pistol and hidden blade aswell as some
Bombs for sabotage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 22:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> West Germany and Japan were both pumped full of money through the Marshall plan and IMF so they wouldn't become enemies in the future. As they no longer were allowed conventional militaries or to build weapons (e.g. Missiles, Nukes) they had more money to invest in consumer goods-why a lot of good products come from these two countries today. They both have military bases from the US permanently with Japan being more occupied of the two-with many of its islands having huge bases.

Germany did recover under Hitler but this was undone by the Wars end and Germany was decimated.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 16:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surprisingly on slot of ways Victorian London still feels a lot like London. Love walking from south bank (which doesn't properly exist in 1868) to convent garden  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 16:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it is definitely 2008-the parodying of the war on terror, financial crash on the radio, a lot of the music, the tech and ting it feels like 08. I can't believe this game came out nearly 9 years ago!!!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 20:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nearly all of them!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 20:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are too many neo-Nazi's prowling this sub reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 02:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think MW2 has the best system as there was no supply drops  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 22:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is completely off his nut though-some of his monologues in the first season point to him being like this    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 22:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's not crazy he's sort of telling himself to snap out of worshipping mr Robot  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 22:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah because he can't believe he's said it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Perfect pick up lines don't exis... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 20:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 17:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never watch any of his stuff his voice just annoys me. More than anything his stupidity (he genuinely is a moron) is the main thing I can't stand. Everything he says racist, bigoted or otherwise stems from this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mr Robot on Religion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 15:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 14:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I am ignoring it especially the ones in Southern France you definitely have got your years mixed up. Spain was still primarily Muslim but the golden age of Islamic Spain was over. Islam wasn't one monolithic entity. Most Muslims the crusaders fought were the Seljuks who were seen as heretics by most of the Arab Muslims. Not to mention the Egyptian Muslims actually sent envoys to the crusaders to work against the Emirs of Baghdad who had armies in and around the Holy Land.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 05:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact is Pope Urban was asked by Alexius I to send Knights over to Byzantium to help stop the Seljuk Turks from taking over. It was not a defence of western/Catholicism as many make it out to be - it was initially a defence of orthodox eastern Christianity which the Pope wanted to use to send knights to recover the Holy Land. Those are the facts.

Real Muslim aggression in Europe was by the Ottoman Empire in the 15th and 16th centuries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 01:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah this is good advice especially what you say about the different styles of 2v2 and 3v3

And the teammate thing is bad but probably because I had a really bad couple of experiences topped off by a guy who kept calling me a noob despite the fact he was shit and at fault for most of our goals and that I'd already scored 5 goals 

Should probably play with my friends to avoid this frustration  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 00:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just a natural progression I guess  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 23:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the advice ! And I know saying your teammates hold you back is never a great excuse and for doubles I would never do it, but there are just so many occasions where one comes smashing into me when I'm trying to clear it or cross it - or they they are just generally following the ball. In doubles this doesn't matter as much because there is way more space to take the game into your own hands  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 23:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just you go from foreplay to oral foreplay to sex (I guess first is kissing or just touching)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 22:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not American but I thought it was a good way to describe escalation. Definitely how I went through it and most people my age that I know  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When did today's sexual practices become societal norms? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 22:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So most of us know (and stick to) the '4 bases' concept when it comes to sex (the escalation from foreplay to sex). The escalation is seen as normal today for everyone and if you have had sex it's likely you gone through all the 'bases'. So my question is: when did this became the norm? 

In historical dramas set before the 1900's most couples just go straight to sex. In shows like peaky blinders and Boardwalk Empire (set in the 1920's) a lot of the other things are incorporated (I know these are not the best indicators). Foreplay and other things have existed forever but just wanted to know when it became the societal norm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The standard on 'standard' is so bewildering </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 22:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've recently got into Standard on ranked and I am shocked at how bad some of my teammates have been. I am Challenger III rank but I feel I can go higher but I'm always let down by my team. Compared to Solo and Doubles at the same rank Standard players seem way worse - you can't even rely on them to make decent saves and they all just rush towards the ball at all times. This has happened multiple times - has anyone else had a similar experience ?

I feel because on Standard you can get ranked up by having a good team so many lesser players populate the higher ranks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
