<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2923</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 07:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't say enough good things about the diamond tremolo. Best sounding to my ears and very tweakable in a usable way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 07:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine is the empress vintage modified superdelay. It's not my favorite but it's very versatile and sounds good. Hasn't been booted from my board yet. That and the Meet Maude are my two delays currently in use. Meet Maude is my preference for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 07:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have 2 that I've already paid for coming my way and neither has shipped yet. Patience is definitely the name of the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 08:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had one a while ago and ended up selling it. I could never get behind the actual distortion so I really just ended up using it for the "feedback" a couple of times for recording. I like the freeze more for that kind of use, especially live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did a personal inventory today while working on my resume </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 05:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 19:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The diamond compressor is super high quality and very easy to use. It also has a built in tilt eq that is very handy for cutting through the mix in a live band situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 17:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 17:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 10:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Duesenberg starplayer special -- diamond comp -- archer -- meet Maude -- universal audio Apollo -- pro tools 11 -- native instruments guitar rig (fender black face amp)

There were other pedals in between but they weren't engaged. 

Would've used my real supro or vox, but didn't want to wake the girlfriend. Also, guitar rig sounds surprisingly good. I use it on recordings all the time, especially when I'm working late at night. It beats the shit out of the Waves guitar amp plugin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 06:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I couldn't find them for sale anywhere yet. Am I missing something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 06:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, fender blenders can get naaaaaasty. I used to play in a band with a guy who had one and it felt like someone was shoving a pencil in my ear we he turned it on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fairfield Circuitry Meet Maude Demo (audio only) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 06:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 06:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://soundcloud.com/subject2923/meet-maude-demo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 06:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I paid a little more than that for mine($195 American including shipping), so I would say that's a good deal. I just posted a quick demo if you want to see what it sounds like --- https://soundcloud.com/subject2923/meet-maude-demo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 06:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just made a quick mess around demo here ----- https://soundcloud.com/subject2923/meet-maude-demo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 05:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a really dark and gooey analog delay with switchable randomized modulation ( off/a little/a lot) and a built in compressor (a little/a lot) and it just sounds amazing. It's honestly what I was hoping the black fountain would be. That's not a dig on the black fountain. There is $100 difference in the prices, so there (ideally) should be more features. It feels a little more alive than my other pedals, and it has this thing I've never experienced in a delay where if you crank the feedback and play, it goes on and on and gets murky and crazy, but if you hit another note or chord it kind of ducks the soupy glue and will follow what you are doing (I'm assuming the compressor is doing this). I had it cranked to almost 100% wet and was doing that with the modulation turned on and I started feeling a very pleasant, soft wooziness drift over me. 

Anyway, I've been with it for about an hour now and I have to say I'm extremely satisfied. It also has a tone control and an fx loop and can be controlled by cv (though not at the same time).

It can do short delays and relatively normal stuff well too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 03:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eschew obfuscation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 03:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (that's a good thing) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NPD] Meet Maude, the first pedal to ever make me feel like I'm straight up on drugs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 03:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 01:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The zeta design is really cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 21:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not listening to it right now, but I feel like there's a slow kind of deep phaser on the guitar too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wednesday got me like </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 20:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wednesday got me like </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 20:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 07:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know, but here's a cheesy pun off the top of my head:
"It's just a phase" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 04:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the moogerfooger is way more tweakable, but I can't see how anything could sound that much better than this one. I really love the foot controls and the general design of it too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NPD '70s Maestro MP-1 Phaser (designed by Bob Moog) It sounds like god is chewing on my guitar. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 23:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 04:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see what you did there! Fender... Champ... Eh? Uh? Yeaaaah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 08:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drone Zone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 18:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the question? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have yet to play with any Rainger FX, but this seems like it could be verrrry fun... and super annoying to my girlfriend and pets. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 06:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy annoy your cat day! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 01:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 21:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhh, I probably just haven't noticed the others because I don't check them as obsess... uhh I mean frequently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does r/guitarpedals disappear and then reappear somewhat frequently from the "my subreddits" dropdown menu? Is this only happening to me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 21:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 07:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roland space echo... echo... echo
201, baby </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 05:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is probably Richard Swift's studio. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 04:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't believe so, unless you've modified yours somehow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 00:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I talked to Paul Barker (the malekko dude) the other day and he said their new pedal platform is going to allow for a lot more crazy shit like this in the future. I think so far it's the scrutator and this one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
