<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2662</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bearded douche w/a a rib tattoo doing something unnecessarily athletic, outshined by senior draining free throws. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Famous Statistician </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A famous statistician would never travel by airplane, because he had studied air travel and estimated that the probability of there being a bomb on any given flight was one in a million, and he was not prepared to accept these odds.

One day, a colleague met him at a conference far from home. "How did you get here, by train?"

"No, I flew"

"What about the possibility of a bomb?"

"Well, I began thinking that if the odds of one bomb are 1:million, then the odds of two bombs are (1/1,000,000) x (1/1,000,000). This is a very, very small probability, which I can accept. So now I bring my own bomb along!"
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL That a man once tried to sue Pepsi because he found a mouse in his can of Mountain Dew, Pepsi defended the case by proving that Mountain Dew can dissolve a mouse in a few months. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boy: come over </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I see you're trying to do work. Let me just flop and be cute right here." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 07:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 03:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's the joke... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 01:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A fact that I keep rediscovering.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Muslim man goes to a bookstore and asks if they have the latest Donald Trump book on immigration... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 00:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you spot a blind man on a nudist beach? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
