<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject195</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 20:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would they have to reshoot anything? 

Just put the filter on scenes you've already shot and use the new suit in all the shots after that? It could be the exact same suit just greener </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 19:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this SNL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 19:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's been saving them all season </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 19:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dude you missed out on Mad Guilt Tripping/Uber hyprocracy and 133t hax bro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 19:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cant believe that it wouldn't be more time/cost effective to just make a new goddamn suit that is green. I don't understand. They have to edit every scene he is in that much more now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 19:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you say that like they are smart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 08:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After oliver got stabbed in the chest and fell off a cliff and then came back to life I didn't think Arrow had any logic.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 08:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't spoil something that's already rotten..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 07:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> probably just didn't want to pay the actor for this episode </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 07:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly wouldn't be surprised if he fired more arrows this episode than the entire season up to this point combined.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 19:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's actually a good answer.  Thank you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [S02E22][Spoiler] Slight continuity error? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 17:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay admittedly, this a pretty minor detail, but did anyone else notice that when Zoom shows up and takes Barry's dad, Barry is wearing his normal street clothes. But when he catches up to Zoom he's wearing the Flash suit. 

So either this is a continuity error or Barry actually took time to pick up and put on his flash suit. Why waste that time? When Zoom is involved every picosecond counts. If it were me and Zoom had my father, I know I wouldn't waste any time stopping to get my super hero suit. 

Just a minor detail that bothered me. 

Whatever though- Speedforce - He aint gotta explain shit. 

Absolutely loved the episode overall though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 17:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> \\\\\_***(    )***_*//*
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 16:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha man you are confusing me. Does Henry Allen have a nose or not?!

PS. I love all of these comics. They are great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 15:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>     I'd like to preface this comment by saying I think all of that is fucking great and hilarious and I love your comment. 

Okay, that being said, I don't understand one thing.  

I completely get mocking the Olicity Shippers because they were awful to KC. I fucking love it. 

and I get nod/"fanservice" to the loyal KC/Laurel fans because they were awesome. Respek.

I also get the writers speaking though Caitlin about loving Laurel/KC. 

**But** I just don't understand why Flash writers would throw shade at Arrow.  

Don't get me wrong, I think it's great and arrow writers definitely need some shade, but don't they all work together? Aren't they essentially on the same team?? Why would they throw shade if they are essentially on the same team? Is there some BTS strife we are not aware of? Are the writers of flash unhappy with where arrow is right now? (I mean that would be understandable given the level of organic manure on the show right now.) 

Idk seems weird. Just my thoughts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 15:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this point I feel like they are going to do some sort of reset. I just don't see how they actually let a nuke go off in their universe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 15:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find that critique more valid because it points out the shitty writing. They should never be in a situation like this to begin with. 

There are better ways to give Felicity a "Greater Good" decision.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 15:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've just been seeing lots of people comment, '*she murdered thousands of people,*' or '*she's literally a mass murderer,*' and things like that. 

While I think it's incredibly stupid that the writers went in that direction (and I think that is what we should focus on), I just don't think it's fair to say those things. 

How do we know she could have directed the nuke anywhere but Havenrock? Everyone is assuming she could have just have easily directed it into the ocean? All she said was that she changed something to 20 miles west of where it was. Maybe that's all she could do? 

I'm usually the last person to defend Felicity and I really dislike her character right now, but to me it just seems like people are just so upset with the character that they are jumping on any opportunity to hate her even more.  I think there are plenty of reasons to not like Felicity's character without this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 15:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a fair critique. 

It did flesh out her character though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 15:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I meant they were mocking the Olicity shippers that tweeted "bye bye birdie" when [arrow spoilers](#s "laurel died.")  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Bye Bye Birdie" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 06:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it just me or were the flash writers mocking the tweets that said this after arrow s04e18 by having laurel say it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 02:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate your point of view. I think my main gripe was with people making it seem like she was *soley* responsible for all their deaths.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 02:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm pissed that the writers decided to go with a worldwide nuclear threat. That isn't something a street-level vigilante can handle.

I agree with you  100% on this point. This is just poor writing 

To add to what you've said, I also think it was poor writing because it would have implications for other people in the DCWverse. And that forces us to to ask questions. We have to wonder certain things. 

Why wouldn't anyone on Team Arrow even attempt to contact the most powerful person they know, the Flash? Or the smartest people they know? Cisco/Caitlin/Dr. Wells?

* You could say Barry is busy with Zoom but what is the point of fighting Zoom if the whole earth is destroyed? And what about the others? 

* You could say that they can't just call the flash every time they're in a jam, but they've already done that last season when Barry saved them from Lian Yu. Why wouldn't they do it again this season?

Why would the governments of the world sit idly by and do nothing while this is happening? The fate of the whole world is in the hands of 4 people? Seriously? an IT girl, her dad, a black driver and a vigilante who doesn't kill anymore? No one does anything? No countermeasures were employed at all? Argus has no countermeasures they can take? 

This is an all hands on deck situation. This is an "if we don't fucking stop this, fucking everyone fucking everywhere fucking dies" kind of situation.. Why wouldn't they every single person they could to help? Why wouldn't they contact Roy? Constantine? Vixen? Curtis?

Nah, we got Felicity and her father, I think we're cool.

These things really break the immersion for me because they just don't make sense. This is not a normal response to this situation. And it's stupid because they didn't have the foresight to see that.  

I think they really overreached with the 'nuke the world' route.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [S01E15 Spoilers] Predictions about season 2. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 00:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just watched S01E15 and thought of this. Note: This is pure speculation. 

So if they succeed in taking out Savage (which seems very likely to happen at this point), there is still the problem of the Alien Invasion, right? They still need to figure out a way to prevent that from happening or to quell it when it does happen. 

Well, based on that loose end, my prediction is that season 2 will be about trying to stop that from happening. I'm guessing they use the Waverider to travel through time to pick up other DC ~~heroes/villains~~ legends to form a team to take down the aliens. 

I could be dead wrong here and they could resolve this loose end by the end of S01. 

But what do you guys think? 

If you disagree, what are your theories/predictions for season 2 at this point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 23:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If she can change the GPS to the Havenrock coordinates then she can change them to the ocean as well. 

how do we know this for sure though?

I do agree with you that the whole thing is goddamn stupid though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 23:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eyebrow Makeup Smudge at the 0:19 mark? 

pfft.

2/10 would not bang. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [S04E21] I know we are annoyed with Felicity but... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 23:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Major E21 Spoliers Below!

___
...Why are people blaming Felicity for the death of the all of those people hit by the nuke in Havenrock? 

This is really bothering me. Think about it. 

* *ARGUS* is responsible for the existence of a chip that can control all of the nukes in the world. Really smart ARGUS. 
 
* *Lyla* is responsible for losing this chip to Damien Darhk (Diggle and Oliver are kind of responsible as well by proxy for failing to stop him.)  

* And ***Damien Darhk* and *HIVE* are responsible for actually launching the freaking nukes.** 

* All of the nukes were launched and would have hit and killed **billions of people** around the world.

* All of this up to this point has nothing to do with Felicity and would have happened without her existence. 

* Because of Felicty and her father, all of the nukes except one were stopped.

* Despite their efforts, one nuke was still definitely going to kill **millions of people** when it hit Monument Point. 

* Felicity diverted the nuke that was going to kill millions slightly, at the last moment, and instead it killed only 'tens of thousands' of people.

How can we honestly hold Felicity responsible? She saved **millions of lives** by diverting the nuke headed for monument point and by averting the other nukes. 

The only argument that could be made is that she could/should have diverted it somewhere else but we don't even know if that was possible. The way it went down, if she (and her father) hadn't been there, millions if not billions of people would have died. Instead it was 10's of thousands.  

Now I don't pretend for a moment that the writers did a good job here; I'm just saying this based on what happened. I totally think it's fair to point how stupid this was from a narrative/writing perspective and that's what we should be focusing on IMO. I just don't think we can honestly blame Felicity for this. There are plenty of reasons to dislike the writing right now and where her character is, but it seems asinine to me to blame her for these deaths. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 22:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too bad Guggie told EBR at the beginning of the season that oliver/barry/felicity definitely survive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 22:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Laurel's courtroom scene earlier this season was actually one of my favorite parts of this abysmal season for what it's worth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 18:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An attempt was made...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 17:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then*
And yes that would be fantastic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 16:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> \\\\\_***(    )***_*//*
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 05:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That student's name?

Kneel on the grass bison </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 01:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey man, 

I think that haircut style would be okay but TBH if you are really trying to improve your appearance I would start with just basic grooming and clothes that fit you. You are a good looking guy if you just put a minimal bit of effort in. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 01:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> calm down Harvey Spectre </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 01:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a ~~liquid~~ cat has a definable size but takes the shape of whatever container it is in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 01:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bitten </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 01:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much money do you think this cost in ammo? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 01:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> get back motherfucka you don't know me like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 01:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting how each successive kick is more powerful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 00:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...but you fuck just one goat... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 19:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> timestamp? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 19:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait. I thought you had to be shitty at watercolour  in order to be good at it. or at least that is what reddit has taught me. 

/u/Shitty_Watercolour has lied to me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 19:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i can ~~hear~~ see her accent

"Thanks OBauma" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 19:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but how? 

You people amaze me sometimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 18:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how you capitalized Friend like he's your One True Friend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 18:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can dig it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 18:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love these. 

Why is Henry Allen the only one with a nose? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 18:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh grodd dammit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 18:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for not using the overused and cliche title of 

    dog.exe has stopped working.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 17:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~yall finnish or are yall dutch?~~

Edit: I am bad and I should feel bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 17:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I guess the one thing we know for certain is that it's good that he didn't throw it down and break it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 17:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they meant,

When asked:

* Where she wants to go? 

 - "I don't know."
             
 #OR

* *What she wants to do?* 

 - "I don't know. "

Then she still complains even though she didn't contribute any constructive ideas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 17:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took a guess haha. How'd you know it was Olive Oil? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 17:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. TIL. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 17:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least he had the decency to set the ~~wine~~ bottle down without breaking it. 

Edit. Maybe not a wine bottle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 17:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's still an improvement though, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 17:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> screw things up how exactly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 16:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  IK HOU VAN JE MAX


I LOVE YOU MAX </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 16:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #[\\\\__\( *  __  * \)_//](https://gfycat.com/BossyAccurateAsp\))

Edit: RES is fucking it up :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 15:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought we were done thanking Obama after he thanked himself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 15:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "C'mon Son" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 15:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> link? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What seemingly small thing makes you irrationally angry? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 22:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 10:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> found out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 09:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mike Colter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 09:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 09:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n0NjBwamHPc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 18:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, I couldn't sit through that show. I made it a couple episodes and had to stop.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 14:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here are mine for Chrome:

* [Imagus](https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/imagus/immpkjjlgappgfkkfieppnmlhakdmaab?hl=en) It allows you to view an image just by hovering your mouse over the thumbnail. Very helpful in browsing reddit. It's better than hoverzoom in my opinion. 

* [Google Dictionary](https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/google-dictionary-by-goog/mgijmajocgfcbeboacabfgobmjgjcoja?hl=en-US) - Allows you to look up the definition of something by selecting it. 

* [uBlock Origin](https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/ublock-origin/cjpalhdlnbpafiamejdnhcphjbkeiagm?hl=en) - Best adblock out there IMO

* [Center Image](https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/center-image/dkiklnjkgjkmamgoaggongdmekajdlki?utm_source=chrome-app-launcher-info-dialog) - Centers an image when opened in a new tab. Seems silly but I can't go back now.

* [Emojify](https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/emojify/lpkndkffkmhcdkkdmeeelikmadjjmebe?utm_source=chrome-app-launcher-info-dialog) - Adds emojis to chrome

* [Wikipedia Search](https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/wikipedia-search/lipakennkogpodadpikgipnogamhklmk?utm_source=chrome-app-launcher-info-dialog) - Search Wikipedia easily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 14:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally prefer [ublock origin](https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/ublock-origin/cjpalhdlnbpafiamejdnhcphjbkeiagm?hl=en) to adblock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which browser extensions/addons should everyone be aware of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 14:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 09:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there's a lot of implicit racism and sexism going on in the fandom in sort of an unconscious way. 

#Jesus Christ. Seriously? 

I couldn't give two shits that she is a "Black Female Character." 
That's not at all why I had a problem with her character. 

I found her character annoying because her character was annoying. Period. IMO it was poorly written at first. It had nothing to do with Candice Patton. It had nothing to do with her being a woman or black. I just didn't like the way her character was written. --The same way I didn't like Laurel's character at first or Felicity's character now. Hell even Cisco took me a while to get behind because he was so corny. 

*OH, you don't like a character that happens to be female and black? Welp. Must be sexist and racist.*

What a fucking narrow minded view. Stop projecting. 

/endrant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [S4] So, does it bother anyone else </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 01:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...that none of Team Arrow (with the exception of Laurel and Felicity) seem to have real day jobs at this point? 

What do Ollie and John do during the day? Is John a stay at home dad? Does Ollie just sit in his bunk and brood? How does Thea support herself? Is Felicity supporting  everyone with her Palmer-Tec money?! I guess John has Lyla to support him. And I suppose  we had Ollie running for mayor which took up a big chunk of their free time earlier in the season. But what about now?

Don't get me wrong, I get that their focus is on saving the ~~city~~ world right now. With everything that's going on right now, it doesn't exactly make sense to go Job-hunting.. But Idk. I just feel like the characters aren't really grounded in reality anymore. What is tying them to this city at this point? 

I know this is pretty far down on the list of things to give a shit about at this point with everything else that's wrong with Arrow currently, but it bugs me. I think it's just indicative of larger things wrong with the show right now. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 01:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I just hope we don't have the "How-could-you-not-tell-me-now-I-can-never-trust-you-again-until-next episode" trope when he finally does find out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 17:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. I think you put words to what I was feeling. I think those same things were how I felt about Laurel's character early on in arrow. At least Laurel had reasons to be bitchy though since she had been through quite a lot. 

I also feel like the plot revolved around her way too much  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 17:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you feel that she is irrelevant to the plot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 17:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Thankfully Eddie died so now thats not a problem anymore.

haha jesus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 11:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that wasn't really my point but okay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 11:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While you're certainly entitled to your own opinion just the same as all of us, I disagree that Iris is 'cancer.' 

Even when I strongly disliked her character I never really thought that it was to the point they need to kill her off. Lately, I actually enjoy her character most of the time. 

Also I think Felicity was fine when she was a side character. But the last two seasons the writers have ruined her character imo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Iris. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 11:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Discussion Time. 

To be perfectly honest. I really used to to hate Iris's character, especially around the middle of last season. *(To be clear I never had anything against Candice Patton but just the way her character was written.)* 

I don't really know what it was about her character, but early on in this show, I could just never get behind her. Maybe she felt too similar to Season 1/2 Laurel Lance from the arrow (in all the bad ways). Maybe it was the illogical decisions that she made. Maybe she didn't have enough depth (like a lot of other CW female characters.) Idk. I just didn't like her. 

However, now I feel very differently. In fact, I feel like the writers should be praised for turning her character around. Somewhere along the way she has turned into a great character. She doesn't make nearly as many illogical decisions any more. She now adds to the show rather than detracts from it. She has been great comic relief lately. Her chemistry with cisco last episode was fantastic and just fun to watch. She is confident but not overbearingly so. She is a love interest but it's not shoved in your face every five seconds. She speaks hard truths with out some sort of sarcastic quip. 

Maybe it's just so refreshingly different than Felicity's character currently that made me think of this. Idk. 

But I'd love to hear all your thoughts on this. What do you guys think?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] Has anyone put together a chronological cut of the flashbacks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 09:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even know if this would be worth watching but it interests me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 08:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even know how Oliver is still functioning. He has lost so much.

Off the top of my head, he has lost his father, his mother, shado, Laurel, Tommy, Yao Fei and the Salmon Ladder.  Roy is gone, just like his balls. His fiance left him and so did his pride. He is homeless, and unemployed. He is not mayor. He isn't even the main character of his own show anymore
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 07:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you might have meant 'finale.' and I see it going that way too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 06:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just keep watching and hoping (in vain) that it will once again be the show that I used to love so much. 

I feel like we are all caught up in some sort of elaborate bait and switch scheme.

How does a show fall so far?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 06:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And in the end, that's what I want the show to do. Make me feel something. And nothing in Arrow is making me do so.

Nowadays it seems all i feel is nausea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 06:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See the real reason this makes me mad is because they wrote it this way when it was completely unnecessary. 

Why not just have them fucking steal it? 

At least that would make some goddamn sense. 

Because Even if they did fucking clone the design for it, how the fuck do they build a new processor in 10 hours.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 05:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speeforce </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 20:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right you are Ken </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 19:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Ken </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 08:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> darkforce </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 07:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard it both ways </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 07:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wait are you telling me /u/onbenchnow invented onions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 07:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guys, they were talking about the green filter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 07:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eh. people gotta vent man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 07:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so you're telling me that saying things like "I wish he would go choke on an ear of organic corn," is too far?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 07:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/aTMOTA4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 07:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget about the Jewish Customs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 06:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not gay but... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 06:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right when someone said Iris was Black Laurel, someone flipped their shit about how racist it was. 

I was just like seriously?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 06:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to say Door all the time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 06:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell that to my professor. 

He had questions on the test that had nothing to do with the course material but rather "what did I say in last class? It had absolutely no bearing on whether or not I understood the material he was supposed to be teaching me. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 06:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also a bad question. If you have 12 roses and half of them are red, there is nothing definitive that states there are ONLY 6 red roses. So half of the roses could be red but the other half could be too. 

Like the old riddle how many months have 28 days in them? Answer: All of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 06:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree. 

The question states that 1/2 of the roses are red and then asks how many are not red. 1/2 is the simplest logical answer given the way the question was asked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 18:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DHEOF_rcND8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 18:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  More Healthier </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 10:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what does it look like closed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 08:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dislike the Ollicity bullshit as much as everyone else but I mean relationship pain is definitely real. Sure it's not as traumatic as someone literally dying but break-ups fucking suck. And Oliver was engaged to her when she broke it off. I get what you're saying but I also get why they added it. 

What bothered me is that somehow she is still his light after she broke it off with him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 07:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha thats definitely the same bus, but admittedly a much better picture </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 06:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I wish he would have actually died when Ollie killed him the first time. His character has slowly gone downhill since then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Shitpost]Season 5 Poster leaked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 06:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 05:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> annnnd these are the people that uncle guggencancer listens to..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 05:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Google Magic](http://vignette3.wikia.nocookie.net/greenarrow/images/9/98/Oliver_Queen_Stephen_Amell_Shado_Celina_Jade_and_Slade_Wilson_Manu_Bennett.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20130920235703) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 05:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Manu Bennet looks a little derpy in this picture for some reason </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 05:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Darkhalark

My only comment is that I like this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 05:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bruh. There are so many other things wrong with the series right now that this is small ~~potatoes~~ corn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 05:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> these are dank. 

#YOUCANTLOCKUPTHEDANKNESS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 05:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh. That makes more sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 05:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess her plot armor wasn't strong and powerful enough for an implant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 20:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/aTMOTA4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 18:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may not want to look at the production photos for next week then. [Spoilers](http://imgur.com/a/6GZ8W) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 18:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, I think most of us liked Felicity or at least didn't mind her when she was still a side character. For some reason the writers started shifting their focus away from what made Arrow great in the first place and started listening to a very vocal minority of fans on twitter/tumblr and brought Felicity to the forefront of everything. Now it's just gotten to the point where nearly everyone is sick of her poorly written character. Also while EBR seems like a great person (at least from the image she puts out on social media), she doesn't really seem to have the best acting chops, which became more evident as she was brought to a more central role. That hasn't helped matters much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 07:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you can't lock up the dankness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 07:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'd much rather see him with booty spivot. I don't think that barry and iris really have that much chemistry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 06:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck. Spot on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 05:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "fetish" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 04:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard it both ways.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 02:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is that a psych reference? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 23:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey diggle kind of felt bad for a sec </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 23:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem that I see with it is not that she's good at it but that its just one more reminder of how much Oliver needs her to get anything done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
