<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3191</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does ghosting mean? Sorry. I am old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love you. Can you be a sweatheart and help me with some yard work? By help,I mean do it for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giants fan smiles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happens monday? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are they legally allowed to discriminate and only hire christians since its a police for  a private organization? What about parking tickets? I think university police write parking tickets and the money goes to the university. How does that work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would you tell quickly that someone has a bullet proof vest on?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont read anything in their expressions. None of the major news papers or cnn mentioned their expressions. I think you are reading too much into this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesnt getting shot with a vest on still hurt like hell and often lead to broken ribs. I think a few rounds to a bullet proof vest and most guys would be down right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would think that its not uncommon for police officers to be treated for depression and anxiety given what you have to do right? Is that black mark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did he injure the guy? If the guy gets up like that and yells isnt it threatening or was the guy clearly just being an asshole to the cop? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They beat people in guantanamo bay. That was the CIA. Not the police. There are interviews with fbi agents who were disgusted by it and say it doesnt work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What crime is it to curse at a cop? I honestly dont know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alabama church to being legally allowed to have a police force. What does this mean? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What powers would a church police force have? Could they write tickets and the Church pockets the money? I think University police can write parking tickets and this money goes to the school. Would Church police be allowed to discriminate in hiring practices since the Church is private. This is creepy to me. I would think private security would be sufficient if they want to protect people. 

Just looking fir opinions from working police. Would Church Police only have authority on Church grounds? 

http://www.al.com/news/montgomery/index.ssf/2017/03/alabama_senate_committee_oks_p.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think hiring private security is ok. Its 4000 people in one place. Difference with a police force is that they can arrest me and I cant legally tell them to fuck off. 

I wonder if these police are allowed to write traffic tickets near the church. Does that revenue go to the church? University police give parking tickets and that goes to the university. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Id like to see the interview. Isnt a police force a public entity? So can the church discriminate and non christians? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Subs turning into TMZ. Odb is into the cougars.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fluker likes having a job. Most guys dont make it past their rookie contract.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With john jerry back, fluker is here to play RT. Bobby hart was the worst tackle in the league last year. I think he graded in the 40s. Fluker graded in the 60s , but san diego has more depth than the giants so they moved him to guard.

A tackle who grades in the 60s bad. But its 20 points higher than hart.

Maybe they will get better in the offseason fundamentals and such. Who knows? Not many guys have thevtalent to stsrt in the nfl no matter how hard they practice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giants have no cap space to get someone else. Marshall is a good blocker for a WR, but he is a bit small to play tackle. 

Maybe they go tackle in the first round. There is a guy from wisconsin who the draft guys say could be available. Knock on him is he only has one year as a starter. So likely a project.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They disnt bring in someone to replace him. The giants eanted jack conklin last year, but tennessee traded up. Conklin was an all pro last year. Guys who do that as a rookie have future hof written all over them. Eli apple is pretty good and may be reall good.

But if conklin was on the team, flowers would be on the other side already.

The giants also offered a 3rd round pick for joe thomas, but the browns wanted a 2.

I think the giants need to hope they get a good tackle in the draft. Doesnt have to be the fiest round.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is probably why he is unsigned. Not sure if anyone will give him that much. The highest paid FAs go quick. Then the guys who were asking for too much money need to scale back what they want. 

What is the market for a solid starter quality DT who isnt a star?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can the cowboys afford to sign them? If they both go you are down a starting safety too. Do the cowboys have depth in the secondary? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the franchise number for guards is reasonable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah i know. I think f he doesnt fire comey. The activity with russia is likely unethical but legal. If its illegal. Comey will likely be fired. I dont know if having people talk to russian agents who informed you about hacking is illegal. I dont think it is. They will also not cooperate and lie.

Typically with these things is that people get caught lying to the fbi for something that is legal, but embarrassing. 

Im also not sure how you prove communication if no one was wiretapping them at the time. Unless they get it from intelligence assets watching the russians. Trump wont talk to them. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont know how much of a gop response. They have an agenda. They will only go so far and they can couch as firing because of how he screwed democrats.

I think there is a limit to what congress can do. If the fbi stops investigate congress can only subpoena what they have. If they dont get more what can congress do? They dont have the skills or tools to investigate this? The fbi does.

On top of that with all the layoffs trump wants people will be afraid of losing their jobs. They could get laid off. Coukd get a national security letter. 

We dont want comey fired. I think that if there is nothing illegal to the russia stuff trump,will just let the fbi investigate. They will attack the fbi to fight political fall out. Then sme new scabdal will happen the next day.

There is alot of sleezy shit that is political ly damaging, but legal. The fbi investigates law violations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last year during the campaign, Bernie Sanders said James Inhofe is one of his best friends. Surprised the hell out me. Sounds like a good guy just off. Makes me wonder if we can crack him on the back of the head that we might be able to fix him.

I dont have a link. I think it was a town hall on cnn or a debate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Typically with lower wages with less hours. No benefits after being unemployed and desperate. Over ling stretches industrialization makes life better. Life in the US is definitely better than it was 100 years ago. Economists tend to ignore all the displaced peole then copy and paste stuff from text books like its thr gospel. Its a model. You can fimd test cases where the model fits to a point. Economics isnt thr Theory of Relativity. Its not that accurate. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Say you are a mormon. Evangelicals hate Mormons. Then say jesus smoked weed with native americans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dont leave. Voach thrm to be smartasses and argue. Say the Dragon Reborn will battle the Dark One at the last battle. 

Or argue with her and p say you are a Mormon and that your fearless leader found the true book under a rock. Jesus smoked weed with Native Americans. 

Hen claim she is insilting your religion. Or just claim its turtles all the way down. Go scientology and claim Xenu is coming. Say Zeus banged his wife and that is why we have a moon. 

Ask her for mechanics of a virgin birth. Did god jerk offon her belly and cum dripped in? Did Joseph use the poop hole loopholw or atleast get his dick sucked?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I had a kid in that class, Id coach him to be a smartass and say he is a scientologist and that Xenu created the universe. Or that Satan is the true god. Or go Robert Jordan and state that the Dragon will battle the Dark One at the last battle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long do cats take care of kittens? I see them placed with families after just a few weeks. If mother and child stay together in the same home do they ever have a bond? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea what that means </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I googled the president can fire the fbi director. Its not like a fed appointent. I think it only happened once so its a political shit storm. If you google this as a question you will find some articles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess he s all over the player. Then again single payer helps business. Corporations dont have to cover medical insurance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To Get video him watching incest porn  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 06:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was a kid in the 1980s. Big fantasy series in the 1980s were dragonlance and dragonbone chair. This fit that mold. The tropes are what drew people in. Jordan was a newer author. All he published before was some romance books and some conan books. Publishers were looking for stuff like this. Robert jordan said this in interviews. Start with the familiar and taje you somewhere else. In 1990, the end of the eye of the world was fresh. I read the book in 1990/1991

Also his universe the world repeats 7 ages. So its both in our future and in our past. We are their legends and they are ours. At the beginning of the first book Thom Merillion refers to us. Mosk and Merc fighting a war (moscow and america). Going to the moon on an eagle ( the eagle has landed)  He has christ referencescat the end too. Rand goes, I deny you. Then the dark one goes Something like "fool do you expect to work?" It doesnt work. There is a faq on one of the jordan fan sites explaining alot of the references to myths and religion. The wheel of time is from Hinduism. Alot of the Forsaken are names from Norse references.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 06:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Return of the king they were at pallinor fields. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 05:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jordan used the whole pattern thing to explain things he wanted to happen. I thought it worked well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 05:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Two Rivers is an Americanized version of the Shire. Goes in non trope directions after the first book.

This kind of thing was expected when jordan got published. He had to start here to go somewhere else. Btwm the idea for only femalr wizards is because jordan wanted to create a world where the womans movement took place so long ago that one remembers it. He mentioned this in an interview at the end of the audio of book 2. 

In this universal time repeats itself. So the characters are both in our future and in our past, we are their legends and they are hours. Its why you have the king arthur references( there are more in future books).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 05:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try the audiobooks. Male and female readers for male and female characters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 05:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lord of the Morning! I have come for you. 

First line of dialogue in the book. Best line in the series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 05:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shh...dont tell anti vaxxers this. This is our chance to get their kids ourt of the gene pool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 05:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump probably didnt know who Andrew Jackson until his staff told him this was on his agenda. The man doesnt read. 

You can probably prank trump abd take him to a fake presidents grave and he wouldnt know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 04:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eagles should have flown the ring to mordorvand dropped it in the volcano. The nazgul were off doing shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 04:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I check them out of the library. If i domt like them, i stop reading and return them. Im sophisticated like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 04:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the story any good? Extra chapters that dont maje it in a book are often low quality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 04:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can write a sentence about a woman rufflung her dress and then talking about how stupid men are. Then copy and paste it so it fills up 500 pages and email you the word doc for free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 04:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted a lews therin book. Just one. Not a series. Covers the end of the war. Maybr some flashbacks. Dont give away everything. Relatively short so we want more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 04:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just like trump an atheist embraced by thevreligious right. Soviet union was an atheist state. No fucking way a kgb agent is devout. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 04:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pick one. See if you like it. If so read book 2. If not stop and go to the other. Check out of library so no cost.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 04:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope its not filled with women ruffling their dress and talking about how stupid men are... Over and over again. Lets hope Robert Jordandis not rub off on him too much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 03:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They eat ther own. Remember When Paul Ryan was the darking of the right? I dont think Ryan is going to go because no one else wants the job. They know they are next. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 03:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hannity understands ratings. Foxnews ratings took a hit when they took on trump. Now its suck up to trum, because its what sells ads.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 03:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is alot of money in telling right wingers what they want to hear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 03:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This kind of fbi nvestigation will take a long time. They have to go over everything. Long time until we get anything from Comey. My read is Comey realized how much he fucked up with how he handled Clinton and this time is keeping his mouth shut. He is also legitimately worried about being fired. If he is fired trump will kill the investigation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 03:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would expect trump to fire comey if there is anything illegal. If its not illegal trump being a corrupt shit bag offering to blow putin in order to get financing... I expect trump to just attack comey. To him, its just another scandal.

I think there is alot of trump is a total shitbag that fll under "no one thought to make this illegal" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "M Cuban is a terrible NBA owner. Gets fined all the time. Last place team. Sad!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cuban is a republican. He said on twitter he likes most of trumps cabinet picks. Probably hoping to have him impeached to get at pence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ebooks. Plenty of space.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well if republicans stay in power there wont becroom for this in the history books. Need space for Noahs Ark and the history of people running around with Dinosaurs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will go up on Mount Rushmore right below the bust of Trumps ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone needs to put Reagan administration officials on tv and go whst the fuck is wrong with him. Russia is just the weaker successor state to the soviet union. Instead of a stupid communist economy, they have a smart  number of corrupt assholes who control everything to enrich themselves. There is only 1 news outlet. Its all government news. Political oppenents get murdered. 

The state prior to the soviet union was called the Russian empire. This is just a smaller Russian Empire. 

What the fuck is wrong with right wingers? Instead of the evil empire, Russia is the asshole empire. These right wingers are pathetic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all know Trump,didnt read it or really pay attention.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you wver had sex with anything that is not a human being? Sheep, ya like Sheep? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you say, I want a muslum ban and do it, then its a muslum ban. If you prevent evidence of a threat and block entry from a country (particularly in a time of war), im sure it will be fine.

I dont know how this will go in the supreme court. I think its racist bullshit, but I dont know enough about the law to knkw if its legal racism. I expect the supreme court to back 6-3 or 7-2 one way or the other. I dont expect this to break on political linrs.

Well assuming Gorsuch gets confirmed. Democrats now have an excuse to fillibuster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes sessios did! When Sessions was at the White House, he said Please pass the salt. We all know that is code word for, we are bugged. Watch whst you say.

Its likely alot easier to bug Mar A Lago then the White House. It woudn surprise me if the Chinese/Russians bug the shit out of that place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are tou voting for an insane number of positions or do you just have an insane nmber of candidates? If its alot of candidates, whst does it tale to get on the ballot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they dont wrk out a lng term deal, the giants will pull the franchise tag. They have until july 15. Jpp has sid he wnt play on a one year deal again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fluker isterrible. He sucked at tackle o he moved to guard and was not very good. The hope is he sucks lss than Bobby Hart who was the wort tackle in the league last year per PFF.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I expect Dwayne harris yo take a pay cut or be cut. Jt thomas was injured all last year and cutting him would free up $3m. I am surprised they have not asked him to take a pay cut yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They expect him to make a full recovery. Getting reinjured during the year is a bad sign. I hope he is ok.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im surprised he hasnt signed yet. I figured there would be alot of interest in him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giants are out of money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He faded a little toward the end of the season. He was likely helped by having 3 all prod in the secondary. He is probably one of those guys who yiu file as decent. Could improve. Im hoping the Darian Thompson comes back healthy and takes the job. I think he has the potential to be very, very good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If al jefferson is really good this year will enough dead money clear so that the eagles can sign him to a big contract? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of this likely that running dont last long. Most dontbmake it pastvtheir rookie deal. There also are very few good backs in the league. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im not sure how much of a contract he will get likely no giaranteed money. Probably less thsn the $6m the jets owe him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop lying. Trump wants to get rid of the alternative minimum tax. A quick google search has a laundry list of sources. 

https://www.google.com/webhp?sourceid=chrome-instant ion=1 espv=2 ie=UTF-8#q=trump+alternative+minimum+tax *
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was on CNN. I dont have a link. They discussed his taxes. He was at 5% before the alternative minimum tax. They said Trump has proposed tax reform to eliminate the alternative minimum tax. 

Quick google search of trump wanting to get rid of AMT. 

https://www.google.com/webhp?sourceid=chrome-instant ion=1 espv=2 ie=UTF-8#q=trump+alternative+minimum+tax * </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 08:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesnt make trump look good. He only paid taxes because of the Alternative Minimum Tax. He wants to get rid of this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 08:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bad things happen to who he is a backup too. Who wouldnt want Fitz as Bellicheck's backup? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 21:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most complaints from kids can be written off. They are just kids.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 21:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are absolutely people who are not temporarly poor. This is coming from a guy with a 7 figure networth. If i can understand it, others should too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 21:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They help people oike me who dont preorder. Its loud and clear when a game sucks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 21:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like donald trump? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 21:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most places wont pay overtime and cut you off. I dont know where you get that many people dont want 1.5 pay. They cant get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 21:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am in IT, I have aggresively job hopped over the last 18 years. During the 2008 recession, I went down in pay ( still above 100k). Companies offer salary based on previous employment. So you generally wont get a huge raise with 1 job switch. You need several. Also you dont want to exclusively switch jobs for money, to maximize income over time, you need to target jobs which will make you marketable.

This is a max you will top out at in your profession. Occassionally very high paying jobs come availabke. Those almost always are short term. They wont tell you that. Be careful with taking those. If you are out if work for few months it can cost you money.

Getting paid more also means being really good. It requires working on your skills outside of normal business hours. I also find reading technical forums and tech blogs from people who disect tech studf very useful. One useful thing to do is to ask alot of questions in a variety of tech forums and participate in discussions. There tend to be alot of trolls who are assholes to people who ask alot of questions. Once you get trolled your thread is ruined. I advise having multiple accounts so it looks like different people asking questions. Asking questions on a texh forum really helps speeding up learning new skills.

You dont need to spend hours every day working on your skills. The linger you are in the profession and the more you do, the essier it is to learn new skills. 

Learning on your own us never as good as doing it at work. If you are in a dry position where your skills are stagnating, its time to move on. Only time its not is when the economy is slow( 2009-2010 for example), then securiry is more important. 

I like to read IT forums on y ipad sitting on the couch.

I also recommend.
1. Periodically apply for jobs and take phone screens fir practice. Take notes on what you dont know. Yes you often get stupid questions in interviews, but you cant fight city hall.

2. You can always pass and say that you talked to your manager and you are no longer worried about being laid off.

3. When you pass on a job always either say you accepted another position or you are comfirtable where you are and that you talked to your manager about job security. Even if you hated the place. You never know if you will need a job. 

4. If you dont want the job. Stop at the phone screen. Less likely if you apply again that anyone will remember you. Some people hold grudges if you pass. 

The answer to the question about why you are switching jobs is I am worried about layoffs and just want job security. They are moving jobs to india, always works. Every company has layoffs so they get it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im a good looking guy. I just hate it when women check me out. You dont understand my pain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That falls into new to me. I cant be the only 40+ something on here like this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually understand this. Alot of people can be down on their luck. As people get older they may not be physically able to do manual jobs. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who cry about shitty computer games because they pre-ordered and didnt wait for the reviews. No Mans Sky to name one. The reviews start coming out the day of the release. If people just waited they wouldnt get away with dropping trash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you have no pity for that people frequently complain about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know a guy who was sued in another state for child support. Had to pay a lawyer to go down there. Woman never showed. His wife thinks it may have been a waitress they had when driving through. 

Costs money just to fight these things. She was likely desperate, but its not his problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His acne scars make him look badass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im 42. Few years would be new to me. If its slang from the last 10 years(atleast) its new to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously didnt know that. Guess I should use the google more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im a guy. But my ego is boosted by your homo erotic reply </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On that note, fitz is the perfect assistant head coach for the patriots </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never heard that one. Is it new? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He used his profits to become CEO of six flags </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FAs would sign for less in exchange for stock tips. Now they sign for more in exchange for drama and endless bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont understand your username. What is fupa? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm.. Its Fitz related to Putin? Did a qb end up radioactive? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just waiting for cowboys fans to go dont worry romo is your for your first round pic...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a lesson for busts who get big money contract. Save your money cause you wont get more. Have a thick skin when people laugh at you.

That being said. Im a big boy. Happy to be a high paid bust </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speculations on twitter really isnt the media. Its just assholes looking for clickbait.

I never beleived bullshit about the 49ers. First off he never played under Shanahan. He was backup and you dont limit yourself to 1 team. Lowers market value. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His being up all night due to his enlarged prostitute which shrinks his blatter. He gets up to pee. Then tweets to keep himself busy. 

This has no bearing on his mental stability.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we buy their personal nfo? Lets put up a bounty for naked pics too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Irrational exuberance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you go, if you give me sex, i can get ryan leaf to tweet you? How does thst work out for you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My oubes started falling out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sandiego has as many nfl teams going to rhe playoffs next year as LA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are giants fans defending bobby hart st RT. He had a 47 pff rating. They say he has potential. Some serious dumb shits in these parts. Fucking irrational optimism. I should sell them stock in the brooklyn bridge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hes perfect if you are holding up banners at training camp that say tanking for draft picks. Dont try to hard or you will get cut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> browns are tanking again. Might as well keep the qb cheap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pff graded hart at 47 at tackle by farcthe worst in the league. Hart doesnt belong on most nfl rosters. Uana unga is young too, but he sucked, hart is shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alt righters get defensive when you talk about torturing hitler. They are afraid they are next. Since they identify with hitler. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is really cool. Thanks for leaving it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Id argue that Paul Ryan is ballsy. Takes bug balls to fuck this many americans.

Im one of the people getting a tax cut. Wont even notice it. I dont even balance my check book or pay attention. Auto pay everything. From selfish piint, id rather keep obamacare in case i get cancer and for so pme reason im broke. I wont even notice the tax savings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cause im fucking with his history. Go take a picture with you butt lover Putin.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Ware got to kiss Elis rings. No sacks in the 2007 playoff game or in the games in 2011 when the giants won the superbowl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sacks were not a stat lts first season ao if this average includes LTs rookie year, it should be removed which would likely make LT #1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill parcells drafted 2 of those and he really wantd Reggie White in the 1984 supplemental draft. He git over ruled.

If parcells had his way lawrence taylor and reggie white would have been team mates starting in 1984. Along with hof Harry carson, 2 time all pro leonard marshall, nd all decade linebacker Carl Banks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jeff hostetler was Phil Simms backup for for 6 years. Simms get hurt in week. Hostetler leads the giants to a ring. 

Earl Morrall was Jonny Unitas backup in the 60s. Unitas gets hurt, Morrall wins the mvp and leads the colts to a loss in superbowl 3.

In 1972 he took over after Griese got injured to finished the dolphins undefeated season and run to the playoffs.

Ryan nassib was Elis backup for 4 years. Last year he fell off the bench and up on IR. Dangerous job

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hart is so bad at rr a shitty dj fluker is a big upgrade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rams paid whitworth so much no one else was likely close </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jpp doesnt have a contract. He isn going to sign a 1 year deal. Giants have until july 15th to retract the contract if they can work out a long term deal. His year hit wont be as big as his franchise player tag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This oesntvsay what th cap hit is. Remember marahalls hit is only 4.5m. Ill bet alot of it is non guaranteed in year 3 that he will never see.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Id pose with it just for fun. Put an American flag on it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im a liberal and I call bullshit on this. Donald Trump is more Bozo he idiot clown president than Hitler. These numbers are way too high. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 01:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Georgw martin has made alot of money from the TV show. He owns a theater and an art house in Santa Fe. He blogs about them all the time. Those likely take alot of his time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When trumpster trash call this fake news remind them that before obamacare there were 57 million uninsured. This bill puts the number at 52 million. So its entirely likely when you slash the medicid expansion and subsidies. So they insure 5 m more people than before obamacare.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mccain has abpn entire atate. This guy has one disctrict. That isnt possible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would have been better to fry his balls, rip his finger nails out, and torture. Would be fun to watch that shit on youtube. Fuck hitler </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put 24x7 tales on spicer and call him baghdad bob at every opportunity. Fuck woth the man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I support white genocide. Interracil babies make us homogenous </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of us are. Lots of guys who get it are cracking jokes on twoxchromosones and the wimen there realize we get the joke. Plus we are just immature. No true male can pass up the excuse for masturbation or fart jokes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine what happens if someone does War of the World radio show again and some sumb rednecks start shooting at Amazon drones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. Im a jewish liberal. Id kick the shit out of a nazi on site with with my trusty bat named Lucille. Im hateful. Im the democratic parties Neeganwhen it comes to nazis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Magic decoder rimg from a cracker jack box </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump meant the paparazzi took unflattering photos of him and he feels obama supported that and laughed at him forvbeing fat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Primary is meaningless. If 10% of the pop is democratic. Racist Shitbag is likely playing to gis racist shitbag supporters. As long as he is in office, put him on tv as much as possible. Make republicans have to respond to him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Background is determine whether you can be trusted to not intentionally steal classified information. Doesnt include a test to see if you a fucking idiot.

This looks like it has names on it. If I had a clearance I wouldnt want my fucking name released.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? Oh damn. That I did not know. How did a racist shitbag get elected? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh damn. That is funny. Move it close to aazon hq to fuck with Jeff Bezos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too bad he didnt live and get put on trial and publicly executed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
