<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3065</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 03:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bear Grylls, we could jump out of a helicopter and land out in the middle of nowhere, almost die but make it back to civilization alive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 03:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lolz even harder!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 03:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They say great minds think alike. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 03:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A guy named Everett I worked with, he was 52 and had either a heart attack or aneurism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 03:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lolz were had!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 03:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Girl you're so hot you got me smokin' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 03:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only need two...a book titled ABORTION FOR DUMMIES and a pack of coat hangars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 06:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Canada to the Youkon Territory!  I lived in Alaska for 4 years and want to go back permanently so if it has to be another country lets just go across the border into Canada.  White Horse looked cool when I went through there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 06:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was 22 when I got married almost 20 years into it now so that was the right age for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 06:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I told them not to be looking at naked people and don't ever tell anyone where you live or go to school...basically told them someone will snatch them and they will never see mommy or daddy again and it seems to work.  My 7yo is very good at looking stuff up and learning about things that interest him which is good in my opinion because computers are not going away.  I had to look things up in an encyclopedia when I was 7 lol!  It is interesting to see what these kids will be doing with all this information. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 05:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a good question and I am pretty much letting my kids do whatever they want on the Internet.  I was always told TV would rot my brain but I think I'm ok so I'm pretty sure my kids will be fine.  I was talking to my 15yo daughter the other day and she mentioned tentacle porn.  She didn't understand why people would watch that and I explained to her about Japanese censorship laws which basically led to it.  My 12yo daughter watches lots of my little pony but is now getting into anime like my older one.  My 7yo boy plays roblox and watches Minecraft videos all day.  He knows to stay away from the "bad" websites but I'm sure one day he will get curious and I will know.  We do make them turn in their phones and tablets at bedtime so they don't stay up all night.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 14:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, he died because he did too much drugs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 05:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea that cool winged demon tatoo I wanted 20 years ago would be covered in hair lol! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 05:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoever the idiot is that drives slow in the passing lane making everyone pass them on the right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 05:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Benny Benassi's Satisfaction video.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 05:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I blacked out and don't remember. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 05:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't that important.  Get off the internet and go do something useful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 05:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fat people that ride the scooters at Walmart because they're too fat to walk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 05:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $30,000 to pay off my credit card debt would be nice...seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 05:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep that pretty much covers everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 04:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Start training for local triathlons and someday if you are good enough you can compete in the actual Iron Man Triathlon held every year in Hawaii. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 04:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because most people are not very active and do not burn off enough calories laying on the couch.  Supposedly they are high on the glycemic index which when eaten by themselves causes a blood sugar spike which in turn causes an insulin spike causing your body to store fat.  (I'm not a doctor) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 04:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in the military for 20 years and traveled all over the place.  I have not been everywhere but I have almost seen enough.  So far my favorite place in the entire world is my home being with my loving family, wherever that may be.  Alaska was awesome and I want to live there for the rest of my life...but I'm stuck in Texas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 04:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this sub mostly 15-17 year olds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 04:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, set low standards for yourself so you won't be disappointed later in life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 04:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ask them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 02:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a mechanic so pretty much anything except idiot people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 22:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you and good luck with your future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 22:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good info!  I like the old military badges, I've never seen the tank badge for the British but I have seen the Nazi tank badge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 21:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I'm talking about!  That shit will ruin your life one way or the other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 21:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sucks, people have a tendency to not think about how they might be in 20 or 40 years if they don't take care of themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 15:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smoking is so bad for you, I'm so glad I quit.  Don't ever start smoking.  Sucks your mom can't or doesn't want to quit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 14:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fat people getting fatter.  It is something that is 100% preventable, just stop eating so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 13:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry to hear that.  Try not to make the same mistakes yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 13:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad you were born!  It's nice being alive isn't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 13:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I quit way before I had kids, I found a good woman that gave me a choice of her or drinking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 08:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Find out where they live and fuck their shit up in the middle of the night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 08:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was literally putting on my uniform and getting ready for work when I was in the Air Force.  I lived on base so I hurried up and got to work.  We didn't do much work that day, just watched TV and played ping pong waiting for something to happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 07:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what do you do with a toboggan? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 07:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd kill my old boss for $1 billion...maybe less. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 07:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait a minute...what is this lottery coupon you speak of?  I've always heard it called a lottery ticket (USA). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 07:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sing it Annie! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 07:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You ever been to a Turkish bathroom?  It's just a hole in the floor and a garden hose to wash your ass with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 07:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, all the lazy fat fucks hog up the scooters while granny is left with her walker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 07:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad was an alcoholic also and it sucked growing up like that.  He finally quit drinking when I was around 15 because one of his buddies got killed drinking and driving but the damage was already done at that point.  I told myself I would never do that to my kids if I ever had any. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 07:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Military culture for sure.  There is nothing like partying with your brothers after work on a Friday night at the dorms (Air Force).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 06:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw a house engulfed in flames one night on my way home from work.  There was no fire department around, no cops, no neighbors outside and there were other houses nearby.  I was imagining a family being burned alive while they slept.  Thankfully later I found out the house was empty because of earlier flood damage.  Apparently the heaters and fans they were using to dry the place overloaded the wiring and caught on fire...they didn't have flood insurance but luckily they had fire insurance, go figure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 06:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My kids and my wife think I'm amazing also!  Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 06:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, THOSE PEOPLE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 05:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First untethered space walk ever.  A politician named Budd Dwyer blew his head off, we had one of those big satellite dishes and were watching news feeds so we saw it live.  Space shuttle blew up.  911 attack happened while I was literally putting on my uniform getting ready for work when I was in the Air Force.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 05:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One word...Acclimatization. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 05:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Already bringing brisket  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 05:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, Texas is bringing brisket </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 05:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I was gonna say that too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 05:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea, I got the fuck out of there as fast as possible and never bothered looking her up...but let me take a look at Facebook real quick just for the hell of it.  Well it looks like she disappeared. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 04:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buy myself a secluded tropical island and have everything I ever wanted brought to me for the rest of my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 04:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^^ The correct answer ^^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 04:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm over 40 and still ride the shopping cart across the parking lot instead of walking lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 04:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I made it to work ok, love you baby!! Xoxoxoxo  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 04:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol I did too much drugs when I was younger...didn't catch that last part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 04:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I almost joined the Army because I wanted to be a Ranger sniper...instead I joined the Air Force and was a mechanic, but hey I didn't get my ass shot off and don't have any PTSD issues.  I often think about what may have been. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 04:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boring!  Unless you're high as fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 04:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How they raise their children.  Like people who let their kids throw temper tantrums because they don't know, or worse yet, don't want to deal with their kids behavior.  But hey, let them be little shits so one day they can smoke enough meth where they can't take care of themselves and get to live with you for the rest of your life...Brandon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 04:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not gonna happen.  This whole going to Mars thing people are fantasizing about right now is a bunch of wishful thinking.  Yea it's real nice to say you want to go to Mars but actually doing it would be suicide.  Let's say you somehow survive the radiation on the way there, wtf are you going to do once you get there and realize you are on your own?  You won't be able to run to the store and buy more bottled water or food or medecine or sanity.  What purpose does sending humans to Mars have besides saying we did it?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 04:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do work for old people...they have a bunch of money but are too old to do work anymore and shit still needs to get done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 04:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends what is at stake.  In certain circumstances I will do what is necessary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 03:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stopped being an alcoholic and quit smoking before they were born...if that counts.  Otherwise we would be living in a trailer in the woods with NO INTERNET like a bunch of scrubs...like I grew up.  My kids already have a way bigger head start in life than I did.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 03:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The theory comes from a *veteran* alien hunter.  I wonder how many he has found so far.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 01:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pic of the two badges in your hand, the one on the right is a British tank badge.  Found this with a quick google search:  It's a British Army cap/hat/ beret badge for RTR (Royal Tank Regt) or RTC (Royal Tank Corps) with the Kings crown, Kings Crown Badge as worn in WWII, But in service from 1924 to 1953 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 06:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man that looks like fun!  I was a member of the Fairbanks cycle club a long time ago and we went on many rides that looked like this...now I'm stuck in Texas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 05:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not gonna lie...I have been pissed off at my MTB all summer and haven't ridden it since April.  My last ride I did 40 miles but should have done 65 that day.  I trained my ass off all previous fall and that winter to get ready for the Ouachita Challenge in Arkansas.  I got sick with some viral upper respiratory thing a week before the event and hadn't fully recovered by the ride time.  Lately though I want to start riding again but every time it rains here in Texas they shut down the trails for at least a week and it sucks living here.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 05:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My daughter loves my little pony and it's pretty much the only show she likes that I can stand to watch with her.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 01:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I looked for instances where federal land was relinquished to state control but I couldn't find any.  However it appears federal lands are already being exploited in Alaska's north slope and the people of Alaska have no say in what the federal government is allowing to happen in their own state.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 00:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, they are advocating to have the federal government turn over the control to each individual state.  http://talkingpointsmemo.com/livewire/gop-platform-committee-wants-feds-to-turn-fed-lands-over-to-the-states </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 05:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had an aluminum frame break (specialized) so it happens.  They replaced my frame under warranty and I never had another problem with it.  I've never had a carbon bike but I am assuming if you bought from a reputable company they will have some type of warranty as well, it would be worth doing your research on the companies website before you buy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 02:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lacking forethought is a big one in my opinion.  I see a lot of "snapshots" where, as an example, it looks like someone simply saw something cool then zoomed in with their lens vs walking closer or perhaps walked up to it and stood over the object while looking down at it as if someone were using their smart phone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 21:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is ignorant parenting right there folks.  She probably never even discussed the presidential election with her children, I know I did.  My boy is also 7 and he voted for Trump as well in his schools mock election.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 02:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There used to be one north of the park on the main road but this was 20 or so years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 01:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always feel like I'm in a pinball machine the first ride back...then I'll smoke that shit the next ride! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 01:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea if I've been off the trails for a while the first ride is absolutely terrible.  Hitting every damn rock along the way and getting my ass kicked by little hills.  Then the next day I'm sore all over.  Then I get pissed off because I let myself go for so long and then I hit the gym and trails harder the next time.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 05:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They will be ok by next week, just a little crying and infighting going on right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 05:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That shit is too funny!  Better get that trade marked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 05:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Don't make Texas have to bitch slap ya'll out west now ya hear? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 05:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a bunch of sore losers.  Better luck next time, until then get over it and stop acting like a bunch of fucking idiots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 04:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My kids school held a mock election and my boy (2nd grade) voted for Trump!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 00:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try using natural light next time, the pop up flash on cameras suck, they tend to over expose whatever is closest and under expose everything else.  Also a side view of the lizard would be better...on a log or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 06:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come back and tell us when it actually happens, until then this is not news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 06:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit is definately a liberal echo chamber just like mainstream media. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 05:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're gonna need a lens with a longer focal length if you plan on doing more moon shots.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 05:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it the way it is!  Makes me want to be there also but I'm stuck at work.  I like the sun behind the sail, good timing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 05:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would much rather see a half naked woman in the pic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 04:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You definately nailed the half rotted flower look.  Personally I would have found one not half rotted but that's just me.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 04:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not gonna sugar coat it...it's a weird pic.  It appears you are out in a forest and the question is what is up with those rocks?  They don't "belong" out there. Also it looks like you just walked up and zoomed in a little with your lens and snapped a pic...not much effort or preplanning went into this shot and I can tell.  If you want to take more "good" pics take a look at www.photo.net to get some ideas.  The good news is it can only get better from here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 04:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I need to stop looking at that sub...it's depressing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 04:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smokey mountains? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 04:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To me the scene could do without the entire left side from just a little left of center.  Also the light is not ideal in the background.  There is too much contrast between the sunny areas and the darker rocks in mid image.  I think the colors in the foliage would show up better if the sky was overcast and that would also solve your contrast issue.  Maybe I'm used to seeing overly photoshopped images and thinking those look nice.  Anyway, it looks like a very cool place and I wish I was there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 01:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yet they still have witch doctors dismembering 4 year olds in order to find a lost cell phone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 00:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may be on to something...oh wait there is already a category for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 18:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bought my first MTB when I was 22, a 97 GT Outpost lol.  Went from smoking a pack and a half of cigarettes a day and weighting 210 down to 180 and not smoking.  It was the best decision I ever made for my health.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 17:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the chicken version of the Matrix but there is never a happy ending </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 17:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ordinary take offs, not even full afterburner with a steep climb out...lame </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
