<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2997</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 08:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There wasn't a new episode of Supergirl this week, but there's a new episodes of AoS today (hence Coulson and Daisy in the picture). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 05:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  What's the sauce tho?

Just google "cw netflix" and look at any of the top results; this is old news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 05:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We know; this was announce nine months ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 03:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unrounded final rating: 0.68 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 03:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. But I do find this joke really old and played-out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 03:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure. But it wasn't because of Prison Break, otherwise Heatwave would also be gone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 02:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prison Break isn't why he left </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would there be much focus on reviving a flop? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About $3.50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 02:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Why do all the DEO employees know who Kara is ?

Because the DEO has known who Kara was since shortly after she landed on Earth, it's never been a secret to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 09:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its fate was sealed after the first 4 episodes, if not before that; at this point what's surprising is that NBC brought it back at all. The rest of the season should air at some point but it may well be Saturdays in the summer or something like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 06:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only 15 years since that episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 05:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or shoot threes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oliver definitely wore it better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time intentionally fouls while down at the end of a close game, how is intentionally fouling while up any different? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Superman as a regular would be a terrible idea, but Brainiac as a Big Bad could be cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 00:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That they wouldn't get international rights, and that they already have their own Marvel shows so AoS/AC wouldn't really bring them anything new. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 00:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There will be a new season on NBC next year

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 22:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Presumably Jessie L. Martin exists on Earth-1 but doesn't look quite the same as on our Earth, or someone else played Tom Collins in Earth-1's *Rent* ( la *Last Action Hero*). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 21:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  No reason they can't add AoS to the their roster. 

There are reasons for Netflix not to pick up AoS, same as for why they didn't pick up Agent Carter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On that table "skew" refers to the percentage of the show's total viewers that lie in the 18-49 demo (for some reason they don't explain this on that page). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 18:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Fuck those leaches.

You are the leech in this situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 18:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Spottedratings has a page where you can compare shows in categories including male/female skew.](http://www.spottedratings.com/2016/09/the-2016-17-daily-year-to-date-rankings.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 08:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That movie had many flaws but Michael Clarke Duncan as Kingpin was not one of them. D'Onofrio does a fine job in the TV series but he just doesn't have the physical presence that Duncan brought to the role. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 08:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I should probably finish season two of Daredevil one of these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 08:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If anyone's unsure if this is legitimate, just click one of the links to the article's sources. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 08:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I have this theory that Marvel bribed ABC to get AoS renewed for Season 2. 

[AoS finished its first season with the 5th best ratings among ABC's scripted shows that year (out of 25)](http://tvseriesfinale.com/tv-show/abc-tv-show-ratings-for-2013-14-season-30249/). No bribe was necessary for ABC to renew it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 08:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  does anything on ABC have better ratings

[Yes, most of ABC has better ratings.](http://tvseriesfinale.com/tv-show/abc-tv-show-2016-2017-season-ratings/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 05:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the writers making the DEO suddenly incompetent in order to make Maggie actually useful, because they couldn't come up with any other way to make her relevant. It's kinda telling that they couldn't find a role for her without nerfing existing characters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 04:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TV distribution rights are sold by country/region. The CW only operates in the US, so their app is only for the US; the Canadian rights to Arrow were sold to CTV. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 01:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GO POKES! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 01:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should post this to /r/arrow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 22:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Yep](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/1996_Paris%E2%80%93Roubaix)

Edit: apparently they did it [two](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/1998_Paris%E2%80%93Roubaix) more [times](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/1999_Paris%E2%80%93Roubaix). And then Domo-Farm Frites (which was basically just Mapei) [did it](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Domo%E2%80%93Farm_Frites). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay but that's not an explanation for why it turns her evil *on the show*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/Hamburgo2087's point also holds for demo numbers:

Arrow has aired 9 episodes since the winter break - 7 of them have rated in the range of 0.50 - 0.60 in the 18-49 demo. That seems to be Arrow's core live demo audience at this point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Supergirls target audience is females while Arrows should have always been a mixed demographic but ended up skewing towards females for a couple seasons there.

All the CW superhero shows skew male in viewership, even Supergirl (though it skew less male than the other 3). Now the CW could still think that the target audience is females and be forcing story elements into the show specifically to appeal to them, but if that's the case then they're ignoring their current audience (which seems foolish IMO).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 20:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The CW app is just for the US, OP is in Canada so they should look for a CTV app. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Not sure if you are being serious

The /s tag means the answer to that is no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of the Berlanti DC shows on the CW. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It means Netflix has first-run distribution rights </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 06:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The CTV website appears to have it available to stream for free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 06:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [She gone, bro](https://www.reddit.com/r/FlashTV/search?q=what+happened+to+gideon restrict_sr=on) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 06:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  they'll have to distribute their CGI money even more, making the CGI on the Flash even worse. 

How does that follow? Do you seriously think the CW would order a new show and not give it its own budget? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 03:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a Canadian article and Riverdale is a Neflix original in Canada. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 00:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think Whedon going from Disney to WB is related to his Fox shows leaving Netflix. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 22:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Social media presence is important in that it [hopefully] leads to views, but by itself it doesn't make networks money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 22:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whichever advertisers pay more for (which I think is currently broadcast as opposed to digital). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> \#4 doesn't really bother me, but otherwise I have to agree with these. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Ok...so karamel got together, they broke up, they got back together, they broke up...he's a jerk, he's not a jerk, he's a jerk...shall I continue?

How is this relevant to the discussion at hand? This thread is about Alex/Maggie, not  Kara/Mon-El. Anyways people can find the Alex/Maggie stuff boring *and also find the Kara/Mon-El stuff boring*, it's not an either-or situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that including the crossover? The crossover is a major outlier and should probably be omitted when using previous ratings to make predictions like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unrounded (prelim): 0.53, up from last week's 0.48. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These ratings are even with the past two episodes.

Edit: and up slightly in unrounded numbers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  with the announcement of Katie Cassidy being a series regular in Arrow S6 and the Legends trying to fix the reality I have a pretty strong feeling that they will end up changing it back with the addition of Laurel being alive. 

Except they're announced that Katie will be playing Black Siren next season, who is already alive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct.

Edit: Also voice acting typically doesn't take that long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [sEARCH BAR](https://www.reddit.com/r/FlashTV/search?q=what+happened+to+gideon restrict_sr=on) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would who's writing Black Lightning have anything to do with the Flash's CGI? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 09:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Berlanti-produced superhero shows are on break. iZombie is DC and its season starts next week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 08:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  why another?

Because the CW can't come up with anything else to do, so they're going to ride the superhero wave until it inevitably crashes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find the Alex/Maggie romance pretty useless, but Mon-El gets way more screentime than Maggie does so yeah I'd say he's the bigger problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She had a cameo in 1x23 (though by the time that aired LoT had already officially been ordered to series). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If not, I could certainly see this being on Friday nights to have DC every night.

The CW almost certainly won't put a new show on Fridays, and the DC shows are currently only 3 nights a week anyways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  they hired a high-caliber costume designer to make this costume and they released this promo photo

This doesn't say anything about the pilot's chances of getting picked up. It's not like the people producing the pilot are going to be like "eh, it might not get picked up so let's only bother with second-rate costumes and stuff".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's still in the pilot phase.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unknown </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the first picture of him in costume, he was confirmed for the role ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah OP's title is shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't have unrounded finals yet. The star for preliminary numbers is gone is gone because they're not using preliminary numbers, but they won't have unrounded finals until early next week at which point they will update their chart; until then their chart will read  _._0 because they're listing two decimal places without controlling for significant figures. It's a quirk in their charts that I've noticed after following them for a while.

If you don't believe me, look at how *every* new broadcast show from this Monday is currently listed as _._0 by tvseriesfinale:

* [The Voice](http://tvseriesfinale.com/tv-show/the-voice-season-12-ratings-mondays/)
* [Taken](http://tvseriesfinale.com/tv-show/taken-season-one-ratings/)
* [Dancing With The Stars](http://tvseriesfinale.com/tv-show/dancing-stars-season-24-ratings-spring-2017/)
* [Quantico](http://tvseriesfinale.com/tv-show/quantico-season-two-ratings/)
* [Superior Donuts](http://tvseriesfinale.com/tv-show/superior-donuts-season-one-ratings/)
* [24 :Legacy](http://tvseriesfinale.com/tv-show/24-legacy-season-one-ratings/)
* [APB](http://tvseriesfinale.com/tv-show/apb-season-one-ratings/)
* [Jane The Virgin](http://tvseriesfinale.com/tv-show/jane-virgin-season-three-ratings/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Shes a main ~~recurring~~ cast member for Arrow (Season 6)

As Black Siren, who is still alive, so that doesn't require any rewriting of history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't know that the final was a 0.70, just that it rounded to a 0.7. Unrounded finals won't be available until early next week (tvseriesfinale will list _._0 initially but they'll update it when they get unroundeds). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm well aware of all that. The point is that the actors are performing in front of a live audience rather than having a purely artificial laugh track added afterwards like arhanv was talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Shows in the early days of TV were filmed in front of a live audience

Most current shows with 'laugh tracks' are also filmed in front of live audiences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you have a computer with all this knowledge why don't you use it?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Season 4 is pretty much guaranteed for syndication reasons. Beyond that is not, but as long as it's ratings stay in CW's top few shows it'll be in very little danger of cancellation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Why don't you use the search bar?](https://www.reddit.com/r/FlashTV/search?q=what+happened+to+gideon restrict_sr=on) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 08:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zolomon phased a bullet out of Harry without hurting his insides. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Episodes for a show like AoS are written a few months before they air, and it's been clear for months now that AoS is in danger of not getting renewed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From that article:

 In recent years, the 100-episode milestone for syndication has been lowered to 88 episodes

So AoS will reach the syndication milestone at the end of this season (and it's already in syndication as /u/Scrimshire said). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's better than everything else on the CW aside from the Flash, so yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 01:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not yet official but that's pretty much a formality at this point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just going with what the CW gave as their expectations for Supergirl, which was for it two be in their top two shows. It is currently meeting that expectation. Ratings are down across the entire network, but that's not an issue specific to Supergirl and we don't know how much lost revenue from lower ratings is being made up by stuff like the CW app. As for budgets, we don't have hard numbers for those so it's hard to quantitatively account for that (also the only CW shows getting 0.5s or higher are the superhero shows and Supernatural).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Now its doing worse than the Flash.

But better than every other CW show. The CW said they expected it to be one of their top two shows, and it is (and I doubt they expected it to do better than the Flash seeing as both had similar ratings at the end of last season and Flash was already on the CW). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Strictly looking at ratings, this is bad.

Strictly looking at *which* ratings? To say it's bad you first need a context; if that context is 'CW ratings from ten years ago' then yeah it would be bad, but if the context is 'ratings from current CW shows' then it's good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unrounded: 0.67 (preliminary), up from last week's final of 0.64 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a time when a 3.0 was a bad rating for a show on the Big 4. Times change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  does anyone want E1 and E38 to merge?

I don't, I would prefer to not completely destroy the backstory and continuity of *Supergirl* just for the sake of occasional crossovers that are already easily possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 16:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  but they used to be!

They actually didn't, people just mistakenly thought graphite was a form of lead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 16:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because you might not like TBBT doesn't mean its ratings aren't the highest of any show on broadcast TV. SNL's ratings are second-highest, i.e. better than every other broadcast show save one (which show that one happens to be is not particularly important); it's not desperate for viewers by any means. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 10:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CW Music Meister wishes he was as cool as Q. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 10:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The latter half of Season 2 at least had an overarching plot.

Eh, only really up to 2x18; after that it pretty much became "Zoom does evil things because reasons". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 09:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It was like "Zoom! 21 episodes of random villain filler, and then Zoom dies."

I though for most of the season Zoom had a coherent plan, the problem was he achieved the goal of that plan with six episodes left in the season and then proceeded to just do generic mustache-twirling villainy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 09:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Like the kids will have 1 grandfather.

Only because their other grandfather is dead, which is not particularly uncommon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 09:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And the karmel drama for the entire season hasn't pissed you off?

Who says they're not annoyed by that as well? It is possible to not care about the Alex/Maggie relationship while simultaneously not caring about the Kara/Mon-El relationship; not everyone who dislikes one relationship does so because they're shipping another. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 07:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This season of SNL has been a ratings powerhouse, beating every network offering except for The Big Bang Theory

Read the damn article before making yourself look like an idiot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 07:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I swear if I see a Tommy is Vigilante thread LOL. Unless NBC suddenly cans Chicago Med I don't see that happening.

Oh I can guarantee that we'll see 'Tommy is Vigilante' threads (actually I'm pretty sure there have already been some), and they'll be just as dumb as the 'Tommy is Prometheus' threads were. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 07:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By "particularly in the spring" I meant anytime from February through May. Again, go and actually look at the air dates for old shows: they went on breaks all the time, and it was no more predictable than now. 

For example, here's how some well-known TV shows were scheduled in the spring exactly 20 years ago:

* [ER](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_ER_episodes#Season_3_.281996.E2.80.9397.29): on break for Feb 27, March 6, March 13, March 20, March 27, April 3
* [Seinfeld](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_Seinfeld_episodes#Season_8_.281996.E2.80.931997.29): on break for Jan 23, Feb 27, March 6, March 20, March 27, April 3, April 17
* [Friends](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_Friends_episodes#Season_3_.281996.E2.80.9397.29): on break for Jan 23, Feb 27, March 20, April 10
* [Frasier](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_Frasier_episodes#Season_4_.281996.E2.80.9397.29): on break for Jan 28, Feb 4, March 4, March 18, March 25, April 8
* [Law   Order](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_Law_%26_Order_episodes#Season_7:_1996.E2.80.9397): on break for Jan 22, Jan 29, March 6, April 9, April 23, 
* [The X-Files](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_The_X-Files_episodes#Season_4_.281996.E2.80.9397.29): on break for Jan 19, March 2, March 9, March 30, April 6
* [Roseanne](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_Roseanne_episodes#Season_9_.281996.E2.80.9397.29): on break for Jan 21, Feb 4, March 11, March 25, April 1, April 8, April 15, April 22, April 29, May 6
* [Star Trek: Voyager](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_Star_Trek:_Voyager_episodes#Season_3_.281996.E2.80.9397.29): on break for Jan 22, March 5, March 12, March 26, April 2, April 16
* [Home Improvement](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_Home_Improvement_episodes#Season_6_.281996.E2.80.931997.29): on break for Jan 21, Feb 4, March 4, March 18, March 25, April 8, April 22

That's a lot of breaks, and no less random than the ones shows take these days.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 06:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  20 years ago shows generally ran straight through the current half-season once they started. Shows didn't randomly take a week off here, a month off there

Sure they did. Go and look at episode lists from back then and you'll see that shows often had breaks (that weren't the winter holidays), particularly in the spring. Broadcast TV schedules have run from September to May for many decades, and the only way to stretch ~22-25 episodes over that time is with breaks (and the single several-month break that some shows do these days is a relatively modern phenomenon).

 unless the network was actively trying to kill the show by sabotaging its ratings

Why do you think networks would try to actively sabotage the ratings of their own shows? If networks are sufficiently unhappy with a show's performance they don't need to 'try to kill it' they just pull it from the schedule and replace it (then possibly burn it off later on weekends and/or the summer); leaving it on the schedule but deliberately trying to hurt its ratings would be moronic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 06:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This age of completely disjointed TV show seasons

The past 40+ years? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 05:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Would they go 17-1 in a power conference?

Probably not, but then in a power conference they wouldn't necessarily need to go 17-1 to get a 1-seed, so that's not a great comparison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The next episode airs on April 24. (Also April 3 is next week, not two weeks from now). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Kevin Smith remembered that J'onn can read minds?

Gabriel Llanas and Anna Musky-Goldwyn remembered that J'onn can read minds; Kevin Smith didn't write the episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  once Thawne rewrites reality (for as temporary as it may be) how will that effect The Flash?

Not at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She'd be at most his foster sister. Barry wasn't adopted by Joe, Henry was still his legal father. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 22:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not unhappy about this, but it does further prove how poor the current Arrow producers are at actually planning things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 22:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was just taken in by them. Joe presumably had some form of legal guardianship over him, but Henry was still his legal father. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not even that, Barry wasn't adopted by the Wests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   I don't care if your a conservative or liberal, but I'm a watcher of this show and don't want to be banged over the head with political nonsense.

Exactly. I hate watching ham-fisted political crap in shows, even when I agree with the underlying message. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because in 7 months hair will grow 3-4 inches, which is far less than the difference between his current flashback hair and his pilot hair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
