<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2159</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 13:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty fun too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 19:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> X </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 20:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn I didn't participate in the third ranked season because it started immediately after the second and I was still oozing salty frustration from that grind. And then this time there was months of break between and the reward I miss out on is an Atlanta. Curses! Until next season I guess...

Looks like they improved the system a lot though. Lots of good rewards still and the unicum bonus is going to make it ez pz status. Let's go see if cruiser is going to be as hard as I think it'll be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 20:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So far away... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 20:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could probably make the head as a separate piece that fits in place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 20:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boats is life, my friend. But I'll stop by for some Mirage. Tons of good games out this year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 20:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reithur! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 19:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The RU DDs are support cruisers under a DD flair. Stick with friendly ships, focus enemy DDs as priority from range, then burn everything else. Your AP works double time on broadside targets, battleships too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 19:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP ships are generally pretty fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 19:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do I look like a random pubbie to you? No sir. I'm a self proclaimed mega tryhard and I keep HE loaded 24/7.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 18:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Atago is best solo dolo yolo cruiser. That ship can handle every situation and fight 1v1 against any ship with enough skittles. For this reason she is my favorite.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 14:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> T10 play is overrated anyway. Good T8-9 matches are my favorite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 14:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you're the exception. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 13:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tashkent is a beast... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 20:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smart phones do calling and texting and angry birds. The upgrades between them do not affect the quality of software you originally purchased it for in most ways. Comparing game consoles to smart phones is apples and oranges.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 20:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the few advantages of owning a console is that it's plug and play until the next release. Now these new consoles that aren't actually new consoles but upgraded versions of the same console which is different than a next gen new console because reasons I dare not try to tackle come out alienating "early" adopters of this gen getting the inferior version of the current console that didn't last half as long as the previous gen but games will still work for the less upgraded current gen but be worse in ways to the better current gen that's not next gen because they are the same console but ones better.


Well, the good thing is that this will probably convince more people that PC is the way to go.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 19:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully soon, I'm running low on some flags. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 19:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These "upgraded" versions of current gen consoles are going to be a confusing fucking mess for the general consumer. What an embarrassment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 19:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PS4 has the only exclusives I care about that aren't on PC.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 15:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have a PC? If yes, get game on PC. If no, get a PC. If not possible, then get it on PS4.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 15:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good choice bud </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 01:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can go your whole life without fucking a goat, you fuck one goat you're a goat fucker for life. Same with shitposting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 00:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shitposters cost extra. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 23:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much the best warships vid there is tbh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 18:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Selling hard carries, $40/hour. Minimal bitching about teammates.

Edit - actually serious  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 15:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pharah gets shredded by so many heroes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 13:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh baby </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 13:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DS3 is priority numero uno </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 18:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zao is like the one ship that could take a nerf or two tbh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 18:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At T10, when everything is OP, nothing is OP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 16:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2016 is a legendary year for games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 06:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you recommend some tracks? Can be trap or whatever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 14:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One and done is how it be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 14:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Says is quits, still posts on subreddit. If you are done with the game that's fine, but constantly ragging about how you're quitting the game just brings unnecessary negativity around here to people that aren't unable to adapt. If you're done with the game than be done and leave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 01:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NOOOOOO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 01:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TO THE TOP WE GO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 22:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Overwatch is a fantastic game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 22:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't seen much hate for it rather than a lack of interest. And the hype for blizzard games never die even when the game has huge flaws (Diablo 3). 

Personally I really hate the humor in Battleborn and that's going to be hard to look past. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 19:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not just the dispersion buff that'll help them (though vertical dispersion was a big issue), but also the improved firing angle of the rear turret and buffed secondaries. T8+ US BBs are gonna be beast mode. Can't wait. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 19:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's simply no way of competing with a new Blizzard IP. Overwatch is going to be HUGE. Battleborn might be a great game for the genre that offers a completely different experience than Overwatch, but it doesn't matter. This was either malice, stupidity, or just shit luck but it's not going to go well for Gearbox.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 18:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least 3, no more than 4 and a half.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 18:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ayyy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 17:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm aware, I'm a big fan of both dota and csgo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 17:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So defensive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 17:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean they have a couple guys that work on game balance but those games have been developed for a long time now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 17:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> me too thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 16:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be surprised if Valve ever developed (and released) a new game. They make so much money not doing anything it's crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 15:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Fuck you, demons!" 

Was my take on the story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 14:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None of this is actually accurate to time dilation. Downvoted for misinformation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 14:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time dilation occurs with speed relative to other things, has nothing to do with altitude. Satellites are moving very fast relative to the earth, hence their faster time relative to earth time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 13:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The competitive side of the game seems to favor T8 right now. Though, I'd say the ability to seal club really stops at around T6+ if you want to base WTR around that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 21:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to see the stats after the ship has been out a while though. Just a few days of play isn't enough datas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 20:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meet you in the middle for 99.5% of the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 20:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When my div mates see the Atago roll out, they know it's srs bsns time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 20:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good players can crank out far above average damage. Doesn't mean the ship is OP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 20:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like a reasonable set of regulations. Personally, after 2600 games I have never encountered intentional TK that I can remember though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 20:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If your torps hit a friendly, it's your fault every time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 17:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 17:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 76% winrates in all T8 cruisers disagrees.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 17:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. Turns out Wargaming actually know what they're doing. Who saw that coming? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 17:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not so sure. Amagi gets torn up by cruiser AP and HE. NC not so much. But yeah you're right. Amagi shell velocity and accuracy will make her mid/long range engaments. Mainly good for flanking where she won't be under much fire.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 17:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but they don't have the armor to deal with staying too close too long.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 17:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly what I meant. USN BBs will be the king of the mid range which is where cruisers live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 16:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> T8+ has some seriously influential cruisers. A number of them can, with a competent captain driving, take on BBs no problem. It's why BBS have kinda fallen out of favor in high tier. And with a lot of cruisers getting powerful abilities such as radar, being able to challenge them properly is important. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 16:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno. I assume at some computing device. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 16:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sub likes downvoting stuff. I'll pop you an upvote as you were indeed correct. 15 HE shells certainly can devastating strike a DD.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 16:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> High tier cruisers are crazy strong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 16:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those buffs make it a lot better. Most people don't realize but the NC already has a fast rudder and quick turning radius. With the ability to get the back gun on target more reliability and have way more armor than Amagi and AA and the accuracy buffs.. The Amagi now has what over the NC? A couple knots more speed and an extra gun? Amagi might be a little better still as a sniper but we all now how useful sniping BBs are. NCs are going to DESTROY the mid range game. Might not be a bad thing, cruisers have had it too easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 15:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fully agree that USN BBs need buffs, but overbuffing is a real possibility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 15:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck tracking close range with that 51 second traverse. 203 HE destroy DDs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 15:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the firing angle buffs might be reverted if anything. They need the accuracy though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 15:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should be able to get all guns on target with NO because of how quick and tight the turning is. Even then, those guns will put out less avg damage than Mogami in most situations. Only way NO is favored is an AP fight vs other cruisers close range. But if your opponent is smart they'll just use HE and make your small health pool go down a chunk at a time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 14:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> T8 and above get accuracy buffs, secondary buffs, AA buffs, rear turret firing angle buffs, and speed buffs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 14:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 155 Mogami is not too great because of the turret rotation. 203 Mogami is a beast though. Great concealment with great maneuverability and fire chance I feel gets too often overlooked by the 155 nerf. If it wasn't for the heal on the Atago, I would argue 203 Mogami is the better ship. 

New Orleans I don't like. 35k HP doesn't cut it at T8+. Everything else about it is good though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 14:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't be surprised if they revert some of the USN BB buffs. Those ships are insane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 14:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems you're correct, just watched a video that was posted a couple days back on it. Going stealth always has a 3 second delay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 13:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let us, dear friends, not forget our dear friends the cuttlefish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 20:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smoke was nerfed, SA is busted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 19:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smoke is not busted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 16:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> .... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 16:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you fucking sorry!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 05:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we're going to bring 4 Kutuzov next time we play you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 22:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 12:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh what's up DM. You guys have been kicking ass, keep it up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 22:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I play a lot of competitive warships through the training room (at T8) and radar is hard to use on coordinated teams. DDs that are backed up by BBs will keep pesky radar cruisers away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 21:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> US BBs buffed, German HE buffed, doubloons rewards for ranked, UI buffs, unicum ranked play buffs... biased Wargaming now based Wargaming.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 20:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chapy has better detection with worse maneuverability. Also chapy gets radar which makes pubby DDs cry. Kutuzov gets smoke and more range. They are very similar ships. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 20:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're pretty similar ships in their role, but Chapayev is probably a little more flexible because of its HE spam. New Orleans is far more maneuverable though and can fight other cruisers close range better.

Edit - it should also be pointed out that the Chapy has a massive citadel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 19:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where is based iku </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 18:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh shit time for celebration, upvotes are on me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 18:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but it happens so infrequently that i just don't worry about it. I agree ita a dumb mechanic but if you're so strapped for cash that you don't want to risk the 1% det chance on T10 you should play lower tiers to build up money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 17:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but you're like the most negative person on the subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 17:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Low tier DDs probably, but it's still going to be uncommon. "Farming" is going to be more like play 50-100 matches get 10 flags.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 17:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it comes with the US BB buff then yes it'll be a terrific patch. Wargaming is usually on point with balance though. There's been a couple odd choices but the game has always improved every big balance change imho.

Edit - a word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 17:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kutuzov AA is impenetrable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 17:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HE is darker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 16:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just so you know, you can tell the difference between HE and AP in the base game. It's subtle though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 16:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Means prepare your anus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 16:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> will have their status rebalnced

dis gon be good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 21:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blizzard outta know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 17:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stock prices might go down and down but the going rate for kidneys is always on the rise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 16:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Premium cruiser? *wallet intensifies* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 13:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who are good at the game wouldn't use aim assist! That's absurd! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 13:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well in my last 10 games haven't been like that, so I guess we're at a conundrum here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 13:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Kutuzov is my  favorite ship, I quite enjoy the DD meta. 

On a more serious note, I haven't noticed MM being consistently lopsided. Not like what you're on about. Could just be luck and a few odd rounds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 17:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to miss his tweets to Ted Cruz :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 03:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> May the flames guide thee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Denzel Curry - Narcotics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 01:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 22:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a simple man. I see a shitpost, I upvote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 20:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's tru tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 18:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This subreddit is the king of armchair game devs I swear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 16:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tashkent can stealth torp with CE but I'd still rather stack AFT/DE. Makes both AP and HE a strong option. 

BFT is also a straight up 10% dps upgrade, don't pass that up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 17:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dispersion and AA for T8 and above most likely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 17:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> US BBs are big team players. If your team abandons you, it's not the US BB's fault. There's no bias. US BBS are getting buffed next patches too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 16:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure what an angle locked anvil attack is but I think they wanted to keep planes fast for their uses on large maps and ability to scout properly and relocate (away from AA if needed).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 16:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well yeah I saw you say that you didn't like the AA changes but you didn't say why, so I just ignored it as rambling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
