<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1989</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a word for the special relationships that some industries have with governments? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 06:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not lobbying, but for example. economists, investors, and political commentators seem hyper aware of certain industries as a whole (banking, agriculture, healthcare) for many reasons, or at least for the reasons that I'm not aware of. If that is lobbying, then clearing up for me the differences between companies and industries lobbying would be appreciated. Is there a particular word for that though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What chart, guide, infographic, or poster do you really like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 05:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Ignorance is not knowing, stupidity is knowing and making the worse decision anyway." - One of my favorite teachers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 23:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> still waiting on what would be an awesome compilation of "wait for it...the mongols." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 23:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *casual whistling* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lets talk about palettes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 22:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So lets clear things up here. I don't even know what's what anymore. I was talking with my barista friend who recommended a bean that had 'tobacco' notes and then I find myself in a cigar shop and the salesperson directs me toward something with 'coffee' notes. I am getting the impression that these two examples are part of a larger issue of the lack of consistency.Can someone help me understand how to categorize, describe, and understand flavor to as granular of a level as I need to?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Honest Game Trailers joked that Ash only got sent out to train so that Professor Oak had more time to stay at home with Ash's mom. This interaction between them sold me on that idea. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 22:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 20:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. To the point of not being idiot proof, I get it, nothing is and carrying is just as much a responsibility as a right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What have you always wanted to try, actually tried, and then thought to yourself that once was enough? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 20:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 12:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm talking about supply on the shelves. We all have to recognize that this industry in particular is full of people that but and resell at a profit. Aftermarket parts, magazines, munitions, etc. If your friend turned his hoarding around into a profitable investment, that's a different story but from the bound of it. He is in the minority demographic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why is carrying a 1911 cocked and locked not grossly dangerous? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 10:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that it's locked but I imagine it's not impossible for the gun safety to catch against something. I mean, it's not unheard of for firearms to get some part of the holster caught inside the trigger guard and cause an accidental discharge. I dunno, just looking for someone to put my mind at ease. I am totally comfortable with the idea of concealed carry and am actually looking at some options for myself. I do see that one of the gold standards are 1911s though and just want the reassurance that cocked and locked isn't going to cause any issues.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] Why is ammunition, of all things, so susceptible to fluctuations on the supply side of supply and demand? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 07:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You always hear about how hard ammo can be to get in certain political or economic fluctuations but *why* is that so much more sensitive than anything else?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Death row inmates get whatever they want for their final meal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 07:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 04:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll look for the link to the video that taught me all of this, but as far as I know, that is not proper cigar etiquette at all. People need to be aware that it is an organic, perishable product that reacts to the organic matter that hits it. Especially if that organic matter is from another person. I believe that one of the original reasons for dressing a band around a cigar was so that the tobacco wouldn't be ruined by the oils (and sometimes other contaminants like sweat and germs) in the hand of whoever was handling it. Definitely disrespects the product, changes the flavor, and contaminates what someone else would eventually be putting in their mouth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I found this guide to detailing a car but it looks like it's going to cost a lot. Does anyone have any tips for doing this on a budget? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 02:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wp70NiIYtZY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do uncommon astronomical events happen so often that they don't seem uncommon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 00:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I get it, I understand that the universe is unimaginably huge and wonderful things happen all the time but it seems like every few months, something happens that only comes around every few hundred years  if not less often than that still. Is my shock just underestimating the frequency of the awesome events that are visible from earth or is this just one hell of a time to be alive?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 23:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a Texan. Can confirm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 19:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) You could potentially negotiate your starting salary to ask for a smaller pay reduction from the switch.  

2) Not a lot of people are fans of their bosses so hopefully, if there are any theatrics at play to get you to come in, you can see through that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 21:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like a federal level program. Does the state or city have anything to do with it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who cleans the streets? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 21:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who cleans roadkill, trash, and abandoned cars off of the road? It I've never seen any of these things being cleaned by any sort of crew or specialized vehicle (that I know of) but drive regularly enough down the same roads to see the before and after of the work and wonder.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have a very clear memory of telling my parents what I learned in school one day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 21:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We were watching a movie in science class today and one of the scientists said that the two most primal desires humans have are for food and sex."  

And without skipping a beat my dad turns and tells me "Well at least you can cook." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by forgetting [how] to make coffee. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 21:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "One is none. Two is one. If it's important, you need a backup." - CGP Grey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 09:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jNgP6d9HraI  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What unique security issues, if any, do the users of Linux (or anything open source for that matter) have to deal with? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 07:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 07:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So then followup question; what does a 'pure', single, 'un-timbred', overtoneless frequency sound like?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 07:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have played guitar for years and am familiar with harmonics from a perspective of technique but never had it explained to me that way. Hahaha.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 06:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> , that, and the other thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: The physics of different kinds of sound. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 06:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, so I have a good understanding of the basics. The amplitude of the sound wave is volume and the frequency of the sound wave is pitch. But what about the different *kiiiinds* of sound? How do they all differ from one another? Like, even if you were to play a piece of music at the same volume on two different instruments, they would sound distinctly different and I have a hard time conceptualizing *those* differences.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 06:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That explains why it 'claps' slowly in one direction and quickly in the other but doesn't explain how it's able to move back in the other direction in the first place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 01:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll try to get pictures up later. All the text is on Russian and only describes features like 'waterproof' but I can annotate the translation if need be. Its mechanical and vintage, yes, but still seems to run fine. And I think we are closer to the 'no chance at all' end of the spectrum.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] What should I consider when buying a strap? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 00:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a watch passed down to me through family but it is only the movement. It's turned out to be really difficult for me to track down what kind of band originally went with the watch because it was made in a country that no longer exists. I think I want to eventually start wearing it but don't know if I should go with matching steel, classic black leather, rubber, fabric, or something else entirely. Anyone want to give me food for thought on this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What should I consider when buying a strap? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 21:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What kind of foods pair well with pinot noir? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 21:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 10:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvote upvove upvote upvote


#nerdfighters

#DFTBA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I detail? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 00:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now, I'm not an ignoramus. I googled it. But I am asking it here because there are special considerations to be made for what I am cleaning and I wanted some input from this community. There is dust inside and out from sitting at a body shop, I had some body work done on a couple panels on one side be a use of an accident, I made the mistake of parking under a tree that just rained sap onto the half of the car that wasn't worked on by the body shop (thank god), and a friend spilled energy drink inside around the center console area, leaving a sticky residue. So knowing all of that, what are my detailing steps now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 23:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got eyes on the back of my head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 18:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, the phonetic alphabet *doesn't* rhyme but if you sing the alphabet, a lot of letters do. Namely b,c,d,e,g,p,t,v, and z. Hence, we have the phonetic alphabet (or so I assume).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whose bright idea was it to let so many letters rhyme? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 17:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The military's phonetic alphabet is cool and all but in the age of having to talk to customer service reps over the phone about account information, letter names seems unnecessarily similar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 11:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But what about the Olympic park where the athletes stayed and the path that the torch runners took? Its not just stadiums that go into an Olympic event. Some venues have even gone so far as to redirect certain businesses into and out of certain venues to play with the visibility of the area to ticket holders that need to do shopping and sight seeing in the downtime.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 10:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An amazing project and I don't know how long it took but this needs to be seen by as many people as can see it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the 1936 Olympics held in Berlin by the Nazis set the template for every Olympics thereafter including the torch relay, televising the games, and the grandiose construction projects undertaken by host countries. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 10:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 08:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spoiler Alert.  

I've seen the movie, I like the gun, but give people a warning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Troubleshooting] Camera troubles. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 06:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a laptop plugged into a docking stations which is plugged into a few other peripherals including a monitor. I am not using the docking port on the laptop, but rather a USB 3.0 connection on the back to one of the portable docking stations that has a bunch of kinds of ports. The camera that Skype recognizes is the one integral to the laptop, not the computer monitor, and I cant find where to go and what settings to play with to change that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 04:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I reiterate. Interesting thought, I want to believe it, I'm not calling you stupid. I just want the truth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 04:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting thought but I want a medical professional to confirm this not that you've disclaimed you aren't one. Lol. I never thought that critical mass was something needed to be taken into consideration.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 04:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So its like printing a *caution: hot* label on coffee cups? A legal thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 04:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm aware of the overuse issue. I just wanted to know that the things that were being missed weren't the superbugs that already had immunity. lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 04:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In all fairness, I'm asking a slightly different question.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Both major candidates have expressed both views on multiple issues over the years. What should I believe when they assert their current stances? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 04:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not going to link the compilation videos of either Trump or Clinton going back and forth and saying yay and then nay (or vise versa) on abortion, Iraq, marriage equality, healthcare, etc. It's out there and it doesn't take a lot of searching. Obviously, they are now (for the most part) aligned with the views of the party they are aligned with, but is there any confidence that a voter can have, a voter that  has deeply held party affiliations, that the candidate will represent them once in office? And furthermore, is this even unique to these 2 candidates or commonplace? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: What is the .1% of bacteria that certain cleaning products don't claim to kill and should I be worried? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 03:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 09:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And by mainstream defensive cartridge, you meeaan...? Kind of a follow up question to that is if defensive rounds are the really expensive kind. I was at the store not too long ago and picked up some crazy looking and crazy expensive rounds. Tri-tipped bullets and non-lethal 357 magnum birdshot-type rounds, etc. I know not to use crap ammo because that can lead to malfunctions but what exactly is the crap ammo to stay away from and what exactly is the defensive cartridge to carry on my EDC?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 08:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you hit the 'general direction' nail right on the head for me so thank you. Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some good recipes to cook up on Monday and have for the week? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 05:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lists of said recipes, sources, and general direction would also be much appreciated. I know my way around the kitchen but usually don't have to put forethought into leftovers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 02:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've enjoyed the videos for a while, I only learned through seeing this one today that he lived in the area.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 01:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can a team Valor artist get on there version of this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Engineering Explained's Jason Fenske takes an NSX around town </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 23:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fragrance companies deliver some of the best audiovisual in their ads because smellevision doesn't exist. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 19:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 18:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The art of the PSA, people. This man has mastered it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 09:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *unnecessarily* loud... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 00:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The blue rubber ones that the auto parts store throws in the bag for me when I but my lights.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 21:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No condensation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 20:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maaaaybe that was my problem but I'm pretty sure they were the regular ones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 20:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why I always wear gloves. And yet still.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 18:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The door lock bulb, I don't know what else to call it. Its the little orange lights that flash when the car is remotely (un)locked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My lights go out unreasonably fast. Is it a sign of a larger problem? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 18:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 02 Acura MDX. I replaced my headlights maybe 2 months ago and one went out (this is part of a pattern, not just a single faulty bulb) and my door lock bulb on the other side just died. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: why do so many people have problems with their mechanics? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 18:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd think that an industry like car repair would be so saturated that everyone would be on their best behavior in hopes of standing out of the competition but everyone has a horror story so...what's going on here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 06:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Real fun with all of those potential dates.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where do you go to fact check? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 05:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 00:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excerpt of that speech were placed in this song and I love it.  

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WQzZk69P69E  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 00:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No quite the answer I was looking for but valuable nonetheless. Mind if I pick your brain about the brass and powder? Ammo reloading is one of those things that I am also starting to pay more attention to but even considering that it could pay for itself eventually, the upfront costs still seem like a little much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some good tips for living with roommates for the first time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 21:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: I rent a house with 2 roommates. We each have our own bedrooms but I share a bathroom with one roommate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 20:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my not-expert opinion, anything modern takes the worry of reliability off the table, no? Shootabiliy is a mater of preference. The 9 mm is a lighter recoiling gun than 45 but I notice no difference at the range with my performance between the 2. Of course you still have to be mindful of the over-penetration and the noise and such.  I am considering for myself as an EDC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 17:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) The PRM30 is exactly along he vein of something I had in mind when I wondered why we can't trade the stopping power of a single projectile for capacity.  

2) Maybe a stupid question but.. *rimless* ammunition?  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 17:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By a factor of 6? really?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 17:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have heard that a lot and would probably personally opt for something 9mm and double stack, but I can see where the 45 could suit some people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do we use the calibers that we use? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 17:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I started looking into the world of concealed carry and self defense, I quickly learned that the 2 main cartrige sizes are 9mm and 45 ACP. 22 caliber is almost never talked about. And that got me, someone who has yet to encounter a situation that requires the use of a self defense gun, why the rule of thumb is wanting to fire off less shots of more powerful ammo? And that actually goes for any use of a gun now that I think about it, right? Home defense, hunting, pest control, maybe not competition shooting. What is wrong with sacrificing caliber for capacity and just being willing to pull the trigger a few more times? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMP] Looking for a video. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 08:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feat. Alexis Texas (I think), definitely a blonde who might have been kinda tipsy at the beginning of the video. It started with her and a bunch of men in the living room clothes and talking and then she took one into the bedroom at a time. Overall length was about 30 minutes on one of the major sites. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 07:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never heard of it. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] It seems like using a chef's knife over a santoku or the other way around is largely a matter of personal preference. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 06:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I wrong or is there a specific designated purpose for each of the two? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 03:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought about it like this and it makes less sense now. Wanna take another crack at it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 03:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gas, groceries, home goods, office supplies and tech, transportation or service/parts for my car or bike, entertainment to an extent, etc. Ya know, the things I am inevitably going to have to spend money on. I'm as tight-fisted as need be but the reason I didn't take this to r/frugal is because I specifically wanted to know what was in the area an had a decent reputation for working with students.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 03:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know how to cook. Not what I was asking about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What places in town offer some good student discounts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 03:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: What about giving a smaller engine a turbo charger makes the car 'better' than 2 extra cylinders? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 02:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please translate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 21:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/xJYnowK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 20:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not so sure about the liquor. That requires them to have a lisence as far as I know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Laptop connected to a docking station won't use the monitor's camera for skype. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 10:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can provide technical information if need be but I do think it's worth mentioning now that I am going through a portable docking station that connects to the laptop via USB 3.0.  The laptop also has it's own webcam build in which is what it s using right now, by default, staring at it's closed self. I only get functionality with my current set up if I opt for a 2 monitor solution.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 10:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/DAE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm looking for a good pairing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 09:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the classic combo of a good cigar and a good brandy or cognac is something I'm looking for and I have the particular cognac in mind. It's Remy Marin 1738. Does anyone have any suggestions? I'm pretty open mined but if I had to give you a starting point to help narrow the field down, then I'm looking for something on the milder end of the flavor spectrum, that smokes for 30-45 minutes, and doesn't break the bank. I have no preference for shape, country of origin, or brand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 09:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha. No problem, I guess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 06:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely understand all of that. My question was aimed at the exceptions to the rule and I was wondering what the reasoning was behind the occasional movie that gets released on a Tuesday or Wednesday.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why are movies only usually (and not always) released on Fridays? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 06:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 04:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it beer, wine, or liquor?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does Amazon not sell products that require a verification of age? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 03:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand that things like adult content, tobacco products, alcohol, an even cars if they wanted to go there could be a logistical challenge to implement but as long as there is a verification process for the age, mailing address and shipping address of the purchaser, then I don't see the problem that Amazon would have with asking customers to do some extra paperwork.  

Edit: Alright, so I've gotten answers to the aforementioned alcohol and porn but not for cars or tobacco, and while I'm at it, lets also bring firearms into the conversation. The verdict is still out on why I can't find cigarettes, cars or guns on Amazon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 21:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Torture testing aside, if I just wanted to buy a bunch of magazines for my home defense semiautomatic pistol and send rapid fire down range to hone my scenario shooting (like reloading, clearing jams, and drawing from the waist and such), I don't want that to inadvertently damage the gun. Even if it is something as notoriously reliable as a glock.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does testing, cleaning, and mainaining a gun entail? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 20:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been reading up and watching some reviews of some guns and when the reviewer says hat they have put thousands of rounds through the gun without any issues and have not specified over what period of time, is it alright to sometimes assume that it was thousands of rounds on a single day? That sounds a bit excessive but if you are trying to prove that the weapon is resilient, it's a good way to make your point. In all my years (not that many of them to be honest) I haven't even approached 1000 in a single day and the cleaning of the gun afterwards was still cumbersome.  

Edit: I'm probably better off not admitting this but shout out to u/doomrabbit for pointing out that I originally put this in the wrong sub.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 20:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good catch. Embarrassing. I could swear I posted this to r/guns 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does testing, cleaning, and mainaining a gun entail? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 19:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been reading up and watching some reviews of some guns and when the reviewer says hat they have put thousands of rounds through the gun without any issues and have not specified over what period of time, is it alright to sometimes assume that it was thousands of rounds on a single day? That sounds a bit excessive but if you are trying to prove that the weapon is resilient, it's a good way to make your point. In all my years (not that many of them to be honest) I haven't even approached 1000 in a single day and the cleaning of the gun afterwards was still cumbersome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 18:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well per example, the 2-pack of cartridges I need for my printer cost $64 online through a retailer, maybe more than that in the physical store if memory serves, and only $9 through amazon with prime free shipping nonetheless. I checked on Ebay and those 2 price ranges are both fairly common.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What products have a significant brick and mortar markup that you can avoid if you are willing to wait (and sometimes pay) for shipping? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 03:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The examples that immediately come to mind are button cell batteries and printer cartridges. What else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 00:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #PoGo_Nation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm new to the area and new to the Meeutup app. Does anyone else use it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 00:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 05:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #sharknado </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 19:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the same Leatherman micro and got a lot of use out of it over the years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 17:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 03:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 03:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't do what exactly?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 01:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The screams are all getting drowned out by the music and the blood blends into the red paint job.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 00:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any other day, duh, but considering that I'm already 'that guy' that's driving around in a brand new sports car, it's admitedly getting to my head just a tiny bit. A friendly reminder of what it takes to not be 'that guy' would be greatly appreciated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 00:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll check up on your list but I know for a fact it's not Swift, Crow, or Underwood. I'm familiar enough with those artists that I would be able to go from there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some dos and don'ts of enjoying a muscle car without getting in trouble or damaging anything? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 00:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am driving a mustang now and have never driven a muscle car before. It's a loaner. I wanna enjoy it but I don't want to end up paying through the nose for anything I didn't know was a mistake at the time. I'm normally an excellent driver with only parking tickets on my record.  

Edit: I no longer have the car but I sure had one hell of a time with it. Thanks to all who commented who helped me make all the right considerations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] A beautiful blonde singer with a song about the summer and boys. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 19:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She might be a country artist. I think I remember the country tropes in the music video; trucks and farmland and guys being all outdoorsy and athletic. Only other think I can say is that she is really really pretty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1 [TOMT] A beautiful blonde singer with a song about the summer and boys. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 19:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 19:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does this case follow the contour of the phone or is it one of those that helps the phone lay flat on a flat surface?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A beautiful blonde singer with a song about the summer and boys. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 17:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What case has worked really well for you and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 17:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not gonna call it a phablet but let's be real here. This is a big phone. I'd like the drop resistance and screen protector features (not to mention water resistance or the battery extensions) but if they come at the cost of the inability to hide my phone completely and comfortably in my pant pocket, then no thank you. That's at least been the experience with my current case (minus the battery extension) and I'm looking to change things up. Any suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] Is it really wrong to call a wine something other than it's proper name? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 18:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A friend was explaining to me the difference between the pinor gris and dessert wine that comes from the same grape from the same winery (picture him holding a bottle of the dessert wine) and I responded to him by asking about the pinot gris in his hand and he staunchly corrected me as if I wasn't listening at all. It was a dessert wine, not a pinot. I didn't ask for the clarification in real time because sometimes when I am being purely inquisitive, I can come off as argumentative, so I bit my tongue .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 18:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The house is on a slab but the deck is elevated by posts entirely to compensate for the height difference between the house and ground outside.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 04:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Republicans were the party in the north that among other things, were fighting for free states. Democrats were, for an equal amount of time, the party of the south. There was a definite platform switch somewhere in American history. Not one that caused a mass-migration across the north-south boarder, but a mass migration of political identities across the aisle. I know that for a fact. I'm just trying to pin all the details down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How did the political identities of the two major American parties become reversed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 02:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 06:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you'll get more, right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know if you get a compound effect from using incense while near a lure? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 06:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 22:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The size of the team usually fluctuates around the high teens, low 20s. A class was not offered last year and we had a consistent dozen but now that the class is back, I can see turnout coming back up to the 20s.  And yes, that was very helpful. I simply have a lot of information floating around in my head. My background is speech and debate, not education, and I was only filling an interim role. We are now looking for a coach to step into my shoes as I a moving away for school.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 16:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Advice for managing IEs would be awesome. There are just so many. My biggest concern is getting a novice pointed in the right direction and up to speed enough to be self-sufficient. How do you not overwhelm a kid with information like rules, format, and the peculiarities of that event? We also don't have the luxury of using many rooms. 1 classroom with 2 storage spaces, 2 classrooms occasion, the hallway, and a computer lab.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 07:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I ask you, as a coach, how you organize practice? Maybe offer up some suggestions? I just do things how I've always done them as a competitor but am not quite qualified myself to teach someone how to run that side of things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking to train a replacement coach. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 23:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone here (preferably a coach but I am completely receptive to competitors' input too) have experience or advice with helping an incoming team coach get up to speed and get started on the right foot come September?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why does food meant to be eaten hot feel colder than room temperature when it cools down and food meant to be eaten cold feel warmer than room temperature when it warms up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 20:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 18:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like teaching it to shake would be less risky.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 17:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right. And at the end of the day, not having to use your gun is better still. I'm not a hunter so range shooting, home defense, and doomsday preparedness are the name of the game for me. But purely in the name of pitting one thing against a similar thing, I was just trying to get insight into the reliability and ease of use differences between the different types of guns.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Union, Celery, and Carrots </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 05:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've noticed this trifecta of vegetables being called upon in quite a few dishes from soup and slaw to roasted or sauteed  toppings for red meat and chicken. I was just curious why this particular combination of ingredients is as popular as it is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 05:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you circumvent that lack of reliability from the lower pressure by loading your shells with more powder or does that introduce different issues?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 04:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not inferior. I recognize the advantage of the semiautomatic feature. But I am under the impression (and maybe misconception) that pump action is the better of the 2 specifically when it comes to spitting out whatever you can think to put in it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 04:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> camera skills for days
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for clarification on shotguns. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 04:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought of taking this question to r/nostupidquestions among others but wanted this community's feedback. I'm not a stranger to the world of guns but I am nowhere beyond scratching the surface. I have been watching YouTube videos and a statement catches my ear here and there that shotguns are the ultimate tool of choice because it gives you options. (hunting, home defense and non-lethal crowd control to name a few) Now I know that there are different off-the-shelf options like slugs, buck shot and bird shot, but that's not what I am looking for clarification on. I know that you can load up a spent shell with just about anything and in some zombie preparedness tutorials, shot guns are the tool of choice of the guy behind the camera, particularly pump-action. Can semi-autos not handle such a robust variety of ammunition like shrapnel or whatever else I could think to shove down the barrel? What about their construction makes semiautomatic shotguns inferior in this regard?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 23:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a student, not an athlete. If I am going to go with the back-strap option for anything, I'd like it to be discrete enough to be comfortably worn under a backpack if not just resting inside of one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 22:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is the name of the library blacked out? I want to participate! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm looking for a product that might not exist. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 19:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want a gear bag that is big enough to hold my 2 locks (a mini u-lock and 55 cm kryptonite chain lock) among other, smaller, miscellaneous gear, yet small and flexible enough that when the locks aren't in it, I could stuff it into my backpack and go about my day. The other option is a pannier/backpack 2-in-1 but those that I've seen either only have 1 internal compartment (I would like to keep my school supplies and laptop separate from bike gear) or are priced in the premium bracket. Maybe someone here could fill an amateur in on what the norm is that works for most people but I have my sights set on this unicorn bike bag.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 10:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Follow-up question: Assuming day-to-day speak is relatively fleshed out, how rich can the vocabulary get before signers resort to spelling or simplifying? Is it the same as with spoken English? I recognize that vocabulary level is often a matter of audience and context and I know that there are many forms of sign language but I imagine a rule of thumb exists.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there any telltale wear pattern that studded tires leave on roads? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 08:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that you need to change your tires to accommodate the weather and the legal consequences aside, forgetting to do so could lead to a lot of condition issues on the road surface (I'm not sure about the condition issues of the vehicle itself if someone wants to clarify that too).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do people who sign instead of speak overcome a limited vocabulary? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 08:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I imagine them spelling out words with the ASL alphabet but do signers ever try to 'speak' around a word they can't think of like we do in normal speech?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How is making an antivenom different from making a vaccine? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 19:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watching an archer hit their mark in slow motion is mesmerizing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 19:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if the question of the chicken or the egg coming is less of a philosophical conundrum and more of a cultural exploration of dietary norms? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 10:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How were we able to come to industry standards like battery sizes C, D, AA, AAA, and still have a head-spinning number of button-cell battery options. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 06:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also thought about flairing as engineering or technology.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't want to have to buy a Bluetooth dongle. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 04:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I purchased the Aftershokz Bluez 2 on Amazon and they paired great with my phone but not my computer. I have a Dell that is just 1 year old, runs widows 7, and doesn't have hardware comparability issues otherwise.  The Bluetooth on the computer doesn't recognize the headset. I found a third party driver that supposedly works but am too suspicious of it to want to download something just to try it out. I contacted Aftershokz via email, asking about and linking the download page to the driver and there response was simply a long-winded 'good luck and let us know.' I'm at a crossroads here where my next step is either download or buy a usb bluetooth dongle and that is the point where I am out of my depth and would like a second opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was your 'Had I known what I know now, I wouldn't have done it that way.' moment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 03:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the name of the flavor of things like unions and garlic that don't quite hit taste-buds the same way a spicy pepper does but can still be just as pungent? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 02:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 22:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reductio ad absurdum. Someone who refuses food now because they aren't hungry can't be confused with someone who will starve to death out of refusal to eat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 21:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are other ways to make your voice heard. Polling agencies still call, politicians are paying more attention to what opinions people voice on social media. The reasons people abstain are numerous and I'm glad you pointed that out. It's not even on principle or simply to express displeasure with both options. Say (in some other world) that you would be pleased with either option or you don't care about politics at all. You could argue that one *should* care and that their voice *does* matter but they are within their rights to not care enough to be decisive or be contempt with either option, knowing full well that they shouldn't be complaining about it later down the road. If someone asks me if I want an apple or an orange and I say that I'm not hungry or I like apples and oranges equally and would leave the choice up to them, I don't see the problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 21:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not being indecisive per say, so much as it is decidedly not making a choice, which, for all the hooplah about how important it is to be heard ad a part of the democratic process, can be completely valid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CMV: Given the choice between the lesser of two evils, the third choice of indecision can be the best decision. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 21:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to be gun ho on the lesser of the two being the better option all the time but sometimes, it can just be too close to call, or even if it isn't, the better option between the two still has potential to be worse than the consequences of indecision. And this can but doesn't necessarily have to get political. I am not trying to make a political point here but all those parallels are easy to draw with the current climate. Even if you think the person you aren't voting for would be either only marginally or unimaginably worse than the candidate you do like, there is some credit due to the people who see the difference as marginal and the thought that we don't have to 'settle'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CMV: Given the choice between the lesser of two evils, indecision can be the best choice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 20:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 19:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A couple episodes per night, shouldn't be too bad. I'll look forward to procrastinating like that when school starts back up again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 19:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to binge it. How long did that take you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 18:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe tmi but I've tried boxer briefs and, by the standards of them doing the job, squats and sit-ups are high impact.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the male equivalent of a sports bra that men use to keep things in place while working out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 18:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CMV: Given the choice between the lesser of two evils, indecision can be the best choice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 10:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 09:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well food is universal, but more to the point, I think bbq is uniquely American and spreading to the rest of the world. They say that almost every culture has a rice dish, a sandwitch, and a soup to call it's own.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 08:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=C-52AI_ojyQ  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 06:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm told that newspapers still exist."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> in the spirit of the discription of this sub, can we get a megathread going on actual adulty things </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 06:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How to do laundry, organize your filing cabinet, maintain your finances, maintain your car, etc. I know that, for example. r/personalfinance can help you with your budget, but it'd be nice to have that all in once centralized location.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 05:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russian
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 04:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MegaThread a list of references? Good idea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help me explain the use of 'the' vs. 'a/an' to a non-native English speaker. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 04:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 04:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In what regard?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something that is quintessentially American that would shock you if someone seemingly American didn't know about or like too much? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 04:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was born and raised in the US, still living here, and I'm proud to be an American. But I grew up in a household full of immigrants. I like music and movies that are older than I am. Especially since it gives me a leg up in those categories on trivia shows when I watch with my family. But I sometimes hang with my friends whose families have been here for way longer than mine have and miss a lot of references. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 02:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mythbusters is playing in the background of me surfing Reddit right frickin now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some mistakes guys make when it comes to online dating? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 01:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 01:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not bashing you for it but I don't like mouthing back at them as much as just screwing with them for the sake of pure enjoyment. Most of those guys are just trying to make a (more or less) honest living. The PoSes are the higher-ups that we never get the chance to bark at.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by wasting a lucky egg before knowing what it was for. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 20:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was a while ago before all the talk about actually catching and keeping pidgeys and using lucky eggs to gain xp.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 20:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, I'm also subscribed to r/math and was expecting calculus. Had to watch it twice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 23:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That'll do, Pig. That'll do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Level Up Rewards Chart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 20:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the most memorable thing you have seen a street performer do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 18:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 09:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On number 7, I'm not trying to be argumentative or say you are wrong but I think you underestimate how accurate GPS is. Something else is going on here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 09:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better is subective. If cheaper is your idea of better, yes. If you are looking for quality, rule of thumb dictates stay away from the made in China stuff.  
And of course there are Chinese originals. It's commonplace for the Chinese market to copy the American but that's doesn't represent the entire market. I was just pointing out that patent law, like most kinds of law, become harder to enforce across political boindries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Things I want to know. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 09:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) Has anyone figured out the walking cheat?  
2) Predicting eevee evolution / conclusively making peace with the fact that it's random  
3) Is 2 moves the maximum per Pokemon in this game?  
4) Do incense help people on your team or only modules?  
5) Does the number of max items or Pokemon you can carry increase with your avatar's level? What about the radial reach for Pokestops and Gyms?    
6) Where are all the side quests? .. I think this game would be getting less people in trouble if side quests asked us to do productive things like do math problems in exchange for something in the game like stardust, Pokestop items, or even Pokemon.  
7) What are the *exact* distances/ distance ranges represented by each number of footsteps that supposedly tells you how far away the Pokemon is from you? And is there a way to figure out what direction to go in?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to know what my state's laws are and I want to hear it straight from the horse's mouth. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 08:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do I go to find out, beyond a shadow of a doubt, what is legal and what is not? I'm looking for the authoritative source that lawyers, police officers, court officials and legislators use.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 07:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Let's kill all the lawyers, Kell 'em tonight." - The Eagles in a song fantastically named 'Get Over It'  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 03:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Different countries have different IP laws. A lot of American brands have to worry about the Chinese versions of their stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 03:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not quite that. These patent trolls aren't the big bad corporate guys on wall street. They are still terrible, but not the same kind of terrible as the too big to fail types.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 22:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I've heard too many stories of bad people calling out of the blue and doing bad things."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by boiling water in the bathroom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 21:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 20:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OR] Bicycling under the influence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 20:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll preface this by saying that this hasn't happened to me *yet* but I can foresee myself either running into a situation like this or avoiding it entirely depending on the responses I get to this post.  

So, I'm of age and I use my bike a lot to get around. If I were to bike to a friend's house or a bar (either down the block or across town... as if that matters), have a drink, and decide to bike back home that night, under the influence of alcohol, I understand that that is treated just like driving under the influence and I could spend the night in jail, have my driver's license suspended, have my bike impounded, have to pay fees, etc. What would be my course of action at that point?  

Forgive me for not thinking that BUIs are not as 'serious' of a crime as DUIs. Maybe someone can explain that to me too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I got another unsolicited call from Microsoft to fix my computer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 20:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gave them my local FBI branch's number to call back, called them myself, and they weren't PO'ed or anything but redirected me to the FTC's line instead. FTC is the government body that dals with these kinds of scammers. FBI said I should try to probe for a callback number to the scammer first then call the FTC to report them. That's 1-877-382-4357 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 19:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much! Which milk boils down the best for when the recipe calls for cream?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that there is a thriving industry of companies that acquire patents and make all their profit by either litigating or settling on the infringement. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 18:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baking with milk substitutes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 07:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So as I'm sure most of you are already aware, cooking (and baking especially) are both just as much sciences as art forms. However the  textbook forgot about the students with dietary restrictions. For those who can follow the instructions, sometimes milk is called for, or cream, or sweetened condensed milk, or 2%, 1%, buttermilk, etc. Whereas our dairy free options are the milk that comes from almonds, coconuts, soy beans, etc. Not exactly a 1-to-1 correspondence. Does anyone have any experience with substituting out specific ingredients?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who are some figures that were greatly influential throughout history but are not quite household names? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 05:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Survey] How do you hold your pistol when firing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 04:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a small collection of semi automatic pistols (looking to get a revolver some time in the future) and am aware that there are different 'styles' of gripping the gun when you go to shoot. I have tried ambidextrous shooting on the same gun with the non-dominant hand wrapped around the dominant hand and when that non-dominant hand is the right one, I make sure to keep it under the ejection port. What has worked well for you? Is there a single proper way to do things that I am just not aware of or is it personal preference?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why are humans and domestic dogs seemingly the only animals that require dental upkeep throughout their life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 04:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 22:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: We a re missing pictures of people strapping their phones to ceiling fans for PokemonGo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 22:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the comparison metric? Quality? Box Office sales?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is Niantic 'the Pokemon company' and what happened to Nintendo? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 20:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 16:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right but rules are there for reasons. u/ThisOpenFist gave me the reason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do spelling bee participants pronounce the word both before and after they spell it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 23:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
