<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3415</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instead of joining a church look for local charity groups that are non-secular. More often than not religious based charities push their message alongside their free meals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is true. 

Atheist's don't base their morals on their atheism though. Atheism is the rejection of a god claim and nothing else. If an atheist hates gay people it's because he's come to that conclusion for some, albeit most likely unfounded, reason. Where as the religious get their morals from an ancient text book that explicitly tells them to kill gay people. If they do it or not it's still repugnant that anyone would insist religion is for the morally virtuous. 

The real harm of religion can be more easily seen in Africa, where missionaries have given uneducated locals the bible instead of food and resource education and now we have active groups of militia men who kill anyone who is found to be gay or breaking "god's law."

You think the gay men being rounded up in Chechnya is just because of a little bit of personal bigotry? I'm willing to bet it has it's base in a religious influence. 


As a personal aside, any book that would advocate the stoning of men, women, and children (looking at you the Bible and the Koran) for petty minor "sins" that is found throughout human nature is a book not only worth disregarding but also disposing of. 

No exclusive good has ever come of religion that could be achieved by non-secular means. Religion is belief in the unfounded and it's easy to dupe the gullible into doing horrible things with it's claims. 

I stand by my statement firm and strong. Fuck religion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regardless of the good works they do do they believe in their own doctrine and follow it's edicts? It's wonderful they help people but it doesn't mean the things they believe aren't morally bankrupt. 

Regardless of whether they are doing good or not the beliefs at the core of the system are twisted as can be. They can feed the homeless one day and then preach hate the next, that is the cycle of religion. 

They could just as easily feed the poor without the pretense of religion for doing so, so it being a church is irrelevant to the good works they do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm the poster who will disparage all religions. 

They are archaic and often barbaric remnants of the past that only the weak willed and feeble minded cling to. Basically, if you can't think for yourself join a religion. If you're a terrible human being with no empathy for others, join a religion. 

You may think you're different "Well I don't hate like all the other Christians/Muslims/Etc." but you're still supporting a religion based on the most vile and brutal laws man kind has ever seen, a religion with no real backing or evidence to prove it's even true. 

Religion is designed to keep the poor poor and the stupid stupid while benefiting those on the top who full well understand what a big scam it all is but still push forward to empty the pockets of their followers in the name of their god. 

It's sickening and in my opinion is never justified. Show me one demonstrable thing that you can get with religion and no where else and you'll have a reason to be religious...but no one can. Religion is useless and I for one can't wait to see it disappear into the dark chapters of humanities history.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Wel that just complete bullshit. Everyone is replaceable. And people are always looking to automate whatever job your doing. lazy or not it doesnt matter we are all just tools to someone else

Read your original comment and compare it to your statement now, they are two different claims. 

And who is they? And how do you know they would prefer automation? 

In a world of automation don't you think a business with real human employees hand crafting their product the old fashioned way wouldn't appeal to someone? 

Automation isn't the answer to everything and I doubt it will be. Automation is great and it will be helpful to have the more mundane/dangerous industries using it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm planning on making a heavy industry style building for storing all my items in soon, I love your use of the tin and copper plating. As someone said it's really reminiscent of Starbound! 

How did you make the water green? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> document it for someone I never met and never will

If you could reproduce supernatural phenomenon you'd be in line for all sorts of scientific recognition. You shouldn't want to prove it to me you should want to prove it for yourself and everyone. 

The fact that you didn't document it leads us to believe what you're saying isn't true. You may of had experiences and lost stuff then found it but to chalk it up to super natural activity is really jumping the gun on logical explanations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand what you're saying but I disagree with you with your original statement that everyone will be replaced. 

Lots of jobs will be replaced yes but not every job can be automated or will society want it to be automated. While I understand we would automate them if we could that wasn't your original claim, you've changed your claim over the course of three comments from everyone will be replaced with automated work to we will replace jobs with automated work IF we can. 

You're the one who doesn't seem to understand what I'm disagreeing with here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> James Randi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Picture's of dead pools.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not being nit picky I'm disagreeing with you, don't get no panties in a twist. 

I disagree with your assertion that everyone is replaceable with automation which I do not see as actually happening. There are many jobs which will be automated yes but not everyone will be or is worth being automated. 

A few notable examples would be anything dealing with psychology, physical therapy, high end customer service...there are some things you simply can't replace with a machine. A human element is necessary for some of these fields to work correctly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You assuming the automation is also effecient. That isn't always the case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks good and the effort was nice but honestly OP that was pretty boring and the ending made ZERO sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have a very sunny out look on life. 

Everyone is replaceable. 

Nope. I'm more than positive that there are many jobs which would be hell to automate or not worth the frustration.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly this isn't true if multiple NPC's die. One can move into another dead NPC's house before they get the chance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing or the Ordinary Shirt and Ordinary Pants, which is a cosmetic which gives you armor the appearance of your characters default clothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 02:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where better to leave that opinion than here?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So no. Do you think you could go back to this house? Why didn't you document this if you could reproduce it on a reliable basis?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see what you're saying, I guess we just have a disagreement on what the term better here means and I was just doing my best to be technically correct. I concede the point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because 60's sell more for having a better average roll doesn't mean that 60's are the best availible. That is my point the 63's that are being sold are going to be better than the 60's of the same quality because they had higher rolls. Just because mostly good 60's were sold doesn't make the statement "More often than not the best items in the AH were ilvl 60" true. The good rolled 63's are always better and were...and super duper expensive. 

I'll agree most people rolled with 60's because of Act I farming but that doesn't mean there weren't 63's on the AH that had better stats. If there was that makes the 63's the best items on the AH by fact. 

We're in full agreement except for the statement "the best items on the AH were often ilvl 60" because as long as a better ilvl 63 item was there they were not the best items, just the best AND affordable items.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played hundreds of hours at release and no...ilvl 63 was ALWAYS the go to. You could have a good 60 but if you went to the AH 63's were always available and way outclassed the 60's.

I think you mean the best and affordable were often ilvl 60.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so the best items on the AH were more often than not ilvl 60 items!

You originally said the best items were ilvl 60 and you're wrong, ilvl63 had the best stat ranges. Just because there were more ilvl60 doesn't mean 60's on average were better than 63's just because there were more of them. 

I get that you're just trying to say you'd find more 60's than not but it doesn't make your statement of them being better true at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friends laughed at me and told me I was dreaming when I told them we should just be allowed to start in at the highest level GR we already cleared. 

They thought the Greater Rift Trial was a good thing...what idiots.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 12:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Muddy shoe? Bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know not what you speak of and Google show now enlighten me, have my upvotes of ignorance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want celestial keys like Lucy in Fairy Tail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Citation needed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because you don't remember doesn't mean it's not actually you moving the scissors.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you reproduce this phenomenon consistently?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I see is shoes, leg, and a belt buckle. 

What are you getting at OP? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dig a few screen length tunnels and a bulb will be bound to spawn on them eventually.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would the Hallow NPC sell? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Simple and plain, I really like it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 17:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I have one...you want mine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 01:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of that just raises more questions. 

If God is unable to prevent evil, then he is not all-powerful.
If God is not willing to prevent evil, then he is not all-good.
If God is both willing and able to prevent evil, then why does evil exist?

Trilemma by early skeptics. 

I don't think God truly grants people free will. It's "believe in me or go to hell." 

If I came to your house and held a gun to you and said, "Worship me and give me all your wordly possessions because I am a god." would you do it? It's not free will if I'm threatening you. With the Christian god it's much worse...an eternity of torture. 

Why would god have to weep for the evil on earth? He made everything that exists according to your theology so he must of made evil too right? Is anything in this world NOT to his design? 

And how does the removal of free will cause our fabric to fall apart? It's already debatable if we have free will as we currently understand it, so that is a claim without any backing that needs a lot of clarification.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
