<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3297</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 08:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I consider the Silent Hill HD collection a disaster or Mass Effect Andromeda. I would not call Halo: MCC a disaster, and comparing it to cancer? I think that's being a little hyperbolic, don't you think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 07:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was the "Master Chief" related games they focused on optimizing (Halo 1-4). They then gave Halo 3: ODST a shiny new polish to it. I guess since they were basically working off of the Halo 3 engine and it was easier to update than Halo Reach's engine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 07:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  For the longest time TONS of players experienced bugs that would delete progress and saves. It was unplayable for months and months.

For myself, the multiplayer and single-player have worked since I bought it back in December of 2014. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 07:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd probably say he's more influenced by Satan as he's depicted by making bargains at crossroads, which is a VERY devil thing to do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 07:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's baseless speculation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 22:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really liked the last 15 minutes because it's a payoff as a character moment for Michelle as she's now ready to take on the unknown after a life-time of running away from all of her problems.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I accept your apology." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's not forget that Snyder doesn't make these films in a bubble. He's also coordinating with the studio heads and since they hold the wallet for the film, they can decide what to do stylistically.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Book of Eli was dope.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He doesn't write most of his scripts. Man of Steel was Goyer, and BvS was Goyer and Terrio. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Pitch Black: It's an excellent horror movie, character study, trope bender, expectation dodging analysis of survival with great characters. This film's iteration of Riddick is easily one of my favorite fictional characters ever because of how surprisingly complex his views on survival are. 

* Cabin in the Woods: A genre-blender where the artifice of horror films itself is put into terrific view including how well horror and comedy are put into equal measure.

* Shaun of the Dead: Both a great parody of classic Zombie films as well as just a great zombie film with Edgar Wright's stellar writing and direction.

* Tucker and Dale vs. Evil: The film plays terrifically with the viewpoint of perception as two innocent southern buddies are mistaken for hillbilly psychopaths by dumb college kids. 

* 10 Cloverfield Lane: If you want an absolutely TENSE film that utilizes payoff and dread, this movie delivers in spades with great performances with a densely claustrophobic setting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Die Hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Halo 4 had default sprint, flinch instead of descope, redundant weapons, elongated maps, customizable loadouts, weapons unlocked through exp. Cod had those things. Halo 4 added them.

Halo Reach added sprint into the series including making it default at the first level of the story, stop blaming 343 for that inclusion. Flinch is less annoying that descoping especially with risk vs. reward of constant firing. Redundant weapons? I wouldn't know about that, as I felt that there was a lot of great variety and usage, even among the Promethean weapons which catch too much flak. Elongated maps have also been implemented since the Bungie days of Halo. Customizable loadouts have been around since Halo Reach. I do agree that Halo 4 shouldn't have had weapons locked behind experience, but I think that was done for the sake of getting players adjusted to different weapons and experimenting in multiplayer as they were progressing. 

 Ordnance drops are directly comparable to kill streaks. This removed a huge aspect of Halo in regard to power weapon control.

Because it was always a scramble for power weapons, and then once you maintain control of the power weapon spawn points, good luck trying to change the tide of battle. 

And you keep harping on Halo 4 for bringing in things like Armor mods, when that was BUNGIE back in Halo Reach. 

I would argue it's still not the same because of how Halo 4 is designed especially in terms of weapon balancing (which Call of Duty has none), vehicle and terrain usage, regenerating health and shields, weapons and grenade usage, and a myriad of other gameplay ticks that are unique to the franchise. 

You want changes for the worst for the Halo franchise? Just look at how Halo 2 and Halo 3's spotty equipment usage and dual wielding absolutely decimated weapon balancing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The convent are still around, the forerunners still have badass super weapons...

The Covenant in Halo 4 are supposed to be scattered remnants clinging onto what's left of the fleet. They're scavengers and underpowered religious zealots. It's The Didact and the Prometheans which are the big problem now. 

The Forerunners have always had super badass weapons and tech among the stars. They've always had it since even the days of Bungie. 

 The even got rid of the whole "humanity is fucked" vibe I always liked about Halo. They made humanity top dog 

I liked the change up because we now get to see a version of humanity flourishing and new routes for story to take place. The military in-fighting over trusting the Chief and Cortana's very limited knowledge about the Didact was fascinating, especially from both a macro-narrative and personal standpoint for the characters. 

 a made every cardboard cutout of a character a Spartan.

I disagree here. As much as I don't like the overall story of Halo 5, Fireteam Osiris has an interesting cast of characters, especially with Tanaka, Buck, and Locke. Fireteam Majestic in Spartans Ops weren't interesting, I'll give you that, but I would easily say that I enjoyed Fireteam Osiris and Palmer in the Halo 4 campaign (not Halo 5 or Spartan Ops) over a team like Noble team in Halo Reach where too many of the characters didn't feel fleshed out (like Carter or Jun).

 Its like a made for TV sequel to halo 3...

I wouldn't say that at all, especially with how much I detested Halo 3.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved the Halo 4 campaign. I thought it was downright brilliant in terms of actually crafting a narrative. 

I like a lot of Bungie's attempt with story with Halo: CE, the Arbiter's story arc in Halo 2, the fractured narrative in Halo 3: ODST, but overall, I personally felt that their writing for narratives has been problematic (especially with Halo 3, which I still love, but found to be the worst narrative of Bungie's crop of Halo games). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I respect that stance, but I disagree with it. I thought that 343 finally paid attention to character arcs and narrative with Halo 4. I liked both Halo 4 and Halo 5's multiplayer as well (I've never NOT enjoyed a Halo FPS multiplayer), but I thought Halo 5's story wasn't as good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll still say that the best thing that Tarantino ever worked on is still True Romance, with his best own directed work being Inglourious Basterds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 18:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You are a buttwiggle

Whoah, hey, let's not say things we can't take back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 17:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok. I really dug the Hell out of the Elektra stuff especially how they tied that to Stick and the Hand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 08:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a bad show, it's just....'eh'. It's competent enough not to be bad, but not interesting enough to be good. It's just a meal of plain yogurt and water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 08:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even without the Punisher stuff, I thought that season 2 of Daredevil was awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 07:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly, no. It's a reference to my family name of Gorog, which is Hungarian, a palindrome, and also the name of a monster in the Star Wars universe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 05:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked that they revealed the entire show to be based on spirituality, but I did not like at all the fact that they had so many questions, they kept saying they would answer all the questions, and then did not answer all the questions. That's just lying to your audience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 05:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a fan theory that Jack gathered all of his allies over the course of the original run of the show, and attacked Aku in a desperate gamble for the last time portal. Most of them were killed and Jack has had PTSD ever since over that failure, and he was clad in that armor. My theory is that it's a constant reminder over his failure to his friends in his obsession to get back to the past. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 05:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're then reminded of your youth with your parents as you enjoyed your family boat on the Eastern shore. Your heart is filled with regret over leaving the East coast and your family for a disappointing life in Los Angeles. You tell them you're happy and you've found meaning, but you haven't the heart to tell them you broke up with Zoe and the company will be laying off people in the next two months.

You feel like life is slowly closing in and don't know how to escape. Then you see another guy throw a beer can over a bridge and you realize that your life does have meaning. You don't wait to see if he catches the beer can.

You get together with that cute waitress at the coffeee shop, you leave your little cubicle at the special effects company and begin working with that small animation team thats ready to take on the world, and you discover a spiritual side to life you thought you had lost. 

As you walk down the beach with your fiance and your loyal lab, you look at the setting sun and think, "Thanks, beer throwing guy." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 03:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, there was a time when movies would be either R or PG. But because of the levels of adult material getting through in PG movies, they created a new category, PG-13, in order to better encapsulate that kind of content. Jurassic Park WASN'T released back then. It was released when PG-13 was a rating, and I would argue that it was rightly put into that category in terms of content, especially with the terror and gore they DO have in the movie.

Because it existed at the time where movies had PG-13 ratings, they aimed for that demographic. PG-13 doesn't usually mean Family Friendly. Tremors is a PG-13 horror film and I wouldn't characterize it as "kiddie" (which isn't a criticism lobbed specifically at you, but just from a general standpoint to those using that argument) I think is an intellectual cop-out of actual artistic criticism) or Family Friendly. Just because there are children in Jurassic Park as main characters and they don't violently die doesn't mean that it's a kid-friendly adventure, otherwise Aliens would be considered a Family Friendly film (Hell, I'd argue the kids in Jurassic Park get worse physical damage and terror than Newt in Aliens). 

There are PG-13 films that I've felt had bigger impacts in terms of violence, sexuality, and other adult themes than R-rated fare without being explicit. In fact, when they're inhibited by how much content they can show, PG-13 movies can get more creative in terms of how it's executed. 

Drag Me to Hell, The Dark Knight, The Others, The Ring, 10 Cloverfield Lane and Cloverfield are just some PG-13 movies that have some of the most horrifying moments I've ever seen on film without being explicit. It's also hard to argue that these films would be R or PG without the PG-13 rating because we don't know. Temple of Doom and Gremlins were rated PG at the time of their release, but public outcry demanded another level between those ratings, hence PG-13. 

If we argued that if we remove every movie rating except "G," then every movie would be rated "G". So what? That doesn't remove the content in the movie, nor does it discredit what that film actually has inside of it. If Jurassic Park was made during the time of ONLY PG or R ratings, it would have to decide which side to air on in terms of content, but because they had a PG-13 rating, they were able to make a film with more extreme content than a PG movie, but still have broad appeal (which I would not characterize as inherently "family friendly") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 00:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait a minute. Are you saying that being resurrected from the dead was consistent with what they were putting forth, but the fact he brought out more bread and fish then was expected is somehow the real big surprise? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ....but the PG rating did exist. Are you saying if the PG-13 rating didn't exist, it would be a PG film? PG-13 was/is a rating, it was rated that rightly and I'm not really sure what your point is on subject. 

It would be like saying "if the PG-13 rating didn't exist, Zemeckis' Beowulf movie would have been an R-rated film".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It's over, Atheist! I have the (moral) high ground!"

P.S.: I'm a Christian, don't worry! I upvoted you, and these are just for fun! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 18:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, depending on how you define it, animation in mature/adult platforms is already THRIVING in the video game sphere. From the dedicated capturing of realistic motion in Splinter Cell: Chaos Theory, to simple animation design for clarity in Mark of the Ninja, to studio Ghibli designed artistic eccentricities with Ori and the Blind Forest, animation for adults is alive and well. Even things like Tales from the Borderlands, Life is Strange, Witcher: Wild Hunt, or Alien Isolation relies on traditional animation for their characters.

Adult animation in the west is a weird area of taboo. Thanks to South Park for starting the trend and Family Guy for solidifying it, adult animation has bursted through when attempting comedy (like with Chozen, Moonbeam City, Metalocalypse, Harvey Birdman, Archer, etc.). But for action/drama, there's still a bit of a hurdle. It's still difficult to get a straight up action-drama animated series FOR KIDS/FAMILIES. Thundercats (2011) was cancelled after one season, most of Cartoon Network and Disney's animated lineup is compromised on comedic series, more serious animated DC/Marvel shows like Young Justice or Spectacular Spider-man have been substituted for far more comedic fare with Justice League Action or Ultimate Spider-man. Hell, I'm impressed Legend of Korra made its way to the end of its run. I think there's also a bit of the early 90s resurgence of people over-policing the violence level for channels with action aimed towards kids, so it's just easier and more profitable to ignore it. It's even stranger once you look at the trend of live-action shows and movies incorporating more explicit adult elements like gore, sex, and swearing, yet animation has had the bar set even lower for what can and can't be shown. 

And, as other people have mentioned here on this thread, Samurai Jack Season 5 seems to be directly aimed at a more mature crowd with its action.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the context is that the dog is at the farm, and when think of a strong, southern, wizened, comforting voice, I think of Sam Elliot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is funny, but what does this have to do with Jordan Peterson? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mind flashed back to my youth and I suddenly remembered hundreds of Halo AMVs set to this song.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now, if we can just get Gary Oldman as J. Jonah Jameson, then it will be a great exchange between companies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's a genius, playboy, billionaire, philanthropist.

Hmm...... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HE DOESN'T WANT TO BE FAMOUS? I'LL MAKE HIM INFAMOUS!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay. I can respect that point of view. For myself, I thought it was a great film and a better adaptation of the storyline than even the comic (which I felt seriously dragged in places and had a kind an ending that didn't tie as well back into the main themes of the story as the film did).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 16:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can imagine him with the voice of Sam Elliot.

"Come over here for a spell, young one. Let me tell you about when I chased sticks in my youth. My, times have changed." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 15:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You think that's bad, look at the "Dear White People" story going on in NC university right now  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 05:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't measure success by an aggregate of public perception. I can only judge a story by what quality is has. I thought Iron Fist was middle of the road. The worst MCU story so far, for me, is the first season of Jessica Jones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 04:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MAGNUM!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 01:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is "Fear the Walking Dead" any good? From the commercials, It just seemed like a desperate cash grab for another Walking Dead show </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 01:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Iron Fist was...."eh". Not great or terrible, just perfectly mediocre. And this is coming from the guy who loves the MCU. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 22:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did somebody say "Gwent"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to see Gendy take a Executive Producer route on Adult Swim and get them to spearhead more American animation aimed at more mature crowds that focus on drama/action.

We already have plenty of animated shows with adult comedy (South Park, Archer, Moonbeam City, Chozen, Rick and Morty, Family Guy, etc.), but I'd love to see more of something like Sym-Bionic Titan, Thundercats (2011), Spectacular Spider-man aimed at an older demographic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's because it's much easier to write a character arc for a flawed character than it is for a much more well-rounded likable personality. For instance, in Captain America: The First Avenger, he's basically the same type of good-hearted man from start to finish, so his journey is more about showing how much he's willing to do for the sake of defending his own values and friends he's made.

With a character like Logan or Batman, you can have them as very flawed human beings becoming better, and that journey can be a lot more easy to chart out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In terms of getting caught up with the story? Not really. There will maybe be a character or two or a plot line that started with the original series that will have more weight with this new season, but it seems fairly self-contained (at least if you start with the first episode of THIS season, as it stops being episodic and relies more on long-form storytelling over their 10-episode arc).

In terms of art and story/character enjoyment? Hell yes. This is one of the best pieces of western animation to ever be created. It's a mastercraft of western animation with such terrific experimentation and flexibility with stories they can tell. It's worth tracking down and watching the episodes where available.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That band episode never fails to make me laugh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fortunately, the DLC for Mankind Divided has been pretty good so far. I REALLY hope they make another one soon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not quoted anywhere. I feel that from his genuine disdain of corporate types and rich people in his films, I don't think he'd have a positive response to Hammond. I also feel that Cameron REALLY straw-mans the argument by calling the movie "for kids" in simplicity where I don't think that's the case at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention, I personally think he detested Spielberg making the rich businessman a sympathetic character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it was PG-13 and not PG. There are still some real scares in there and some bits of gore and horror.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Pitch Black: Character study, monster movie, dissection about the ethics of survival. This movie has it all, and CONSTANTLY inverts movie tropes and expectations.

2. Jurassic Park: Yes, I consider it a horror film. An excellent story touching on the classic touchstone of science going too far with scenes wonderfully drenched it terror and tension, with great characters.

3. Brotherhood of the Wolf: This genre-bending story is just so extreme, experimental, and outright bizarre that it has to be experienced to be enjoyed.

4. Pan's Labyrinth: A dark fantasy that delves into the most cruel and evil that humanity has to offer between a story concerning one girl's climb to understanding and shedding of her innocence.

5. Tucker and Dale vs. Evil: A hilarious send-up of slasher horror stories where the protagonists are the southern chaps mistaken from crazed hillbillies. Dark humor and creative uses of genre conventions makes this a perfect pairing with Cabin in the Woods. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * The Count of Monte Cristo (2002)
* Rush Hour 2
* Return of the King (although I'd want the entire trilogy up here if I could) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was a good scene but the overly sentimental face touching ruined that moment for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Av/a/tar was a great show

The Mo/vie was bad

It's snow/ing on Mount Fuji

7/5/7

Inverted Haiku. Get on my lvl, nUb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SWEAR TO ME!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, "shakes". Don't know what you're getting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Avatar was a great show

The movie was bad

It's snowing on Mount Fuji </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "And stay out of the Woolworths!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 04:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do wish that Link had more expressiveness in the rest of the game, especially with other characters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 04:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A surprise, to be sure, but a welcome one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the choreogrphy is fine. The worst thing is that it's just soo....bland. If it was terrible or good, we'd have something to talk about, but it's like it goes out of its way to be just competent enough not to be bad, but not good enough to be interesting or different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alaskan  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do we do anything, Ross? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I absolutely LOVE that movie. Perhaps my favorite crime thriller ever made. If you can avoid it, don't let anyone spoil the plot for you.

It's really a terrific film :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "BINGO!" How fun!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, I find your lack of faith disturbing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not Marvel Studios fault that people copy their work poorly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved The Wolverine (especially that third act and extended unrated cut). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm praying for your friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 02:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We respect you, Sergeant Butthole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 01:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Dry heaves harder) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 01:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Begins dry heaving in the corner) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but to be fair, Karl Urban isn't in DOOM 2016, and that makes me sad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read that with Stark's voice from Farscape. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will be about Harlan Ellison going back in time to stop the movies from ever existing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 12:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that really a controversial opinion? 

For myself, I thought that the first three seasons of the show are BRILLIANT and some of the best episodes of animated comedy ever made. But when they came back, they lost that spark of seeing who they were. Sacrificing the characters and jokes that worked for the sake of generating shock value in either content or humor. The characters have become unlikable monsters, the jokes have become ghastly, and the show seems only possible to love by the most jaded and cynical audience members. 

I personally think that Family Guy needs to end for its own sake.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Baseless speculation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm watching it right now, and it's.....'eh'. Nothing's really jumping out at me for that show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't like Jessica Jones. Three episodes in, it was very good, then it went crazy in the wrong direction, especially with how Jessica justifies her behavior and a lot of the weirdly written characters (like the entire support group, or their version of "Nuke").  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked all the non-Punisher stuff in season 2 of Daredevil, but that's just my opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the "Immortal Iron Fist" comics (great run) him being white and being an outsider is actually a part of the story, and it's great. Why didn't they use that in the story? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It certainly did! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 07:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, and I'm not saying it isn't there, but it's nowhere near as strong or defined as in "The Wolverine". In that movie, it's after Charles dies....uh...for the first time, and the death of Jean, who figuratively and literally haunts him for his choice to kill her, and wants him to 'join her' in the afterlife. At the start of The Wolverine, he has less than what he has in "Logan". Besides his body deteriorating and Charles' slowly losing his mind, Logan doesn't really have an avenue of showing loss as Logan's state in The Wolverine. He's barely surviving with his life out in the wilderness, getting drunk,  having no actual path, and no longer being with the X-men. Even in "Logan" he has a goal of getting a boat with Charles to escape the U.S. with his limo services - he still has something to live for, even though he contemplates trying to kill himself (when did he get the bullet again? The retcons and continuity shifts of the X-men movies isn't a negative for me, but damn is it confusing sometimes). In The Wolverine, it's all the more tragic because he (at that point) can't die even though he wants to, and Yashida finally offers him the ability to do so.

He had already gone through a "total loss" story. Losing the X-men, Charles, his purpose, and even the desire to end his own life were already explored to great extent in The Wolverine and here it just seems like a passing fancy that was already done far better in another film. 

I also couldn't help but think that the antagonists were fairly weak, and unlike The Wolverine's development of Yashida being actually involved with Logan giving a personal touch to the story, these guys just seemed removed from Logan's entire life, and the problem is that they don't give them any more interesting layers to make up for more personal antagonist. What's confusing is that Logan seems to have such a negative view of the X-men when looking over the comics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Well, I don't share the enthusiasm.

Okay, you're more than entitled to hold that belief, and I respect that belief. 

 it conformed to some many of the Superhero movie tropes.

I don't think it particularly did, especially as Deadpool finishes his path of vengeance by brutally murdering Ajax in cold blood rather than being noble or merciful by letting him live. And that relationship between Wade and Venessa is completely earned by their chemistry together and story where it begins as a satire of them trying to one-up each other's most screwed-up past details. It's the subversion of the subversion by making their seemingly nihilistic comedic enjoyment of life reveal that they actually care about each other (which even extends into Blind Al and Weazel, who underneath all of their selfishness, ego, and character flaws, they actually do care about Wade). The reason why that scene of Wade discovering he has cancer is so impactful (for me) is because this serious turn of events comes after the audience laughing along with them with their year-long sexcapades for belly-laughs and absolutely trashing romantic expectations with the whole "proposal with the ring" gag. Wade almost mechanically tries to make a joke in the office, but the way Renolds plays that moment and how it's filmed, it's meant to be a sad tragic moment where his comedy is ineffective against the seriousness of the situation, which will be a constant companion for him in the future of the movie. 

 Like, is it fair to mock movies for using post credit sequences to advertise future films in a movie that uses a post credit sequence to advertise a future film?

The joke here is that they're paying homage to one of the first movies to make a post-credit sequence with a self-aware character in a traditionally straight-forward Hollywood film, Deadpool also takes up so much time talking about a sequel they have not filmed or casted for yet poking fun at the fact that these studios are more than willing to sell out money to get franchises and sequels in the works without actually solidifying their plans; even further enhanced by the fact that Wade suggests they use Keira Knightly for the role of Cable. 

He's also actively making fun of the fact that they're subverting expectations (at first) by saying that they don't have enough money or clout to tease a proper sequel MCU-style, and then subvert it again, by really having Wade just kicking around ideas they were thinking about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My initial feelings after "Logan"... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 00:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked Holland in Civil War, but I personally need to see more of him before coming to a conclusion about his interpretation of Spider-man. 

Spidey is my favorite hero, so I hope Homecoming is good. I was just really...."meh" by the trailer they released.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that was a funny moment and that, more important, it solidified the idea of Wade being able to directly break the fourth wall, even affecting the presentation of the movie itself that he's in, as well his character tendency to not take always take dangerous situations seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  For ASM2 I understand why people dislike that movie, but seeing that awesome fucking costume more than makes up for it for me.

For myself, I LOVED the character arcs for Peter, Harry, and Max as they all struggle with the idea of hopelessness and abandonment. 

  Spider-Man 3 though I've never quite gotten why people didn't like that movie. All I see is people complaining that the Emo Dance scene is cringey as hell, even though it's definitely supposed to be that cringey.

The dance scene wasn't in itself a problem. For that moment, it felt like it should have belonged to a more exaggerated fantastical version of Spider-man, but I didn't inherently hate it.

The problem for me was more in the fault of its characters. I HATE Mary Jane in the films (which is too bad as she's one of my favorite comic book characters), Harry's amneisa sub-plot goes absolutely nowhere, Flint's sub-plot with his daughter is never resolved, Eddie's whole side-story is incredibly truncated for the sake of having it all in one film, and the butler's silence for why he never told Harry about his father aggravates me to no end. 

Once again, that's just my opinions on the matter and I think no less of anyone if they enjoyed or even loved the film. I did very much enjoy the fight scene choreography. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 21:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good list of shows. 

I'd recommend:

Band of Brothers, Riverdale, The Expanse, Dark Matter, The West Wing, Daredevil, Prison Break, Cowboy Bebop, Trigun, Star Trek: The Next Generation, 24, Firefly, Buffy: The Vampire Slayer, Deadwood, The Twilight Zone, Samurai Jack, Legion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 20:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Police Squad. It's an older show with Leslie Nielsen and the guys behind "Airplane!" And the Naked Gun films

It's only 6 episodes so there's not a huge commitment and they're some of the funniest bits of comedy ever shown in television. GREAT STUFF!

Also, I'd recommend checking out samurai Jack as that's an awesome show </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 19:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay. I disagree on the idea of it being a simple tale. The narrative structure, characters, writing, artistic commentary on the superhero genre of films, action scenes, creative blend of comedy and action, genuine emotional pathos, and so many other elements came together in such a fantastic way. It is a standard villain, but he functions so well as the deplorable hatable antagonist that makes Wade's revenge journey so sympathetic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 16:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   No marvel movie has reached the highs of the dark knight trilogy, days of future past, logan, spiderman 1 and 2, and dead pool

Yeah, I gotta disagree there. Personally, I thought The Dark Knight Rises was a bad film (not terrible, but something that just left a bad taste in my mouth after watching it). Next, I think that the best of the MCU is easily among the greats in the genre - Iron man, Iron Man 3, The Winter Soldier, Avengers, Age of Ultron, Civil War, Doctor Strange. 

Days of Future Past was great. No questions there. I also really liked First Class. My only real criticism is that unlike the Avengers films, First Class and Days of Future Past really just focus on 1-4 characters intensely and then all of the rest of the cast is just put in the story as background fodder for fight scenes. 

Logan was very good, but honestly, I still much prefer "The Wolverine" especially with that fantastic unrated extended edition. 

Spider-man 1-2 and Deadpool are good. Also, I personally LOVE The Amazing Spider-man films, but that's just me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 16:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Sony was the Spider-Man venue that had incredible two movies, one disappointing sequel, and two awful reboots until they had to give shared custody to the MCU.

For myself, I liked Raimi's first two Spider-man films, thought Spider-man 3 was terrible, and I LOVED The Amazing Spider-man movies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 16:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I think most people on Reddit, a place where the movie is revered, were saying that they would eat their shoes or murder a hobo if it got nominated for an Oscar.

Personally, I came to my conclusions about the film separate from Reddit, and my LOVE for Deadpool and how well it's constructed that ties together so many elements so flawlessly. I honestly think it's one of the best American comedy films and superhero movies of the last decade. I don't know if it should win Oscars. I feel like the Academy has mistaken atypical story content and artistic oddities with quality filmmaking, and I personally don't believe they actually nominate and award the films most deserving of particular categories. 

 A lot of the dialogue was cringeworthy, 

I disagree. In fact, I didn't think that way of any of the dialog.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 16:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, the weird juxtaposition of which superheroes the public trusts and who they don't is a fascinating dynamic they do explore in the comic books. Specifically, in the FANTASTIC "Marvels" 4-issue limited series, we focus on a normal photojournalist in the Marvel universe as he's growing up in a world that's becoming far weirder and dangerous than the day that came before it. 

Included in there is an analysis of why the Fantastic Four are totally trusted, yet the X-men aren't, which I find to be fascinating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 07:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love this movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 06:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moonbeam City, Megas XLR, and Thundercats </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not an anime fan and I'd heartily recommend Cowboy Bebop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has expanded </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> General knowledge has said that console wars are fought with publishers but they are won by developers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MAKE IT STOP!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 16:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I BLINKED AND YOU WERENT THERE AND I WAS SO SCARED THAT YOU NO LONGER EXISTED!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 04:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enjoy! We sure as Hell can't now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Riverdale (surprisingly good)

Legends of Tomorrow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wilmington, NC could have been that way but our governor was being a jackass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The downside is now that extreme content will be normalized instead of being something worthy of talking about. Are used to like the older shows that worked on anyone doing insinuation better than extreme content shows  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't like Jessica Jones (I thought it veered WAY off course after episode 3), but that's just my opinion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really did like Luke cage. I still think Daredevil is the gold standard for superhero shows (including Legion, imho). I hope it's not the disappointment that was Jessica Jones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Jessica Jones had a very good introduction with the first couple of episodes, but it lost all sense of narrative and character after that and went absolutely nuts in the wrong way. That's my opinion anyway. I thought it was a very weak show, and I was hoping it would be good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Y'all goin' campin'?.......ha ha ha ha ha!!!!!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  foolish given the amount of revisions and even the source material.

If you're talking about re-translations, it's only revisions in the idea of conveying the right meaning of the original text. For instance, "Thou shalt not kill" is more like "Thou Shalt Not Murder" which may be conveyed in every iteration of the Bible.

I believe in God and Jesus, but that's because of the evidence. I was raised Christian, and in College, I began questioning my beliefs as my parents and Christian community encouraged individual thought and analysis. Through Christian apoligetics and my own journey of knowledge (especially in terms of Historical evidence and arcahoelogical confirmation) my trust in Christianity has been heightened more than squandered. Science doesn't discredit the Bible, in my view. I'd take a listen to the videos of John Lennox and how he discusses Christianity (his debate with Richard Dawkins is electrifying). Science is the mechanism which indicates the agent, especially if one is to assume of a rational intelligbility of the universe. 

Don't bury your head in the sand. God said to love with all of your mind, that means your intellect. It's not a sin to doubt or to ask questions. Go explore the world and drink in knowledge! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
