<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2472</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 21:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The police said that he is a witness, not a suspect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 21:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really, Obama only stopped the visa waiver program, he did not ban refugees, immigrants or Green Card holders from those countries. They were still able to apply for a visa at a U.S. Embassy or Consulate. This is Trump's team talking point where they are trying to blame Obama for their irresponsible actions. 

For more in-dept look at the two orders, you can check this article from [Foreign Policy magazine](http://foreignpolicy.com/2017/01/30/sorry-mr-president-the-obama-administration-did-nothing-similar-to-your-immigration-ban/) and other articles by major newspapers. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 20:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's according to [Star Trek Fan Film guidelines](http://www.startrek.com/fan-films) that were imposed by CBS/Paramount last year.


* The fan production must be less than 15 minutes for a single self-contained story, or no more than 2 segments, episodes or parts, not to exceed 30 minutes total, with no additional seasons, episodes, parts, sequels or remakes.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 20:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the objective behind the travel ban? To stop terrorists from coming here, right? If that was the case then how come Saudi Arabia   Egypt are not on the list? 

This is just a ploy for his supporters to appear like he's doing "something", while in fact he's targeting poor Muslim countries, that none of their citizens were involved in terrorist attack against the United States, and leaving out the real trouble spots because of his business conflicts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 20:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Political fundraising emails

And this is the problem, Trump asked people not to use emails:


 [Trump](http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/312334-trumps-solution-to-cyberattacks-write-it-down-and-send-it-by): "It's very important, if you have something really important, write it out and have it delivered by courier, the old-fashioned way because I'll tell you what, no computer is safe,'


It is clear that none of his supporters are getting those fundraising emails since they're following their dear leader's advice   stopped using emails. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 19:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is a map from Bloomberg shows how [Trumps immigration ban excludes countries with business ties.](https://twitter.com/bpolitics/status/825757916720406533) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 19:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats conservative hypocrisy for you. These are the same people that were denouncing political correctness non-stop and then whine when they are call out for their policies and actions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 19:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like the others said, he was referring to Chewbacca.

The character of Malcolm Tucker is known for his bizarre metaphors like that time when he described an MP after a TV interview as a sweaty octopus trying to unhook a bra! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 19:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The movie In the Loop is set after series 2, the three TV specials and before series 3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 18:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The statement said the studios continue to be big believers in fan fiction and fan creativity and encouraged amateur filmmakers to demonstrate their passion for Star Trek as long as their works were nonprofessional and met the companies guidelines for fan films. Mike Bawden, a spokesman for Axanar, said the agreement allows the company to make no more than two additional films of a maximum of 15 minutes each that could be distributed on YouTube without ads. Prelude to Axanar can remain on YouTube without ads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Star Trek Copyright Settlement Allows Fan Film 'Axanar' to Proceed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 18:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 18:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep!

Malcolm: The one about the fucking hairdresser, the space hairdresser and the cowboy. The guy, he's got a tin foil pal and a pedal bin. His father's a robot and he's fucking fucked his sister. Lego! They're all made of fucking Lego. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 17:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For all we know, she might be a Slovenian Mata Hari. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 04:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I bet Dumpster has some business stakes in Saudi that explains this.

Yep, that might be the reason for not including the Kingdom in the Muslims travel ban as well.

From [Bloomberg](https://www.bloomberg.com/graphics/tracking-trumps-web-of-conflicts/):

* Saudi Arabia: Trump lists companies on his FEC filing possibly related to a development project in Jeddah, Saudi Arabias second-biggest city, located outside Mecca: DT Jeddah Technical Services Manager LLC, DT Jeddah Technical Services Manager Member Corp., THC Jeddah Hotel Manager LLC and THC Jeddah Hotel Manager Member Corp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 01:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm pro-Hillary

And I'm Superman, the last son of Krypton!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 01:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A map from Bloomberg shows how [Trumps immigration ban excludes countries with business ties.](https://twitter.com/bpolitics/status/825757916720406533) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 01:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I second that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 01:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taxing drug cartels ?????
Are they really that dumb or there's something else going on here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 00:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're experts, not clairvoyants.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 23:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think federal judges and civil society are next on his list.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 23:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First they came for the media: 

[Steve Bannon](https://www.nytimes.com/2017/01/26/business/media/stephen-bannon-trump-news-media.html?_r=0): "The media should be embarrassed and humiliated and keep its mouth shut and just listen for a while, I want you to quote this, the media here is the opposition party. They dont understand this country. They still do not understand why Donald Trump is the president of the United States.


[Kellyanne Conway](http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/316750-conway-on-the-media-when-are-they-going-to-fire-these-reporters): "Not one network person has been let go. Not one silly political analyst and pundit who talked smack all day long about Donald Trump has been let go," I'm too polite to mention their names, but they know who they are, and they are all wondering who will be the first to go. The election was three months ago. None of them have been let go."


[Trump](https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/825690087857995776): Somebody with aptitude and conviction should buy the FAKE NEWS and failing @nytimes and either run it correctly or let it fold with dignity!

Then they came for the dissenters in the Senate:

[Trump](https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/825823217025691648): The joint statement of former presidential candidates John McCain   Lindsey Graham is wrong - they are sadly weak on immigration. The two senators should focus their energies on ISIS, illegal immigration and border security instead of always looking to start World War III.

The message is loud and clear, no dissenters are allowed in Trump's America.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 23:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Hill changed the original title of the article.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police pepper-spray protesters at airport </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 22:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 22:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm not aware of the UAE or Egypt being major sources of terrorism pertaining to the US, but maybe I'm ignorant on that.

Most of the hijackers came from Saudi Arabia   Egypt, and two were from UAE. 

Egypt   Saudi Arabia are facing attacks from homegrown terrorists almost weekly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 22:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You guys have no proof this is about his business.

Sure we do.

[Trumps Immigration Ban Excludes Countries With Business Ties](https://www.bloomberg.com/graphics/2017-trump-immigration-ban-conflict-of-interest/)

* Egypt: Trump lists two companies on his FEC filing possibly related to business in Egypt: Trump Marks Egypt and Trump Marks Egypt LLC.

* Saudi Arabia: Trump lists companies on his FEC filing possibly related to a development project in Jeddah, Saudi Arabias second-biggest city, located outside Mecca: DT Jeddah Technical Services Manager LLC, DT Jeddah Technical Services Manager Member Corp., THC Jeddah Hotel Manager LLC and THC Jeddah Hotel Manager Member Corp.

* United Arab Emirates: The Trump Organization has a licensing and management deal in Dubai with Damac Properties Dubai Co. for a golf course and luxury villas currently under construction. Another Trump-branded golf course, designed by Tiger Woods, is under development with Damac nearby.

* Turkey: Trump Towers - Licensing deal to use his name on two currently operating luxury towers, one commercial and one residential, for which he received as much as $5 million last year, according to his latest financial disclosure. Shares in Dogan Sirketler Grubu Holding, his partner on the project, surged almost 11 percent after Trumps victory. Trump said in an interview with Breitbart News that "I have a little conflict of interest, because I have a major, major building in Istanbul. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 21:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Bannon: "Darkness is good, Dick Cheney. Darth Vader. Satan. That's power. It only helps us when they (liberals) get it wrong. When they're blind to who we are and what we're doing,"

When you have Dick Cheney, Darth Vader and Satan on your side, you don't need the joint chiefs. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 21:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's only one week into Donald Trump's presidency, and he already has his first "heckuva job" moment. For those who don't remember, in the aftermath of Hurricane Katrina in 2005, President George W Bush publicly praised his emergency management head, Michael Brown, for doing a "heckuva job" with recovery efforts. That comment was hung around the president's neck like an anvil, as flood waters swamped parts of New Orleans and the city descended into chaos. It started a public approval downward spiral that led to sweeping Democratic victories in the 2006 mid-term elections. History will judge the long-term impact of Mr Trump's Friday afternoon immigration order, but his early praise for its implementation will not easily be forgotten. "It's working out very nicely," Mr Trump said in a brief response to a question on Saturday afternoon. "You see it in the airports, you see it all over. It's working out very nicely, and we are going to have a very, very strict ban, and we are going to have extreme vetting, which we should have had in this country for many years." On the ground at major US airports, things weren't going quite so nicely, however. Immigration officials were having a difficult time implementing Mr Trump's order after receiving conflicting instructions on who to bar from entry into the US - and what to do with them once they were held. And as the day progressed, and word spread of the detentions, crowds of protesters at international terminals grew from dozens to hundreds to thousands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's executive order: Amateur hour at the White House? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 21:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 20:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Critics point out that the nations where the Sept. 11 hijackers hailed from  Saudi Arabia, Egypt the United Arab Emirates and Lebanon  are not included on the list. Neither is Pakistan, the home of the 2010 Times Square bomber Faisal Shahzad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump speaks with Saudi King </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 20:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Michael Flynn Jr., who was released from the transition team after spreading a debunked conspiracy theory about a Washington pizza parlor, was formerly a top adviser to his father. He has a history of spreading conspiracy theories and racially charged comments on Twitter, as recently documented by CNN. As protests burst out Saturday against Trumps order, which bars entry to the United States for citizens of seven Muslim-majority countries, Flynn Jr. took to Twitter to celebrate. Making America Great Again! #MuslimBan #saturdaymorning #AmericaFirst @GenFlynn @realDonaldTrump, he wrote, including the Twitter handles of his father and the president.

What a moron.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flynn's son says 'Muslim ban' is 'necessary' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrong! 

Obama only stopped the visa waiver program, he DID NOT ban refugees, immigrants or Green Card holders from those countries. They were still able to apply for a visa at a U.S. Embassy or Consulate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 18:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He's recently finished a graduate degree at the Naval War College.

Wait, are you serious? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "Not one network person has been let go. Not one silly political analyst and pundit who talked smack all day long about Donald Trump has been let go," she added. "I'm too polite to mention their names, but they know who they are, and they are all wondering who will be the first to go. The election was three months ago. None of them have been let go."

What the actual fuck happening?

Edit: [Trump](https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/825690087857995776) tweeted this today 

 Somebody with aptitude and conviction should buy the FAKE NEWS and failing @nytimes and either run it correctly or let it fold with dignity!

Trump and his team clearly want to control the free press   turned it into state-run media.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conway on the media: When are they going to fire these reporters? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He should ask C.J. to tutor him! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 15:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The Looming Tower traces the rising threat of Osama Bin Laden and Al-Qaeda, and takes a controversial look at how the rivalry between the CIA and FBI may have inadvertently set the stage for the tragedy of 9/11 and the war in Iraq.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Looming Tower: Tahar Rahim To Star In Hulus 9/11 Drama Series </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 15:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Colony': Carlton Cuse breaks down a major event in the show's most recent episode. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 04:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FBI probes threat to 'blow up' Denver-area refugee center </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 03:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 03:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "The franchise has kind of wandered all over the map," the Avatar and Terminator director told Vulture when asked about Scott's upcoming Alien: Covenant. "I don't think it's worked out terribly well. I think we've moved on beyond it. It's like, okay, we've got it, we've got the whole Freudian biomechanoid meme. I've seen it in 100 horror films since. I think both of those films stand at a certain point in time, as a reference point. But is there any validity to doing another one now? I don't know. Maybe. Let's see, jury's out." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> James Cameron Isn't Impressed with the Shape of the 'Alien' Franchise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 03:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> James Cameron Isn't Impressed with the Shape of the 'Alien' Franchise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 03:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 01:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was Dan Bennett the new head of Redhats played by Christian Clemenson.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 23:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  On Friday, during a visit to the Pentagon, the president signed an executive action affecting U.S. policies towards refugees. Mr. Trump said the action calls for extreme vetting of refugees to keep foreign terrorists from entering the U.S. As he signed it, the president announced, thats big stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump says refugee plan would prioritize Christians </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 23:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 20:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  For those that dont have our back, were taking names, we will make points to respond to that accordingly.

Nikki-It's a great day in South Carolina-Haley: First order of business at the UN, making the naughty List. 

What an amateur.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UN envoy Nikki Haley pledges to 'take names' of those who don't support US </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 20:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 19:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know much about him but here is an interview he did about his most recent movie [The Wave.](http://collider.com/the-wave-roar-uthaug-ana-dahl-torp-interview/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 19:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The British reporters asked most of the questions and Trump took just one question from the America media, guess which one?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 19:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing of it is, when he ain't exploring he's a picture postcard of a drunken, self-destructive fuck-up. And when he is exploring... he's pretty much the same motherfucker. But on a good expedition, he runnin' in front of the pack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess the current one but he didn't go into details, just the fact that Q is a woman. 

 "The real-life Q is looking forward to meeting you and I'm pleased to report that the real-life Q is a woman."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It appears that the British government didn't officially acknowledge the existence of MI6 until 1994! 

Perhaps your tour guide's information was outdated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did Legends of Tomorrow Just Acknowledge What a Terrible Villain Vandal Savage Was? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 17:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 17:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MI5 is the British domestic intelligence service. MI6 on the other hand is the foreign intelligence service like the CIA.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dominic West Joins Alicia Vikander in 'Tomb Raider' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 17:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The head of MI6 has revealed that the real-life gadget inventor known as Q in the James Bond films is a woman. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 17:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 17:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely not a puppet. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 16:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Jason Bourne. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 05:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Putin: [If you're going to lie, don't make it so obvious.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=09flnukGraU feature=youtu.be t=142) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 01:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is abusing the power of the presidency over a fucking crowd size? Impeach this idiot asap.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 23:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best amateurs. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 23:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mexico, we're just kidding!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 23:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Ashley Killough](https://twitter.com/KilloughCNN/status/824722910132785153) 

 Trump on Air Force One: Beautiful. Great plane. Really beautiful..nice plane. via pooler @jeffzeleny and CNN photojournalist John Bodnar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Beautiful. Great plane': Trump was 'in awe' of his first flight on Air Force One </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 23:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Save CNN From Itself: CNNs management has let down its viewers and its journalists by sidelining the issues and real reporting in favor of pundits, prognostication and substance-free but entertaining TV moments. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 22:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 21:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Trumps attacks on CNN may be a response to the networks recent coverage, which Trump views as biased and unfair. But sources say there may also be a personal dimension at play: According to people close to both sides, Trump has told White House staffers that he feels personally betrayed by CNN chief Jeff Zucker. **Trump complains that Zucker should be programming CNN more favorably toward him because of their long relationship, which can be traced back to 2004 when Zucker put The Apprentice on NBC**. Trump has also said to White House staffers that Zucker owes him because Trump helped get him the job at CNN. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Donald Trumps War With CNN Personal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 21:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump picks leader for federal agency overseeing his D.C. hotel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 21:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 20:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "Mike Pompeo, is Mike here? Mike? Mike Pompeo, phenomenal guy," Trump said during his speech Thursday at the retreat, looking around the room and gesturing to the crowd. [...] "Where is  where is Pompeo? Where the hell is he? Did he ever come here?" Trump asked the audience, shielding his eyes from lights as he looked into the crowd.

What a fucking moron.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump: Where's Pompeo? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 20:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Judge Maryanne Trump Barry has urged her brother to choose her colleague Judge Thomas Hardiman, Politico said Wednesday. Maryanne is high on Hardiman, said one adviser who has spoken directly with President Trump on the matter. Politico said Barry and Hardiman serve together on the U.S. Third Circuit Court of Appeals in Pennsylvania. Barry, 79, was first appointed to a federal district court more than three decades ago by then-President Ronald Reagan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's sister pushing colleague for Supreme Court pick: report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 23:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still no 'Dark Matter' season 2! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump order calls for weekly list of crimes done by undocumented workers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 22:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Walking Dead: Sonequa Martin-Green on what her Star Trek role means for Sasha </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 22:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Theresa May Warns Donald Trump The UK Will Not Condone Torture Of Detainees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 21:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Universal Wins Bidding War for Michael Bay-Produced Script About Trump-Like Dystopia: 'Little America' is set in a future where a U.S. president has bankrupt America and China has called in its debts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 20:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bryan Singer to Direct Pilot for Foxs Upcoming X-Men TV Series </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 20:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats Coming to Netflix Canada in February 2017? [Canada] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 20:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 20:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The White House seemed to be using the same tactics the Chinese government routinely uses against the foreign press corps: Make false claims to support an alternative narrative. When challenged, threaten reporters  and then try to delegitimize them. Like the new White House, the Chinese government has tried over the years to convince citizens not to believe their own eyes. For instance, when smog enveloped Chinese cities, the government would insist it was really just fog. This tactic grew increasingly absurd as air reached staggeringly toxic levels and people faced post-apocalyptic scenes that no propaganda campaign could overcome. The Chinese government is much more candid about its air pollution crisis these days, but still tries to manage reality and mislead citizens. Earlier this month, the government ordered provincial officials to halt smog warnings and then censored news of the order when it leaked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For Journalists Who've Worked In China, New White House Tactics Seem Familiar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 17:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The email listed quotes from, Fox News Sean Hannity, the USA Today editorial board and various other outlets under the headline Praise for President Trumps Bold Action. Such emails are common during campaigns, but rare from the White House, as federal resources are rarely used so explicitly to promote praise of the president.

The American dictator.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 17:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The president can sign whatever executive orders he likes, McCain said in a statement responding to a New York Times report that Trump has drafted an executive order paving the way for the return of George W. Bush-era detainee treatment standards. But the law is the law. We are not bringing back torture in the United States of America. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McCain warns Trump: 'We are not bringing back torture' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 17:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 01:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Conservative radio host Hugh Hewitt on Tuesday warned that President Donald Trump begins his administration on thin ice with Democrats, who could move to impeach the new president if they retake the House of Representatives in 2018. Democrats and liberal groups have already launched an effort to impeach Trump over allegations of conflicts of interest, including with his new Washington, D.C., hotel. A watchdog group filed suit Monday, claiming Trumps business dealings with foreign countries that rent space in his buildings or lend money to his real estate empire violate the foreign emoluments clause of the Constitution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is a statement from [The American Mustache Institute](http://www.americanmustacheinstitute.org/2016/12/official-statement-donald-trump%E2%80%99s-unacceptable-mustache-discrimination/):

 Official Statement: Donald Trumps Unacceptable Mustache Discrimination - ... Rucker and Tumultys revelations, however, may be the most offensive yet, suggesting John R. Boltons sexually dynamic Mustached American lifestyle eliminated him as a candidate for the coveted secretary of state position. Donald was not going to like that mustache, one associate was quoted as saying. I cant think of anyone thats really close to Donald that has a beard that he likes. The paradox, of course, is that Mr. Trumps orange face and spaghetti squash mane would, theoretically through his own Clark Gable paradigm  who ironically had a mustache  make Mr. Trump himself unfit to serve in a position of leadership.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The complete quote: 

 The main federal law against conflicts of interest exempts the president, but that does not mean such conflicts cannot exist. Additionally, other ethics laws do apply to the president, such as the STOCK Act against trading on government information and the prohibition on bribery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By endorsing this debunked claim of massive voter fraud, Trump is casting doubts on the 2016 election and practically calling into question the legitimately of his own presidency.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Pressed for those studies, Spicer then offered a falsehood of his own, pointing to a study that came out of Pew in 2008 that showed 14 percent of people who voted were noncitizens." Thats inaccurate on multiple counts: There is a study that found that 14 percent of noncitizens voted, but its not from Pew, it didnt come out in 2008 and it has been widely debunked  including by members of the survey team on which the study is based.

'Baghdad Sean' strikes again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spicer makes misleading voter fraud claim to defend Trump's false voter fraud claim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Engage!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is delusional, period.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sanders: Trump 'delusional' on voter fraud claims </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 20:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worse than interfering in a presidential election   dragging their feet investigating Trump's team contacts with the Russians? Don't think so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is not just EPA, they are coming hard on other agencies as well.
 

 [DOT reins in social media postings after Interior blackout](http://www.politico.com/story/2017/01/transportation-department-social-media-on-hold-234044?cmpid=sf): The Department of Transportation has become the second federal agency to tap the brakes on its social media postings since the dawn of Donald Trumps presidency. A department source told POLITICO early Monday that employees were told not to publish news releases or engage on DOTs social media accounts. A department spokesperson later called it a recommendation, saying a career employee had suggested to DOT's agencies that they refrain from issuing news releases or posting to social media until more guidance comes down from the new administration.

[Voice of America](http://www.politico.com/story/2017/01/donald-trump-voice-america-234078?cmpid=sf) is next. 

 President Donald Trump on Monday dispatched two aides to scope out the studios of Voice of America, heightening concerns among some longtime staffers that Trump may quickly put his stamp on the broadcasting arm that has long pushed U.S. democratic ideals across the world. The arrival of the two aides  both political operatives from Trumps campaign  comes after Voice of America received blowback over the weekend for sending out a series of tweets about White House Press Secretary Sean Spicers claims about inauguration crowd size that looked to some like an endorsement of his false statements. The news outlet later deleted one of the tweets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks real but this is Trump we're talking about, it's hard to be sure about anything when it comes to Trump.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 18:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump tweeted this 50 minutes ago

 [Trump](https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/823937936056008704): A photo delivered yesterday that will be displayed in the upper/lower press hall. Thank you Abbas!

I didn't know that the inauguration was on January 21th! #alternativedate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 03:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The Department of Transportation has become the second federal agency to tap the brakes on its social media postings since the dawn of Donald Trumps presidency. A department source told POLITICO early Monday that employees were told not to publish news releases or engage on DOTs social media accounts. A department spokesperson later called it a recommendation, saying a career employee had suggested to DOT's agencies that they refrain from issuing news releases or posting to social media until more guidance comes down from the new administration.

And the purge continues. 

Edit: [Voice of America](http://www.politico.com/story/2017/01/donald-trump-voice-america-234078?cmpid=sf) is next. 

 President Donald Trump on Monday dispatched two aides to scope out the studios of Voice of America, heightening concerns among some longtime staffers that Trump may quickly put his stamp on the broadcasting arm that has long pushed U.S. democratic ideals across the world. The arrival of the two aides  both political operatives from Trumps campaign  comes after Voice of America received blowback over the weekend for sending out a series of tweets about White House Press Secretary Sean Spicers claims about inauguration crowd size that looked to some like an endorsement of his false statements. The news outlet later deleted one of the tweets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DOT reins in social media postings after Interior blackout </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 03:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 03:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boy, we're witnessing the emergence of the most corrupt government in the history of the United States.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 02:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The FBI, you say? No wonder [Trump blew Comey a kiss](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KRCLId6rooM) yesterday!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 02:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well said.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [/r/nottheonion](https://www.reddit.com/r/nottheonion/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Merkel advisors say Germany has 'given up' on Donald Trump acting like a President </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 20:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's White House to include 'Skype' seats at daily press briefing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 20:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 19:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The Pennsylvania Avenue hotel, which Trump leases from the General Services Administration, trailed its revenue projections by almost $2.3 million in September and October, House Democrats said in a letter today, citing documents provided by the GSA. In the letter, sent to the agencys acting administrator, Democratic Reps. Elijah Cummings, Peter DeFazio, Gerald Connolly and Andre Carson argued that Trump violated the terms of his lease once he became president because it doesnt allow elected officials to benefit. They asked the agency to turn over its correspondence with Trumps company and to show how its addressing the issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 18:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And then they [WH press corps] begin to think they should judge the president.

Is Trump now the King of the land and no one is allowed to question him!? What the fucking wrong with these people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 17:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fake crowds for fake President.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 16:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "Social media postings sometimes provide an important window into a persons #mentalhealth, the department tweeted from its official account. "Know what to look for. [...] "Are you guys watching @realDonaldTrump's twitter? tweeted one person. "I am concerned about his mental health. He's a danger to our country. "Medal of Freedom for whoever at @DeptofDefense was responsible for this, please, read another tweet.[...] "Hope y'all survive the next purge." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Defense Department links social media use to mental health in official tweet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 16:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 04:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> redditor for 6 hours! lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 00:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't give it to Wikileaks, better to leak it to the media directly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 00:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 00:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is very much pointless to argue with hypocritical voters who were raging against the corrupt establishment and yet they have no problem with a sitting president refusing to release his tax returns. 


None of the previous presidential candidates since Nixon were required by the law to release their tax returns and yet all of them did release them for the sake of transparency   accountability, outlandish concepts for the likes of you Im sure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 23:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Of course, another crucial aspect to this transformation is the presidents contemptuous attitude towards the media. My, the delightful similarities. From blaming the press for engaging in secret conspiracies to undermine him to threatening their access to his White House palace to refusing to take questions from certain reporters, President Trump reminds us of several of our own leaders. In fact, an Arab leader complaining about CNN coverage is pretty much a staple of our political life. This took an interesting turn on Saturday when the president accused the media of manufacturing his feud with the mukhabarat and his Minister of Information Mr. Sean Spicer castigated the media for reporting the size of Trumps inauguration crowd. The not-so-veiled threats by the president and Mr. Spicer to the media are very much in the spirit of Arab governance. 

Welcome to the Kingdom of Trump!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  President Donald Trump on Sunday warmly greeted the man who some Democrats say handed him the presidency. At a White House reception for law enforcement, Trump spotted FBI Director James Comey and, stretching out his arms, called him over. Comey strolled across the room to greet Trump, who shook his hand and put an arm around him, slapping him on the back.

Edit: [Video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KRCLId6rooM) of Trump blows a kiss to his FBI agent Comey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump gives FBI Director Comey a pat on the back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 21:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't tell Trump! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 21:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama didnt just release his tax returns during the 2008 campaign; [he also released every tax return during his presidency showing income ranging from $447,000 to $5.6 million.]( http://www.voanews.com/a/donald-trump-shrugs-off-tradition-release-tax-returns/3535394.html)

Why you need to deflect from Trumps refusal to release his tax returns by talking about Obamas tax returns that were released to the public? Get fucking real for once.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 21:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better send it to the [New York Times](https://www.nytimes.com/newsgraphics/2016/news-tips/) and other news outlets.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 21:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently Mike Pence needed to reminds White House senior staff to raise their hands as they were taking the oath! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump on 'beautiful' letter from Obama: We won't tell the press what's in it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 20:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All talk talk, no action! /S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like Putin is getting tired of his orange agent!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lies, damned lies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Bond adds, We have step one: massive numbers of people raising their hands. The question is if there will be an organizing group that can take that and use it to change things, rather than have this be an expression of anger and discontent alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How grassroots activists can use the Womens March to build concrete political power. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that why Trump was whining about his crowd size at the CIA and then his Minister of Propaganda held his very *first* press briefing to whine more about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "All I asked of my colleague Sen. Schumer was to treat President Trump the same we treated President Obama," McConnell said

We can agree on that. Schumer should make it loud and clear that his top priority is to make Trump a one term President.  

Edit: A word.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 17:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm aware of the NYT story. What I'm saying that TV anchors should be more aggressive when confronted with outright lies by the Trump team. Time and again they let people like Kellyanne Conway   Reince Priebus get away with lies.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 16:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The White House response is that hes not going to release his tax returns, said Kellyanne Conway, counselor to the president, during an appearance on ABCS This Week with George Stephanopoulos. We litigated this all through the election.

What is he hiding? #ReleaseUrTaxReturns

Edit: As long as the media is not pushing back, like [George Stephanopoulos](http://www.mediaite.com/tv/kellyanne-conway-says-trumps-not-going-to-release-his-tax-returns/) did in this interview, Trump's team will keep getting away with murder.

Edit 2: [President Barack Obama has released every tax return during his presidency, showing income ranging from $447,000 to $5.6 million.](http://www.voanews.com/a/donald-trump-shrugs-off-tradition-release-tax-returns/3535394.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump wont release his tax returns because people dont care, top adviser says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 16:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 01:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump cares! He tweeted [232 times about ratings.](http://trumptwitterarchive.com/#/archive)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brennan deeply saddened and angered at Trumps CIA remarks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 01:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 00:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * 2017: Donald Trump averaged 27.7 million viewers.
* 2009: Barack Obama averaged 37.8 million viewers
* 2001: George Bush averaged 29 million viewers 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 22:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 20:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama averaged 37.8 million viewers in 2009. George W. Bush averaged 29 million viewers in 2001 while Trump averaged 27.7 million viewers.

Edit: Added the years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TV Ratings: Trump Inauguration Sinks From Obama in 2009 in Early Numbers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 20:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Discovery Review: Netflix Sci-Fi Film Is a Dark, Twisty Spin on the Afterlife </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 20:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 19:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Final .5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 19:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  However, there is an island out there, and Lindelof says its ours for the taking. [Executive producer] Carlton [Cuse] and I always said that we welcome any future crack at the [intellectual property]. Lost was bigger than us and bigger than [co-creator] J.J. [Abrams]. Theres something really exciting about the fact that George Lucas sold the Star Wars universe and now the people who grew up watching it are making it. Maybe the same thing could be said for Lost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Lost' EP Damon Lindelof talks reboot chances </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 19:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 18:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A 14-page opinion dated Friday from Justice's Office of Legal Counsel asserts that a federal anti-nepotism law that applies to agencies across the executive branch does not cover the White House itself.[...] A Justice Department spokesman said the opinion was posted online Friday afternoon. When such opinions are promptly made public, it is usually at the request of the White House. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justice Department blesses White House post for Kushner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 18:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 18:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And? We usually have several posts about any given breaking news.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 17:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. I don't understand why some people think it's a bad idea for him to be involved, after all he wasn't in charge of the last 3 movies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 17:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Holodeck](http://blog.softwareinsider.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/08/holodeck-voyager.jpg) confirmed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Protests Worldwide as Trump Takes Office </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 17:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 16:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of his supporters are pensioners   the rest are jobless with extreme "economic anxiety"!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 16:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chris Wallace called Trump "an insurgent, the leader of a revolt that has won and taken control of Washington,! That alone qualify Wallace to receive the Presidential Medal of Freedom. /S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 15:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A fantastic day and evening in Washington D.C. Thank you to @FoxNews and so many other news outlets for the GREAT reviews of the speech! Trump wrote early Saturday morning. He posted the tweet from his personal account, @realDonaldTrump, rather than the official account he now controls, @POTUS. Trump had previously signaled he would likely continue using the personal account after taking office. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump tweets praise of Fox News for inaugural coverage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 15:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 15:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Were going to have people who have looked down a rifle scope, Flynn often said at meetings during the transition, according to one senior transition official.[...] Flynn believes if you fill the NSC staff with people who have borne the battle, as he likes to say, you will get better outcomes. The risk of that approach? When the only tools you have are hammers, every problem looks like a nail. 

Prepare yourself for the forever war!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CBS and Paramount settle lawsuit over crowdfunded Star Trek fan film 'Axanar' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 15:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He'll be back! James Cameron is reportedly planning a new Terminator film </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 15:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CBS, Paramount Settle Lawsuit Over 'Star Trek' Fan Film </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 01:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 00:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  [Obama](https://twitter.com/BarackObama/status/822550300942856193): Hi everybody! Back to the original handle. Is this thing still on? Michelle and I are off on a quick vacation, then well get back to work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama promises return to work after vacation in first post-presidential tweet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 00:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 00:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a second I read that as John F. Kennedy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's crowd size misses his mark </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 00:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 23:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Melania looks a lot like Claire Underwood.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump poised to reinstate 'global gag rule' on Roe v. Wade anniversary: report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 01:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 01:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3rd season will be the last of the series.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 01:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL hilarious coming from t_d redditor. 
Go back to your safe place.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 01:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Trump](http://i.imgur.com/LUVjbXX.png?1) - brought to you by the Daily Show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 01:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So by "displaying our military" you're saying that Trump was talking just about typical "military marches"? Riiiiiiiiight! 

That must be the reason the military denied their request. SAD!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 01:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Interview with the Washington Post yesterday](https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/how-donald-trump-came-up-with-make-america-great-again/2017/01/17/fb6acf5e-dbf7-11e6-ad42-f3375f271c9c_story.html?postshare=831484737469175 tid=ss_tw utm_term=.1896d0d02410)

 Being a great president has to do with a lot of things, but one of them is being a great cheerleader for the country, Trump said. And were going to show the people as we build up our military, were going to display our military. **That military may come marching down Pennsylvania Avenue. That military may be flying over New York City and Washington, D.C., for parades. I mean, were going to be showing our military,** he added. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 00:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  According to the report, the military shot down the request because of concerns about how it would look to have tanks and missile launchers in the parade.

No kidding! This is not Russia. 

Edit: Apparently Trump wants [military parade](https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/how-donald-trump-came-up-with-make-america-great-again/2017/01/17/fb6acf5e-dbf7-11e6-ad42-f3375f271c9c_story.html?postshare=831484737469175 tid=ss_tw utm_term=.1896d0d02410) in NYC as well!

 Being a great president has to do with a lot of things, but one of them is being a great cheerleader for the country, Trump said. And were going to show the people as we build up our military, were going to display our military. **That military may come marching down Pennsylvania Avenue. That military may be flying over New York City and Washington, D.C., for parades**. I mean, were going to be showing our military, he added. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 23:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Educate yourself!

[NPR](http://www.pbs.org/newshour/rundown/a-designated-survivor-the-most-powerful-man-for-3-hours/): Designated Survivor Most Powerful Man (or Woman) for Three Hours - By tradition, one Cabinet secretary is chosen every year to be the designated survivor and skip the presidents speech in the case that those seated together in the confined Chamber  including the president, vice president, Supreme Court justices and the remaining 14 Cabinet secretaries  were wiped by an attack on the Capitol and the line of presidential succession was no longer functional. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 23:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fake outrage.

[Fox News in 2016](http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2016/01/12/gop-sen-hatch-is-designated-survivor-for-state-union-address.html): DHS Secretary Jeh Johnson designated Cabinet member 'survivor' for State of the Union

[Fox News in 2015](http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2015/01/20/transportation-secretary-anthony-foxx-to-be-designated-survivor-during-state.html): Transportation Secretary Anthony Foxx to be 'designated survivor' during State of the Union speech </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 23:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Sen. Mark Warner couldnt believe what his Republican counterpart on the Senate Intelligence Committee had just done. With no advance notice, Chairman Richard Burr (R-N.C.) declared to reporters that his panel wouldnt look into possible collusion between Donald Trumps campaign and Moscow as part of its investigation of Russian interference in the election. So Warner, a Virginia Democrat who is the panels ranking member, promptly enlisted every Democrat on the committee to oppose Burrs move and presumably boycott the investigation if he didn't reverse himself, according to congressional sources. Barely 24 hours later, Burr issued a lengthy statement backtracking on his own comments. The committee would indeed examine links between Russia and individuals associated with political campaigns as part of its larger election-hacking probe, Burr wrote in a joint statement with Warner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the Senate's Russian meddling probe almost blew up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 23:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 22:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And while theyre barred from donating to the $200 million in inaugural festivities this week, lobbyists have been collecting checks on Trumps behalf, according to four lobbyists interviewed by POLITICO who are directly helping raise the funds. The loopholes in Trumps restrictions are so widespread that many lobbyists said theyve concluded Trumps ethics rules arent really meant to change how business is done in Washington. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Trump lobbying purge that wasnt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 22:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Leftovers' Carrie Coon Teases Finale: 'They Chose the Right Ending' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 21:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 21:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump: When you're a President, they let you do it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But her father's [sexual obsession](http://www.politicususa.com/2016/10/08/grotesque-history-donald-trumps-sexual-comments-daughter.html) with her is appropriate. /S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ivanka Trump: Speculation that I'll be first lady 'inappropriate' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Colony': Carlton Cuse on Season 2 "Reset" and Letting Its "Sci-Fi Freak Flag Fly" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 03:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Colony': Carlton Cuse on Season 2 "Reset" and Letting Its "Sci-Fi Freak Flag Fly" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 03:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Colony': Carlton Cuse on Season 2 "Reset" and Letting Its "Sci-Fi Freak Flag Fly" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 03:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 02:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  From his pick of nominees for posts in his cabinet to his belligerent use of Twitter (our conversation was a day before he traded barbs with Congressman John Lewis) to his unwillingness to cut ties with his business to avoid conflicts of interest, they see the same person theyve always seenthe consummate classroom troublemaker; a vain, insecure bully; and an anti-institutional schemer, as adept at gaming the system as he is unashamed. As they look ahead to his inauguration speech in two days, and to his administration beyond, they feel confident predicting that he will run the country much as he has run his company. For himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He Has This Deep Fear That He Is Not a Legitimate President </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 02:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 02:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Secretary of State, Secretary of the Treasury, Attorney General, Secretary of the Interior and the rest are advisory positions? Go back to t_d or keep watching Fox.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 01:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The Republicans ](http://www.politico.com/story/2017/01/cabinet-confirmations-republicans-democrats-233799) don't care as long as he's one of them!

 Sen. Johnny Isakson (R-Ga.), the chairman of the Senate *Ethics* Committee, said theres nothing untoward about Prices investment activity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 00:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Democrats said that they werent surprised by the drumbeat of disclosures about Trumps nominees, blaming the incoming president for failing to sift through the records of his top administration officials. The Trump people didnt really vet the way that Bush did, Clinton did, Obama did on these nominees. Theres going to be all kinds of things that come out, said Sen. Sherrod Brown (D-Ohio). People arent defeated very often for confirmation. But they withdraw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans blow past Trump Cabinet controversies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 00:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 00:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump and Putin would know for sure! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 00:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you read that on Fox? Because you are WRONG!

[Confirmations of Barack Obama's Cabinet](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Confirmations_of_Barack_Obama's_Cabinet)

[The Obama Cabinet: Confirmations   Nominations](http://www.npr.org/templates/story/story.php?storyId=99674016) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 00:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, OP mentioned another book by the same author called 'Armada'.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 00:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading the synopsis is what led me to think they are similar 

 A shuttle from the video game Armada picks Zack up at his school and delivers him to a top-secret military facility in Nebraska. There, he and other top performing players learn about the existence of the Earth Defense Alliance (EDA). The EDA reveals that the Armada video game was actually developed as a simulation of an imminent alien threat from aliens on Europa, called the Europans. The threat was kept secret from the public, and Armada was then used to train video gamers to pilot drone ships to protect Earth from the Europans, and identify which gamers would be best for the task. The EDA reveals that the Europans have a three-phase attack commencing within a few hours. These recruits have been chosen for special missions during the attack. Shortly after the briefing, the secret base is attacked by a scouting party, during which Zack disobeys orders, causing the destruction of over five hundred EDA drones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 21:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy crap! The lady is nut.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 21:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that a real quote? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 21:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, other than Gen. Mattis do they have a single qualified person in Trump's cabinet?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Star Trek: Discovery casts Spocks father, pushes premiere date - the series is no longer going to premiere in May as previously announced. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 19:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 18:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not yet but from reading the synopsis on Wikipedia the first half sounds very similar to 'Ender's Game'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 18:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Trump's lying is, like everything about him, hyperbolic to the point of self-parody. We may expect politicians to fudge the truth in the heat of battle, but Trump displays a contempt for the very idea that someone in his position should be expected to confine himself to true statements. On the stump he repeated falsehoods that had been debunked. He retweeted false and racially inflammatory information distributed by white nationalists. Paul Waldman has described Trump's "epistemological netherworld" as a place where "facts are meaningless, knowledge is useless and nobody can really know anything." One of Trump's main surrogates recently took it even further, saying there's no such thing as facts. No such thing! That worldview will come in handy for the people he is appointing to lead federal agencies whose public service missions they oppose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Norman Lear: Why Do People Fall For Fake News? (Guest Column) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 18:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
