<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject398</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 15:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 15:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah fuck yeah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 15:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I can help you achieve that just let me know what I can do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 15:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being American and with the current events happening I think I'd like to go to Cuba. I would like to hug a few Cubans and tell them I'm sorry for the way my government valued their lives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 15:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my inspiration? That is a very long sad story The short version... I refuse to become numb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 02:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks , but I don't really think it's amazing. It's not as hard as I or most people believe. You just have to be willing to roll with the punches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 02:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks I'll try. 3 months is a long time to go without any fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 00:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks and I can already see you may win $5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 00:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit 1: Now remember this is my first time to solo travel I've never traveled much before. My flight arrived here on January 1st. My rides car broke down halfway to Santa Ana and I had to stand along the highway for a couple hours and get in another vehicle with somebody else but all went well I'm the end. Just took a long time to get to Santa Ana. On the second I was offered a free ride around with a young Canadian couple to some of the Mayan ruins and crater lake . Had a wonderful time. Days there and four I was asked to accompany a older German couple on their motor tour because their driver spoke poor English and wasn't confident. I didn't have much choice of where I was going but I got to go a lot of places for free. The German couple even insisted on buying my meals. So far I've only met new friends. If you knew what kind of deal I made to stay here in Santa Ana you'd like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 23:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [caption](http://imgur.com/d4AQsNQ.jpg) at the end of my third day here I was driven up into the mountains to casa Alaska for a cup of coffee this was my view. The coffee was good too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 23:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's my way of proving to my friends back home that I am actually here. And if I tried to get my big head into a picture with my huge head of white hair that is all you will see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 23:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking forward to it keep in touch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 23:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pupusas was my first meal! Plantains were served with my first breakfast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 23:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I can guarantee it is me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 23:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of places I've been have had pistol grip shotgun guards at the doors and occasionally I have seen armed military running the street but never felt threatened never have seen any problems. I also ran into a female Ozzy who could not have weighed 100 pounds who has been backpacking here and Central America for 3 years and she said she has never ran into any problems. She started when she was 19 and she's 23 now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well I made it. 62 year old man in Santa Ana El Salvador with a backpack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 18:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jan 1st to El Salvador and Guatemala for 3 months. You folks helped a first timer take the plunge. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 00:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I [M] get on the plane Jan 1st at 6am for my very first extended travel experience at 62 years old. I land in El Salvador and will be picked up by the Villa Napoli B B, I arranged to stay at in Santa Ana with them. I made a deal to help out around the place for a very nice discount and the use of extra amenities. I will use this as a jumping off site. I will catch a bus on Jan 2 to go to Xela, Guatemala to work in a hostel there for a couple weeks or more then back to Santa Ana to spend some time there. Then Who knows???? The freedom adventure begins. If anyone wants to hang out or meet up I'll buy you a few beers and maybe feed ya a meal. I leave Central America on March 30, well, that's the plan so far.
Thanks to all of you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 02:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love those creamy, orange, frozen little bitches! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't care when or who with so how do I find cheap flights? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 00:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My son Jacob, some hot ass women and my daughter-in-law. Can you guess which one she is? Jacob and the Good People-I Love Women Remix (ft.CRANE) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 01:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 13:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could it be possible to make a combination of colloidal silver / copper to treat these tumors? From what I understand colloidal silver it effective in killing cancer cells it come in contact with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-22 15:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've used a Flowbee off and on for decades. Just a caution from a 62 yr old guy, do NOT try to manscape with one of these and do NOT think you learned a lesson from the first time and try it a second. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 18:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Honey, why does the cat smell like fish?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 04:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Extra nipples on the males. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
