<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3750</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 21:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but 10 miles an hour doesnt really seem that much, especially when its already 60 that hes doing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 19:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im pretty sure you are supposed to cover the closer post with the wall, otherwise the ball will have more time to fall. Horrendous positioning from the keeper aswell.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 16:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How the fuck is he the asshole for driving the speed he feels comfortable with? Hes not drastically slower than the limit, and he is obeying the laws. If you want to get into a pissing contest and be so manly that you drive a bit faster than him thats fine, but the person isnt an asshole, you are just frustrated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 14:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine is the sneakiest son of a bitch know to mankind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 23:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Todays menu, and I cant stress "todays" enough, was his meal, then a plant he found on the balcony, bread he found somewhere, a plastic bag, toilet paper, spaghetti he stole from me, a slipper, a sock, my bag, followed by two of his regular meals, and still he waited around for food. When he realized he wasnt gonna get any, he had a fight with my stuffed bear and fell asleep on my head for the millionth time today. God I hate that i love him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 22:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a beagle and its geniunely the same situation, except this guy weighs about 25 kilos less so its a bit easier for me. However he decides he needs to make up that difference with speed so I pretty much get knocked out by a dog flying the speed of sound twice a week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 14:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the key word here is naked, and in -30 degrees celsius things would start to fall of. And I doubt casual attire will keep you warm enough longer than a night to survive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We thought Berdych didnt qualify, we were wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 23:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched the horrific italian accent scene atleast 15 times, and everytime I speak italian i always say "Buongiorno" in the most hideous way I can and chuckle a bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 21:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But a lot of them saw Troy. After all its half naked Brad Pitt and Orlando Bloom being a twat, whats not to like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 11:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats why I love clay, when I was a kid playing, whenever someone called out i just said point out the trace. Made everything a lot easier.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 23:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dad died when I was 6, couldnt handle saying goodbye to his first son. I just curled up and cried.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 14:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With that first down at 3 minutes left went down my money for this month, so close yet so far... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 23:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a guy who doesnt follow nfl too much, and has a bet on the packers winning, what am I looking at right now, possible comeback or not?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 15:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since 2008 Dortmund lead their h2h 11-8 if you set aside the draws. Hamburg has 2 points after 9 games played with a goal difference of -16. And beside all of that it was 1.5 on Dortmund which meant that they arent extreme favourites, so in my mind honestly this was a gift.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 15:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly tho, why the fuck would you bet on Hamburg? You are a Werder fan judging by the flair, and Hamburg keeps losing games and changing coaches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 09:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And this is Rijeka Crnojevica in Montenegro where I live. 

http://imgur.com/QXGWbgs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 18:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You wouldnt believe how opposed is eastern europe to it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We say that is wrong to take children to LGBT support events as they are too young to make their own choices, yet taking them to church and christening them is considered a good thing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 18:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 16:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Berbatov trying lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 22:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, some of the through balls he gives, just astonishing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 21:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except when he takes a penalty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 14:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marion Bartoli is that you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would you say was your signature shot, the one you are the most proud of and thats an edge over your opponents? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 11:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me its the forehand down the line, not a shot in the world that im more secure in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 13:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well in a surprising turn of events he is well again, the same dog he was the previous weeks. However I found a vet, and have his number just in case it gets bad again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 23:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, if its expensive ill take out a loan, just wanted to see if someone shared an experience the same as this. God I hate that I care so much about something now, spent the whole day thinking about this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 23:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was forced on me, as a gift that i couldnt refuse, and this injury came right between a car repair and a couple of other payments so im a bit short on cash right now. We have one shelter which is the same as putting him in a dumpster cause its run by incompetent people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 21:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I should probably mention that I live in the Balkans, Easter Europe in a city with 20k people, so vets are exclusively expensive and hard to find. But if he keeps acting like this, its my only choice isnt it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 14:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude I live in the Balkans, these are about half way across the world for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 15:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah I mean highlights of the game, they are usually about 3 and a half minutes. I saw the seahawks vs cardinals one, it lasted over 6 minutes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 15:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesnt nfl offer their own highlights on their youtube channel?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 23:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bring Risse back, hell I'd take Balza right now so I dont have to watch another minute of the second coming of Christ.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 19:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd kill for a pair of these, but I live in the Balkans so ill never see them again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wonder why I fall in love with something I cant have... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 14:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 22:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somewhere in Torino, a quiet snicker is heard, as a blonde man gazes into the television, gloating and speaking perfect italian.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 16:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blakes is listed as 125. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here is my little ball of hatred, named Khan, taking a break from terorizing socks and stuffed animals. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 16:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 22:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude Italian is not that hard, and this is his third year in Italy...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 16:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbf LeBron would have killed Westbrook if he put up a halfcourt shot with 18 on the clock as he did before, but I agree that the thunder team was lightyears ahead of the team where Sasa Pavlovic was a starter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 19:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Borussia 2 penalties and hit the post so go ahead universe, shit on me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 19:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually I was wondering the same thing during the Gladbach match since i had a feeling Stindl wasnt gonna score. It must have been like 10, or more since it was a second penalty of the day... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
