<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3240</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 09:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's definately not as interesting as other people's can be, but here goes:

In high school, I never dated much. Had 2 boyfriend's that lasted about 3 months each. Never asked to a school dance, on dates, etc. My first semester of college, I went to my towns local community college because I am broke and I didn't have the most amazing grades. It was late October and I was going to the enrollment office to talk to an advisor about what classes I should take (this is 2014 btw). Being October, there's a shiton of other people there waiting to see advisors. The wait was like 2 hours. I figure, fuck it, I've got no where to be and our enrollment area was connected to our student lounge so there's a bunch of chill nerds just hanging around playing smash.

I decide to watch a game from a little behind everyone else. I'm not very good at playing, but enjoy watching and talking to people who play. I sit next to this sorta greasy nerd guy and just start up casual conversation.  Now, I should mention, I had never been to this lounge area before. Our campus was under construction for several years and our enrollment office moved locations every damn semester. This wasn't a place I probably would have ever gone to on my own. Why I decided to just wait the 2 hours and not come back in the morning, I'm not sure. But from behind me and greasy nerd guy, walks up some cute blonde guy, asking the nerd guy for the math notes from the math class he had missed.

And what caught me first? Cute blonde guy is wearing a green sweater that is almost IDENTICAL to the one I'm wearing.

 So after, of course, freaking out about our matching green sweaters, we proceed to talk for the next almost 3 hours (the wait was way longer than predicted) and almost missed seeing the advisor. I learn this handsome boy's name is Jake, we are both obsessed with Legend of Zelda, anime, coffee, little eateries, etc. and the rest is history. We saw Big Hero 6 on our first date. We now live together and our 2 year anniversary will be November 28th :)

TL;DR: Met cute guy at school with matching sweater that had the same nerd interests as me, and coming up on 2 years together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 08:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ability to carry all that heavy, large stuff without needing to use much space. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 08:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DON'T HURT ME </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 08:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read somewhere that art and music were part of the original Greek games. As an artist I would LOVE to see artists compete in some way or another. I have an idea of how they could do it, but any sort of support for the arts would be amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 08:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sooo late to this thread but as someone who really loves music, here are the ones that are either just sad, creepy, haunting, etc. that always get to me (no particular order):

A lot of stuff by Coldplay since they're my favorite band buuuut

A Rush of Blood to The Head - Coldplay 
Girl With One Eye - Florence + The Machine 
Landfill - Daughter 
As My Guitar Gently Weeps - The Beatles
The Scientist - Coldplay 
Bigger, Stronger - Coldplay 
Gasoline - Halsey
Like Real People Do - Hozier 
Useless - Anarbor 
Everywhere I Go - Lissie
Goodnight Moon - Go Radio

Honestly, I could probably list a million songs but this is a good start (if anyone even sees this lol)


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 07:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um...are you dating my boyfriend too?!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 07:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was surprised to find that I often remembered more basic art history knowledge than a lot of my art teachers. My drawing teacher even asked me about images sometimes when talking to the class for more back up info. But I certainly wouldn't say I know a LOT more, just maybe more than the average person, and only because I retain knowledge and memories well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
