<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1497</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 09:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More:

http://i.imgur.com/PJER7n5.jpg

https://c2.staticflickr.com/4/3135/3033581688_f1c9f8694f_z.jpg?zz=1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These are cooked penguin eggs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 09:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 09:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks very much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trying to import my old FireFox bookmarks to my new PC but I can't find the right folder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 09:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My PC shit itself and I was able to recover the files I had on it. Among these were my FF bookmarks. I can find the places.sqlite from the data on my old hard drive but I can't find the corresponding place on my new one to paste it.

It should be here:

\Users\[yournamehere]\AppData\Roaming\Mozilla\Firefox\Profiles\[somefolderendingin.default]\

But I cannot find that anywhere. Could it be something to do with hidden folders? That's all I can think of. How do I find this seemingly non-existent place?

This should be easy but I'm stuck. Anyone know something I don't?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 09:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another islamic triumph!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 09:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not rape if she's dead. How many times do people have to be told? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Witcher 3] I don't play gwent. There are some quests I need to complete with the console as a result but I'm not sure what the instructions mean </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 09:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't even remember how to play. So I found the console commands, no problem. But I don't understand what it means by:

"Win current gwent game with specified number of power points."

The command is "winGwint(#)" - I'm not sure how to proceed. Can anyone tell me what that line means? I assume I enter some number -but what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 08:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking great racing, too. The cars are very evenly matched. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 08:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit's fucked cunt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 07:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't call me that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 07:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought so. Thanks for that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 07:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you get stung that many times, does one sting hurt more than the rest and you focus on that or is just general agony? I've always wondered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 05:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you 'recondition' onions? I never thought I'd read those two words together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 05:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These drugs act on different receptors in the brain. They therefore have effects that are markedly different in terms of physical pain management and conditions like anxiety.

Yes, they can have overlapping areas of effectiveness but they are fundamentally different and that would be seen in more long term use. 

You don't keep giving benzos for extreme levels of pain (say, severe burns or pain from cancer) over an extended period when opiates are known to target the receptors responsible for that pain. Yes, the benzos might help in the short term because they sedate you, among other things but that's not their primary function with regard to pain management.

Likewise, there's no good reason to prescribe strong opiates for anxiety and panic attacks, etc. Yeah, the opiate will knock you around a bit and help in the very short term but for long term management of that type of thing, you use the benzos. 

Both opiates and benzos can have very severe withdrawal symptoms. And you can actually die from benzo withdrawals (like you can with alcohol). That's what a doctor has to weigh up when prescribing these things over a long time. Is it acceptable for the patient to become dependent on the medication. Can they taper off it if and when the illness subsides? 

Also: Prescribing drugs to treat something they are not meant to is called off-label use. It is very common and not illegal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1988 turbo S - trying to find the clutch slave cylinder without much luck </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got some sort of clutch problem where the pedal has either got almost zero play (compared to a few mm normally) and/or it wants to spring back up towards the driver. 

The clutch itself engages and does not slip under heavy acceleration so I went and got a new master and slave cylinder, hoping that might help.

I can easily find and access the master cylinder but the slave is nowhere to be seen. I'm suspecting the starter motor may be in the way. Does anyone know?

Also, it's a 952 (which means it's right hand drive). Is that going to make any difference? I'm pretty sure it's not on the driver's side in my situation.

Anyone got any ideas on this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I've been trying but no, I can't find anything at all in the surrounding area where others have said to go. Just nothing at all. It's getting frustrating. I've searched a pretty large area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's bad but I didn't even come close to enduring what some of the others had. Terrible things. Terrible for the families, too. There comes a point where you see someone and you know it's over. But what do you say? What do you do? Hope for a miracle or something? 

Spending even a couple of days in the paediatric wards is a real eye opener. It's sickening, really. I was lucky in that I come from a good home and my parents could take turn staying at the hospital with me while the other worked. Some families are fucked up to start with and *then* they get a gravely ill child. 

It's hard for them. I remember seeing some people who could not afford (or had to wait for) an automatic ventilating machine for their child who could not breathe. Someone had to manually squeeze a bulb 24 hours a day just so they could breathe. Who knows how long they had to wait for the machine? That's the sort of thing people don't think about when they donate money to the various charities. It's stuff like that they'll never see. I wish people would understand things like that.

But anyway, thanks for the kind words. It's caring people who who give a shit that made lives like my own a bit better at times. And for that, I am truly thankful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 03:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks man. I did look. But all I found were a bunch of commands and not how to implement the console stuff without installing weird shit to do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you guys for real? This guy was shouting that, with a knife, in public and you want to dismiss it as a misunderstanding? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy living fuck I hope that hurt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why kill him? That would be bad, no? People can learn a lesson. Some just take more encouragement than others. It's well documented. He could come out a model citizen - albeit with a few rusty joints and a severe attitude change. He's only human, after all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, so it looks like a standard roller. This is the pic I am looking at:

https://www.picclickimg.com/d/l400/pict/331621610232_/GIZEH-70mm-Plastic-Cigarette-Tobacco-Rolling-Machine.jpg

You have the left hand side of this pic facing to you.

Pull the rollers apart and put in the filter and tobacco. Or just tobacco. Keep that side facing you.

Now, push the rollers together to trap the tobacco. You will have to experiment with how much you put in. Some rollers do both fat and thin cigarettes. There will be a tab on the left hand side for that (could be RHS, you will work it out).

Put your thumbs on the roller closest to you and pull DOWN. Rotate once or twice but no more.

Keep the rollers together and insert the paper - gum side up and facing you. Roll it down and lick the gum. Rotate (downwards) once or twice.

Pull apart the rollers and there it is. I have used a few different types of these and they are all very similar.

Now, learn to roll with your fingers. It's faster and easier. You'll fuck it up the first few time but you'll be amazed what you can do when you really need a smoke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, that's WAY too easy for us and him. Let's delve into the truly disturbing. A realm he opened. For no good reason. Something that he bought upon himself. Let him hear his own screams echo against the cold walls. Let him feel the hopelessness, the futility of begging. I wonder what promises he would make, just to make it stop? Let him wonder when we will tire of this sick and horrible game. Let's parade his broken and mangled body for the victims and their loved ones - if they can stomach it. 

We'll take turns, lest it affect us in the same way. We wouldn't want *that*, would we?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Morals mean nothing to me in a case like this. I'm not the one who tortures people for fun (not information or anything important - just for fun). You can't seriously expect such a 'person' to be treated with any kind of dignity. With any kind of respect. Mercy. No, those things be damned. He dug his own grave. He must lie in it, as he forced others to. Perhaps you could get a half-arsed "sorry" out of him. Everyone cracks at some stage. Why not find his limit? And go a bit over it, of course... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I knew. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget this is only one instance of the suffering he inflicted. How many other instances were there? The mind boggles. Yes, I genuinely think some lessons need to be learned. Who knows? He might come out with a view to help people instead of hurting them. And if he doesn't, well there's nothing much lost, is there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't say. I don't actually know the answer. Perhaps ask someone if phenergen might help? Dunno what you guys call it. But at the same time, a bit of itching isn't all that bad. You've only got one hit each so just try it out. 

Pethedine and morphine made me extremely nauseous. Well enough to ruin the high. Oxy wasn't that bad for me at all. Results may differ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 420? Go blaze it, ya seppo cunt. WTF is that shit? A fucking wizard's pipe from Harry Potter or some shit? Pull yer head in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, they form a triangle, which resists flexing to the best degree. The tubes are sized accordingly. A triangle is exceedingly strong. They may look very thin but there is most likely a generous margin of safety there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could at least get the whole car in the shot. But I dunno, I'm not photography expert. I just know what I like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your guess is as good as mine. And I'm thinking some 'artistic bullshit', if you know what I mean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't get the Turkish tobacco, from what I have read. Dunno why. Try a proper tobacconist. Were are you? I used to go to a place in Adelaide that had all sorts of things I'd never seen, as well as being able to blend your own from the various jars he had. Look for a big city and find the tobacconist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although I disagree with refusing warranty on something the car is programmed to do, your brother is a fucking halfwit. And you should have cut him loose. But still, this should not have been removed by fuckwit mods. So I guess we are were we are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although I disagree with refusing warranty on something the car is programmed to do, your brother is a fucking halfwit. And you should have cut him loose. But still, this should not have been removed by fuckwit mods. So I guess we are were we are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So be it. Although I don't see how. Why not smash their elbow 25 times with a hammer and see if they change their tune? We can move on to the genitals, after that... Worth a try, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then they need to be taught why you don't do thing like that. Verbal instruction won't do it. Moral guidance won't do it, either. They have been exposed to countless heartbreaking things, like the rest of us. They not only failed to see it was wrong, they actively sought to do it to others. And in my view, the only lesson that will teach them is repetition of their own actions - on themselves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go look up the oral bioavailability before you bother insufflating. Might not even be worth it. Especially if you are not used to it. I've always found oxycontin makes me itch like a bitch. It's pleasurable but annoying at the same time. You may also have problems with nausea. Did they give you an anti-emetic (like they should) when you had opiates in hospital?

You're probably gonna get a reasonable buzz from it, given your history of not using it habitually and it not being extended release. It's different for everyone. Just suck it and see.

I must say pethedine (which I think you Americans call dilaudid) was the absolute best. Had it multiple times for kidney stones and morphine was garbage, in comparison. And for some reason, they don't even keep it in hospitals here in Australia anymore. Fucking weak as piss cunts. Maybe someone enjoyed themselves 'too much' when they were in agonising pain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much did they start with? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see it all the time, terrible efforts at unusual angles and aspects. Like taking a picture of a headlight and you can't see the rest of the car, for example. People are trying too hard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And there you go. You said it - Christians don't really follow their own religion. Islam is by far the worst in terms of scriptures and actual adherence to those teachings. Why can't they all be confined to their own area, so the rest of us don't have to put up with them? Trump tried and failed. I hope the next guy succeeds. I really do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking hell - Poland always cops the shit, doesn't it? They're always in the wrong place at the wrong time both in reality and in the possible future. What did they ever do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He deserves to be in prison with only one rule - you can't kill him. Do anything but actually finish him. Fair's fair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno about anyone else but I'd have no problem whatsoever with doing what he did to her, to him. And broadcasting it for all to see. Cunts like that need to learn. The hard way. If that makes me 'just as bad', so be it. Fucking jesus, my mind is spinning right now. People like that need their own medicine and I won't hear any different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could also make your own with posterazor. You can have a really big picture and set the printer to print it out in pieces. depending on how good your printer and skills are, you could make something pretty nice.

http://posterazor.sourceforge.net/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck's sake. I could come up with something better than that and I'm not even into science fiction. Weak as piss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would they really be using high voltage stuff? Why? What difference would it make? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to have a massive Marlboro McLaren one of Michael Andretti. Similar to this:

http://farm4.staticflickr.com/3399/4646617207_6129641db8_z.jpg

It was huge - about 1.8 m long and maybe 0.9 m high. It was awesome. It had the Marlboro logos and everything. I swapped my big Smashing Pumpkins poster for it and I reckon I got the better deal.

On the other side was Dick Johnson Racing with the V8 Ford at Bathurst but it was a drawing not a photo. It had all the Peter Jackson/Ford logos and livery.

Some utter cunt stole it when I was out. I never did work out who. Hope they took good care of it.

Depending on how much you are willing to spend, perhaps you could go to a professional printers and get them to print your favourite picture in the style you want. Get it laminated, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why only 3/4 of it and why the stupid aspect ratio? Why must people do this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck it would be funny to watch the day he forgot to unlock it. Almost worth camping out for. If it wasn't -20 C. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The girl I loved. The rest be damned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mainly worked with titanium, nickel and zinc (inorganic processes). The money was good but that shit is boring to me. I really want to do something like you are. Real research. Real chemistry (in my personal opinion). If I did it once, I suppose I can do it again.

Hope your new career progresses nicely. You certainly sound like you know what you are doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, stop it. ISIS and the "moderate terrorists" would never have existed if it weren't for an illiterate warlord called mohammed. Islam is fundamentally fucked. People who want to follow in his footsteps are fucked in the head. None of them have any redeeming qualities. Absolutely none. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pirated Witcher 3. Console commands don't work. What can I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a pirated .iso I got ages ago. Just started playing again. Got some bugged quests I need to fix but I quickly found that the console commands can't be accessed. Pressing ~ does nothing at all. Can this be fixed or do I just have to live with it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a chemical engineer. Yes, I love my science! I just started doing a chemistry degree because unfortunately, we did next to no real chemistry at uni. Only the basics. I did more chemistry in my final year project than most of the others in my year and I loved it. The others were concerned mainly with physical separations, which are not so exciting for me. 

I was studying the catalytic and pyrolytic destruction of a couple of the ozone depleting compounds - R-22 (chlorodifluoromethane) and Halon 1211 (bromochlorodifluoromethane). I found it super interesting and rewarding. But when I got to the real world I was working with much more mundane stuff. 

So, yeah I get what you are saying. Tellurium just seems interesting to me for some reason. I guess everyone has their personal interests within their own area. I can't wait to do some proper organic synthesis. I've been reading about them since I stole a book from high school (I gave it back).

Thanks for the comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only because they have to. If they don't, they'll be next. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing that so little mass makes such a massive difference. And they can pinpoint where it's going wrong. Truly impressive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, I don't know those terms. I don't think this course is that sophisticated (yet). The only real choices I have are paired t-test (dependent samples) and two sample t-test (independent samples). 

I'm thinking these are paired samples as they are tested at one point and then the same subjects are tested again at the end of the study. For us, the ANOVA (we don't touch ANCOVA) test is only for more than two samples. 

Technically, this is a really simple question. This course is simply interpreting the stats given, we never calculate them ourselves. I'm just not very confident. It all seems so ambiguous to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll try but I'm pretty sure I did the initial steps and then continued with another quest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 11:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno if they still use it but I used to get cyclophosphamide - a.k.a nitrogen mustard. Sulfur mustard is used in warefare. Nitrogen mustard is worse but less stable. It irritates the mucous membranes, sometimes resulting in blisters at even chemotherapy doses. I would have to say it is one of the nastiest compounds I have ever encountered and it went straight up my arm. In those days the only form of anti-emetic available to us was maxolon. That's it. It didn't work most of the time. The pain from constantly throwing up was unbearable. I couldn't eat proper food for weeks at a time. 

And the other drugs were also horrendous. Vincristine gave me permanent nerve damage in my legs. When I used to get it, they would shot it up and I would be paralysed from the waist down for a good while. They had to carry me or push me in a pram to wherever I was going. It was also embarrassing for a kid to be in a pram at 8 years old. 

Then you had actinomycin and adriamycin. Almost as bad as n-mustard. As soon as that shit was going up my arm, I would often projectile vomit before the shot was finished. One time, the doctor missed the vein and squirted the tiniest bit into the surrounding flesh on the back of my hand. I thought I would surely die. The back of my hand was like half a tennis ball. I cried for hours.

I got off lightly, compared to others, though. They have problems with almost every part of their bodies, in various combinations. They still invite me back to the hospital to do follow up tests on the few subjects who lived - i.e. me. I have one leg shorter than the other, severe nerve damage of the lower peripheral nerves, a scarred bladder from radiotherapy and stunted growth, in general. 

And yeah, I feel like I've wasted my life. But that was because I spent most of it trying to forget. If it were not for my family I would have simply shot myself long ago. But I can't do that to them. That would be even more cruel than what has already happened. So what am I to do? I just sit here and exist. I went back to uni this year to find something to do and I have nothing but self doubt. Everything seems like it will fail me. A constant and unending sense of impending doom. Every little thing seems like a huge deal - like it will snowball into something even worse. I wouldn't wish it upon anyone. It is pure misery.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 11:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's great for mild analgesia - exactly what it's for. After that, I couldn't be bothered with it. Maybe it's the promethazine they're after. A synergistic effect with codeine, perhaps? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 10:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just keep saying what you want to say. Someone will always try and tell you you're an idiot or something. I get it all day, every day. Say something controversial and someone *will* bite. Learn to suck it up. Give it back to them just as hard as they give it to you. Then forget about it because arguing on the internet is retarded.

Reddit is a great place to practice this. No one knows who you are. No one really cares. You can make as big a fool of yourself as you want. What's gonna happen? Some other anonymous dick is going to say something nasty? Big deal. Use this shithole to practice giving and taking insults. It's fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 10:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's not working you should be happy. Don't play this game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 10:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the larger prop has more 'purchase' on the water. It can impart a greater total force, even at lower speeds. You can run a larger prop with less pitch and it can be as effective or more than a smaller prop with much more pitch. That is my understanding of the matter. After that, I'm pretty much out of my league to make further comments. 

Perhaps they are factoring in fuel efficiency and like to run an engine at lower revs? I'm not really sure. It's an interesting problem that I have not really thought about before. I'm sure you'll be able to find a better answer somewhere but I'm not sure where. Is there a boating subreddit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 10:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm no fan of Jalopnik but this is a reasonable list:

http://jalopnik.com/the-ten-most-ingenious-f1-cheats-ever-1465111260 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 10:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're basically trying to prevent the prop from cavitating. A given prop can only spin so fast until it cavitates. Then you need a bigger one. But the bigger one has to spin slower because the leading edge at the periphery is going to start cavitating at a slower shaft speed. 

Basically the shaft speed/angular speed has to coincide with the diameter of the propeller. You're probably aware that the increasing angular speed for a given diameter results in a larger actual speed at the blade tips. As in, if you have a circle of radius x and a circle of radius y (where y is greater than x), the peripheral speed of the second circle will be faster than that of the first one for the same shaft speed. I've butchered this answer pretty badly but I think yu can get what I'm saying.

You might like to look through this thread I found:

https://www.reddit.com/r/askscience/comments/2dr7oz/why_is_a_boat_propeller_so_small_compared_to_the/

Also:

http://www.thehulltruth.com/boating-forum/107304-how-does-prop-diameter-help-hurt-performance.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 09:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you get a fucking brow implant? That's some neanderthal shit right there. Jesus christ, you could headbutt your way into a bank vault. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 09:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just keep marking all the emails as spam. Hopefully it ends up getting flagged all over the place. Well, I'd like to think it works that way but it probly doesn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 09:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like the smell of stale piss when you walk into an unfamiliar RSL club. Mmmmm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 09:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus christ, it's hideous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 09:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The smaller the prop the faster it spins, usually. It's geared, so running a diesel will make little difference. If you have a small vessel with a large displacement, perhaps the optimum solution is multiple props? But I guess the real question is how fast do you want to go and how much fuel can you stow on board? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 09:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you can just quit any time you want? Yeah, I used to think that, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 09:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much more does it weigh than it should? 5%? 20%? 3 kg? 6 kg? What sort of margin is being discussed?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Witcher 3] Pretty sure I've got a bugged quest. Any way to save it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 09:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [PC] It's "The Mutual of Beauclair's Wild Kingdom", where you find a site where a basilisk has killed some people and you are to investigate it. I was on my way somewhere else and only did the very first bit. Now, when I return I cannot find any evidence or a trail to follow. Been searching for an hour and nothing.

This thread describes the bug and it seems to be what is happening for me. What am I supposed to do? Can I use console commands or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 09:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you consider tiny? 5%, 1%, 0.5%? Whatever it is, the larger community are generally complicit. Where do these arseholes sleep at night? Someone else knows what they're up to and doesn't report them. Which communities are sheltering them? I wonder... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 08:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, yes, we keep saying it's a tiny minority? I thought so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 08:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Codeine is fucking weak, full stop. It's garbage. You get a very mild buzz the first few times and it's over. Can't understand why you seek out such large quantities. The effect plateaus at a moderate dose, anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 08:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Desperate times call for desperate measures. What do you realistically suggest? Repeat the mantra that it's ''only a tiny minority'' until the whole thing comes to a very, very ugly head? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 08:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Germans have taken steps to ensure Nazi ideology is not celebrated. It's outright banned to do so. Yelling sieg heil and doing the salute can land you in prison. 

WTF have muslims done as a whole to suppress the hatred and violent tendencies of so many of their fellow believers? Next to nothing, that's what. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 08:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of the above. If they keep going the way they are, people will eventually elect leaders who will take a proper stand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 08:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the useless fucks are second and third generation and they still refuse to fit in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 08:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When they insist on putting their religion before everything else, it's hard to include them. How many times do we have to hear them say "I'm a muslim (*insert country here*)"? No, your nationality comes first, every single time. Your religion be damned. They preclude themselves from many things and then wonder why no one likes them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another islamic triumph!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucken oath. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Having trouble deciding which test should be used for the given data </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given:

"The data for scenario B revealed that for those on the oatmeal diet, the reduction in LDL levels was on average 12 units, while for those who do not regularly eat oatmeal, the reduction in LDL levels was on average 8 units."  

Q: What would be the appropriate statistical test to use to determine if oatmeal was more effective in reducing LDL levels compared with a diet without oatmeal? Explain why.

So, I'm thinking we have two groups and we are studying two variables. One variable is categorical (yes/no) and the other is numerical (I'm going to assume continuous).

This leads me to think a ~~2 sample~~ paired t-test would be suitable to study this data. It can't be ANOVA because we only have two groups and it can't be a 2-sample t-test because the data is not independent (the groups and measurements are separate). 

Is that correct? It seems too easy, like I'm missing something. Can anyone comment?

edit: Oops, I meant to write paired t-test, as the subjects are being tested before and after the diet. The data IS dependent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries, mate. It feels weird to even say it. I don't think I've told anyone but a former girlfriend and maybe one or two really good mates. But if it helps people understand why people like me are angry and disturbed, I guess it's worth the effort. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I remember extreme pain from having a drip in my arm in a freezing cold ward. Your arm had to stay above the covers. It hurt very badly. If we were lucky, the nurses would have time to warm up the bags in the microwave (most of the fluid was just saline to push the nastier drugs through). That was heaven.

I remember the day I was diagnosed very well. I was at a mate's house. I was almost six. We were skinny dipping in the pool when his Mum noticed a swelling/protrusion in my abdomen. She called my Dad, who promptly drove me to the doctor. Doctor took one look and declared a major operation was to be done that very night. I was terrified. I wanted to run away. But there was nowhere to go.

I don't know what to do to move on. I am trapped inside a nightmare. People do not understand what cancer treatment was like in the mid 80s. It wasn't very pretty, that's for sure. I still remember one of the first things I ever saw after waking up in intensive care was a young girl of about 12, who had just had her leg amputated above the knee. I saw her start to regain her wits. She began to realise what had happened. It was real. The panic and distress I saw will live with me forever. It was sickening. 

I knew another young girl, Nadia. She was about 8 or 9 and she was going to the hospital school, like I did. She had broken her neck. She was strapped to a board or in a wheel chair for life. Sometimes she would cry because she couldn't do fun things. All she could do was paint with her mouth. WTF do you do? What do you say?

I could go on but yeah, some things change the very nature of who you are. I take vast quantities of drugs for depression and anger management. They sort of work. It's hard to form relationships after so many have been taken from you. So, now what do I do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, a similar thing happened to me. We had a newsletter sent out every month. I don't know why I looked at it. On the back page was a list of kids who had died. And sure enough, there people I had been friends with on that list too many times. When I used to go Camp Quality there were several times I would turn up excited to see someone but they would just say he isn't here. And they didn't mean just not at the camp. 

My first friend I ever made (who wasn't from my local school or town) was Brian. He had bladder cancer. We met at the first CQ I went to. We were both 6. It was a great week. We got to do all sorts of things. We like archery. We said we would see each other next year and do some more archery. But that never happened. Brian never made it. And that was the start of a long and sad journey to nowhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I had not known him for long and a lifetime has passed since then but what I mean to say is that one day he was fairly normal and reasonably happy for a kid stuck between the hospital and Ronald McDonald House - like me. Life was not fun but it was bearable. 

We used to play with the army figurines together and sometimes ride bikes people had loaned to RMH around a little track - when we had the strength. Other times we watched cartoons. And then one day something changed. Something was wrong. He didn't act the way he used to. He just sat there. Didn't want to play. Stared off into space. I did not understand. I tried to continue as normal. But he was not his normal self. 

Soon enough, he wasn't around any more. I might have seen him twice more and then never again. My Mum had to explain what had happened. She was crying. At first, it did not register. I thought it would be OK. But it wasn't OK - that began to dawn on me after a while and the full horror set in. But it was too late to do or say anything. I never saw him again. Just like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. Didn't think of that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. Been a while since I looked at the box. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just meant that from what I have read, people seem to steer clear of it because it many compounds stink and it's rare and/or difficult to work with. I was just thinking it's a shame it doesn't get more attention. There's not much info available on compounds of tellurium, that's all. Maybe the stink is exaggerated and it's just not that interesting. I don't know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I don't think others understand. The feeling of you will be next has left me living 'on borrowed time'. For 30 years. It rarely goes away. I used to go to Camp Quality but I stopped after every year I went, the kid I wanted to see wasn't there anymore. And it wasn't because he didn't want to go... He wasn't there to go. 

I missed so much school. I couldn't learn properly like the others. I had to teach myself how to do things, much later on. How to write properly. How to do maths. It was hard. I felt like a fool. 

I still remember just being in pain and uncomfortable all the time. Those feelings still pervade into adult life. It's hard to describe. And who do you tell? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It just looks 'odd'. Perhaps heavy acceleration is playing a part? I don't know a great deal about GTR Skylines.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you think might happen? If you've been following the news, it's nothing at best. NK have no way to deliver a nuke to anyone but themselves. There will be no nuclear exchange. It's basically impossible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too much of the wrong type, more like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got some MonteChristo ones and they were fantastic. Almost as good as the full size ones. Guess it depends how much you pay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're on a visa for high school? Which 7-11 are you graduating to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My McShit shirt. Maccas logo with the McShit word in it's place. a lot of people comment that they agree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Needs moar boost, I say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lit? Don't bring that seppo lingo here. WTF? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too much, too soon. I assume you are talking about weed. Where I come from, we call it 'greening out'. You feel sick, paranoid and anxious. 

It will pass. You just have to work out your limits. I've been smoking for 20 years and if I have a break and then get on it too hard I will feel somewhat similar. It goes away after a few hours and a good sleep. 

Don't worry too much, just go slower, next time. Weed is like any drug - you can over do it and pay the price. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay. So now people can spend even more on their overpriced shit. Which feature will they remove next? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why so many do not take cannabis seriously. For too long it's been pushed as some cure-all bullshit. Fucking hippies and their save the world with weed crap is why people dismiss it. It *could* help with any number of ailments. Could. Saying it's going to save the world, the environment, the sick and the dying is just crap. Like anything, it has its limitations. Shit like this does not help get it legalised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the glass is half empty, it's twice as big as it needs to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean they are allowed to have a wheelbase of their choosing? Better make a rule that makes them all the same. We can't have teams choosing dimensions. FIA would have a fit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I do have a strong feeling about it being that way. But I still worry that I'm hopelessly wrong. It just makes sense to me for some reason. 

This could be a good excuse to attach a pressure gauge to a propane tank (or something easily obtainable) and see just what happens. Pretty cheap experiment, really. I doubt you and I are the first ones to wonder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, we're talking about blasphemy *in* islam and you're still carrying on with fucking nonsense. Wake up to yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but lots of things are extremely toxic and they are made by the ton. Phosgene, fluorine compounds, arsenic compounds, hundreds of things. What's so terribly hard about studying tellurium compounds, in comparison? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fascinated by tellurium compounds, due to their acute stinkiness. Why aren't people trying harder to work with them? They could possibly have enormous benefits if they could be studied with some way of shielding researchers from the smell. 

I really want to know what they smell like. As a person who doesn't find H2S and other foul smelling compounds particularly nasty in terms of smell, they must be something else. Have you ever smelled them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember many years ago a high school girl here in Australia died of TSS. It was all over the news for weeks. Just terribly unlucky, I suppose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hyperfighting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonder if he ever goes diving again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
