<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2840</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me reading is like launching a rocket. Getting off the ground is hard af, but once you're "in the zone" I can keep going for a few hours. Also, remove yourself for places to get distracted. No phone, no console or computer, just a book. Super great motivator.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in the Middle East, and all throughout school, our teacher would flip tf out if we draw a six pointed star. "WHAT ARE YOU? A JEW? DO YOU SUPPORT ISRAEL?" I don't agree with them, but the propaganda runs really, really deep. He government ordered, yes, ordered, our school to staple the pages of the holocaust in our history books so that we don't see Jews as humans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> subject2840 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dick

Tf why do parents call their kids this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 big things:-

1. Since now texting is our "normal" means of
communication, it's what we're used to. Texting is an extermely low level intensity of communication compared to talking. Tl;dr people can text loads but not talk to an actual person. 

2. You can talk to people as far away as Austrialia or America, but you won't talk to your mom or dad because Mr. German guy is texting you. Tl;dr families are drifting apart.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really changes based on wear. If I see a pretty fat man at McDonald's, I go smh, if I see a guy 3x his size on the road, walking, then I wanna be his friend. He's actively trying to better himself, instead of accepting the rut he's in. True respect for him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How to do a in the hand riffle shuffle. Takes maybe a day or two to learn, but looks like you're a professional poker dealer at the end lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy killed the man who raped his 5 year old daughter. People got triggered when he wasn't charged. He shouldn't have been.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since the majority of people(that I've seen) can't do this, I decided to voice my advice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well since I'm an island, I'm gonna make the other countries build walls on their lands that're facing me with their money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 06:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds awesome tbh. Y'all should become the chancellor of Germany and the other the American president. Best way to gain power quick and easy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 06:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a great teacher tbh  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 06:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bro I'm just naturally good at it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try to get an honest opinion. Like if you're into drawing, ask for what they DONT like and what needs improvement instead of something where they should say "oh yea it's good". That's why I always ask my friends, who're fine with telling me my work ain't good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When someone says your work is shit? The opposite is also true IMO. Keep at it until you become good, then show them your new, improved work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: You're not qualified to judge yourself </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gills for sure. Imagine just swimming from Russia to America lmfao the look on America's face </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Golden Age. About how the world was a grand and noble place, but has turned to the shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Julius ceaser. Release him with an army in Lesotho, watch as he takes over the rest of Africa and Eurasia. He'll be a better leader than any of em tbh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone who's nice because they can be and not because they have to be. As a male teenager, finding these kinds of people who're my age is extremely hard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can make a very convincing sound of a goat. To the point some people in school were freaked that there's a goat in the school not realizing it's a person.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yemen civil war. People get hyped about over watch but don't give two shits about the masses dying in Yemen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
