<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject322</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best way to setup Mac/Windows SNES Netplay? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 21:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 10:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch the video where its showing his skin tints. One slices a tomato, maybe his taunt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was the incest speech at the end of the Garret's wedding episode a joke, or sincere? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 11:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 10:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Context? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was dropped from the lobby of the game, lost points and am grouped as a leaver. Battle.net has been dropping a lot of players, and it's got to stop. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 01:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My connection is great, no lag whatsoever. But once in awhile during a game it'll say "You've been dropped" out of the blue! Impossible to reconnect at that screen and you need to restart the entire client.

Which takes a long time, obviously.

Ever since the Zarya patch I've been hearing this happen to other players. But this is the first time I was dropped in queue and penalized in such away! 

It's ridiculous, honestly. 

Who else has been having these problems? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 10:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sleepy Canadian here! I'd love for the code, as I cannot afford to sign up for Amazon Prime (Thus excluding me from Twitch Prime.)

Here's a hot tip. Sign up for google survey rewards on your android mobile device, and you should have enough money for at least one arena run every three weeks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 20:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Hulk Suppresses him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 08:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not going to tell you. It's super sad and you gotta read it if you like "The Hulk" and "Bruce Banner" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 06:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Incredible Hulk: The End </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some of the most useful, or important phrases to learn before you travel somewhere? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 22:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 18:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But with such small cool downs you'll be forced to play around her shield a lot which is an advantage in and of itself.

In the end though, underpowered or not,I've not had so much fun playing a hero in ages </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 07:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the gold at the end of a random comment chain rainbow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 06:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tyreal for sure, Uther not so much. ETC's heals aren't strong enough I don't think, Tyrande for sure is a fun hybrid. I've not tried Auriel so I cannot say, and Kharazim and Rehgar are both very fun!

Abathur is totally a support spec. He's not great, at the support part, but his buffs, his symbiote his shield and he can even heal. Solid little dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zarya is so much fun </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 04:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/vUAmg89.png

You see how I did a small amount of seige dps but I got the most votes? Well that's because there's no damage prevented stat. I was able to protect Illidan (An amazing character to play with, because of his life steal and the trait that powers up your energy when allies under the effects of shield do dmg) and Malf's heals got so much value in fights, because the healed under my shields.

I controlled the battle grounds with my R and dealt decent damage all throughout the game. (Not great) With my Q I was able to pick off fleeing enemies and poke for days.

There need to be more hybrid heroes. This support tank thing Zarya has going on is so fun. It's like playing double tank double support with only three heroes! 

Sure I didn't do much other than enable, but I enabled so well.  I've never had so much fun with a new hero. And I'm a specialist man! I rarely play tanks, but now I cannot wait to get this gal's master skin!

PS: Vulture goes great with base skin. Armoured horse looks fantastic with her storm skin. Base skin is cooler. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 21:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really unsalvageable at that point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jim Sterling reviews: Oversnatch a porn parody of Overwatch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 20:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 01:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For sure
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm starting a team. The "Dependables". You cannot ask to join you need to be nominated. I'll be starting a discord server. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 21:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 21:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats exactly it. If yiu have help.

But in thinking in terms of solo queue. You cannot count on your teammates to know how to play with Azmodan since most people don't play him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 19:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Towers of Doom and Cursed hollow, build his minions and take invasion at ten. Seiging wrath at 1. You break channels with your poke, including your minions, while your ult and your lieutenants push out lanes.

He's also amazing on infernal shrine for similar reasons, though his dunk is just amazing at stealing enemy shrine kills. (And getting stacks for hitting heroes is so easy on all of these maps.)

Tomb, he's bad on. It's too small for split pushing.

BHB he's great on for similar reasons as the previous, plus it's huge so stopping yoru split pushes really slows down the enemy. (Never push with your ult. Drop it and go to a new lane.)

I haven't used him on Braxis, though if it's anything like haunted mines he's a god.

Dragon shire he's bad. He's not great at holding points. Though he;s good in the middle for poking

Garden of terror, he's okay because it's big. But the objective is not something he's good at. Either defending or securing seeds.

BOE he's bad on. Belive it or not. The obj he's poor with and it's easy to make a rotation out of mid to stop his split push.

Sky temple, good because it's big, bad because he cannot hold points or help contest them as well as other heroes.

EDIT: Level 18 Azmodan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Misha the key to Kerrigan's Ultralisk? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 07:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 16:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is from the ddos attacks I think </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 16:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This helps make the case for a custom auto select </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA:Muradin prince increase and Diablo decrease coming in a week. Buy Muradin now, wait on Diablo. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 21:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 02:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She'd always be on fire if she was fully talented. You'd never be able to eat her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 15:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It vanishes once it takes damage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 17:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Azmodan: I think this cause for a *Heavy exhale* celebration...

TLV: Eric: I'm the MvP! Baelog: No you're not, its me! Olaf: Nordic sounding gibberish. E B: Shutup!

Raynor: Heh... Will you look at that.

Valla: Don't think this will quiet my vengeance.

EtC: Couldn't have done it without the band.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Avengers dumped The Punisher in a super prison at the bottom of the ocean before he joined his Thunderbolts team with Red Hulk and the such. How did he get out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 07:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 00:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah he wasn't working for them. He freaking became the boss of his own group. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 20:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah Cloud 9 is such a good character. Really tragic wish they'd use her more. And Hardball, I'm not even sure what's going on with him at this point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 20:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah? I'll be giving that one a read. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 17:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fingers crossed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 17:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I've been reading that. Its a bit of a bummer. The really set up a whole world of young super heroes with "the hunt" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I enjoy following the stories of the young heroes. Did anything come after "Avengers: Undercover"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 07:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Azmodan shines in placement games when your first 5 are cursed hollow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 05:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, Azmodan is a split pushing machine. Keep dropping his general into what ever far lane while you help your team poke curse. Try not to take it if you can help it. Your general will do massive work, and then so will your Demonic invasion. Buff your General and Demon warriors, and do your thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 18:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that's kinda stupid. I want to browse all kind of marvel things, but all that's turning up is that nonsense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone is spamming every mildly possible subreddit with some symphonic universe thing. Just search "Marvel" by newest and you'll see it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 18:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 06:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was actually a comic event called the Age of Ultron around the same time. Ultron sent armies from the future to dominate the earth. It was a play on the "Age of Apocalypse", another alternate future where Apocalypse rules. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 15:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's part of the curret roster of "New Avengers" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 23:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why wouldn't you want new people in your channel? How does that hurt?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 23:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ARAM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 18:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What people need tobask, is when will there be a reward mount for playing SCII?

We've got a preorder mount, sure. But so does WoW.

Every other game, Diablo, WoW, and Hearthstone have reward mounts. I'm not counting overwatch because of how small a presence it has at the moment. What should have been a great reward mount, the vulture, was hidden away behind the friend wall. Most people playing the game for months at this point already invited their friends making surfing the only way.

Use the legion fell hound skeleton and give us a zerglingount Blizzard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 16:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a level 15 TLV player, you can totally judge TLV for their deaths. If your TLV dies too much, he's not doing his micro, which is his whole thing, which means you're losing on soak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 16:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought you were giving him a score for his question and I was confused. "Does Alarak mean this score is sarcastic?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 18:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, Murky is supposed to suck, and to be honest, he can soak two lanes right from the start solo his wave clear is that good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 03:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, Ragnaros seems neat. And it's too bad about Cho. He's real neato. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have 1995 Dust. What cards should I make? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 03:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not very good at this game. So I'd love suggestions. Lore Master cho sounds fun, what are good combos with him? What other cards would you suggest? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 01:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can walk down the sidewalk and be aware when someone is walking faster than me and behind me, so I can move out of their way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 04:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh I just saw this on Imgur and decided to share. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rick and Morty meet the Avengers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 04:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 02:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohhh OP. That's amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 00:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know much about what's going on. 
What made it unwinable? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 00:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too! Its awful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 00:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, the MVP screen is super crazy laggy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 00:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, the MVP screen is super crazy laggy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 00:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, the MVP screen is super crazy laggy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 01:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all, looking for a Chair League team! Level 15 TLV </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] Someone has been killing people critical of the champion of free speech "Vladmir Putin" to sully his reputation, he has hired you to catch the killer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 19:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Ultimate Showdown of Ultimate Destiny - Super production quality amazing video all around. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 02:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 03:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh shit this is cinematic as fuck
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 20:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The title of the original picture was "My daughter commanding the kites"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PsBattle: Small child commanding a fleet of kites </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 17:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 16:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did do that in the comics though. Sam Wilson is now Captain America, and the New Falcon is Hispanic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 23:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah this seems solid too me actually. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Using skins, or similar themes, create a theme team, give it your honest rating </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 21:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zerg Swarm
Kerrigan - Master Skin
Zagara -Master Skin
Abathur - Master Skin
Dehaka - Master Skin
Butcher - Butcherlisk

4/5

Without a support this team is a little squishy, but the roam and gank potential is huge! Plus both Abathur and Zagara mean plenty of split pushing and soaking opportunities while the others do their good work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 14:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. And if you have a teammate with executioner, suddenly you become a swirling vortex of pain, which because of the slow enemies cannot escape </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People who are still using outdated technologies, why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 02:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I found a place where the recycling rate is 98.1% </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 02:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 14:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some guy in /r/personalfinance isn't a credible source of medical advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 14:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like this info, I shall look no further for anything that contradicts you, like rules. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 14:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Vaccines don't cause Autism" - Some guy on a twitter

Me: Well hot damn, makes sense. I'll take some convincing 

*Reads well written, if very misleading, article about how vaccines cause autism

Me: Oh my god. I'm Autistic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: If you want to be good at gift giving for EVERYONE, ask them to guess what you bought them, buy the first serious thing they mention. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 14:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 02:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 00:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She still had psionic storms as early as her first intro as queen of blades </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 00:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah, I just mean stylistically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 20:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah indeed. I also like fighting against Diablo, because I've played him so much I can dance out side of his range, provoke him into doing silly shit etc. 

But when there's a good Diablo, tearing into your backline, dropping stuns and putting you into sour positions, there's no doubt why you lost that team fight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 20:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Diablo is one of my mains, and I feel so powerful tackling people into a wall, flipping them over me, and summoning an Apocalypse to stun the enemy team. Even lighting breath has it's moments.

When I'm playing Diablo, flipping someone and pushing them into my team, body blocking them, using my stomp for that last little tick of damage, all those things make me feel like I'm living the Lord of Terror dream. (Even though I usually use the angel skin. Haha) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 20:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to take this discussion topic to just say how sad I am with Kerrigan's Character Design.  Not her kit, or how she plays or anything of the sort. The style of it. She should be a combination of Psionic and Vicious, but instead she's more like a zergling than a Queen.

Her stun, should start with a static ripple, and erupt upwards with psionic energy lifting your character as part of the stun,(Think her crushing grip ability in the Heart of the Swarm Campaign) her pull should likewise be static purple energy pulling enemies towards you.

Her leap, is fine because you want that balance of Zergy and Psychic. But I really feel like they didn't do her design justice. She is the most powerful psychic in the known universe and you only get one nod of the head to that in her underwhelming ult.

I love Kerrigan and I'm sad that she's been turned into a simple monster when she's supposed to be a demi god. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Since, in game, D.Va is a famous Starcraft player, I would love if Blizzard made all the "Gremlin D.Va" memes cannon, maybe even give her an in game tag of one. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 03:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I googled searched it for those of you too lazy

https://www.google.ca/search?q=Gremlin+D.Va safe=off espv=2 biw=1600 bih=775 source=lnms tbm=isch sa=X ved=0ahUKEwjSrJqK1rDOAhXFOhQKHc9VBdcQ_AUIBigB

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 23:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right off of Huron and Bloor is the "Fox and the Fiddle" free Karaoke everynight after ten. I go there a bunch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 21:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RemindMe! August 6th, 2017 "Birthday of /u/the_makaarina "

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 02:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be willing to help you with this idea OP, I came from that Ask Reddit thread, and this seems like a nice way to help someone out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 02:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Username checks out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 19:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> remindme! 24 hours </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is your favourite hero, who is your best hero, and who do you find most interesting? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 18:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Favourite is D.Va
My best is Reinhardt
And most interesting is Symettra. 

Shout out to Bastion, I love his concept and I really hope to see a video or comic featuring him soon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the story behind your username? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 02:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 22:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah

I'd love to hear some of his stories. Is he on Reddit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone in jail or isolated for a long period of time, what was the most startling advancement in technology or society you had to get used too? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 21:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 21:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But there's barely any of that either. It's literally Ironman and Captain Marvel being very polite to one another about their argument. The biggest conflict was inhumans vs Stark and that was resolved pretty peacfully </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 16:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just find it weird that so many comics are talking about the fight as though it's in progress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about Civil War II that might mean incredibly light spoilers, it's about pacing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 14:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tons of "Civil War II" comics are mentioning this "Big super hero fight" as though it's happening and everyone is fighting right now. But the main ones with Iron Man and Ms. Marvel, are just them rallying the troops. It doesn't seem as organic as the first one, where everyone was forced to choose a side immediately.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 15:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No no I figured it out! I designed a Rak'shir concept, basically, they fight in the middle the whole time, and you try to build a big minion clump. Then after a set timer, the clump all dies, whomever had the biggest clump wins. Who ever gets five wins, wins the game. 

This would make farming mercs and wave clear very important though.

This way there is no push to one end of the map or another.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 22:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no Cow level </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 21:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Killing your oppent's bases, and fighting in the middle to save your creep from them/kill their creep.

But obviously there are flawed parts to this, I'm sure Blizzard would manage much more masterfully than I. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rak'shir map(refined) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 14:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, so I wrote about a "Rak'shir" map before, and I realized the concept was flawed. I've fixed the flaw of giant minion clumps and here it is.

First, Rak'shir is a Talda'rim(protoss) ritual, where two highlord hopefuls battle against each other with psychic energies, hopefully forcing their foe into a pit.

The map you see this on in StarCraft, you need to push with your army, because the hopeful that you support needs your army's psychic power to win.

So too in this game, you will need to assemble an army with a value of 60 at the hopefuls before your enemy does.

Every time you assemble an army that size, your hopeful gets close to critical mass, and the first one to assemble an army like that three times, wins. Each time you hitbyour size cap though, all minions in mid lane die.

Each basic minion is worth one, there are several zealot camps (Three charge lots) to actvas merc, each one is worth three, your forts spawn stalkers worth two and your keeps spawn immortals worth four.

Eventually four merc camps will be unlocked that are hybrids, each worth twenty.

Then late game a hybrid behemoth is unlocked worth 35.

Three lanes, and like towers of doom when you take a fort it becomes yours, spawning for you it's unit.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 04:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah yeah just got mine
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 16:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I even busted out my old heroes smurf email. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I once dated a 3 foot tall model who played a supporting role in Cat and the Hat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 18:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was a pretty little thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 15:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HTML 5/Css 3 and JavaScript if we want to be fancy.

I can teach The first two. :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 14:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heroes never die
Murky
TLV
Uther
Diablo
Rexxar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think the first project we do, should be to make our own website where we showcase future projects, and project notes for those who want to learn from us. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 18:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 18:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be happy to Mod, I'm here to learn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Lost wallet at Pride, not starving just want a pick me up! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 23:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like it said in the title, I was out enjoying Pride and I misplaced my wallet. I've got food, but I want comfort food. Haha 

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 05:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leoric isn't a Minion of hell, he was driven insane by Diablo and hates Demons. He even has special conversation with Diablo in HOTS referencing that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 01:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Toxin Son of Carange has amazing art and tons of Symbiote goodness.

Then there's an Anti Venom Punisher team up that's a lot of fun.

The MacGargan Venom in the Thunderbolts (During Civilwar/secret invasion)/ Dark Avengers in Dark Reign is really fun too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 25 [M4F] Toronto - Looking to spread some rumours </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 16:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, hey clicked on my link did you? Dandy. 

My name is Tom, I'm 6'3 I've got two tattoos and I'll be looking to get a lot more. I'm slim, and so long as you close your eyes, an amazing dancer.

But, listen, I could go on and on about myself - Tell you about my hobbies like reading. How I devour novels within hours of buying one. I could tell you how I absolutely love day dreaming, or that I enjoy long, long walks (Sometimes both at the same time.). My favorite style of music? Geek Rock. Not that you'll hear it from me. Or how I was working with a rocking tech company a few months ago, Nerf Wars were one of many office hazards. If I was embarrassed about the fact, I'd probably try to hide the fact I like gaming, video and table top, but if someone were to ask me. I'd probably let them know. 

You may also hear rumours that I'm a fantastic cook. Not that I'll confirm them, but I'd be lying if I denied them. Haha 

Maybe I could tell you about how I love watching videos from TED.com, or that I really enjoy listening to comedians as I work? Nah. I'll keep that to myself too. How about the fact that I'm a huge comic book geek, and I enjoy telling people about all the easter eggs in the movie we just watched? No no. I might come off as too nerdy if I told you that! 

Ohh I know. How about that I love hiking and camping? A good beer, and a campfire is a good night in my book. Hmm... But if I said that, then you might start thinking I was a rugged outdoorsy type. Which I'm not. I just like certain things like that, I don't do them often enough for my liking though. 

Those are just a few of the things I'll keep to myself, let you find out on your own eh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 18:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but different cultures do for sure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 17:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They literally say it's an all women's group. There's nothing wrong with that. 

A group of all guys, a group of all girls, and a group of mixed genders each have different dynamics and behaviors.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The community has love for the artists, how about the musicians? "Now you're dealing with Overwatch" Only 775 views on this amazing song? We can do better /r/overwatch! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 04:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 16:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean? What happened? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 00:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did anyone ever PM you the gist of the "Magda dog killing room shitting" post? I'm very curious myself! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 18:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 14:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. I was hoping they'd team up with other heroes at some point. Ohh well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arkillo and Saint Walker, where are they now? Light Sinestro spoilers from like three months ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 02:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all. In Sinestro, Saint Walker and Arkillo teamed up to protect earth. Where can I follow their exploits? Which comics? Sinestro is the only comic I keep up with at the moment because I LOVE the yellow lanterns, so if those two are appearing in other issues, I'd love too see where and in what way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 13:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its amazing. And more suited for an older audience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 02:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Silverwing, Sunwing was the book with this plot, Firewing was the last one, Kenneth Oppel, the Authour, made a prequel Darkwing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 02:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Silverwing, Sunwing was the book with this plot, Firewing was the last one, Kenneth Oppel, the Authour, made a prequel Darkwing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 02:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Silverwing, Sunwing was the book with this plot, Firewing was the last one, Kenneth Oppel, the Authour, made a prequel Darkwing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 22:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm from Nova Scotia. Pm me your number, I'll text you and we can hang out some time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 16:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there, how old are you? What part of the city are you in? What brings you too Toronto?

I've played Dota2 quite a bit, but I'm more a fan of Heroes of the Storm at the moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 18:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well they attack move to your rally p point, and you could talky a hero to target him.

And I saw your design! Loved it, and that's why I made the swarm self replicating.

Because Karl and jaina would be issues for sure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zerg Swarm Hero Concept (Not Swarm Host) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 15:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, so the Hero is not a singular hero, but a representation of the Zerg Swarm. The character you focus on controlling is an Overlord, this overlord has a displayed leash range. Instead of a mount, he moves at 10% extra move speed, and is not impeded by terrain.

His trait, spawns zerlings over time, up to 12, that follow your rally point (Where you click to attack) within your leash. You click your trait to allow them to randomly roam.

If you cross over terrain without them, they cannot attack until they get back within your control zone. 


Your first ability is Frenzy, all your Zerg Spawns move and attack faster.

The next is fungal growth, an Infestor unburrows underneath you and launches the growth, rooting and damaging targets in the impact zone.

The third is Lurker. Spawning a Lurker that cannot unburrow, but will attack so long as it's within your AOE. (Meaning you can place a Lurker on an objective, and leave. Then come back later when it triggers and the lurker will already be there ready to fight.)

ULTS: Leviathan summon a Leviathan to replace your overlord for 20 seconds. Your swarm burrows during this time, other than Mutalisks and Broodlords that spawn periodically. One Mutalisk every 3 seconds, one broodlord every 5.

Brutalisk: Sacrifice all current spawned zerg a Brutalisk spawns with health dependent on the amount spawned.

Talents would be select one zerg unit each level to join your spawn ranks.

eg: level 1 2 more Zerglings, a Roach, two banelings.
Eventually getting queens which could lay down creep similar to Zagara and use transfusion to heal your swarm, hydralisks (Not hunter killers like Zagara has, so weaker.) Swarm Hosts etc etc etc.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 21:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I too would like to know, can someone bump me when an answer arrives?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 21:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd LOVE to do King Maker in Pathfinder if you're interested in DMing it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 21:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What time zone and day? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 04:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet you cannot let that hold you back.

Just provide your siblings with as much love as you can, and don't rub their noses in it when you become an astronaut president!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 17:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well this was beautiful and depressing. Incredibly well made, and will hit home for a lot of people I am sure. But I promise you, there are those out there for whom even what this video declares as positives, do not see as positives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 15:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, it's confusing already. I was about to reply that Damage Control isn't DC.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 15:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the best one. I'd love to see like one agent of shield per movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 15:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the comics, Luke Cage hangs out with the big guns way more than Daredevil or the Punisher. 

Daredevil if he crosses over at all, is usually with spiderman, the punisher some other street level hero. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 14:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did he? I don't remember but that's awesome
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 12:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It used to be a combo. You apoced, tackled, and slamed, and they'd land in the apoc as it went off. If you did anything even a moment too late though, you saved them
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 00:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has to be grave golem. The others represents heroes, which maybe not everyone likes. But everyone likes getting the boss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 19:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I was stating why I think the skin is a waste of a hero, it doesn't need to be new, but it should have lines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 15:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> .... And that's why I'm saying it's a waste </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 14:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah it still hasn't convinced me. I think the skin is still a waste, not because its a skin, but because it doesn't have a voice over.

Keep it a akim, but give widow maker some lines! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 06:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey dude, I had a super similar experience. It was night in like 1950s or so America somewhere, a suburb. I had a briefcase, and I knew I was a salesman. Like door to door, I also knew I was black. Don't know how I knew either of those things. It was just kinda like how you know your own race, and your own job.

So anyway, I'm walking through this suburb, like on the street for some reason, a few street lights here and there, and I look up and I see head lights, they get closer and closer and then I wake up, knowing that's how I "died" then. And I well and honestly belivie that that was a past life. It just felt so real. Not like a dream at all.

I should also note, I didn't believe in that before this dream, and I still don't believe in that sort of thing. But I just know in my bones that that is true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 05:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> D.VA is the most likely in my opinion, but she'd probably not make it in until after Fenix, because of death mechanics being a thing they don't want to dump too many of. (It's why we don't already have Fenix, because they really want to do a Death Mechanic with him.)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 04:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This would actually get me interested in Kael </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 16:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sky Temple is my favourite as the Vikings. Baelog can solo temples.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 15:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same mechanic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 15:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drop pods. 

Dropship grabs minions, they drop in drop pods on location </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 01:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, if you're up for that, so am I.

How do we go about arranging that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 15:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Sadly Skype still highjacks the headphones, forcing the audio out through my speakers. Making it impossible to do a skype call with anything running, and I still cannot make my headphones the default device. I've got no idea what it could be at this point.

Oh. And my headphones are not connected to the volume control on my laptop either. So I can mute my speakers, but the headphones stay at the same volume all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 19:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much! I really appreciate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 17:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh it is a HP ENVY dv7 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
