<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1863</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 13:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In another recent study, we assessed the pacing of 92,000 runners at 14 different marathons. Although men and women both tended to slow their pace in the second half of marathons, this effect was stronger for men. The sex difference was especially pronounced when looking at runners who slowed by 30% or more  men were three times as likely as women to do this. These results indicate that more male marathoners undertake a competitive, risky pace. They begin at a pace that could lead to a superb performance, given their own talent and training, but one that also increases their chances of crashing or hitting the wall.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL male marathoners are 3x more likely than women to start a race at a pace they can't sustain for 26 miles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 13:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 30-Minute Seder is Rabbinically Approved. But is it too short? Or too long? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 04:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 21:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.google.com/maps/place/Yap,+Federated+States+of+Micronesia/@9.5392038,138.0568507,12z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m2!3m1!1s0x677102151db03a41:0xfc9e5841872ab79c </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 13:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting that a study just showed that poor people who live in cities with [better social safety nets and anti-smoking regulations](http://www.bostonglobe.com/news/nation/2016/04/10/place-plays-part-helping-poor-live-longer/jaoIPshzgqiuaPPjUmL5SL/story.html) live longer than poor people elsewhere.  I'd bet those cities also have more trees. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 13:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zika virus was first detected in Zika Forest in Uganda in 1947 in a rhesus monkey and again in 1948 in the mosquito Aedes africanus, which is the forest relative of Aedes aegypti. Ae. aegypti and Ae. albopictus can both spread Zika. Sexual transmission between people has also been reported.

Zika has a lot in common with dengue and chikungunya, another emergent virus. All three originated from West and central Africa and Southeast Asia, but have recently expanded their range to include much of the tropics and subtropics globally. And they are all spread by the same species of mosquitoes.

Until 2007, very few cases of Zika in humans were reported. Then an outbreak occurred on Yap Island of Micronesia, infecting approximately 75% of the population. Six years later, the virus appeared in French Polynesia, along with outbreaks of dengue and chikungunya viruses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Only 25 years ago they feared even meeting together; now gay police are out and proud </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 13:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Zika virus infected 75% of the population on the island of Yap in 2007, after infecting only a handful of humans since its discovery in the Zika Forest in 1947 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 13:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 15:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair point. But if I think that it's fair to describe the parts as part of a whole.  If they were working on smoothing a gem that was part of a necklace, I could say they were working on a necklace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 13:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Next we need to polish the surface to an accuracy of a small fraction of the lights wavelength, so it will form the sharpest images possible. The mirror surface has to match the ideal, nearly parabolic surface to about 25 nanometers  about 3 ten-thousandths of the width of a human hair. Thats really, really smooth; if the mirror were scaled up to the size of North America, the tallest mountain would be one inch high and the deepest canyon would be one inch low. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL astronomers polished a 25-meter mirror for the Great Magellan Telescope so smooth that the largest bump is .0003 times the width of a human hair </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 13:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 13:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
In the human context, the signals carried by the large-diameter, myelinated neurons that link the spinal cord to the muscles can travel at speeds ranging from 70-120 meters per second (m/s) (156-270 miles per hour[mph]), while signals traveling along the same paths carried by the small-diameter, unmyelinated fibers of the pain receptors travel at speeds ranging from 0.5-2 m/s (1.1-4.4 mph). Thats quite a difference! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that instructions from the brain to muscles travel speed through nerves at up to 270 mph, while pain signals dawdle along below 4.4mph </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 13:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 19:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to a 2005 piece in Rolling Stone magazine, When Rahm was a boy, his mother forced him to take ballet lessons, and he threw himself into it with the same intensity he would later bring to politics, winning a scholarship to the Joffrey Ballet As part of a negotiation with his mother, he turned down the ballet scholarship but agreed to attend Sarah Lawrence College, which has a strong dance program. He continued dancing in college but also worked on the congressional campaign of David Robertson. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Rahm Emanuel almost had a career as a ballet dancer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 19:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rooftop solar prices vs. grid electricity prices mapped county-by-county </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 00:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why So Many Americans Think Theyre #Blessed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 23:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Anonymous hacked Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 21:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 14:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An interesting look at the medieval roots of something that is a part of so many lives.

in 1240, Robert Grosseteste, the bishop of Lincoln, used Oxford University money to launch the first documented student loan system. He named it St. Frideswides Chest.

St. Frideswides Chest was literally a chest. Bound by two different locks, with each key held by a different college magister, or faculty member, it resided at St. Frideswides Priory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
