<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2069</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it gets really old. The first game had down time moments. And alien isolation and resident evil 7 have pushed the genre forward, so outlast 2 is a big step back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Resident evil 7 was great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nier looks crap, persona 5 is a jrpg which are crap, yakuza not interesting, nioh is a souls rip off and i hate that genre.

You do know you are allowed to try things and not like them right?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im not hating prey. Im just not loving it. Its ok. Its playable. And nothing else out right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not feeling this game as much as I hoped. The gunplay is super weak </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but a game series needs to progress </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> French? Efficient? LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, thats whats disappointing. Im not asking to be rambo but you have no option but to die if youre caught. Id like some kind of way to fight, even self defense weapons like in the re remake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man, both outlast 2 and prey have me disappointed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Preys gunplay is kinda weak, like most arcane games. And i dont know why, im just not that into the story so far. Ill stick with it though. Its getting widely praised so this might just be me.

Outlast 2 is just one giant chase sequence. The first game had down moments where you could soak it in, which is needed in a game like that. And since outlast, resident evil 7, alien isolation have come along and let you fight back. 

Just two disappointments in a row :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol you keep replying too

And a little bet... how about if le pen doesnt get elected you admit 28 days later is action horror? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im doubling down on you pansys. Some crime such as rape, child molestation and brutal murders 100% justify the death penalty.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 16:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Le penn will never get elected lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 16:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ironically the nazis wanted a third reich under one banner. Hmm... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 16:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah after starting two world wars. Only took that and splitting the country </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 10:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah Germany is well known for its history of non violence </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 10:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the kid wont go, what the fuck is she supposed to do? Let him do whatever he wants and run riot? 

I can tell you from our school system in the UK, being soft on discipline in schools does not help.

Not saying beat him, but this wouldnt harm him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 10:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The death penalty is 100% justifiable in some cases of violent crime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absoloute heroes. These people really need a raise no matter how much they get.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And france still has had more deaths from muslims lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes point and click precision </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LMAO france has got brutally owned by isis  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absoloutely love my xbone and ps4. Both consoles bring me great joy and i think competition has brought out the best in both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nintendo fans are awful.

Literally the worst console for customers. But they can shit out the same old games and the fanboys will buy it. So fuck them.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well thats exactly why hes frustrated. Whats the point of playing if people can point and click their way to win? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol french cuck, you are spending your time talking about a superior british movie. French movies are shit and no one cares lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my favourites. Happy birthday! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No issue with this. Good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would you consider it having a "ton of action " to mean? Is english not your first language, or were your parents brother and sister too?

still cant trump the writer though can you :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they arent a majority. Do you think they would be tolerant if they were? LOL. Religion is a cancer that poisons otherwise decent people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But according to the left in the UK, muslims dont do this stuff! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL wheres your comment that matches the writer? Cant do it, can you?

You are breaking boy, i feel your resolve weaken! You have to literally produce danny boyle now saying its not action! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mark raised his head from his work just to see the door to his detective agency rattle open. Intrigued by an offer of work during this dry spell in between cheating spouses and fraud investigations,  he regarded the scrawny tall man with raised eyebrows.
The man looked somewhat dishivelled , shaking from anxiety and permenantly eached worry lines in his face.  
"Mark Carpenter? I need your services. Urgently. "
Even the mans voice was shakey and weak. Mark felt. a surge of pity and was sure he would take the case. It must be bad to leave this man a shell.
Mark nodded his head. "Sure. Shoot. Whats the problem bud?"
The tall stranger told his strange tale. Of elder gods and blood sacrafice. Of monsters who walk like men. Of evil. But one word caught Mark's attention above all else. Innsmouth. A town whispered in dark corners of the earth . A cursed place no one dared mention. Mark was no religious man, but there was nothing holy about that place. Mark took the mans number and gave him his card. He told him to come back tomorrow.

The man did come back. Marks office was shuttered. The new sign plastered haphazardly over the door now read "out of buisiness". The number the man desperately kept trying to ring was a dead end. The man knew his time was coming to an end. His last chance at help now an empty shell of an office. The last sensation he ever felt was that something was watching him from the shadows. 

On a nice beach in florida, the now retired mark sat sipping a pina colada. He often wondered back to that strange desperate man and wondered what happened to him. But then the pinda coladas added up and joined by teqila . He soon forgot.about his cowardice and how he abandoned someone in need.

But one thing he never forgot. Innsmouth. Fuck that place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone with crippling depression , i feel your pain. Holding down a job would be impossible for me, even though i "look" fine. My mind definitely isnt. People have such a fucking shit understanding of mental health and think because you "look" fine, you must be ok and a scrounger. Id do anything to just not feel like every day is hopeless and life is shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isnt that the point of democracy? To listen to all points of view, even ones you personally think are poor? Demonising people for feeling or thinking differently to you is a sure fire and arrogant way to ensure that your views no matter how legitimate will never win over the people you look down on or disagree with. To smack down others for different views is non democratic, and even facist. Thats why the term regressive left has come in.  I cant even identify as liberal any more because the super left wing have lost all common sense and reason just as much as the right. And UKIP had good points too. importing illegals  has lead to trouble in many western countries, and our resources being stretched thin doesnt lend itself to unlimited immigration. Thats just common sense. But you and people like you made it racist to even suggest that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL still waiting for you to match the writer saying its got action, fuckboi! Whats the matter cant do it? :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL well played </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cant lie, i never saw it. Thats pretty much a disgrace. I honestly thought they were honestly trying to pitch it going back into all our services including NHS.  Im not a liar, I dont even particularly like the tories, I just felt EU was doing more harm to us and other countries by enforcing laws and quotas on us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do I need to argue with anyone? I think point and click mouse and keyboard is lame. Im not out to convince anyone otherwise, thats just how it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a nerd! Wasnt using it in derogatory sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didnt see that before, that was wrong to lie about. I personally assumed it would go to all our services. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poor bitchcakes h, still havent produced anything to beat a writers quote lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 09:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hes kinda right though, its supposed to be a work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 09:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His commitment to selling is incredible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 09:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only if it beat roman to near death and came to finish the job with a booming "IM NOT DONE WITH YOU" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 09:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So is this a walking simulator or are there enemies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 09:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mouse and keyboard is essentially point and click. I dont see the satisfaction in it. It removes most of the manual skill of sticks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 09:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You remoaners all kind of sound the same to me, so forgive me not seeing you as independent souls when you come off as a hive mind

And again, please show me how many concrete promises were given about the NHS recieving all our saved money. Just one concrete promise, please.

And its not "personal preference", its "common sense". I would rather the money be used to fund the nhs, as well as police, emergency services, schools, etc.   Why would you put it all into one service when every service could use more funding? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 09:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/0/how-much-do-we-spend-on-the-eu-and-what-else-could-it-pay-for/

We pay the EU 35 million a day. Hardly peanuts, and much better if it can go back into our country

And again, give me any concrete promises in writing about the NHS getting all the money, please </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 09:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should honestly talk to her about that. I dont know if it will help your relationship but its gotta be better than keeping it inside </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 08:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Choked so hard his pants fell down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 08:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or is it simply that because you couldn't use context or common sense, you refuse to believe that anyone else could?  If you can show me one statement that promised ONLY NHS funding INSTANTLY, please do!

A suggestive comment is far, far from a definitive statement. As you pointed out with your own excellent example , "COULD" and "LETS" are not "WILL".

Where would you say anything was promised? Is "lets" suggestive or definitive to you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 08:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they are such shitty people why does your wife love them. They dont seem like particularly good parents if thats all true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 08:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its the stalker in me :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 08:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Credit to you for being an izombie fan! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 08:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was brutal. Most realistically horrifying scream I think Ive ever heard. She seemed interesting, its a shame she was immediately forgotten about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 08:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im afraid I have zero interest in d and d :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 08:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are we officially out of the EU yet? No. common sense .  I would assume we cant stop giving the money until we are 100% out. They want us to continue paying till 2023 if they have their way. Once we leave that shitshow, and i mean officially done, the money will be freed up. Youre  triggered and not thinking clearly. Youre mad if you think eu would let us stop the payment immediately with no backlash.

And "LETS put money into" isnt the same as "we WILL put money into", btw if you wanna play that game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It said lets fund our nhs. Ie some of that money goes into funding the nhs. It did not say "give it all to the nhs and nothing else".

And everyone with common sense should fucking realise the wider context. What, is nhs the only service that needs investment? Are you suggesting that? I certainly understood the implications, how did you not?

As a proud leave voter, i fully understood the nhs was far from the only service that could benefit. Schools, police, and other vital services could all be funded with that money. Nhs was the clearest emotional argument to mention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> who said it was all or mainly for the nhs? They said that money should go into funding the nhs. As well as the rest of the countrys infrastructure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Randall Flagg is in power, folks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Daily Mail are the right wing idiot version of the left wing idiots crying about brexit being the apocalpyse. Both sides are sensationalist bullshitters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your wife is so lucky to have you.

"Your parents disagreed with me politically, out on the street with them!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 06:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did but that story went too far into the silly realm too. I was hoping for more of a straight up less convolouted story, but the levels were already tied in to arguably the worst cod story to date </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 06:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crush you? How? You voted, lost and now we are leaving.

Thats  real democracy in action, no crushing needed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats fair. But i really thought the cut scenes were top notch and because of how hard they made it to get, i was disappointed i couldnt see the story thru.

I would love an actual cod zombies campaign, full story, like traditional cod. Nothing to do with the current zombies stories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hes not wrong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what do you suggest? Whats your great idea to make russia great again?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The lib dem part gave the 12 year old thing away </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would rather cosy up to Russia than EU. At least you know what youre getting with russia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Truth. Glad to see someone else who can see through eu propaganda </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The religion itself is toxic. All religion is really, but that one especially so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How has it failed? Its happening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I  actually really was interested in infinite warfares story. That seemed cool and actually seemed to make some sense. Cut scenes were great, great cast too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Elaborate? You mean nonsensical </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Holy crap...just started season 2 (spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought series one was good, first ep of season two blows it away!

That ending...wow. The scream as the detective is thrown out the window is absoloutely blood curdling.

The only complaint i have is her partner seemed really physically weak and is easily overpowered in the series. And when hes told about her death, he doesnt seem particularly bothered even though he seemed romantically interested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The easter eggs are too time consuming, convoluted, and just arent worth the difficulty. Its not even like its a decent story from the sypnosis i read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like a shit story too. Time travel?  Alternate worlds? Blowing up moons? Its like the most nonsense any "writer" working threw into a sci fi blender without any regard for decent story telling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In the Line of Duty, season one and two talk. excellent UK series (spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy cow watching this on netflix...so good. As a brit its nice to finally see an exciting british cop show thats as good as american stuff.

Thought season one with walking dead lennie james was good but holy crap the first ep of season two blew it away.

At the end of the first ep season two....an officer is thrown out a window with a chilling scream. My only complain is her officer partner seems very physically weak, and he doesnt seem too upset the next episode despite he had a romantic interest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very low completion rates because most people cant be bothered </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh i do respect other opinions. So fair enough. I mean i hate bloodborne so i kinda get not seeing what everyone loves about something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hand meat  is the only food most get in north korea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I was kinda scratching my head there, Praise be to whedon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What they need to do is Blood Dragon 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont even know who that is! But if it was witcher or something id be equally as nerdy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont feel the need to, if a game wants to try hard for me not to know its plot, not my issue. 99% of players wont ever see it. Seems kinda a poor way to do it, all im saying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Komplete Kunts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yes im aware of my massive contradiction :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you wanna tell me the percentage of people who actually have the easter egg trophies? Id guess a huge minority, am i correct? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well im for sure gonna give it a shot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes and thats the problem, its incredibly bad story telling when it reaches only a fraction of the audience on purpose </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But some of us would like a story without having to do the stupid easter eggs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only zombies with an interesting story was infinite warfare and the easter eggs still made that near impossible to enjoy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it coming to europe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I would guess though 99% of people who play zombies dont bother with the easter eggs. Imo they arent fun. And the story is just...shit. Infinite warfares seemed good but made it too hard for me to get into </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I must know her name </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cant believe in a thread with a smoking hot woman in power armor theres a buncha dudes arguing about friggin lore.

we are truly nerds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was sort of kidding but man I dont get it. the combat i cant understand people complaining about for one thing. I just dont see the complaints . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man....I dont wanna call someones tastes shit but some of you make it hard lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have rendered me speechless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cant be the only one who hates how stupidly convoluted the easter eggs and "story" are, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man....just....thats all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok thats something i can understand lol it is overwhelming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brutally rekt by the writer lol. Can you do better than that? Still waiting lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol i got the screenwriter to admit its action, you have wikipedia. You Got fucking destroyed breh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The  tactical, smart combat, the world feeling alive, the monster designs, the story, the quests all feel meaningful,  great skill trees,  epic monster battles. I dont understand anyone not liking it. I just dont get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He said a lot of action, im sorry, you got raped by the writer. And your idea was shit and you know it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He said its a ton of action. admit you got rekt by the screenwriter.

And your idea for a game really was fucking shit. Thank god that never happened </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will never understand that opinion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  LOL it has a ton of action, his words

Sorry bruh rekt by the screenwriter. U mad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Screenwriter of the movie himself

http://www.indiewire.com/2015/07/interview-alex-garland-reflects-on-his-career-sunshine-28-days-later-sequels-subjectivity-more-262030/

. 28 Days has tons of action, and theres something subversive about it. The Beach novel, in my mind was, in some respects, subversive. I dont want to make great claims for it, but I think 28 Days overdid that. In my mind, it was this sort of punk film. It had a punk sensibility.

REKT


Beat the screen writer saying it LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Screenwriter of the movie himself

http://www.indiewire.com/2015/07/interview-alex-garland-reflects-on-his-career-sunshine-28-days-later-sequels-subjectivity-more-262030/

. 28 Days has tons of action, and theres something subversive about it. The Beach novel, in my mind was, in some respects, subversive. I dont want to make great claims for it, but I think 28 Days overdid that. In my mind, it was this sort of punk film. It had a punk sensibility.

REKT
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drama hahahahahahah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao drama

Bitch please you just sunk your own point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
