<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6681</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 19:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks everyone for the kind words33. I had a great time with my friends. I had some cake and didn't end up purging either which was a plus. I checked the scale this morning, and it didn't go up which made me really happy.(:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today is my Birthday. Wish me luck. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 21:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey everyone,

Today is my birthday and so far it's been going great. The only thing is that I am surrounded by a ton of food, especially sweets, such as cake. I can't deny it without the people close to me getting suspicious. It's stressing me out a bit but I know I will be able to lose it all in the future. 

On a side note, I only have a little over two weeks of therapy left, and then I am home free to lose as much weight as I want. I just gotta keep up the facade until then. 


I'm a little anxious about eating "unsafe" junk food - please send good vibes my way.

Hope you guys are having a good day.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 16:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a male, and at my lowest weight I had a BMI of 15.4 and weighed 104 lbs.  To be honest, I didn't really notice to much of a difference in either size nor girth down there... most of the fat came from my stomach,chest, face and other normal areas. However it is worth mentioning that when you are that thin there is an obvious decrease in libido. I had very little sexual interest at the time.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 15:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look great! Amazing stats too!(: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 15:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am guilty of googling this in the past too. I used to donate quite often (I believe 6 or 7 times) not only for the calorie reason, but for the charitable reasons as well. The only problem is that they weigh you every time you donate blood. I was once questioned about why I was losing weight so fast. I had to stop because I fell below the weight limit to donate blood. Here in Canada it was 110lbs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 21:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm getting by... day by day...

**Breakfast** : Skipped

**Lunch** : Rice and Veggies (326 cal) 

**Dinner**: Peanut butter and Jam Sandwich (350 cal)

**Snacks**: None. 

**Total**: 676 Calories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 20:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can relate to this alot. It reminds me of a spoken word poem I saw on youtube a while back.

my ED is a trusted friend... it won't break up with me, or leave my side. It gives me comfort.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 19:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best movie ever33 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 00:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Without giving away too much personal info, I was diagnosed with a physical disease that will greatly impact my life in the years to come. This, along with other factors (eg. Childhood trauma, depression), put alot of stress on things I couldn't control. So I took control of my life by eating less food. Now, my eating disorder feels like a coping mechanism. If the voices in my head are constantly nagging me about food, It stops me from focusing on other shitty stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 18:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I finished my 24 hour fast today. It felt good to restrict again - but I can't afford to lose weight without worrying everyone. Only 2 more sessions of therapy... So today is a maintenance day. 

Breakfast : Skipped

Lunch : Banana, and cerial (450 calories)

Dinner : TBA

Snacks : TBA

Total:  TBA  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
