<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8986</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-17 03:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha off topic but it reminds me of some joke that ended or began as "Asian, black, or normal" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-16 17:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, yeah, I mean that's why I was put on it in the first place. That, with an SSRI were my first meds to be put on but I've had a lot of problems with SSRIs / SNRIs that I stopped and now am just doing Lamictal / Klonopin. Actually Adderall helped some anxiety (or anxiety-like symptoms) but I can't take it because my heart beats too fast. But it wasn't given to me because I was diagnosed with Bipolar, I think, just Depression... But since depression and anxiety are so highly correlated I just kind of think of them as the same. If one gets helped, the other seems to as well.

I've always wondered about temporal lobe epilepsy. I mean, I wonder if I get it because if epilepsy is just increased brain function (or so I've heard), then would mental disorders be considered under some kind of sub-epilepsy? Do you know more about that? From my googling, I never really found out how Lamictal helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-15 09:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My boyfriend had a rat and when he tickled his belly it would laugh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-15 09:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So would being asexual just be having no libido?  I've been on antidepressants and have had depression get in the way of my libido, so that's the only thing I can relate it to. 

Did you take testosterone to help it specifically?  Do you think being asexual is unhealthy? I think I've heard both sides of it, but not from a person who has been on both sides. Just curious! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-15 09:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone mentioned deja vu up there. That phenomenon actually happens more when you're tired. 

For me, it's when I haven't eaten enough.  It's so simple, but sleeping and eating is such a large part of living that it makes sense we need a healthy quality of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-15 08:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Multiples! Good idea. 

I should get one. My boyfriend has one but he gets adderall powder on his xanax. Silly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-15 08:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That just reminded me of my high school graduation a few years ago.  I was really depressed, but still smiled through all of it.  It was really tiring.  I see photos on facebook of me and I look happy but I remember feeling so depressed.  Holding a smile was like holding a bag of rice on my head (weird analogy but I work at a grocery store). Really tiring, but possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-15 08:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yours sounds more like [depersonalization](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Depersonalization) than mine did. 

You did mention you were tired. Lots of strange things happen when tired. In the end, though, I don't think it matters unless it happens often enough where it's getting in the way of your relationship / life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-15 08:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a time similar to yours, but also different, where I didn't understand the relationship between me and my boyfriend.  Like, I knew who he was, but I didn't see him as someone I know as my boyfriend.  Really hard to explain.  It ended up with me basically being afraid of him, because I didn't understand his motive when he held me. I forgot he was my boyfriend. It went on for a few hours, and it ended when my boyfriend gave me a xanax (my first). He said if it went on for longer and xanax didn't help, he would've taken me to the hospital. I ended up spacing on the floor and stuff. This was before I was ever medicated. Lamictal helped me a lot with this. I don't know what "diagnosis" it would be under, but I would have these fits of... unreality.  I just don't really get them anymore, and much much less severe.

After some research, I found out I think I was going through some sort of derealization/depersonalization.  I was diagnosed with Borderline Personality at some point, so it might be that or anxiety related. A lot of the people I discuss BPD with don't think I have it, and it's just anxiety or depression. I wish I knew. I wish I knew what is causing it, and why Lamictal helps.

Anyways, I have no idea if this is at all similar to what you're going through. 

Hope you feel better now, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-15 08:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going to clean now! After 9 hours of work and just finished taking a test on an online class, my sleeping boyfriend on the couch and I'm still going to clean now. Thanks. Just 60 seconds, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-13 19:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've actually found it cheapest at Costco. Unsweetened vanilla, I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-13 01:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never used the spray ones but the bottle I have is fine. I have light hair so I never have to worry about if it blends in or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-12 21:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use whatever bleach is on sale at sally's. I have a huge bottle of 40 dev and 20 dev so I can mix when I want to get anything in between. Say, 1 part 40 and 1 part 20 = 30. I use 20-30 for my roots. 20 for toner that needs developer, such as Wella brand toner.  There's more variety in that, but I also use Manic Panic's Virgin Snow too. 

Obviously, you have to get as pale yellow as you can before you tone. I actually went light pink before I went yellow, to have a break in between bleachings. It really depends on what kind of white you want to go. Silver-white and ashy-white, Wella is good for. Virgin Snow is good for a gentler white.  If you get pale enough, you can just leave in purple shampoo for a while but that might leave some purple bits (it ends up more uneven).  You can also mix in a tiny bit of blue to a bunch of conditioner and leave that in for a more blue-white, which is pretty stark. That's what I have right now.

The purple shampoo will probably make your pink fade a lot faster since it helps take out color from hair, so be careful with that, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-12 21:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I overspent and got Lush's dry shampoo but it costs way too much. I was just in a "I want to buy something" attitude when I got it. 

Yeah, you use dry shampoo instead of regular shampoo. So use it a day or two after you've actually shampoo'd. It soaks up oils, so I guess if you have really oily hair you can try doing it later that day.  You might be itchy because your scalp is too dry and you're using something to dry it up even more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-12 04:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really use heat products on my hair (I have white hair right now, bleached from natural black). 

Don't do anything to it while it's wet. Don't even brush it. Wait until it's dry before you do anything. When you brush wet hair, it stretches the hair which damages it.  If you do use any heat products, including a blow dryer, use a heat protecting spray. I got a generic one from sally's. 

I don't have curly hair though, so I'm not sure about that! I do know conditioning hair makes curls nicer (obviously). When I wash my hair, I use purple shampoo, a deep conditioner til the end of my shower, then a leave in conditioner and some frizz-free serum. It turns out well. I fake people into thinking I have healthy hair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-11 20:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pink will fade and doesn't have much to do with how healthy your hair is. The amount you wash it will make it fade though. I wash mine every 3-4 days. 

How often do you redye it? The dye won't do harm like bleach will, and will probably help it be softer.  Also, try adding some pink to your conditioner for touch ups in between dyes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-11 20:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depending on the toner, it doesn't do nearly the same amount of damage as bleach.  In fact, a toner like Manic Panic's Virgin Snow is quite conditioning. Although I'm guessing you don't want to go white. Purple shampoo works well, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-11 20:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try dry shampoo! It's helped my hair. Also having second day hair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-09 21:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recommend taking the bell off the collar.  I've heard cats are sensitive to bell noises.  Unless you have kids around that might step on him or something! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-08 08:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep! I work at Mitsuwa and I bought a box yesterday. Totally forgot I had them until now. They were on sale when I got them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-06 05:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know Lamictal helps lots of people, so just stick to it for a few months before deciding how you feel with it, I think.

Your brain fog might be from being hyper for a few days.  Your energy runs low.  

Good luck with it all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-06 01:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Until I reached 200mg, there was such slight results I thought I was imagining anything ever helping. I'm on 250mg and it has helped so much in terms of controlling my own behavior. Much much less mood swings, and not nearly as bad. 

I'm not sure I felt any effects the first month or two. Maybe there's something else that's affecting how your mood is lately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-06 00:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, I meant it will wash out as quickly, but the bottle lasts forever. [Here's a video](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=x3xvdnNvRcM feature=plcp) that shows how much this girl uses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-05 20:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The color is great!

Another thing you can do to save more money is getting a bright pink and diluting it even more.  When I diluted cupcake pink, it washed out so quickly. A bottle lasted me about 2-3 dye jobs on my medium length hair, but using a brighter color and a tiny tiny amount lasts forever. You can still get the same shade! It'd also be easier if you wanted to mix in, say, a lavendar. You have better control of the color. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-01 10:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ha! no problem. i'm just obsessed with my boyfriend's iphone. i don't have one myself :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-01 08:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A small tip is to have the camera back a little further.  See how your finger is still in focus? You can crop it afterwards if it's too small.  It should do the trick! If you have an ipod touch or iphone, i think if you touch the image on the screen before you take the photo, you can choose where to focus.

Also, nice nails! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-29 00:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My personal opinion is that old kimchi juice tastes better in a hot stew, not cold.

I'm guessing adding the hot pepper paste will help thicken the soup, if you have that. I haven't watched the video yet, but in the photos hers looks thicker. I've made her kimchi a bunch of times and it's kind of like the difference between her kimchi and makkimchi. The mak gets very watery and not as thick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-28 22:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious too. 

I can't imagine there's only a 10 second delay between running from the camera to the set up. Is it set for longer? Do you use a remote? 

Great work, by the way! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-27 04:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cinco de Mayo, right next to Titos, has great mexican food too. I keep seeing it on lists, but it's never crowded there. Whenever I'm there, I end up getting the tacos and salsa from Titos, and CdM's enchiladas.

Also agree on Apple Pan! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-24 22:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This is Alton Brown's recipe.](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rIK4DVLHf7Y)

These are just some staples from my pantry! I suppose learn how to make things from scratch :) [This](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iKKvvilb0vY) is another video I love on making beer bread, it's really easy. It's very few ingredients, so it's super cheap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-24 21:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure about what to get for your new place, but here's some ideas for the trip.  If you like meats, beef jerky or make it yourself! You can use Alton Brown's recipe that doesn't use a dehydrator. Homemade protein bars, nuts, applesauce, banana bread (I think it doesn't get stale as quick). Flour and sugar is good for bulk, if you have an oven in your new place. Pasta, cans of beans (good for chili), olive oil.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-21 20:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never seen Twilight, but I thought she was pretty good in The Runaways! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-19 22:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A cheaper version of that product would be to get some actual Biotin, I found some at target for a few dollars. That just looks like biotin with a fancier name. If you already have enough biotin / b vitamins in your diet, it won't do much though.

To take better care of your hair, use heat protectants and a diffuser. You might want to try things like "no heat curls" which was popular a few months back, if I remember correctly. Try having your hair air dry. I have very bleached hair, so I don't even brush it a lot of the time. That isn't for everyone, though. Don't brush it when it's wet! Your hair is elastic when it's wet, so it stretches out and becomes damaged.

It will also take approximately 3 months for anything to show. For instance, if you lost a bunch of hair from stress/poor diet, the hair loss doesn't show until 3 months after the event. It all takes a while for it to happen. And once the 3 months happens, it might only be an inch of growth. Your pre-existing hair won't change.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-18 22:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would happen when they're asleep. It's okay if they're in there for a few hours, but definitely not overnight. They get seriously lazy when they're asleep, so crickets can start to harm them and the lizard doesn't realize. I haven't heard they kill lizards either, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-17 00:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps you could start off with just saying you are attracted to girls? Maybe you two can start off with watching girl on girl porn, for instance. I can imagine it could be startling to have a partner talk about having sex with someone else, but starting with something smaller can be worked up to it. This is from a girl that has had successful threesomes with my boyfriend, by the way! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-16 07:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The student grade materials will be more diluted than artist grade pastels, but the chalk type are much more harmful.  The real artist grade stuff is the highest to pure pigment that you can get in any medium. I had a professor hospitalized from inhaling one of the blue pigments, I forget which. He was mixing it with linseed oil but it got in the air and he inhaled it.

The oil stuff probably won't work anyway. They're probably as harmful as paints and stuff, so it wouldn't matter unless you used them for a long time (like if you paint without gloves every day, holding brushes in your mouth, whatever). Pure pigments can seriously harm though, since you're more likely to get it in your system then things that stick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-16 03:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you mean artist's chalk pastels, don't use them! Some colors are seriously harmful, so you don't want any loose pigment near your face. I used them in a drawing class and had to use a mask. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-14 00:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a much more limited knowledge of Indian dishes, so thanks for the heads up! Indian food is always surprising in what's spicy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-14 00:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find the opposite with indian food! Red being a sweet syrup (like with samosas), but some intense spices with yellow and green.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-13 19:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On beer bread, I love [this video](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iKKvvilb0vY)! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-12 07:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm making chili right now and it's basically like that. Beans + salsa + can of diced tomatoes in the crock pot, put on cheese and sour cream. Great with potatoes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-10 00:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess it was explained above. I don't equate hedonism to Epicurus. I was just citing someone who was hedonistic but not in the way you were explaining. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-09 18:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That kind of looks like when they file your teeth down before you get veneers. I don't know much more than that or him, though.

quick edit: unless that's what you meant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-09 18:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about Bacchus? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-06 19:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (TW for numbers)

I believe those numbers. I'm not sure what is strange about them? I'm around those numbers (5'5, 100lb, 20 years old). I've gained 12 pounds since recovering, making me 100 pounds. I gained 20 at the most, at 108, but lost some recently. 110-115 is supposed to be my goal weight. It wasn't in the most unhealthy way, but it could've been from eating 1400... that's probably the amount I eat when I'm not extremely focused on gaining since it's been a year that I had to gain / more in treatment. I'm always trying, but I'd say 1/2 the time I eat less than I'm supposed to. As well, I've gained about 10 pounds and it has been really hard for me since I never went in treatment. I just had outpatient and gained ~15, but it would seem like I gained ~10 if they checked up on me now. Seeing a nutritionist helped me a lot just to be more comfortable with food, even if I do undereat (as opposed to starving myself). 
1400 isn't starvation, but can very well lead to weight loss.

I feel like this was a whole mess of numbers in that paragraph. I guess saying those numbers specifically makes me want to defend her, since I'm similar. Of course I had AN but I'm thinking about after treatment and the long term effects of that had on me.

And yes, I do understand it's reality TV. I'm from the US too and it's horrible! I think BBC does it better, though. You do have to question everything. I watch RuPauls Drag Race and just about every other sentence is a voiceover. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-06 05:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can understand both sides. I think I'm far enough into my recovery that when I see something like drinking so much coffee, my brain reminds me that that must feel horrible and caffeine-anxiety-ridden. 

And a strange side is watching the overeaters eat since I feel like I have to eat so much to gain weight. Comparing to what I see as a lot of food to what they see as comfortable and it's no where near the same amount. It's funny, like "if they can fit it in their stomachs, so can I!".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-06 05:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you think they lie about, just curious? 

Also, have you seen the eating disorder specific segments? It's interesting to compare disordered eating and an eating disorder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-05 23:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [These](http://www.snacksforlife.com/images/PC_Deli_Original_sRGB.JPG) are great, although it depends on how "healthy" you want to be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-05 23:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't watched it recently, but I do remember they did a 1 year check up on them.  They got an actual nutritionally based diet plan at the end.  A lot of the overweight people lost weight, and the underweight people gained a little bit.

I think the switching meals had to do with how ridiculous their eating habits are. Seeing it from someone else's perspective.

It is reality TV, though. It isn't going to be perfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-02 10:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell's Spawn... Pretty good.

Just wondering but how could "Guilty" ever work? Guilty Zombies?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-01 06:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually ctrl+f "cintia"... you look just like her!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-31 21:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, thanks! 

Would a B complex supplement work?

I used to take lots of vitamins, but got lazy.. but I'm trying again now.  Omega 3s (the "mood enhancing" ones), vitamin d3, and multivitamin.

I'll definitely come back to the forum if I see results :) I'll go make some quinoa now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-31 08:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That'd be great to know!

Yep, cooking helped me with my anorexia too :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-31 02:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, I'd love to do that. Driving even makes me anxious so I'll love to conquer that too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-30 21:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one thing that really bothered me was that "To Write Love on Her Arms". It reminds me of Invisible Children / Kony2012. 

It's a bit better than this image though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What to do over the summer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-30 20:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm talking about dysthymic periods more than Major Depression when I ask this question. 

My depression seems to get worse in the summer. I'm thinking it's because I'm not forcing myself to do things. Of course, it's a perfect time to go outside and "do stuff" but I'm kind of at a loss. Going outside is kind of stressful and a huge leap from lying in bed all day. I'm kind of pre-planning since I am busy right now with finals, but I'm afraid to get more depressed in a few weeks.

Also, I'm not looking for "watching TV" or "play video games" since those things don't really make me feel better, and I'm guessing a lot of us do those types of things when feeling depressed too. I also have social anxiety, but am learning to get over it, so I'm asking more of gentle ways to cope with downtime. For instance, cooking is a hobby I've gotten into that I think is healthy for me and takes up a lot of my time. 

I'm trying to figure out a work situation that won't hurt me too bad, either. My last job was terrible. But I know that might help in the long run. I'm thinking of doing some type of craft projects to earn some extra money online.

TL;DR What healthy things do you do to keep yourself preoccupied and not self loathe during downtime (ie during the summer when you're not in school)?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-30 20:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is one of the images flipped? I see an indentation on the top of one and the bottom of the other. Just curious, since I know the frontal lobe has a lot to do with this sort of thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-30 20:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, I skipped the part where she wrote what she used. I didn't mean to say that cheaper cuts than what she used would work, just that cheap cuts in general work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-30 17:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently I learned how Kobe beef burgers are bullshit. It's the marbling that makes Kobe great, as well as the fact they don't import it. 

That being said, I think cheaper cuts would work well in this recipe :) Just an FYI!

Also, thanks :) Will try this out in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-30 17:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few years ago, I saw it at target for an average size bottle for $3 if anyone doesn't have a Costco card! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-29 00:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would either add a background or add more white in the painting (probably the former), since the white is so stark. A light wash would be fine. I think it'd look better with a different kind of font, or even handwritten, because that font is "clean" and children's books don't have to be! It looks more personalized that way, too. Although, maybe it being on a white background makes it look too "clean"... 

The main image is great though, just thinking some small adjustments would make the image stand out better :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-28 05:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same thing happened to me, and I was already underweight. No use in eating, slept when I got too hungry. My boyfriend (before he met me) was extremely depressed for a couple years and gained weight, though. 

I've been doing my best to gain the weight back, 2 years later.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-27 17:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sucks because I'm in a long term relationship, and we used to have a great sex life. My libido got lower and lower, and I thought it was the antidepressants. Then I got off of them because I think the lack of libido was harming our relationship. So now I'm only on Lamictal, which shouldn't lower libido, but I still feel the same way. I think I feel guilty for not being able to have sex (it's actually much more painful now), which makes it worse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-27 01:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would probably plan out something like tabbouleh or pesto before I buy it. Something herb-heavy. But maybe that wouldn't work for these? I've never bought them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-26 17:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, I was thinking the same for a final piece in my figure drawing class.

OP: What size paper did you use? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-24 00:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love Starbuck too. She's probably my favorite, but she's been posted on here already. Six is totally hot though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-23 21:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's perfect! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-23 18:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, also, I've only just started season 4 so let's not throw out spoilers...! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-23 18:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What color are you now and what color do you want to be? For instance, if you're blonde and want to go brunette, it'd be much less damaging. I think henna isn't that harmful. Going lighter is harsh of course, especially from black. You also have to consider what layers of dye you've had under it. It's also much easier if you're willing to go short, although I'm assuming you already have it short already.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suggestions on what to do with my hair next? I have white medium length hair (naturally black). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-23 18:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been every color, and have had short to medium length hair. Natural hair color is black. I want long princess hair pretty badly but I think I dye it too often for it to ever get that way without fried ends! Which I have now... This is me [without my hair brushed](http://i.imgur.com/VFSXX). It was this morning and in my pjs, and I put a little bit of purple last night but it didn't really show. My hair gets pretty straight on its own when I [brush it](http://i.imgur.com/X5oE5). That's also right after I did my roots. This is me with my [hair up](http://i.imgur.com/R0QqF). It looks good that way, but thats also the only time I'm sort of dressed better compared to the other two. If it's cut short it [ends up like this](http://i.imgur.com/XlR0V.jpg) because I get lazy. And this is [me with blunt bangs.](http://i.imgur.com/Pyh0S.jpg) And this is [the longest it's been](http://i.imgur.com/tWWyl.jpg). Most of my hair life in the past 5 years has been an [a-line bob](http://i.imgur.com/LBwWX.jpg). That's also my virgin hair after I dyed it and before I decided to go the white I am right now.

So, my problem besides being bored with my hair is that it gets damaged (although it doesn't really show if I try). I want long hair but I also want some sort of medium-length style while I'm getting there. Or should I really just stick to short hair? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tricia Helfer as Six from Battlestar Galactica </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-23 17:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-21 23:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also on top of the vitamins, how is your diet? If you don't eat enough, hair falls out. A lack of protein can do it, since your body wants to keep the protein for the rest of your body and hair/nails are secondary. Stress does too. It also takes about 3 months after a stressful event for hair to fall out. Did anything happen before you first noticed the hair loss?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-18 05:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Added some blacks and things.](http://i.imgur.com/JEu2Z.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-11 20:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure why this happened to you, but a lot of things can cause that to happen.

A bit after I was on Lamictal, a doctor told me that it can make my orally taken birth control less effective, so I switched to the NuvaRing. 

Also, things like stress or not eating enough or whatever can result in skipped periods. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-10 21:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So true.  I get cheaper foods from ethnic markets but the cost of living in LA is pretty insane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-10 21:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asian stores are the best!  

I went to a Korean market and they had the cheapest stuff.  I got 3 bags of spinach for $1 that I parboiled and froze for later use. They had a huge variety of things to choose from, like what seemed like 20 different misos, 50 different kinds of red pepper flakes. It was pretty clean, too. 

Chinese markets are pretty good, but I don't cook much Chinese food and not worth it to go out of my way. 

Japanese markets are super clean, but much more expensive. Although, they usually have cheaper Japanese food (miso, seaweed, whatever...) than Japanese food at regular grocery stores. 

It's been great experimenting with different cuisines without spending a bunch on an entire pantry worth of new spices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-10 21:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I got chicken breasts (skinless) at Sprouts for $1.89 per pound when it was on sale. I bought a few packages and froze them for later. The baked whole chickens they have can be pretty cheap at night. They lower the prices so I see them for $4-5, and fresh it's like $6.

I shop at Sprouts largely because it's the closest grocery store to where I live. Go on Wednesdays and they have double the amount of sales. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-07 20:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think people might be judging the aesthetics because of other things in the picture. The hanging pots thing is actually a great idea. I housesit this expensive house with an amazing kitchen and there are 2 racks for hanging pots. It's just a more spacious environment, very clean and bright. It doesn't look cluttered at all. 

If the picture was taken with a higher quality camera, or if there was better lighting, or there wasn't the random objects in the bottom right corner I honestly think people would think differently. It sounds simple, but it's true. With better lighting, there's more depth in the photo and your eyes could selectively focus better. I'm totally photo-nerding, but whatever.

It's a great tip. I have my rack a few feet away from my sink and it makes me wish I had installed it over the sink now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-07 19:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm the same. I can't take it now because my heart rate gets too fast, but it did wonders for me. It calmed me and I wasn't constantly tapping my foot (or whatever). I'm guessing it's the opposite with people without ADHD.

On the other hand, people say caffeine makes people with ADHD calm but it makes me a nervous wreck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-06 19:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have similar tights that I got off ebay, look up "spiderweb tights". I didn't realize they were spiderwebs when I bought them though. These look cooler. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-06 03:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love BB creams but I'm not sure they actually lighten skin chemically.  They put zinc oxide in them, which is like that white sunscreen stuff people put under their eyes. So it's like a white layer on top. They blend really well though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-04 01:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been told most people's jobs after college aren't related to their majors they studied, not only in art, but in general. There are also a lot of jobs in the art field that people don't say is related to their art degree, like being a curator or art director or whatever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-03 00:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get jealous, but I've had successful MFF threesomes. I'm bisexual, so it was basically FF+M. The other girl and my boyfriend barely touched. It was all about me. It worked out great.

I found some girls via OkCupid. Just be honest about what you want right away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-29 19:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking the same thing, but I guess we'll never know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-29 04:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assumed thats what some people are going for. Kind of like that whole heroin-chic thing where you purposefully pretend to stop caring how you look. I'm thinking like M.I.A.'s hair. The other ombre look, like this one, is like if you had hair that got naturally sun bleached. Just different types of looks I suppose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-27 01:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the info! I haven't read much into it. 

And sorry to hear about your dogs :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-27 01:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious if you have a specific recipe / website you follow? I'm planning on getting a cat in the next few months. Do you refrigerate or freeze? I haven't thought of it for too long, but it seems like it would need a lot of space to store it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-26 07:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it homemade? I know regular raw prepackaged diets are super expensive. I couldn't find the website I saw this on a few days ago, but this guy probably lived in the countryside. He had an article where he threw his large dogs a pig carcass they got for free or something. That's certainly a deal I would never be able to get (being in LA). He said to feed them lungs and whatever they have out back. There must have been a bulk deal he was getting.

On the other hand, I was looking at homemade raw cat food and it included eggs as an ingredient (not main), which would make it cheaper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-26 02:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fed my dog Costco food, although in the end it was more expensive because our dog had allergies to it. He had to see a vet and get antibiotics. We now have him on a $40-$50 for 30 lb bag of food. It's a great start, but be prepared of the consequences, I think.

Another cheap option that I don't do is feed your dog a raw diet that you make on your own. I read that's about $.60 per pound. It just seems like a lot of work for me.

Beds at Costco are great. My dog goes through them every few months, and they have them for $15-$20.

I think for some people, it's impossible to not have a dog. It actually depresses some people, which can be more expensive in the future (less motivation for working, not enough exercise, whatever). It sounds silly, but in that way a dog can be "cost-efficient". But no one would ever ask "Can having a child be frugal?" or if there's a "cheap" way to do it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-23 06:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A cheaper alternative: making yours at home with simply a box fan and some air filters, [here's how](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rIK4DVLHf7Y).

I made a bunch thanks to the video, but my jaw started to hurt from eating too much so I had to stop. I have jaw problems anyways, like being dislocated. Store bought jerky is generally more tender in my experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-19 22:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about for breath?

I have no sense of smell, so it's hard for me to figure it out. The room won't smell, but if I go in for a kiss, apparently I smell. Mouthwash? Juice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-16 21:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, what color is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-15 23:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never been able to smell (congenital anosmia). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-13 04:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I drink Lactaid for calorie purposes. My boyfriend drinks almond milk (he doesn't need to gain) which is 40 cals per cup, and Lactaid is the same as regular milk at like 150-ish calories. You can always add more whey powder, or make it chocolate milk for more calories too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-13 03:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try your best to wait it out. I try to nap. I got pretty nauseous from being dizzy, and eating helped even though my body didn't feel like eating food. The last time it happened it was worst about a week after I stopped taking meds since your meds don't leave your system right away.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-12 08:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paxil helped me a lot with anxiety, but it made me sleep a lot (not in the same way Xanax or klonopin does). If you think xanax makes you tired, it's better to take klonopin at night (it lasts longer) and you'll sleep through the parts that make you more tired. I tried buspar but I think it just made me more anxious once I stopped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
