<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3259</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Women who've had a surgical procedure/s for aesthetic purposes, how has your life changed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 06:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was the surgery you got?
Why did you get it?
Has it improved or made your life more difficult?

Do you find people treat you differently after you tell them/they find out you've had surgery?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Women in interracial relationships, how did your families react? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 06:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm white and find myself attracted to men of other ethnicities. Only problem is my family (mainly my dad) are very traditional. Even if you marry someone of the same skin colour but a different background they get bent out of shape. One of my family members married a black man and they were basically shunned by the rest of the family. So I'm pretty worried that me bringing home a guy who isn't white will cause chaos. 

I'm wondering...those of you who are in interracial relationships, how did your families react? How do their opinions affect your relationship with you SO? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 06:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can tell you that wearing the right size bra is totally worth it. None of that digging feeling or falling straps. Just make sure you go to a specialty boutique or someplace reputable to get fitted. I've heard iffy stories about VS and other chain places about their fitting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 06:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strangely I hate V8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 06:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually attraction is a big part of starting a relationship with someone. However my recent fling I didn't find physically attractive at all. I fell for his personality and getting to know him. For me there never was a physical attraction to him which was weird. Unfortunately he has a huge ego and that got in the way but I can honestly say that for some people getting to know a person can bring on attraction vs automatically being attracted to them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 06:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the time I was 13 until I was 18 I wore a size 34A/B...finally got fitted and have been wearing a 32C since.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 20:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...uhhh yes! Totally... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 06:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 06:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel you...I switched to PB2 because I was eating so much of even the natural Peanut butter but alas, powdered peanut butter just isn't the same.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 06:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No! Strangely I cannot stand ketchup. I'm talking down about jarred/canned sauce used for pizza and pasta.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 05:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Food controls your life. It preoccupies your every thought. It's not seen as something that you need to survive. 

I have EDNOS (eating disorder not otherwise specified) which doesn't fit the spectrum of anorexia or bulimia. I've starved myself but haven't been anorexic. And I purge my food if I feel like it. Currently I eat and throw up if I feel too full. Coupled with my depression, this ED is ruining my life. I haven't gotten my period in over 6 months. My skin is so dry. My knuckles are scabbed. My cheeks are puffed out. My weight constantly fluctuates and I have a skewed self image. I'm tired 24/7 and have no energy. My heartbeat is also not normal. 

With different eating disorders there are different mindsets. However there's always one thing it boils down to: disordered eating. Whether you eat too much, too little, nothing at all, eat then throw up etc. 

Tl;dr: Having an ED is an awful thing that is a mental disorder. I wish I could warn people who think starving/purging is a good idea to lose weight or be happy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 04:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree...prom is very overrated and it's just another dance TBH  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 04:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 01:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say for me it's not a deal breaker but it's something that would make me tentative to start a relationship. I also deal with depression and I think two depressed people wouldn't really be the best for each other. Sort of like a Romeo and Juliet situation. 

If I wasn't depressed then I wouldn't mind. But then I wouldn't be able to understand what is going on in their mind and it would be kind of like walking on eggshells. I think with everyone it's different though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 01:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The lovely bones...not really a tear-jerker but I think it's a beautifully sad movie. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What did you end up doing on your prom night? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 01:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me I ended up driving my drunk friends around. Then spent the night helping to clean up barf and reassure people they weren't going to die. Such fun. 

 I'm curious as to how many of you had the "dream" prom night...you know, go to an after party with your date and end up sleeping together, then got up and went to breakfast together before parting ways. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 01:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't even buy peanut butter because I will eat it all too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 01:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 20:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best is breakfast cereal for dinner!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 20:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tomato sauce in the jar or can :)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 20:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...I just really love tomato sauce haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just drank a whole bottle of tomato sauce. What food do you have an unhealthy obsession with? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 19:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 08:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, I hate how it allows people to become anonymous bullies online. You can take a picture of someone without them knowing and ruin their lives by posting on the Internet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What do you hate about today's technology? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 07:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 06:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Potatoes. Technically you could live off only potatoes for the rest of your life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 01:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's like the lovely bones and we all pass over to a good place </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 10:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice choice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 10:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! I heard her rendition and it was pretty good. I think anyone can cover it and it will still sound good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 10:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a nice addition </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 08:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for reminding me of this song. Forgot how good it is! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 08:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love M83! Thanks for sharing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 08:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was 14. Family member. Trying to stay away from it as of late.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 08:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sad yet beautiful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 08:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yes, once again Reddit mobile has come in handy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 08:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mad world ( piano cover) for me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In the end credits of your life, what song would play? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 07:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 07:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aggressive and nasty. I had my eyes open too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 07:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Call -Backstreet Boys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 07:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I would. Because 100k is better than the life that I'm living now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 00:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honours BA in visual and critical studies or drawing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 09:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Which hole?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 09:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snowy, Icy, and slushy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 09:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's stupid that we are expected to live to work and Need to have a job by the time we are 16 in order to get experience for more jobs. As long as you have the drive to get a job and aren't mooching off other people's hard earned money then you do you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 08:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on their circumstances. Unfortunately my mind would jump more to "lazy" than loser. Or if assume they're well off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 08:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alarm: 6am
Snooze X 4
Accept defeat
Wake up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 08:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Christmas story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 08:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Green is a nice colour. 

Source: Celery </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 08:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ran down the stairs too fast (carpet), slipped and saw my life flash before my eyes. Luckily the bannister was there to save me. Now I cautiously take one step at a time because there's no need to rush! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 08:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "doing it for the vine" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 08:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Throw away your trash instead of littering.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 08:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quit smoking. I'm young and only smoked habitually for a year but it made my anxiety worsen, cost me financially, made me smell like ass and made me miserable. I finally quit cold turkey when my friend who is older and smokes told me that the best time to quit is when you're young. Also I looked at my mom who is a smoker and realized even though she's a year younger than her sister(my aunt), she actually looks about 5 years older. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 08:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Money, gift cards and some nice pyjamas  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 08:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such a great song to run to! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What song makes you feel like you're in an epic movie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 08:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 08:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Family member shared some of his stash with me. I was barely 14 and never even thought about smoking weed before he brought it up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 08:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still care for you but don't feel as deeply I used to about you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 08:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that we are all humans and that race shouldn't matter as much as it does. No matter how you're brought up, I still think we are all biased towards our own races. That's just how we are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 08:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it's colonel...how tf do you get "kernel" from that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 08:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "kar-a-Mel" because that "a" is in there for a reason </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
