<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5711</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 02:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and now for the rest of your life everytime you open Facebook there are going to be 10000+ pictures of her kid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 02:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> she also thinks I'm a lower class citizen because i don't have kids 

BTW i am only in my very early 20s so its not like I'm even that old  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 02:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how is she suddenly more importuned then anyone else because she knows how to have irresponsible sex </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-17 23:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you i do work really hard to stay thin. definitely have better partner 
i feel so much better  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-17 23:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my mother has 3 children I'm the oldest and i don't think she ever wanted kids 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-17 23:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> She's a know it all </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-17 23:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Was in offmychest but told it would fit better here)

my life goal for as long as i remember was to be a mom but since my 18 year old sister had her son 4 months ago i think i have changed my mind. She seems to think that because she's a parent she knows everything about everything i am in the middle of getting my masters and she didn't finish 10th grade but because i haven't squeezed a baby out I'm now a complete idiot. It can only get worse because she's 3 months pregnant AGAIN oh yes she has a 4 month old and is 3 months pregnant. so i never want to be like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not wanting kids </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-17 22:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my life goal for as long as i remember was to be a mom but since my 18 year old sister had her son 4 months ago i think i have changed my mind. She seems to think that because she's a parent she knows everything about everything i am in the middle of getting my masters and she didn't finish 10th grade but because i haven't squeezed a baby out I'm now a complete idiot. It can only get worse because she's 3 months pregnant AGAIN oh yes she has a 4 month old and is 3 months pregnant.
so i never want to be like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-17 22:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually think shame works and i am a fat shammer ( down vote me why don't you) i do it everyday i don't see anything wrong with it.
i mean smokers are shamed and they don't get all up in your face most of the time they usually just move away. 
i have every right to say what and they cant stop me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-17 01:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> get the fuck over your self. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-17 01:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when are tax dollars have to pay for new furniture its getting ridiculous.
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-17 01:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there doctors not miracle workers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-17 01:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i don't even have a witty comment.
this is just sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-16 02:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> watch all the fatties try it out.

then break your truck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-16 02:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the infection i see happening there makes my skin crawl  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-16 02:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how does that even happen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-16 02:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats one ghetto clue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-16 02:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy SHIT 
no way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I never forgive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-16 01:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i don't think i have ever forgiven a person ever.  My family has no problem just forgiving whoever whenever. I on the other hand cannot 
once someone has wronged me i will NEVER ever forgive them 
friends family no one. My family gets so mad at me about it because i cant get past it but i think people forgive to easily history always repeat its self.
i don't think i want to get past it i am much happier this way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-15 21:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and WE body shame ok then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-15 21:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why don't you just fucking lose weight and stop complaining like its just that easy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-15 21:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gag!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-15 06:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i know a few sets of twins and 2 out of 3 of them still live with there twin in there late 20's and have no SO 
also this is the first thing that comes up for a study http://suite101.com/a/only-child-same-as-peers-only-smarter-a63367
do you need more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Only Child </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-15 05:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-15 05:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The smells... that have been smelled </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Farting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-15 04:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think farting is REPULSIVE like its really nasty. Before you say we all fart its not big deal i very rarely ever fart and to prove that i have gone to extreme lengths about 2 years ago i video taped myself at night to make sure i didn't.

but really why cant people go to the bathroom to fart i just think its rude to fart around people like ever.

everyone in my family will run around and fart in peoples faces and think its great i just get grossed out about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-14 00:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when you put things on the internet you take the risk of people saying things you don't like . its like they have never been on the internet before. 
the internet is a public place were we can say and think what ever we want so ha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-14 00:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh sadly it is and thats not even as big as i have seen them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-13 23:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> where did you get this picture? some context would be nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-13 23:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> your hand looks like what i think raj from big bang theory's hands would look like  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-13 23:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't kill it 
I want it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-13 23:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where was this found!!!!!! OMG  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-13 22:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone post a link i cant find it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-13 22:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i would NEVER see a fat nutritionist or dietitian.
I am a registered nutritionist and to be completely honest people who work in my office have been fired for being fat because they don't want a bad reputation. They have had complaints about the advice that has come from fat "cow workers". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-13 22:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they have every right to take the child. 
morbid obesity on a child is neglect . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-13 00:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why would you show people that hahaha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-13 00:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Walmart people are terrifying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-13 00:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i laughed for like 5 minutes 
people were staring it was awkward. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-13 00:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> your not dirty and you shouldn't feel ashamed 
i know your scared 
my sister is 18 and has 2 kids NO not twins so yes i understand scared  
you can do something amazing and give that child up for adoption. you can change someones life 

but ultimately its your choice what you do. once you accept that your pregnant it will be life changing you will relax and calm down and most likely happy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 08:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they make me sick i have seen documentaries on it and there main goal is to be immobile and to me thats just disgusting. There partner will have to care for them and thats the ultimate form of control.
OH and because they cant work anymore our tax dollars are whats paying for her tv,food, internet and medical care  and frankly i don't think i should have to pay for people to do this to themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 04:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how is this any worse then BBW? they are both unhealthy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 03:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you look like a giant penis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 03:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cant 
I cant 
I cant 
handle them anymore  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 03:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no she's fat but she's wearing a corset 
so she gives the fake curvy look  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 03:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats just nasty...... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
