<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9229</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 05:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably lowered it from $9500 to $8500 and forgot to delete the 9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 12:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the sidebar. It has all you need and more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 00:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Panera is probably the healthiest fast food though. I eat their salads a lot and they are actually very healthy once you modify them a bit (like removing cheese and bacon, no ranch, etc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 00:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind Bars are pretty healthy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 12:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It probably never would. 200fps is very low for an airsoft gun and wouldn't even hurt, especially wearing a shirt  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 12:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can also ask in person for an application, even if they don't say they are hiring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 01:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your macros equal your calories so you are wrong about either your calorie count or macro count </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 13:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't matter what you feel. You obviously aren't gaining if people are making those comments. The only way you will know is if you weigh yourself, otherwise you're setting yourself up for failure. And 2 times a week is not enough volume to adequately gain muscle mass. 3 days should be the minimum. Stop making excuses </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 11:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Add calf raises if you are worried </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 11:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't weigh yourself at all, you very well may have lost weight. Don't be an idiot and just weigh yourself once a week. It also sounds like you aren't tracking calories very much, so do that to. I think I can see why you failed last time you tried.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 02:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go for a run or work out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 01:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finding clothes that fit right is all but impossible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 00:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure. I wear a 28x34, but my waist is actually 25-26, but no one makes pants that long with that size waist  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 23:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Legs are slimmer. For someone who is a normal weight, they're probably tight, but I am pretty skinny (6'3" 140lbs) so they got me more like slim fit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 21:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly this. I have a pair of skinny fit American Eagle Extreme flex khakis and they're the most comfortable pants I own.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 17:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm voting Libertarian this election, but I think watching this debate actually made Hilary my second choice over Trump. I vehemently disagree with her on almost everything, but Trump very obviously showed he knows nothing last night.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 16:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very true, although things like lightbulbs (while higher wattage) are similar in design and get very hot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 16:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention a lot of jobs in Alaska don't require a college degree because there are a lot of skilled labor jobs instead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 14:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure about that. Anecdotal evidence, but I have one in my room that's been on for months and I just went and touched it and it doesn't feel warm at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 14:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I started I was. Now that I'm used to it, I'm not usually sore, but I can tell that I worked out from muscle fatigue  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 13:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been eating 3000kcal a day for the past few weeks, and have gained about 1/2lb a week, which is what I was aiming for, but all of a sudden my weight has shot up 4-5lbs over the past few days. I know for a fact that I am not eating over 3000kcal (I am on a meal plan to recover from anorexia), and I've already had the "beginner weight gain" of 3-4lbs from water weight/waste/etc, which was about two months ago.

What gives? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 13:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really doesn't matter as a beginner. I don't have a link, but I remember seeing a report that said there is insignificant differences between 5x5 and 3x8 in terms of strength and muscle growth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 03:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hilary is showing her idiocy talking about gun control. She has no idea what she is taking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 02:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do, but I am pretty underweight right now so I chalk it up to malnutrition and lack of energy (food).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 02:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do 8-12 rep sets and my progression is still around 4 lbs per workout (I have 2 lb plates) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 23:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gaining....

Slowly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 20:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And fuck you and everyone who thinks like that. Fuck socialism. Redistribution of wealth is theft.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 16:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 13:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sidebar ----- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 13:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's probably not nearly enough volume. Check out /r/bodyweightfitness. They have some good advice, although you won't get nearly as good of  gains as if you were lifting weights.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 11:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6'3" 140lbs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 11:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't squat and do everything else still </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 11:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't need 233g of protein. Aim for 1g/lb of weight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 02:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much, yes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 02:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's slow. Which is to be expected from a 20+ year old Jeep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 02:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A bit over 3000 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 02:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a very large Johnson supporter, so me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 02:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. I didn't even know that uncut people existed until I was like 14. I thought I was born cut.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 19:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are doing something very wrong if you are getting fat enough to have man boobs while bulking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 19:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is an amazing color </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 16:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Savior by Rise Against. 

It's not like the rest of their songs either  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 05:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GOMAD is idiotic. Don't do it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 02:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's probably worth more that I payed for it a year ago honestly. Older Jeep wranglers are skyrocketing around here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 02:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here in the greater Cleveland/Akron area.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 02:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll be fine, just eat more. I run 2 miles on days I lift and 5+ miles on my off days. I am gaining at a steady pace of about a pound a week still.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 00:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not eating enough. Eat more. Look at the sidebar and get on a program. 

/Thread </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 17:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3.5k  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 17:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It varies based on program, but generally you usually should be increasing by 2.5-5lbs per week  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 17:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say that it's a post scarcity libertarian-socialist society.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 13:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rand Paul without a doubt. He actively and willingly reaches across the isle to work with the other party to get things done and always stands up for what he believes in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 01:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Download myfitnesspal and track everything you eat and make sure to eat at a surplus every day. That is the only way. You need to eat more or you won't make any progress.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 00:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Service dogs aren't pets though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 23:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were brand new </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 20:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too bad Dell customer support is awful as well as their quality control. Me and my brother both bought XPS laptops from Dell and both ended up with defects. His wouldn't boot up and my screen started flickering on and off after two weeks and was unusable. It took 4 hours on the phone just to get a return mail slip sent to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 17:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the opposite problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 14:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a bad price either. I'd buy that it I was in the market for cheap weekend car to autocross.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 04:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you live in campus, you usually aren't allowed to have a car also parked there in the US. Commuting is different  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 03:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You think that's bad, look at Ford trucks from the 80's. Everything is red. Literally everything  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 03:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because people have a right to do what they want to themselves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 02:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grow up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 02:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calories in Calories out. It's the only diet that works. All (good) diets are just a different way to get there  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 02:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eragon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 02:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen some on Craigslist for pretty cheap that are in good condition still for like $8k </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 02:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, but your going to get down voted by Reddit because 99% of users on here are overweight and lazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 02:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a marathon runner normally. This *is* me running less  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bulking and Cardio: Questions on Caloric Intake and TDEE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 21:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>    Hey y'all, just a few question on caloric intake as it pertains to bulking and cardio.

I am currently on a 4x a week (every other day) full body program and I run 3-4 miles (sometimes more) at least three times a week on my non-lifting/rest days. In addition to that, I often run two miles in addition to lifting on lift days as well. 

I am 6'3" 140lbs and currently eat 2900-3000 calorie a day, but on days I run, I add calories burnt running to that 3000, so I end up eating around 3300 calories on cardio days.

   I have been struggling to gain weight, so obviously I need to increase caloric intake, but first, should I recalculate my TDEE (+300-500 to gain of course) this time with regards to cardio activity and eat the same amount each day instead of eating more only on days that I run?  Or is it fine to only eat back calories burned on days that I run? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 18:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 22re will literally last forever  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 16:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's kinda idiotic to incentivize with taxes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 15:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) Full Body

2) 3-6+ mile run

3) Full Body

4) 3-6+ mile run

5) Full Body

6) 3-6+mile run

7) Full Body


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 12:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it would look really good, in a "Tokyo Drift" street racer type of way if GTR wasn't plastered all over it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 12:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. I get them for 68 a dozen around at my local Acme </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 02:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree and think Trump is slightly better than Clinton. That being said, I'm supporting Johnson and hate both Trump and Clinton  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 01:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...I like it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 00:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's considered outdated? I thought everyone had a landline. Certainly everyone I know does  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 23:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Caaarrrrllllll </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 19:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reds were $5 here in Ohio on Saturday (at least where I work) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 13:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might just be short since you said your mom is short. It's just genetics. Or you may have just not hit your growth spurt yet. Your 16, you've got a few years left until I'd start worrying about being short forever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 12:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it's a stupid question, but it probably doesn't merit its own post, so does anyone here have myfitnesspal premium? Is it worth it? I've been using the free version for the past 3-4ish years and have gotten along fine, but there are some features like being able to set custom goals per day and macros by gram that I'd like to have. Your thoughts?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 20:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes they do. My platoon at basic training in December had at least 8 guys who weren't citizens, could barely speak english and joined to become a citizen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 19:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eat maintenance. Not much else you can do. Just get healthy first and start off light when you return for a workout or two to make sure you are all healed up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 02:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it would be someone on here.  Nice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 21:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Underflow looks bad on everything now IMHO. Hasn't been "in style" since the early 90's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 20:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it 2WD? A lot of them were used by mail carriers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saw this in my school's parking garage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 18:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 18:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, I couldn't get a very good photo due to their parking location. They are both Mercedes Benz Unimogs for those who are curious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saw these beasts the other day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 18:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 17:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> McDonalds is nasty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 17:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I mean, what else are you going to use?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 04:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We attached our crappy D-Battery powered angle heads to our MOLLE rucks at Basic with the red lens on to use as marker lights. Other than that, no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 04:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. I have about twelve of those laying around. Useless for anything thing except maybe reading a map or writing something in the dark.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 04:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a NZXT H440. Excellent case.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 16:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the time. I sleep like, 5 hours a night and get up at 5am every day to workout.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 16:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go any ways. Motivation is bullshit. All you need is discipline.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 16:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get a new pair about every two months when I'm in season or training </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 01:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1995 Jeep Wrangler. I get about 12-15 miles a gallon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 01:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Desperation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 01:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish my Jeep was a comfortable as a JK. I daily my YJ 40 min to school and back every day on the freeway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 00:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got the Infiniti commercial with Kit Harrington as an ad before that. Very fitting  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 00:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. You will gain excess fat eating that much over </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 15:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only do 3x8-12 (plus warm-up) and am progressing well. I only do 1x8 deadlift though, but am still progressing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 14:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like that truck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 13:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not luck, it's hard work and dedication that git him to where he is  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 01:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't. The president and executive branch are supposed to uphold the law.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 01:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My work out at 430 this morning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 01:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 01:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Discipline  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 01:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Starving </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 23:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How on earth did you do three sets of *deadlifts* during the course of one song?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 23:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but eating is hard. I'll eat less than  1500 kcal a day if I don't log calories and force myself to eat more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 21:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eating in general makes me feel like crap and makes my anxiety go through the roof, so I know how you feel. We're all in this together  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 13:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right in the feels. I was forced to sell my '85 Ranger last year and I've regretted it since. I would honestly trade my Wrangler for another, but I can't find any :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 13:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like something from Overwatch  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 13:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course not. That would mean social interaction.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 13:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gaining weight is way harder than it seems. I don't understand how people do it so easily.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 01:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm having the same issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 01:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be exactly the same.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 03:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see nothing wrong with that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 02:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks phenomenal.
Also, I think that is the most phallic shifter I have ever seen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 14:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eat more. It's that simple. If you don't, you won't gain weight. Try liquid calories (I.e shakes, milk, etc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 05:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate when people joke about anorexia like that to me because I am anorexic (the mental disorder and weight wise). I usually just say yeah, I am. And they shut up real quick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 19:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is it bad that we get oil from the Middle East now? The majority of US oil is domestic anyways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 17:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eat more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
