<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8657</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How can I reintroduce exercise in a healthy way during recovery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 02:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I consider myself healthy at this point and if I do relapse, it's only for a couple days and then I pick myself up again. 

I would like to start exercising/dieting in a healthy way though. Every time I consider counting calories the way they should be counted, a voice inside my mind tries to convince me to cheat and go lower than I should. The biggest aid in my recovery has been avoiding numbers (scales, calories, etc). 

How can I introduce those in a better light? What are ways I can stay in shape by avoiding as many number triggers as possible? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Have you read any books that helped with recovering? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 11:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a bulimia and anorexia. I have been to the Emily Program (who are amazing) But I've fallen off the wagon again, I just ordered a dbt workbook. But am curious if anyone has read another book towards self help/recovering that has helped?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Can't eat around anyone but family </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 11:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't been able to eat around anyone but family for the last 8 years..idk why. It's always weighed on me but lately it's just killing me. I can't be normal or go visit my friends at college or dinner or restaurants with my family or anything. My sisters make fun of me because I only eat specific foods because It scares me to eat other things. I have been purging for the last 4 months or so, this isn't the first time...I was previously in therapy for the purging. It's gotten really bad lately and I don't know what to do or why I am this way. 

Any advice or people who are like me please help. There's obviously way more too this story, but I don't want to make it too long that's annoying. Thanks...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: At a loss, I need some help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 00:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, I have wasted 5 years of my life suffering from bulimia. I used to be a overweight girl, but when I was 13 I lost a lot of weight in a healthy way. I was still borderline overweight, and I was not pleased. I started restricting which lead to binging, so I gained weight instead of losing it. For a few years I accepted it and thought that once I'd be old enough I can join a gym and work on myself, but for the time being I will be satisfied with the progress I still managed to make.

When I was 16 I was dating this guy who was very cruel to me and despite his constant remarks on my weight (and controlling my eating) I adored him like any love-struck teenager. In my obsessive need to please him, I experimented a few times with purging, but it was only on special occasions when overeating was unavoidable. Then when I was 17, post-break up, we had a lot of issues in my household that lead to regular binging and purging, yet still pretty under control. I had by then joined a gym and my weight was down to below my previous "borderline overweight" level, but not yet satisfied. When I turned 18 I gained control fairly well and started to actually live like a healthy human being, I was at my prime needless to say. I was in fit shape, I was happy and my weight was finally pleasing to me. I looked amazing and I loved my body so much, yet still I always wanted more. 

On Christmas that year I relapsed, and ever since then it has been a constant struggle. So technically, from year 2013 to this present day my binging and purging has been out of control, eating enormous amounts of food, more than ever before. There were times when I was able to quit for a few weeks but it always came down to other emotional distress that caused me to lose it again. Now I'm back to my "borderline overweight" level and I hate myself for it. It's so ironic that I know very well that if I just ate healthy like I used to, I'd be back down to a weight I'd be happy with. I am so angry at myself for letting this get so out of control. Now I'm living with an amazing boyfriend who loves me for who I am, but I am so overwhelmed with guilt as well as this "addiction" that I don't know how much longer I can take it.. I want to seek help, but at the same time I'm afraid. I want to believe that I can do this myself. Every time I try to quit, I get so anxious and being full is uncomfortable for me that I always end up relapsing. The evenings are always the hardest for me. This has had a huge negative impact on my social life, my studies and in general my quality of life. What am I to do? I feel trapped in myself...

TLDR; Been struggling for 5 years with bulimia, I really want to nip it in the bud, but at the same time I'm conflicted about it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Getting Help for Family Member with Eating Disorder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 22:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A family member of mine is having serious problems as a result of an eating disorder. 

Nobody seems to get it and she is separating the consequences of the behavior on the body from the disorder. Would an intervention be the best thing to do? 

What could I do to break through and offer her help with this disorder? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Gaining weight with Anorexia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 11:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really concerned, I'm 5'8" and underweight. I didn't really have any body image issues causing this, but get really stressed out and physically can't eat... I have to force myself to and it makes me sick, sometimes it makes me vomit. I don't even want my favorite foods. I'm now starting to have body issues because the things I liked about my body are pretty much gone and I'm just awkward and boney looking. I feel gross and am constantly weak and exhausted and it's starting to really trash my self esteem. I've had issues with not being able to eat before, but it's never gotten this serious. I've slowly but surely been loosing weight to the point where I'm currently underweight. I go to college out of state, and I'm not really sure what to do here.

I really need to gain weight and I also want to. How can I start eating normally again when I feel stressed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Nauseous and haven't been able to eat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 11:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! I just wanted to post because I have a question. I have no history with eating disorders, but recently i haven't been able to stomach anything. I am a college student, and when I go to the dining hall and smell the food I get nauseous. I have only been able to eat certain foods like plain pasta. I looked up "food aversion" and it seems like it is for young children and pregnant women. I am neither. Does anyone have experience with this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How Do I Help Her? Binge eating, pop habit, junk food problems </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 23:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I don't think my wife (late 20's, slightly over weight) has an eating disorder. But she exhibits behavior that I think could lead to one eventually if not addressed. 

She confesses to eating in secret and when she's feeling low she will binge eat. Yesterday she said "I binged pretty bad today. I'm so disgusted with myself I don't even want to tell you what I ate."


I know she has addictive tendencies. She's been struggling to kick a pop habit for years. She managed to do it this summer for a few months. But last week she confessed to drinking 3+ every day and when she stopped she got slammed with a migraine so bad it kept her from going to a party she was really excited for.

She will also buy me junk food so she can justify buying herself junk food too. Yesterday when I got home she said there was a pint of ice cream for me in the fridge and when I went to retrieve it it was sitting next to a pint for her. When she does this if I don't eat whatever she gets fast enough she'll end up eating it herself.

She knows she has some issues with her relationship to food. But, and this is horrible to say, I don't think she's equipped to deal with them on her own. We don't get to spend huge amounts of time together because of our work and school schedules. So I can't be there to police her. 

I'm not sure what I can do to help nip this in the bud. I am hoping Reddit might have some advice on how to help her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Is inpatient treatment right for me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 13:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am in my early/mid 20's and recently inquired about inpatient treatment and found out that, thanks to insurance, it would cost MUCH less than I had imagined. That is awesome news! However, I am wondering if inpatient treatment is right for me.

I have worked in an inpatient facility so I am familiar with what treatment entails. I have also read enough to know that there are high rates of relapse after an inpatient stay. Research I have read indicates that outpatient (with family or support system) therapy is more successful. However, I am really interested in alternative therapies such as equine therapy and adventure therapy. I am so sick of being inside my head and really don't feel like spending more energy working through everything internally. I want to expend my emotional energy outwardly, if that makes sense...I want to try something different that is less "in my head". There are no outpatient treatments of this sort in my area, but there are some inpatient facilities that offer such treatments in other states.

Here is the thing: My ED does not hinder my ability to function in society. I am in grad school and am doing well in my internship. I realize I do not have to be debilitated to enter inpatient treatment, but the fact that I am medically stable kind of adds to my hesitation.

I have had body image issues since I was 13 and was overweight throughout most of my teenage years. I have had various ED behaviors for years, but I'd estimate that it has gotten much worse over the past year and a half or so. I am within my weight range but am not okay with it. I have ED behaviors that I engage in in private and what is displayed outwardly are behaviors that people unfamiliar with EDs would not recognize. I often eat in seclusion and will not eat a meal that is not planned at least 24 hours in advance. To do so causes extreme anxiety, panic, and guilt. I am OBSESSED with numbers. All of my time (aside from when I am at my internship or asleep) is spent planning meals or just looking over and over again at meals and re-reading the calories planned. I become paralyzed at the grocery store sometimes when deciding what to buy and end up settling for my "safe food". I could go on...but in a nutshell, I engage in behaviors and have obsessive ED thoughts.

The only people who know about my ED are my best friend, my boyfriend, and my mom. I recently told my dad kind of on accident (but he knows very minimal details...only that I struggle with eating and body image). None of them understand the disorder and they do not know how much it affects me. My mom recently stated that I "...don't have eating disorder behaviors and just eat healthy and count calories". Part of me is glad that is all she sees, but I also wish she could understand how badly I hurt. At the same time, though, I really don't want to burden her. Or my boyfriend. They are supportive, though...at least as supportive as they know how to be.

TL;DR: I would not enter treatment until August (after I graduate) and really, the likelihood of me entering inpatient treatment is slim. Despite the new knowledge that it would cost much less than I had anticipated, it is still not pocket change for me. I do not want to spend $$$ on treatment unless I am dedicated to recovery. It would be a waste to come back and not continue to put forth effort to recovering. I have several months to really think this over, but at this point, I am not sure I am dedicated to recovery. I am scared to let go of my ED, but at the same time, I am so sick of it. It is hell inside my head and it's a private hell...I would appreciate some input on whether or not you guys think inpatient treatment is right for me. Thanks!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Sent myself to the ER again. What's your best suggestion for recovery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 03:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've managed to cut back on my purging behaviour and stopped entirely for about 3 months but with the loss of a loved one it came back full force in recent weeks. Last night after a purge I felt my heart racing, skipping beats and then slowing. A 5 hour ER stay showed everything was normal so I just put myself into a panic with "this is the end" thinking.

I have an appointment with my psychotherapist this week but this is the first time I'm telling her about my disordered eating.

I'm hoping that last night was my last purge. I am so done with thinking I'm going to die from this. It doesn't even keep weight off anymore, anyway. 

I read through all these recovery suggestions that are posted but what is your very best one for recovery? 

Also how did your therapist react when you told them?

I couldn't bring myself to tell the Doctor last night but I'm sure they figured it out.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Handling a clients ED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 02:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work for a company that has support staff who look over about 3-4 mentally disabled adults live more independently.

We have one client in particular who suffers from bulimia. She is also diabetic and requires constant 24/7 care.

However I feel like some of the things we do are not helping her, and instead making it worse for her.

she cannot go to the bathroom unless supervised. Now she cannot take a shower without us looking at the curtain (via the mirror) to keep her from purging. However, none of us have adequate medical educational backgrounds or therapy backgrounds (I have the closest but am not certified nor, educated specifically for ED)

She is constantly told what she cannot and can eat. she is constantly being monitored, punished for her behavior, and punished for purging. No one except for me; tries to talk to her and see how she feels.

I'm just at a loss at what to do. I want to get the state more involved with her care because this company does not seem to handle it well. I feel like they want her to fail. I'm not sure what I can/should do in this situation.

tl;dr: client suffers from ED and is being taken care of by staff not educated to help her.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Personal Mantras for During Recovery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 02:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Struggling a little bit over February, and was re-reading some books to help me through recovery. Some of them have mentioned having specific "mantras" or words to repeat during hard times; any one have any suggestions?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Just rejected from ED clinic, need advice on self help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 01:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi,

I know I've messaged a few times for advice while I was coming to terms with my eating disorder resurfacing again after 7 years but I need a little guidance on going forward.

I organised meeting with my university's eating disorder service, who recommended I get referred to the local NHS ED clinic (UK). After a doctor referral and weeks of waiting and assessments I've been declined help because they don't think I have an eating disorder.

I'm trying not to let it get to me so I'm going to try to help myself. I'm tired of food ruling my life. I'd like to know if there are any other people who've managed to help themselves, and what you found really helped. Books, videos, websites etc to help with feelings of guilt, overcoming that critical voice in your head, and actually understanding what your body needs to eat to be healthy.

Thank you for reading this, I'd really appreciate any advice anyone has.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I feel helpless </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 01:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I started taking a medication used to treat bipolar disorder, Risperdal I gained a large amount of weight in a few short months.

Two years later when my doctor reduced the dosage I started exercising and eating right and lost more than half of the initial weight I gained.

I currently go in cycles. I will go a week of balanced eating and exercise then 3 days of intense binging. This has been going on for months and I haven't made any progress with my weight loss.

I don't know what to do I just feel so helpless in my body. My doctor keeps telling me will power, but I just can't... Sometimes I have to give in, I can't stop myself. Please help.

Can anyone give advice on what I should do?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Not sure what help I need (also Canadian) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 01:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been trying to find help for a while now with no luck, I thought maybe someone here might have had the same problem or be able to help.

I think I have binge eating disorder, or exercise bulimia, or something else entirely. Basically I feel like the binging is the real problem, I do it 1 - 3 times a week but I never throw up. But after of course I feel guilty and horrible so I "get back on track" by "eating healthy" (really, restricting a lot) and exercising like crazy. This all inevitably leads to a binge and the cycle repeats. It's so horrible and I'm really depressed all the time and I can't stop.

My problem is that it's hard to find OHIP (Canadian) covered treatment for binge eating disorder, and the places I have found actually have a BMI requirement to be eligible. My BMI is normal so I can't get treatment at these places. I'm not sure what to do anymore.

Has anyone else had trouble with this? Does anyone have experience getting OHIP covered treatment for binge eating disorder? Has anyone ever even overcome binge eating!? Because at this point I feel like it's impossible.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I think one of my customers may be bulimic. Is there anything I can do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 01:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work in an all-you-can-eat sushi restaurant. The girl in question is in her early to mid 20's, underweight, kind of unhealthy looking. She always comes in with her boyfriend who always speaks for her.
She eats a large amount of food, more than almost anyone I've ever seen eat. She takes pretty regular bathroom breaks and usually comes out with tears in her eyes, which is what lead me to believe she is bulimic.

I've considered confronting her boyfriend while she's in the bathroom, but I can't imagine it doing any good since he obviously supports it. 

Is there anything I can do? If you were her, would it help you for the restaurant to stop serving you? To call you out?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 20:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful post [here](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2lmkw2/request_vyvanse_for_bedbinge_purge_anyone_with/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Vyvanse and Binge Eating Disorder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 20:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
I was wondering if anyone diagnosed with BED has been prescribed Vyvanse and what was your experience? 

Today my psychiatrist gave me the script. I'm feeling hopeful, but the thought of taking a stimulant is a little unsettling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Survey on anorexia and gender </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 22:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm doing a college project on mens anorexia. I would  love to get more feed back via  my survey. I am new to reddit. thank you 

https://www.surveymonkey.com/s/FGRGCJL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How do I help my girlfriend [21] increase calorie intake? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 12:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

Me and my girlfriend are both students, and she is currently relapsing badly back into what she has identified as an ED from her childhood. We both don't really have experience dealing with recovery or prevention, and because of some other factors getting help from a therapist at the moment isn't a possibility.

Currently she has consistently been eating below a healthy amount to maintain her weight, which is already very low for her height, although the only symptoms shes had so far from undereating are dizziness and occasional fainting. Shes working incredibly hard planning out meals each day, but struggles as adding on enough calories to reach a healthy total makes it easier for the ED to take over and make her stop eating altogether that day. We're getting there slowly but steadily but I'm very worried that if she continues to under eat the health issues might get more severe before she manages to start eating a healthy amount consistently.

Does anybody here have any experience with this kind of situation, and do you have any advice on how I can help her to add on calories and eat healthily without me triggering her? :) Ive read amazing responses on this subreddit and its incredibly assertive and supportive to hear so many stories of success.

Thank you! :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: found myself in a pickle and looking for help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 12:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made a throwaway for this, because it could potentially affect my job. I'll give a little history first. I know it is a bit lengthy, but I sincerely am trying to get advice of some sort.

I am Male, 23 years old. I had been overweight since around the 4th grade, age ~10. My parents would always just order pizza or take us to fast food. I would just eat whatever, whenever. I knew I was fat, it bothered me alot, I would be very upset with myself alot, but I never did anything about it. After high school, I diddy bopped around a bit but decided to join the Military. I changed my diet slightly, starved myself, would not drink anything, slightly worked out just enough to pass the initial weigh ins for MEPS processing. At boot camp, we had very regimented PT and diet (obviously, I know). I lost a ton of weight there and got to a good weight and BF%. Once out of boot camp, my problems began.

These problems have been going on, in the forefront, for about 3 years now. They might have been going on for longer but I just hadn't noticed them. Ever since I lost a bunch of weight in boot camp, i absolutely dread putting it back on. I am absolutely not happy with my body right now even though I am at a good weight/BF%. Everyone tells me how I am looking great, but I am disgusted with myself. People tell me how I've never looked so good, and compared to my previous weight, I obviously appear much better. But that doesn't stop me from being disgusted with myself.

I never swam when I was a teenager because I was embarrassed to take my shirt off. To this day, I am still embarrassed to do so. At work, we often take our blouses off and work in just our trousers and (tucked in) undershirts. I hate this and always put on a sweater if I take of my blouse since I feel like people are staring at my perceived gut.

This ties into my biggest fear which is gaining weight again. I am absolutely terrified by this. I've been to Afghanistan. I remember being on combat patrols and being more concerned with how many calories I ate for the day than the people shooting at me. I would get annoyed because I would lose my train of thought and have to start my mental count over again. The patrols would get back to base and I would excuse myself to the head and make myself throw up the MRE snacks I ate while out on patrol. This problem is with me everywhere. Whether in country or at home. I will be home with my wife and just think about how disgusting I must look to her. I will eat dinner and make an excuse in order to take a shower so that the water will drown out the sound of me making myself throw up dinner.

This brings up another problem I have. I absolutely cannot buy groceries. If I buy food, I practically cannot stop myself from eating it. By eating whatever I wanted, when ever I wanted, it is like it is carrying over. Bagels in the pantry? Well, I might as well eat them. I have to wait until I feel my stomach rumble, and then buy food. And only the amount I need to eat. If I get any more, I will eat it. It makes living with my wife very difficult. We are both military and we are stationed in 2 different states. I get to see her every other weekend or so. But when I get to visit her, I just feel like I can't help but to eat all of the groceries that she had bought. Then I fell disgust with myself for eating so much. Then I purge. My wife has almost caught on a few times but I keep making excuses. I am too embarrassed to tell her. I don't want to tell her and admit that she was right all along and that I've been hiding things from her.

I try to eat healthy, but I will go to the store and I will break down and buy pizza. or oreos. Or chocolate. And I will devour it all. Why? Because I am in the store and I will literally think to myself, "Yes, I can get these. I'm just going to throw them up after I eat them anyway. So what does it matter?" It is a terrible repeating cycle.

I go to the gym every day and work out. I obsess with trying to track calories. I will purge multiple times a day. I will take laxatives and the such to force myself to purge. IT comes in waves though. Sometimes I don't purge for a week or two. Sometimes I purge every day, multiple times a day. sometimes I take laxatives multiple times a week. I am writing this as I am making plans to purge the dinner I ate.

I desperately want to get professional help, but I can't because of the military. I have to see a regular care provider, who can then recommend me to see a specialist, who may send me to a therapist. The problem is that the therapists and such are in the Mental Health department. I will be absolutely ridiculed at work, mercilessly. Not to mention the fact that I would have now seen a therapist which means I am on a watch list for further mental issues. Add that to the fact that Eating Disorders are grounds for Separation from the military. I would then have a AdminSep due to Mental Health reasons, which will follow me for the rest of my life. I am afraid of how this would affect me for my future in things like employment.

I don't know what to do. I don't know how to make it stop.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 01:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful posts:

[Article on coping](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2qv5o6/navigating_that_frightening_time_of_pregnancy/)

[Focusing on pregnancy "superfoods"](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2qt9q6/request_pregnancy_and_bn/)

[Handling body changes in pregnancy](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2r5s9c/request_recovering_from_an_ed_and_thinking_about/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: 25 weeks pregnant and afraid of relapse. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 01:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Forgive me if this post makes little sense. I'm trying to be as vague as possible as this is my first post here.

For some context, I am 21 years old and I have struggled with these disorders since I was a kid. I was underweight for many years and after high school I "recovered", meaning I stopped restricting/purging. I of course gained a lot of weight. While I still struggled with my body image and I still practiced some bad habits, no one questioned whether I was sick anymore.

I got married in August of last year and at that time I was considered slightly overweight. I struggled with that, of course. I was okay though, I was simply living and being happy. As the title says, I'm 25 weeks pregnant now and I actually weigh less than I did when I first became pregnant (in September) due to extreme and constant morning sickness. 

I eat when I'm hungry (and I'm not often) and I try so hard to eat things that I know will help my baby grow. But now those habits are resurfacing, even if in a different way. 

While I don't restrict myself, I am obsessing over what goes into my body. I would rather eat nothing but an apple and bowl of shredded wheat all day than eat something the stereotypical "unhealthy person" would eat, if that makes sense. I know it doesn't make sense, though. 

I'm trying to be healthy for my baby, completely to a fault. I'm afraid that this will evolve into a full-fledged eating disorder again.


Has anyone been in my position? Please, give me any advice you have. It will be SO appreciated.

TL;DR I was recovered mostly, became pregnant and began obsessing over food again. I need to be healthy for my baby but I'm afraid of developing a disorder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I am a bulimic. I need some advice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 02:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello reddit, I am very new to reddit, so forgive me if I am somewhat bad at posting. 

My story starts when I was a Senior in high school. At the time I was studying and preparing for college and exams. But it was also during that time that I had my first real relationship. My ex boyfriend was an international student in his 2nd year of college, neither my family nor I thought that our relationship would last very long. He was going to leave in a year, but somehow because of me he decided to stay longer. I loved him, and thats probably hard for a lot of people to understand considering what he encouraged me to do. He was from a culture where skinny was everything. If you weren't skinny then you weren't beautiful. If you weren't skinny then you were a nobody. Unfortunately I wasn't. I never really was skinny growing up, and I really didn't let it get it me. But after dating him for a couple months, he started pushing me to eat less and exercise more. At first I thought he was just concerned for me health, but then one day he just blatantly told me that he told I was fat. Of course like most girls I was mad that he would say something so mean and hurtful. But then I went to his home country the summer I graduated high school, and I saw where he got his idea of beauty from. This sight, along with his consistent comments on my weight, pushed me to lose weight. I kept telling myself I would lose ten pounds and stop. Once I lost ten pounds I would try to lose another ten, then another ten, until I got to the point where I was skinny, but always sluggish and tired. I stopped eating and stopped exercising, because i just didn't have the energy to do so anymore. My family were all worried about me, but he was proud. Proud that his girlfriend was "beautiful" now. 

Eventually my mother told me that if I didn't start to eat, she would hospitalize me. So that's what I did. I ate and ate, and then threw it all up. I did this going all through college. Even after we broke up, I couldn't stop. I tried stopping so many times, but I don't know why I can't. Now I am with a great guy. He doesn't know this about me. But I really want to stop. 

Please reddit, can you give me some advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to help my parents help me in recovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 17:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got diagnosed with anorexia for about 5 years ago, and have since then gone through different phrases, both ups and downs. I quit treatment a short while after the got the diagnosis. 

Over the last years I've had more tendencies towards bulimia and I've also gained a lot of weight. I've been off and on recovering by myself for a couple a years, but the longest time I think I've managed to pull off without a b/p is x weeks. 

My family knows about my situation, and when an situation occurs the response is usually anger (I don't blame them though, also, they have been in family counselling.). But I also feel frustrated that my mom doesn't do anything for helping me. 

How can i seek her help more? (I'm not even sure if it's possible to get more help. Also, we can't afford any treatment places etc.)

I've tried rooting out my triggers but I can't seem to find them. Mainly it seems like stress, but also being at home. (I'm currently living at my mom, as i'm 16. Also my mom is always asking me after meals about "how many calories was in that? etc, because she have started calculated all of her meals and is always informing me about it. which is really triggering) 

Maybe it's because i find my family situation stressful. (The days I'm not home until eight is usually the days I don't binge.. but i can't do this everyday.)

Is it ACTUALLY possible to recover?
How can i seek more help from my mom regarding helping me recovering from bulimia?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eating Disorder Awareness Week: Does how you feel determine what you eat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 13:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Advice on how to manage anger and stay motivated in inpatient treatment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 20:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently being treated in an inpatient care facility against my will. I do wish to get better and I understand that my condition is serious. But I wish to get help in the outpatient care instead.

I got where I am right now by seeking that help, but since my physical condition was so severe, right there and then, they chose to put me in here.

How do I deal with the anger I feel? I feel like I have not been heard since they don't believe that I want help, but would prefer to be able to live at home. I am also being told that I would not be able to do it on the outside. Something I object to. I have the motivation to do it. The will.

I grew up with a sister with anorexia and later on bulimia and feel very uneasy around others with the diagnosis. I feel triggered all the time, both because of the horrible years with my sister's problems, but also because I, like many others, compare myself to the others patients all the time. I feel like I will only get more difficult thoughts and have my behaviour around food worsened.

How should I think about all of this to be able to cope and not let the anger and angst get the better of me?

I am diagnosed with anorexia nervosa (binge/purge type). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to deal with triggers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 10:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Everything triggers me. hearing people mention weight, sizes, calories, seeing people thinner, everything. 

How can I deal with this in a positive way and avoid a relapse? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How can I help my girlfriend get help with EDNOS? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 02:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend has EDNOS. 

I fell madly in love with my girlfriend more than a year ago. We have been through and incredible amount together, and I don't want to spend a moment without her. I'm looking for advice on what I can do to make everything better. Her parents and friends in school do not know about this, and she is mortified that anyone will find out. We have had talks about going to see a specialist, or even just a regular therapist to talk through some of it but she doesn't want to talk with anyone else. She is at a healthy weight but struggles almost every day getting down food that isn't enough. 

Over the past few months I have been doing some research on it all, searching for things such as "How to help your girlfriend with an eating disorder" and "Eating disorder self-recovery". I have found lots of good ideas and tips of sorts, but I am looking for some more personal advice. I want to help make everything better, and I am terrified that I will fail at it.

Does anyone have advice on how else I can help her? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: When to share? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 23:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi /r/EatingDisorders -- I'm writing for some feedback from other people -- how do you bring this up to a new s/o. I have been seeing someone for about 2 months, and have come close to telling him about my history/current struggles with bulimia... but couldn't quite get it out. to be perfectly honest, i am scared about his reaction. (My last boyfriend was aware of, and very supportive of my recovery most of the time, but got so angry with me when i back slipped, as if i were doing it to spite him...... it wasn't helpful at all, and made me very guarded about letting anyone else know, for fear of an angry reaction. Its so hard to explain to other people who have never been through it themselves)

in this new relationship, i have been completely honest with him about EVERYTHING, except this. I feel like i may be lying by omission with this one, since its a doozy...

how long have you given a relationship before letting someone in on your ED struggles?

xx thanks for your help.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How do I get someone to accept and seek help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 23:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was wondering if anorexia is considered suicidal behavior. Someone very close to me, but much older is suffering. She is getting worse and worse and I can see that the disorder is linked to depression. I am depressed myself and i am familiar with obsessive weight loss, but not to such an extent. This lady is incredible and such a wonderful person and she told me about her problem. seeing a therapist doesn't always help and I can imagine she feels even more alone than I do. I just want her to live regardless of the pain she's feeling but i'm not sure. the weight of this world is a lot to bear. I can't be helpful because i'm just a dumb 20 year old and i'm crazy. So when she starts talking about death i start to panic. I am so worried. 

I was wondering if there is anything i can do. like i'm not going to send her to a psychiatric ward, that place is awful and causes more problems than anything else. But i want her to live i just want her to live. Is that selfish? i just love her and i'm confused.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Is it possible to get over an ED without addressing the "root issues"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 23:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So my situation is that I know the "root cause" is probably my abusive parents. But there's really not much I can do about it until I go off to college in five months. IDK if it's even possible to get over my ED when I can do nothing about the "deeper issues" so to say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Sister Cutting Off Communication </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 10:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My sister is battling Anorexia.  She's started screening my phone calls.  I am too messed up to jump in to the fray again or fly a thousand miles to check up on her.  I can tell it's bad because this is the behavior she does when she relapses.

I am tempted to send an honest email to her about how the family loves her but thoughts won't make her well,  etc.  I am pretty fed up and while I will be there for her always, I can't try and intercede in her life.  Anyone have any thoughts or suggestions?  How does a brother wade through all of this? 

As an aside, my parents are basically broke and can't afford to send her to treatment again.  If she doesn't step up then she'll be in the hospital again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How can I deal with the guilt of eating? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 10:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was recently put on seroquel to help with my suicidal depression. It's actually working (most meds don't) and it's also helping to force me to take in a decent amount of calories because it causes increased appetite. The problem I'm having now is that I'm upping my exercise out of guilt but it's to an unhealthy extent. I have this thing where I think I can feel the fat growing on my hips and arms after I eat, in my mind I can see it. It's actually starting to not feel as bad now that I'm on the new med but it's still there and I can't keep working out till I throw up just to ease the guilt from eating a normal meal. That's not a good long term solution.

I tried googling it but that wasn't very helpful. What other ways can I deal with the guilt of eating an adequate amount of calories?

Oh and I should probably mention I'm trying to lose some (more) weight. That's how all this started again. That's how it always starts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How can I help my girlfriend who is dealing with bulimia? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 21:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I started dating a girl I am in love with now. She's been dealing with bulimia for longer than we've been dating and only in the past year has accepted it for the problem it is. 

The only thing is she's afraid to get help for it because of fear or what her family and friends will say, I assume. It seemed as if it had been getting better in the past month, but now for some reason it seems to be getting bad again. She's extremely smart but she can't seem to find away to bring herself to seek professional help. 

I just want to know if anyone had any ideas, or tips on what I can do as her boyfriend to help convince her to get the help to needs. Or if not just things I can do to maybe help her a day by day. I know it's something that she has to deal with in her own mind and things I do help very little if at all. (e.g. like me telling her she's beautiful and that I love her) I love her very much and just want her to get better because I know she's suffering with this illness. 

How can I do my best to support her, encourage her to get help, and help her get well in her recovery? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Support for a Friend, is friend asking for help or not? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 17:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
A very close friend of mine is troubled by depression and a crippling negative view of their body. After a history of anorexia, self depreciation and being incredibly withdrawn they confided their present fears to me not so long ago; struggling with how they look   feel, and being tempted to slip back into their anorexic tendencies.

Being a very close friend of mine I've let it known many times that not only do I adore them, but that I am there for them if they ever need me. I myself do have some experience with depression, however in this case, being on the other side of the fence, I am unsure how to advise   proceed. I appreciate that they need professional help which they're currently receiving but my question is simply how can I help?

Having thought about it I may be making the incorrect assumption that they even want my advice. Perhaps they're just sharing so that I can better understand where they're at. On many occasions this year I've unsuccessfully tried to connect with said person and this may just be their way of making me understand. On the other hand I have been turned to, and this does sound like a cry for help. 

I'd appreciate any and all opinions on how I can best offer my support as I am taking this very seriously. Being somewhat of a blunt-tool of a man the last thing I want to do is say something insensitive when attempting to offer my heartfelt support. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I'm not in her shoes, wanting programs that don't focus on the ED, but can help with understanding the emotions that drive the ED. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 17:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
The reason I am writing this is because reddit is the open arena of knowledge and 3/10 times depending on the subreddit you're able to get some insight.

I've been with my SO for about a year and a few months, we've been friends for around 8, she told me in confidence, she has struggled with anorexia and bulimia for years, about 3 months into us breaking the friendship barrier. 

Being an addict that is in recovery 3+ years (every drug on the face of the planet ) I obviously realize that every human is different and that all I can do is be supportive, and I am nothing but be supportive. 

It's hard for me to put what is going on into words but... here's the reason I need insight. She's a single mom and its difficult for her to go into treatment, she had been doing internet meetings but from what I can deduce it makes things worse and being part of an NA program I've been to those meetings in real life where there is no help.. 

What I am asking is...

Does anyone have any suggestions where people have been in a program where it's not about what you ate today or what you have purged today? People that have felt the same way and can talk about why.... Because it worked for me.... 

In my experience face to face meetings were better  for my recovery. I want something similar for her. (Denver Area)

Let me know I appreciate EVERY idea

Thank You </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to improve my relationship while in recovery? ED thoughts surface a lot. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 17:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any advice on how to improve my relationship while in recovery? 

My boyfriend of two years has been super helpful and goes to counseling with me, but I still feel like the disordered/negative thoughts still get in the way? 

How can I keep the relationship strong throughout this process? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How soon should I start to "get back out there" during recovery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 17:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

How soon should I start to "get back out there" during recovery? Should I avoid social situations or fake it until I make it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> #NEDAwareness Week: Three Reasons Why You Should Choose Recovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 01:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Written by Keara Hozella in Quirky Daily. Link at bottom.

This upcoming week is National Eating Disorders Awareness (NEDA) Week in the U.S. While this week may signify just yet another cause for some, to others (including me), the message it carries is extremely imperative. Its crucial to get the word out about this sometimes stigmatized form of mental illness.


This years theme for NEDAwareness week is I had no idea, according to the National Eating Disorders Association website. This years theme includes, focusing on the importance of early intervention and recognizing the diverse experiences of people personally affected by disordered eating, also according to the site.


NEDAwareness Week is vital because of the huge number of people eating disorders affect. According to the National Association of Anorexia Nervosa and Associated Disorders, Up to 24 million people of all ages and genders suffer from an eating disorder (anorexia, bulimia and binge eating disorder) in the U.S., which proves just how prevalent eating disorders are in the world. Notice how the statistic says all ages and genders. Eating disorders are not limited to illnesses that affect teenage girls. There isnt a stereotype for eating disorders; they can affect and ruin the life of any individual. That statistic alone should be enough to start talking about eating disorders and stop keeping them a secret.


The stigma that surrounds any kind of mental illness can prevent someone who needs help from getting it. Its reprehensible, and something that needs to be stopped. Talking about mental illnesses, raising awareness, and supporting those you know are struggling can aid in eliminating unnecessary shame and guilt over having a mental illness.

While this article is an effort to spread the word and bring attention to NEDAwareness Week, it is also a reminder as to why recovering from this horrific illness is worth it. These reasons are brought to you by me, a woman who has been in recovery from an eating disorder for three years.

**Trigger Warning (TW) for talk of eating disorders and some behaviors.**


**Reason #1: To improve your health, regardless of what it may have been like with your disorder.**

Recovery from an eating disorder can bring nothing but improved health for you. While some people may say that they never had a cold or that they felt supremely healthy while in the depths of their disorder, this doesnt necessarily mean that their immune system or health were at their best. Its likely that the immune system was suppressed in order to make up for the body shutting down in other ways. Recovering from an eating disorder can reverse or slow the effects of osteoporosis, improve the immune systems function, and generate a positive shift in overall mental and physical health. Choosing recovery means literally saving your life.

**Reason #2: To be able to truly experience life.**

Spending so much time focusing on your disorder robs you of the pleasures of everyday life. You arent focused on keeping connections with friends and enjoying your life in the depths of an eating disorder because youre too worried and fixated on what you had, or didnt have, for breakfast. Your mind cannot juggle so many negative thoughts and calorie counts at once, therefore being entrenched in the world of the disorder means being completely removed from the realm of real life. It may sound clich to say, but you truly are a shell of a person with an eating disorder. Youre not really present in any situation due to obsessive thoughts of food. Choosing recovery means being able to concentrate on the things that matter to you. For me, this meant strengthening relationships with friends and family members that I had neglected, and graduating from college in the fall 2014 semester. I never would have been able to accomplish those things while in the hell of my eating disorder. Choose recovery to fully participate in your own life.

**Reason #3: To be able to say, Im in recovery/Ive overcome my eating disorder.**

I wont lie and say that recovering from my eating disorder was a smooth and effortless process. It was the most difficult thing Ive ever attempted to defeat in my life.  Choosing recovery every day is still a struggle, even after an inpatient stay that I swore I would never repeat. Recovery meant being able to admit that I had some issues to sort through and address. It was strangely empowering because I didnt have to keep up the faade that I had created while struggling with anorexia. Choosing recovery means admitting to having a problem. This admission is terrifying, but liberating. Acknowledging your issues with food and talking about your eating disorder are the first steps to getting help and choosing recovery.


The wording throughout this article is intentional. The disorder is not your fault in any way, but deciding to recover from it is your decision. You have to choose recovery every day. It is an arduous task, but one that doesnt need to be completed alone. Full recovery is possible and worth every bite, therapy session, and tear. Please look for the support of medical professionals, family members, friends, and trusted people in your life to guide you through the process. Please visit the National Eating Disorders Association, the National Association of Anorexia Nervosa and Associated Disorders, or call the NEDA Helpline at 1-(800)-931-2237 to find resources and get help.

- See more at: http://quirkydaily.com/nedawareness-week-three-reasons-choose-recovery/#sthash.QmMdut0N.dpuf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feb 22-28 2015 is National Eating Disorders Awareness Week, National Eating Disorders Association, NEDA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 11:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: What to bring to treatment facility? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 11:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm finally getting into a residential program! Thanks, r/EDO!

Now, for those of you who have been inpatient or residential, what were you glad you had? What do you wish you'd brought?

Clearly rules differ between facilities, and inpatient is a lot stricter, but general ideas?

OP asks to be linked here, /u/DranoCleanse. Please share here and consider sending her a pm as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Question regarding scripts and walk in clinics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 11:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
I am away from my doctor and he told me that when it comes time to refill my prescription for my antidepressant (and sleep aid), that I can go to any clinic and tell them what's going on and they can refill it, as he cannot write enough refills for the time I am here.
Is this possible, will they write the script? 

I am also struggling with binge eating to the extreme and would like to try vyvanse as I have read here that it can help with food obsessions and curbing an appetite. I do not want to come across like I just want a high, but I do want to ask. What do you think is the best way to go about asking the clinic about getting this? 

I have 30 days left of pills left and really would like to treat my ED. I've tried therapy with a multitude of counselors and didn't get anywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I Have an EDNOS, but No Issues with Body Image? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 04:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently, I came to terms with the fact that I have been suffering symptoms of an eating disorder for a while. However, I am completely unconcerned with my body, and am very comfortable with how I look.

My eating disorder began when I was living in a very hostile housing situation. I would hide in my room all day when out of school and try to interact with my Dad and step mother as little as possible. As a result, I often ate less than a meal a day. At first, I felt every little hunger pang, but after three years of avoiding food just so that I could avoid people, I got used to it. Then I got to the point where I could no longer eat normally without feeling nauseas. My stomach wasn't used to a normal amount of food anymore. I didn't think much of it, and let it continue until I was 22 (about a month ago). I only began eating normally again because I realized what sort of damage I was doing to my body, and that it was affecting my mental health and ability to be logical.

So I'm wondering if there are others out there who have an eating disorder that started after a long period of unintentional starvation, and how they moved forward with recovery?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to stay sane while waiting for residential treatment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 13:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm supposed to start residential treatment for BN mid-March, because my new insurance doesn't kick in until then. I have a therapist, but I can't get a dietician or anything until then.

I'm really just wondering what you guys suggest to keep me a little more on track until I get help. Right now, I restrict to very safe foods and few calories all day, then B/P a ton in the evening. 

I just accidentally stayed up until 3am to do so, and I'm exhausted. I want it to stop now, not in March.

Does anyone have advice on how to handle this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Should I talk to someone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 11:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eight years ago, when I was in my early 20's, I suspected I might have an eating disorder. I was going through some major family issues that set my brothers and I into a tailspin (I don't want to get into details in case it triggers anyone else). My younger brother, one of my best friends, began using Meth. Somehow, unintentionally, I think that I also found some unhealthy ways of coping with the negative feelings I was having by counting and controlling calories.

Things progressed pretty quickly. In about 6 months I lost a lof of weight (I was barely at a healthy weight to begin with). My friends worried. My doctor worried. I told them all that I was fine; I just needed some time to cope.

I got married in the middle of all this. One night, shortly after my wedding and shortly after I'd moved across the country from my family and my problems, my new husband asked if I'd go out to get a drink with him. I didn't want to go because I was at my caloric limit for the day, but he pushed me into it. While out, I got pressured into ordering a drink. A vodka soda. I drank it and immediately insisted on going home because I was so disappointed with myself. I started crying. That's when I got the ultimatum: cut it out or go to treatment.

I started to really work on letting go and, slowly, I began to get better. Two years later I was back at a healthy weight. I began viewing that time as a blip; a time when I was stressed and undereating but not a TRUE eating disorder because I didn't think anorexia was something that could go away so easily.

Recently though, less than two weeks ago, I found out another traumatic piece of news. I found myself not wanting to eat. At first, it was normal this-is-stressful-and-I-have-no-appetite not eating, but it's now starting to look an awful lot like my behavior 8 years ago (only eating small, controlled amounts when I literally think I might pass out). Only now I'm older and I have a baby and a job and things I need to keep my shit together for. 

I want to just stop but I don't know how. What do I do?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Could my [32] wife [30] benefit from professional help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 11:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've been married for 4.5 years. We dated for a year before getting married. During our courtship and for a good year after we we married she was bulimic, throwing up on a regular basis. When I first met her she was a normal wieght. Currently, and for the past 3 years, she has stopped throwing up, is also a lot happier in my opinion, but has steadily gained weight and continues to do so. Currently she is just in the obese range in BMI.

I love her and I am concerned about her impulse control issues when it comes to food and eating. She eats salads, fruits, etc. but also cannot resist eating excessive amounts of sugar and sweet stuff. I don't know if these carried over from when she ate whatever she wanted and could just throw it up. She has admitted to me she has impulse control issues with her heating.

She desperately wants to lose her weight; hates herself for weighing what she does. I don't know how to help her and how to broach the subject of whether or not she needs professional help. Her weight is obviously a very sensitive issue. Also our relationship is on the brinks for other reasons (I have posted for advice on another subreddit). She works a stressful job and is not naturally inclined to physical exercise. 

How can I help her?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Getting back on track. Want to stop dieting/imbalanced eating, but afraid of weight gain. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 00:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi. I just got it through my thick head that dieting has been the cause of my frequent binges, so no more dieting. But I don't want to gain weight and I don't know how to live without either dieting or being obese (I've been doing it since 13, and I was a fat kid all my life before then). 

How can I stop dieting-imbalanced eating- without gaining weight? 

For those who have recovered, what is commonly recommended by dieticians for this? Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eating Disorders Awareness Week 2015, February 22-28 : National Association of Anorexia Nervosa and Associated Disorders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 13:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: 6 Months in and Need to Quit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 10:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lately I have been using binging/ purging as a stress relief method. I'm in my second year of college and everything is so overwhelming. I have never been good with managing my stress (in high school resorted to self harm). I've been able to avoid typical self harming in the past few years, but in the past year or so my stress over classes and studying has manifested in my body image. About 6 months ago I started purging. It was occasional at first but now I'm afraid it has gotten out of control. I'm now purging sometimes 3-4 times a day and I have developed really terrible binging habits. In only 6 months of this I have already lost weight and think I am developing ulcers in my esophagus (constant mild burning feeling towards the top of my sternum, burns when I drink hot/cold drinks). I don't even want to face what shape my teeth are in. 

I'm scared that these health issues are already becoming a problem and I don't want permanent damage. I need advice on how to stop this purging addiction and how to break my binging habits.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: New relationship- should I tell him? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 21:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So last summer I was in treatment for AN for 16 weeks. I still am not recovered. Anyway, I'm in a new relationship and I don't know if I should tell him about my ed. 

I don't think I'm ready to, but at the same time I don't want him to find out later and have him be mad or change his mind about me. I don't want him to worry about me or anything, but I have no idea if I should tell him. 

Should I tell him?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Struggling with needing to lose weight without resorting to ED behavior </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 21:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
I struggled with both anorexia and bulimia when I was in college. I slowly recovered thanks to the support of friends and those who had been through similar things. It's been about a year and a half now since I was at my worse, and I gained back the weight I lost and then somenow, I weigh more than I ever have. 

I struggle daily with thisI want to think I am beautiful, but lately it's been hard due to clothes constantly not fitting, etc. I know that I have gained this weight because I never transitioned from disordered behaviors to healthy ones: I just stopped completely, basically. 

Now, I basically eat what I want, and I'm positive I overeat. I don't exercise. I drink more than I should. I guess I just am really struggling with knowing I need to be healthy and not knowing how to approach it. 

I am so tempted to just do the same things I used to, because it seems so much easier than trying to moderate and make "healthy" choices. I'm not trying to be anywhere near as thin as I used to be, but I would like to be a healthy weight for my age/size, and I'm right at the cusp of that. 

How can I be comfortable with my appearance without resorting to ED behaviors? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Question about Impatience </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 09:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been dealing with overeating for some time now and lately the days in which I lose control are increasing which is especially disheartening since I've begun therapy to try and get better.  I'm so scared to become overweight that I just want to give up and go back to my old ways of restriction because even though I was still miserable then at least I was where I wanted to be weight-wise.  How do you all manage to stay motivated and not lose all hope when bad days begin to outweigh the good days?  Does anyone else sometimes feel that you are self sabotaging yourself in hopes that you actually will become an outcast and people will no longer hold you to the standards of thinness that are deemed desirable in this society? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Overcame b/p, but now regurgitating </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 21:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't seem to find any stories about people in bulimia recovery who are also now /unintentionally/ purging, but that's precisely what's happening to me. I don't think it has anything to do with the size of my meals (or stomach, for that matter) as I've been following a healthy non-ED diet. 

Is this something related to digestion? I hear horror stories about bulimic intestines "shutting down," but I never took it to heart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I'm started to get a little scared of my eating habits and thoughts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 21:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a woman in her early 20s. I recently lost some weight through exercise and eating better (some calorie counting for two weeks, and I think it triggered my development of weird eating habits because it was the first time I really became aware of calories). As I got near my weight loss goal, it moved away from what I looked like and became like a game with the various numbers. I am normal weight by BMI or a little below. Sometimes I look at the number on the scale or my body in the mirror and think I need gain some weight, but another part of me is uncomfortable with that.

I don't count calories, but I find myself trying to tally (no official count, but I have to fight myself at night not to lie there working out caloric estimates for the day). I think I undereat but I don't know. I feel like I think about food a lot. I get kind of obsessive about new recipes and cooking, almost a little out of control in my thoughts at times. I wake up in the night and have to force myself not to start planning out breakfast (and then bargaining with myself and making changes to the plan). I have a hard time stopping thinking about food when my meal is finished. Sometimes I'll portion out reasonable amounts for leftovers, but halve the amount when it actually comes time to eat it. Sometimes I'll take a bite of something and decide, while chewing, that it isn't worth the calories, so I spit it out. I misrepresent my eating to people, claiming I had a snack or am fairly full when I didn't and I'm not. I adjust the day's eating if I'm going to eat out.

I feel like my eating and thinking has gotten disordered, and I'm scared of the realization that, while I think I should work to change it, part of me doesn't want to because admitting it's a problem is scary and the idea of getting heavy again or outgrowing my new clothes is scary, too.

Do you think I am developing an eating disorder? Does you have any recommendations for me?


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Looking for anyone who has residential treatment experiences in Monarch Cove (Monterey, California?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 19:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking at the Monarch Cove facility in Monterey, CA. 

Does anyone have any experience with them? 
How is the residential program? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Documentary Filmmaker Looking for Interview Subjects </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 23:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
I'm a senior at Tufts University near Boston. I'm currently working on a documentary on eating disorders and body image issues in men. As someone recovering from eating issues myself, this project is near and dear to my heart. 

I'm looking for male interview subjects around the Boston area with whom I can speak on camera. If necessary, we can talk about face/voice distortion to maintain anonymity. It's for a good cause and I hope this sub can help me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Having trouble affording food </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 08:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really have many other people here to talk to who will really understand me. I lost my job at the end of December... since I have been desperately trying to get my Etsy shop up and running, but it's been difficult because I am working with literally zero funds at the moment, except the itty bitty bits of money I make from it here and there.

This situation has thrown me (unintentionally) right back into not eating. Simply because I cannot afford food. My refrigerator is completely empty, and my weight is dropping back down again... I was doing so well, SO well... and now circumstances have thrown me into this situation and I don't even want to be here. 

Does anyone have any recommendations for what I can do or how to eat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I just found out my girlfriend is battling anorexia, how do I talk to her about this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 08:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend is battling anorexia, and I just found out a few hours ago. She's going to be up in a few hours, and I want to talk to her about it, but I have no idea how to.

She means everything to me, and it's killing me inside thinking of losing her. How do I go about this? I tell her every day that she's all I want, that she's good enough. I just don't know what to say that will help that I already haven't. 

I'm scared. Beyond scared. Of me knowing making it worse. Of me losing her. I.. I don't know what to do. So, someone, anyone, please. Give me any suggestions you can think of to go about this.

She's the only person I have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: When is residential right? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 19:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Backstory: I was diagnosed with BN about 20 months ago. At that time, I wasn't underweight, but my behaviors forced me to drop out of college, so I entered a PHP/IOP program. I learned a lot, and left after 2 months with few behaviors. The past 6 months, I've been trying to lose weight by dieting, and succeeding. More recently, I experienced a significant trauma. I've been back in my EDO for about a month, and already very behind in school. I can't control myself. I've lost a little more weight, and now I'm hovering just above underweight. I'm not feeling healthy.

I'm about to start weekly therapy (with an EDO-supportive therapist), but I'm wondering if my situation warrants residential treatment, if I can afford it. What do you guys think? I'm only a month relapsed, but I know the trauma that started it will take a lot of work. I'm also finding it impossible to eat meals and snacks normally without help. Any advice/experiences are welcome.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to support my girlfriend who is facing a possible relapse and intimacy issues </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 16:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GF and I are in college now. In high school she had serious problems with anorexia and bulimia. Now it seems she is facing terrible problems again even though she has been better (for the most part) for close to two years. 

She says she has gained significant weight in the past few months, but I haven't noticed it. I don't know if she's actually monitoring her weight closely, or if it's in her head. She refuses to have sex or even too much general physical contact. I am completely okay with this, as I love the fucking hell out of this girl and only want her to get better. 

She becomes very upset when I compliment her, and I must stress that I do find her very very attractive. She is afraid that she will inevitably gain weight and I will eventually leave her. I've tried to explain that I love her too much for that, but she won't listen. 

She is seeking professional help, but she also says she wants to see less of me. I think I make her think about sex and love and physical attraction, and she just wants to forget about all of that. 

What should I do? How can I help do my part? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I feel triggered after getting my wisdom teeth removed and don't want to relapse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 16:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys! I'm currently 20, I had an eating disorder/anorexia from the time I was 13-15, was almost hospitalized. 

I had an amazing recovery and now have one of the healthiest body images and eating habits of everyone I know. Some things I still don't do are: diet, weigh myself, fast on holidays, or count calories.

A week ago I got wisdom teeth surgery. I have an extreme health phobia and am paranoid about the holes getting food in them or getting a dry socket, which has led me to heavily restrict my eating down to still all liquids. this is highly triggering for me, and I feel this retraction of eating bringing all the memories, moods, and feelings back of my ED. 

I haven't relapsed in these 5 years, but once I stop eating, it gets so difficult for me to start, especially when i have a (somewhat) valid excuse.

Any advice would be amazing, my school's counselors aren't open now and I'm panicking. 

How can I fight through this and help myself prevent a relapse? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: First steps for bulimia recovery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 03:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have strugglled with bulimia for 6 years now. It can now be up to 10 + times a day that I purge, depending on when and what I have eaten or drank. I am now at a point where I dont binge, but if I eat or drink anything, no matter how hard I try to keep it down, the anxiety or persistant bloating feeling will not let me. I do not even have to force myself to vomit, I just think about it and it happens. I have done extreme damage to my teeth, which has included the removal of two molars, multiple root canals and cavities. I want help, and I want to fix this. What are the first steps, and what kind of internal damage have I done. I am also nervous about going to the doctor or telling my partner, are these things that I will need to do if I wish to recover? Thanks.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 01:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do read the sticky on Hunger Hormones at the top of this subreddit. 

Other hopefully helpful posts:

[Feeling fat](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2qvpxj/request_significant_other_has_an_unhealthy/)

[Can beat your ED](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1k9vgu/post_request_just_sharing_a_little_you_can/)

[Improving body image](https://www.nationaleatingdisorders.org/10-will-powers-improving-body-image) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: need advice on how to build a sustainable relationship with my OA (overeater's anonymous) sponsor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 23:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just started working a twelve step program with this incredible group of women and men in my area. One of the women in the group, after being asked by my temporary (starting out) sponsor if she was free to help out, offered to sponsor me. Briefly, a sponsor is someone who has achieved abstinence with the substance for at least 30 days and is willing to help a new member take their first steps in the program, keep them accountable, take phone calls and texts from them, and offer them advice. 

My situation is this: my sponsor and I don't know each other well, and therefore our relationship is kind of formal and stiff at the moment. I have a hard time developing rapport with someone immediately (it takes me awhile to become emotionally open with people), but I would like to begin to build a rewarding relationship with this woman that is ultimately fulfilling not just for me, but for her as well. I want her to be able to get something from this sponsor relationship. 


How can I give back to her? Show her she is appreciated? Connect with her more deeply? 

I've been asking her for advice and kind of keeping her updated on my habits, as well as talking to her about what's going on with her life, but I want our connection to be a bit more rewarding than it is purely acquaintanceship-formal. After all, we can connect over needing the 12-step program in our lives and working towards changing our lives for the better. 

Any advice appreciated for forging a more rewarding connection! Especially one where she feels like she, as a sponsor, is getting something out of our relationship. 

tl;dr: 60/f woman is sponsoring me [21/f] through 12-step program. want to be able to connect with her more deeply and forge a relationship that is sustainable, rewarding for HER as well as ME, more close than it is formal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Overcame Anorexia, Now Have Erratic Eating Habits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 00:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi everyone!

First time posting here. So about 5-6 years ago I dealt with anorexia and lost a lot of weight and was very thin. I needed to gain weight back so I did, and now I am in the healthy weight range.

However, my eating habits are not healthy at all. In fact, they are incredibly erratic, and I am concerned about it.

First of all, even though I am a healthy weight, I still cannot see my size positively. Most of the time, I view myself as overweight or obese, and even though the numbers say I'm not (and everyone around me says I'm not) I'm incapable of perceiving myself properly. Every once in a while I'll have days where I can't take how "fat" I feel and will eat a dangerously low number of calories. Other days, I will become obsessed with certain foods and feel the need to eat them constantly. I'll decide I need to eat them right now, and that I have to eat it on any and all things I can. And I'll end up binging on these foods until I feel awful about myself.

I stay in the healthy weight range because I do this weird yo-yo all the time- of restricting my intake, and alternating that with these gross binges on weird food combinations.

And then at the end of the day I feel bad because I still think I'm fat.

Does anyone have any advice?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My SO has an eating disorder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 00:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, thanks in advance for reading/commenting   sorry for the wall of text, please read it though!

So a little background info: My SO is a 16y/o female who has an eating disorder. It all started 2 years ago, she had some kind of virus/disease that woud make her stomach very fragile, she would return all the food she was given... Doctors tried   the disease went away, but she never really recovered, after eating she keeps feeling like she needs to throw up.

Now, her relationship with her mother is... poor... her mother calls her fat   questions everything she eats, telling her she'll get fat if she eats too much... I think this is the first cause (and main cause) why she keeps throwing up.

She also went to see a therapist, who said it could have something to do with her best friend commiting suicide while she was in the hospital. Because she always blames herself for not being able to attend the funeral. Her mom recently told her she shouldn't see the therapist anymore ecause it wasn't helping, I think it helped a lot because she could really talk to the therapist   always felt better afterwards.

Lastly she is really insecure   has never admitted to having an eating disorder, I always supported her   today she admitted that she throws up because she doesn't wanna get fat   that she sometimes forces herself to throw up, but she can no longer feel the difference between throwing up by force or because she feels bad, because food still makes her feel bad.

To clarify: when she eats she feels bad   throws up, but she doesn't know if she feels bad because of the disease or because she doesn't want to be fat.

She is not fat, but she thinks she is...

We haven't been in a relationship for that long, but since she feels she can talk to me about it   tell me secrets she hasn't told anyone in 2 years I feel like I'm the only person who can help her...

Guys... I don't know what to do... I really need some advice here... She is an amazing girl and she deserves nothing more than to be happy about her body   feel confident... I just don't know how to help her... any suggestions?

Thanks guys!

ps: Telling anyone about what's really going on is NOT an option, she trusts me   there is no way I a breaking her trust.

Edited to add: Please notify /u/HashtagThrowaway3 if you respond </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My girlfriend told me she struggles with binge eating-how can I help her? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 17:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend has been telling me that she's had depression and some self-esteem issues, but recently told me it was more than that and she actually has a binge eating problem. I've never dealt with anything like this before, and have absolutely no idea how I can help her.

She's been going through a lot recently and is constantly stressed out - I'm assuming that's a part of it? I've been trying to take her out to movies, the bar, downtown, whatever - but she doesn't seem to want to go out much anymore.

Today she told me that she completely binged yesterday and the day before (I was in class so wasn't aware), and she has decided to give me most of her food and gave me her credit card so that she can't buy any more (she's with me more often than not, so I'll start buying everything on her behalf). 

I'm going to start cooking her some healthy meals when I can, but I really want her to be able to handle it on her own eventually.

Does anyone have any advice on how else I can help her?

She signed up for a group counseling session that starts next week, but I want to know what I can do before that to help her out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How do I finally tell someone that I'm struggling with an disordered eating? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 03:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have always struggled with being a picky eater, but it has gotten to an all time low.

It has been months since I've eaten what many call regular. This is very usual for me.

The problem is that no one knows about it, and even the people who do know I struggle with eating (ex: my mom and step dad), don't know how bad it has actually gotten. 

Whenever I work during the day, my friends at work see me eating everyday at my shift meal. But what they don't know is that when they see me outside of work, I am undereating.

I feel tired, weak, and dizzy all of the time, and I need help. But, I'm scared that they won't take me seriously or they will think I'm being overly dramatic.

I need to tell someone because I can't get over this problem alone. I just want normal eating habits so badly.

How can I overcome being a picky eater? At least be less picky?

How can I eat more regularly?

How can I be stronger and avoid being weak and dizzy?

How do I tell someone, whom should I tell, and how can I be sure to be heard, or taken seriously?

Any help or advice would be greatly appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My best friend seems to have bulimia, how can i help her? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 21:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my best friend (17-18, F) started losing a whole lot of weight since around September of 2013, so much so that it worried her family and close friends. That peaked at some point but recently she's been eating a bit healthier and has gained a bit of weight. Just a couple weeks ago her older sister told me (15-16, M) that she and her parents have caught her throwing up the food she's eaten in the bathroom a couple times, so it seems to have turned into bulimia. She denies it even when they catch her in the act.  They went to a doctor and now no one in the family closes the door when going to the toilet. 

She herself doesn't know that i know any of this and knowing her, doesn't want me to. But i want to be of help. This is one of the most important people in my life and i don't want to see her health and life going downhill. I want to help but I'm not sure how. 

Any advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> REquest: Weightwatcher's superbowl commercial and its affect on anorexia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 15:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who's recovering from being underweight myself, the Weightwatcher's commercial during the superbowl did a pretty good job at stressing me out. I didn't eat anything for the rest of that day, but I felt like reminding myself and this sub to not let little things trigger us back into the disorder. 

Remember: there's no reason to be afraid of regular food. From a business perspective, this ad exists only to scare people, which only acts as a tool for making money.

What were your thoughts on this commercial? 

How do you handle things like this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: HELP - My sister has an eating disorder, and I think we've been handling it the wrong way. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 12:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello,

Im a 27 year old guy who has a 18 year old sister with an eating disorder.

Me and my family found out about a year and a half ago. Her disorder has been categorized as anorexia.

Shes had a lot of friends let her down all through her life, and is a very sensitive person. She has almost no self worth or self confidence as of now. She has nightly fits, which could be described as similar to anxiety attacks. They usually come after shes eaten (she doesnt eat much) or right before sleeping. She tense up, shes recently began also holding her breath. She gets these thoughts in her head that she wants to disappear, that it would be better if she werent here. I know what those are signs of. I suffer from anxiety myself, but thats besides the point.

She is seeing a psychiatrist, and shes been at some brain scanning treatment as well, which she has now stopped. She is getting help, but Im thinking its the wrong kind of help, but Im trying to get my parents to understand that now.

What Im here to ask from you, is to get some perspective on some things. Recently Ive beginning to think we, as a family, has been handling her eating disorder in a very wrongly fashion.

What Ive beginning to realize is that weve trying our best to remove all triggers around her. She gets to decide whats for dinner, every meal is constructed to get her to eat. Theres a lot of mmm and this is good going on. She is consulted on whats for dinner, every single night.

Everybody in the apartment (I dont live at home, but when Im home, its expected from me as well) is behaving, as to not trigger her fits.

Which usually comes anyway.

I want to say that theres a lot of love and support. Were all trying to help her, but Im just starting to believe, that what were really doing, is creating a reality around her, where she can live with her condition, which just makes it worse.

When I had anxiety, I could theoretically just avoid any triggers, and basically live with the condition my entire life. Problem was that one of the triggers was going to bed, so I sort of had to deal with it.

Im not sure what Im asking here. What Im thinking is, that I have to talk to my parents, and get them to understand that they cant design every meal around my sister.

It just seems to me, that were creating an environment where her eating disorder will thrive, and not get better.

Another thing Im considering is, that if my parents dont realize this, and wont get her the help she needs, that I have to tell them, that I wont be part of treating her like this anymore. Talk to her, and explain to her, that Im there for her, but that I believe that the way theyre going about things now, is more hurtful than helpful.

Not saying Ill just bail. But right now I think Im part of keeping her in, or worsening, her condition.

My parents think shes doing better, but I think that its just because theyve gotten effective as removing any trigger, which just makes it hard for everybody to live like a normal person.

I KNOW we have to get her some help, thats specialized in dealing with eating disorders, so I guess what Im asking is, if my suspicion about the way were going around this at home, seems right? Or if Im completely off the charts? What should I do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Crafting   Recovery: manual and visual aids to help recovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 00:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
I'm currently in recovery for bulimia, anorexia, and self harm. I have a history of depression and anxiety and I've been working with my therapist and psychiatrist to come up with new "rituals" or behaviors to replace some of the more destructive things I've used to cope in the past.

One of the things that I've found to be really helpful overall is crafting - specifically knitting or crocheting because it keeps your hands busy and can be pretty meditative. Someone suggested a few months back a craft idea about creating paper chains to track your progress with recovery (each chain is a day, colors represent different things). 

I'd be interested to hear if anyone has other visual aids that help with recovery? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Additional Ways to Support My Girlfriend in Recovery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 02:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keeping this short. I've just started dating a girl who's in recovery from anorexia and bulimia. I'm looking for suggestions on what, and what NOT, to say and do. She eats well and is in good health, and I want to support her in that. She's great about the fact that I have no idea what to say or do, and she's very happy that I ask about what foods she'd like to eat, if she has any aversions, if I can cook for her, etc. She responds really positively to being called beautiful (it's not something she heard often in past relationships, I think) but I want to know what else might be helpful to say to remind her that I think she's absolutely amazing exactly how she is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Is therapy worth it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 12:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've relapsed pretty badly last summer and it recently got worse this past month. I would normally just talk it out with close friends but at this point I think I've become a bother to them. I got tired of the "just love yourself" quotes that they stole from tumblr. I have no family support either. They're part of the reason why I relapsed.

I'm heavily considering therapy at my college campus but I'm absolutely terrified and don't know what to expect. Has anyone been through therapy? Do you recommend it? What was it like?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 23:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful posts:

[Deciding to recover](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2s5uti/request_help_how_do_i_decide_to_recover_bulimia/)

[Books for BED](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2se4oq/request_suggested_websites_or_books_for_dealing/)

[Laxative abuse](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2ecubf/request_have_been_using_laxatives_to_diet_i_cant/)

[another on laxatives](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1xlmma/request_advice_on_coming_off_laxatives/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: ED and other concurring addictions, including amphetamine addiction and alcoholism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 23:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
For the last ~7 years I've had several entwined problems: alcoholism, anorexia-turned-bulimia, and an amphetamine addiction.

Due to lack of funds and support, I've only received a little formal help for the former two; I've mostly been left to deal on my own.
I eventually quit the speed which was difficult, but very final. It's not there? Well, not an option then. I still miss it sometimes, but it's mostly very liberating.

That leaves the drinking and ED.

At my worst as a bulimic, emptying my bank account to go on binges, purging many times a day. I feared for my life.

Overall, I've recovered pretty remarkably- I still think about the consequences of what I do and don't eat on a near-daily basis, but I only truly purge-relapse once every few months.

I've recently been on a serious sobriety binge, which is glorious, but I find that as soon as that one vice lessens, my preoccupations with food burn a little brighter until I eventually relapse again, which triggers me to want to drink again.

I once got into drinking-related legal trouble and admitted to a counselor I was struggling with an eating disorder as well. I was given a couple pamphlets before I faced the judge. I don't remember specifics, but I learned that a disproportionate amount of female alcoholics also suffered from eating disorders. I know I'm not alone.

I'm new to this subreddit and tried to explain this as honestly as possible whilst refraining from mentioning anything too specific/triggering. 

I guess what I'm asking is, of other people that have these concurring problems, what has helped you manage both of them successfully? 

I've been attending AA and can mostly handle sobriety, as drinking is something you just... either do, or don't do, but how do I carry that determination over to something with no clear on/off bounds, and how do I help prevent the two from bleeding into each other?

Any advice is eagerly welcomed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Trying to get better - bulimia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 12:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure this is the right place for this because I think my problem involves a lot more than just my eating disorder. I've been bulimic for three years now. I use laxatives more than anything, which makes me feel like I can't talk to anyone about my problems because it's disgusting, and because I feel like even people with similar problems will find me completely unrelatable.

Currently I'm not getting a lot of sleep because I'm terrified of having an arrhythmia or something. Any time my boyfriend suggests a way for me to help myself I think of a reason not to. I see a psychologist and a psychiatrist but I never mentioned my ED to them, I've been seeing them for years, and I feel like now they're going to think I'm a bad person if I'm open with them. I don't want my parents to find out about my issues, even though I live with them, because I don't want them to feel like failures, and because I already feel ashamed and I don't want to make it worse.

I'm not sure what to do. I know I need to get better. I'm in constant fear of dropping dead and I'm miserable and I know what I'm doing isn't right. I think I just need to convince myself to be helped, and I don't know how to do that.

Can anyone offer advice on what I can do to get better?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 12:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful posts:

[Pregnancy](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2r5s9c/request_recovering_from_an_ed_and_thinking_about/)

[Pregnancy 2](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2qt9q6/request_pregnancy_and_bn/)

[How to approach](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1pl03w/sharing_girlfriend_is_recovering_from_bulimia/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to help friend with an eating disorder? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 12:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a friend who has an eating disorder. She keeps at a healthy weight and has no visible signs, but she eats next to nothing, obsessively counts calories, and is a brilliant liar. I know she binge-eats and then fasts. 

The eating problems came after she got over problems with cutting, however the experience she had with the help she got was absolutely terrible, and she has something against going and getting help. Her mother has also suffered from problems before and she's afraid of triggering them like she had done previously if she asks for help, and her father is not very understanding. 

At the moment the help she is getting consists of myself and her friend I don't know who attends her school and gets her to eat at lunchtime. 

We don't attend the same schools which cuts down our contact time significantly. Everybody else is oblivious. 

I am worried because I know she's getting worse and soon we won't be able to keep what little control we have. She said she would see some help but as far as I know, we need parental consent?

We live in New Zealand if that helps any. 

Any help/advice would be appreciated. I'd like to respect the fact she doesn't want to tell her mum as much as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Hungry but not hungry? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 21:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've recently (within the last couple of months) reached a healthy weight after a sudden encounter with anorexia. It was the first time I had lost a significant amount of weight, and my family didn't really know how to handle it. Eventually I got to the point where I was offered an ultimatum: gain weight or go to hospital. I chose to struggle through with it and gain weight, and managed to reach a healthy weight again. 

However, although I feel much better in myself (much less rigid thinking, less anxious, etc) I'm still deeply insecure about how I look, but I'm working on it. But my problem is, I just can't seem to feel satisfied without eating huge amounts of food! Eating normally just doesn't seem to fill me up. I'll eat a normal sized, well balanced dinner but then I'll have to eat toast, cereal bars, fruit, whatever I can find in the fridge, etc, to feel truly satisfied. 

I was wondering- is this because I genuinely need the calories, even though I'm a healthy weight? (And I don't just mean minimally healthy weight either). Or is it because my hormones and signalling is all out of whack? It's very confusing for me, and quite stressful at times. Any advice would be hugely helpful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I think my wife has an eating disorder and I don't know what to do </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 21:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife literally won't eat vegetables or fruits, and all she likes is pizza, taco bell, burritos, etc. She won't put anything on her burritos, sandwiches, whatever except for gobs of meat and cheese. There is literally (and I mean literally) no vegetable that she likes, or even will try. I googled being afraid of vegetables and I got: Lachanophobia.

She has been like this her whole life and since we've been together for 5 or so years whenever I bring it up she'll flip out and get angry at me. I've tried to get her to go to counseling because I know this is terrible for her health, but again she just gets angry about it and won't listen.

I'm worried now more than ever because she is about 15 weeks pregnant. For one I'm worried it will affect the baby. Two I'm worried that this is how my child is going to eat.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Looking for help-- bulimia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 21:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have always struggled with bulimia since I was a freshman in high school. I finally quit on my own my junior year. I hadn't made my self throw up for almost three years. Then I became depressed and stopped eating much, everyone started telling me how great I looked and it stuck. I became anorexic and I loved how I felt and the way I looked but my boyfriend became concerned and I was too ashamed to tell him the truth so I just slowly worked my way up to eating again but now that I've gained weight I found myself going back to old habits of puking. Recently it's like i'm not even hungry but the thought of puking is relaxing to me. I force myself to eat a lot and then purge it because for some reason I feel like its all my problems purging from my body and flush it away. It's my escape and I hate it. I know its not healthy and I want to quit but then in a few hours I find myself doing it again. 

I know I need help but is there any suggestions?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Journalist Requests input for Article </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 21:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there. I am a journalist and recovered anorexic writing an article against the common idea that eating disorders are caused by 'unrealistic body standards' set by the media/Disney/Barbie.

I want to highlight how the disorder isn't about vanity but is a serious mental problem, and this predominate cultural narrative is damaging.

If anyone wants to discuss their experiences with me please comment below, just to indicate your willingness, and I will DM you to get details.

Many thanks,

Amelia  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I'm relapsing and I don't know what to do. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 12:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've suffered from an ED when I was younger and managed to get out of it without treatment. It wasn't very severe but I was still losing a lot of weight in such a short amount of time. My parents found out and helped me get through it. Since then I've stayed positive and never fell back to old habits.

However, a few months ago I started binging and purging myself. Then even more recently I started starving myself. My urges to restrict are very strong. I can't stop, but I'm scared for myself. My country doesn't offer therapy services, and I'm afraid if I tell my mother and father they'll force me to eat and I'll end up purging myself too. 

Please help me, is there anything I can do to stop thinking this way?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Mostly recovered with lingering fear of being sedentary, how to overcome this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 12:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had anorexia in highschool (4 years ago), including restricting food and over-exercising. I'm pretty much recovered now: I eat totally normally, exercise like a few times a week for maybe half an hour, and am a healthy weight.

I thought I'd put that all behind me, but I recently got the opportunity to travel with a student group at my university for the month of October, essentially on a road trip around Australia for five weeks. Sounds so incredible, and totally covered financially by my school! Coming from the US, this is a huge trip that I'd never be able to do otherwise, and it would be with a ton of friends, too.

But I had a total panic about it -- the prospect of sitting in a car for that long, unable to stand up or walk around, absolutely terrifies me. In my everyday life I don't really notice any fear of sitting, but I don't really have to sit for more than four hours any given day (although I definitely do sit around more than that).

It's just the idea of HAVING to be sedentary that freaks me out, and reminds me of when I was in high school not being able to handle staying seated during the school day since I felt like I needed to walk around. It's not claustrophobia either; small spaces have never bothered me as long as I'm not stuck sitting for hours.

Basically I don't know what I'm looking for from this post, but I just had to get this off my chest. 

Has anyone successfully dealt with this kind of lingering panic of being still for long-ish periods of time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Dealing With Past of ARFID/Anorexia/Binge Eating </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 04:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I modelled for a long time, and loved it. Maybe a little too much. My body type isn't perfect, so I spent a long time exercising and dieting.

In 2011 it started getting out of control. I have a history of OCD and depression, and I think those had a huge effect on my habits. I wanted to model so badly I would severely restrict and then binge and then overexercise. I would feel instant guilt over anyone's comments on my food, be it good or bad.

I had been hospitalized for 3 weeks in intensive cardiac care after severely restricting and overexercising in 2013. I was diagnosed with ARFID and anorexia while in hospital. They told me if I hadn't come in that day I would have died.

However, I fervently denied it. I hid it from everyone. I told everyone I just wasn't hungry or had stomach pain. My mum and boyfriend believed me. I relapsed in February 2014...then July...then I got severely depressed and relapsed in October 2014. I didn't tell anyone why I was that depressed, I figure my boyfriend figured out I had some issue because I constantly called myself ugly and such, but I never told him I had this illness. I told him it was all a misdiagnosis, I was fine. I hid all the guilt and unhealthy habits.

My mum unwittingly has been contributing by making comments about my food. It broke me so badly, but yet I still refused to tell anyone. I avoided her, broke down when I was supposed to return home from vacation. But how do I tell my SO (who was there) "Oh yeah, I don't want to go home because my mum perpetuates my eating disorder I never told you about??" So I just said I wasn't going to be okay going home. I cried and had a huge breakdown.

In the end of December, I had a mental breakdown because I just couldn't control my OCD, depression, and eating disorder all at once. Because I am having trouble facing my mum about this, and it's been festering inside me for years now. My boyfriend then decided to take a break beginning of January because I was having panic attacks all the time and he couldn't handle it.

I am in treatment for all three, but still nobody knows. I have overcome my OCD and depression. But not the eating disorder. It's still there, just less because of therapy. I can feel it pulling me back again and it's stressing me out.

I feel really terrible because I hid it from everyone... yet I know it had a huge impact on my relationship (self-esteem) and even affects my family. I don't know how to tell them or what to do. If I tell my SO, he might just pull away further...yet I want to be honest and tell him why things were so difficult. I want to tell him this stuff but I don't know how. I don't want it to make him leave for good. I just feel lost.

Anyone have advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: New to BN Recovery and Feeling Overwhelmed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 20:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been seeing a therapist/nutritionist for the past 2 months. It's my first real attempt at getting help. I've struggled with ED for 10 yrs and when I decided to start therapy, I was ready to recover. A week ago, my meal plan added more. It went well for a week, and then something changed. 

I went from positive about the changes and recovery to being very depressed and restricting more than usual. I can't get thoughts out of my head that I'm failing or that I'm not sick, I look fine, I don't need help yet. Is this normal to go from positive about recovery to not wanting to?

I feel crazy and fucked in the head. It can't be right to feel like I have to get a lot worse before I deserve this help. As if I need to be dying or emaciated or having everyone worry about me to deserve getting help. 

Can anyone relate? I feel so alone and crazy. I don't want to get out of bed anymore. I don't want to feel hungry or look at food or count another calorie. I just want to give up and disappear. I'm really scared.

How can I stay true to recovery? Why are all these difficult emotions coming up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Roommate is unintentionally triggering me, afraid of relapse. Advice on how to deal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 18:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was a teenager I was diagnosed with anorexia. I was in therapy for a few years and have been relatively symptom free now in my mid-20s.

I have a new roommate who is a Kinesiology major and super into healthy eating and fitness. She goes to the gym everyday and posts a meal plan for herself on the fridge every week. I feel very self conscious eating around her (not that I eat super unhealthy foods but I am not as strict as she is) and seeing her meal plans makes me feel guilty and critical about my own food choices. I restricted my own food intake a little bit last week and I'm starting to worry about slipping back into my illness.

I don't want to tell her about my history or how I've been feeling but I need to find a way to not feel so triggered by her activities. 

Does anyone have any advice? 

Has anyone been in a similar situation before? Thank you so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Supportive things to say to someone in the middle of a binge/purge struggle or over-exercise urge? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 11:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are some of the best things to say to someone who is in the middle of a struggle? 

Meaning, if they are voicing b/p urges what are helpful things to say? 

If they are expressing exercise urges what are some things to say?

 How can someone be supported without feeling invalidated or shamed? 

How can one be supportive and not co-dependent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 12:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful posts (although she does not/may not have an ED, you get the idea):

[What not to say](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2e8boa/what_not_to_say_when_someone_you_love_is_in/)

[Being there for a loved one](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2ajwpb/sharing_some_of_my_personal_experince_on_how_to/) 

[GF criticized body](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2a6v9j/request_advice_on_what_to_saydo_when_my_gf/)

[How to not make it a bad cycle](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1pl03w/sharing_girlfriend_is_recovering_from_bulimia/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Advice needed on how to be more supportive of GF (xpost from r/bodyimage) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 12:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My GF has body image issues and quite possibly disordered eating. For example, she is very hard on herself when she eats more than planned or has to miss a trip to the gym (I should add she about a pound shy of being underweight--though she is not losing weight, but has been at the same weight for a couple years). 

I suggested numerous times that she talk to a therapist about these issues (when a previous therapist wanted to discuss her disordered eating instead of other issues my GF wanted to discuss, she stopped therapy). 

When I suggest she try talking to someone she gets angry and tells me I just "need to be more sympathetic" and "supportive"--so, short of saying, "It will be OK" when issues like these come up (which they frequently do), I honesty have no idea what to do/say. Any help would be appreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-24 21:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful posts:

[Helping girlfriend](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1pl03w/sharing_girlfriend_is_recovering_from_bulimia/)

[Body image](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2qvpxj/request_significant_other_has_an_unhealthy/)

[positive reinforcement, validation](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1gszlf/post_request_update_on_my_girlfriend_with_an/)

[Another](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/237sf5/thanks_and_update_from_the_so_of_a_girl/)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My girlfriend has an ED and I want to be as supportive as possible. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-24 21:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Girlfriend of 8 months has an eating disorder and I want to be supportive as possible. She has been struggling with it for 2 years and recently after being inpatient (May-June) she gained weight. 

Now she is self conscious about it but it's not like it bothers me or like she is very over weight. She has a very supportive family, therapist, and psychiatrist that have helped her so much to recover to the best of her ability, however she still is very worried about her weight and on some days only eats a meal or two with a few snacks in between. 

She understands and accepts her disorder and is very open about it to me, but I would just like some more advice from others struggling with ED so I can know how to handle certain situations or things that commonly bother people with an ED. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to cope with accepting weight gain? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-24 14:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
I am in the middle of recovery from an eating disorder, which I first developed when I was 16 and it has been an ongoing battle ever since. I have suffered very badly twice before my most recent struggle, each time it has been about different things and with different manifestations.

This time it was definitely to do with body image, and over exercise. I am currently seeing a CBT psychologist as well as a dietician etc. I am trying really hard to find the demons in my head , but am really really having a hard time accepting my weight gain. 

Does anyone have any suggestions on how to cope? I realise that everything is relative but right now I feel like I want to stop gaining. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Bulimic and deciding to get help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-24 12:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have struggled with my weight for years and have lost about a significant portion of  twice now. The first time was from being anorexic and the second bulimic. I got pregnant with my son and stopped binging and purging but my son is two now and I find myself back in the same pattern. 

I need help. I don't want to kill myself by doing this. Can anybody suggest how I should start to get help? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Exercise during recovery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 23:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently recovering from b/p anorexia, still have a large amount of weight to gain. My whole life I've been a competitive gymnast. The first time I underwent refeeding (about 4 yrs ago, forced by my parents) I continued to workout, essentially as a reward system (basically they divided my weight gain into percentages. If I gained 20% of the weight I could go to 20% of practices, 40% was 40% of practices and so on). 

Now that I'm in college I don't have access to a gymnastic gym everyday. Also, my treatment team is very adamant about the absolutely no exercise philosophy. 

However, compulsive exercise is not a form of purging for me; in fact exercise tends to prevent binge and purge episodes since I know purging hinders my workout performance and the physical act of working out relieves stress for me. 

Is there any safe way I can exercise during recovery? Maybe weight lifting? I know cardio is a no go due to worries about heart complications, but is there a form of exercise (besides yoga, I really am not a huge fan of yoga) that wouldn't be physically dangerous? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: What could I have done differently? What can I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 20:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a mom to 4 kids, 2 of each sex. My oldest, 13 yo daughter, had been showing signs of disordered eating. I tried not to think to much of it, believing the philosophy that food/diet is only a big deal if you make a big deal of it. I think that only works if there isn't an existing problem.

Two years ago or so, my husband and I, who are both clinically obese, started using My Fitness Pal to track caloric intake. He and my daughter, over my arguments, set her up an account. He feels that everyone should be aware of their calories. I argued that she was 11, and no, she should just eat when she is hungry and stop when she is not. I lost. My daughter was eating normally at that time, and at the upper end of a healthy weight. The pediatrician said that she was in a category called "in danger of becoming overweight." I did not mention this to my husband, because one of his big fears is that our kids will make choices that lead to them becoming significantly overweight.

With growth spurts in height, I didn't think much of her slimming down. It happened slowly, and seemed reasonable. Grandparents, assholes, would make comments to me or her about how great she was looking, my dad privately tell me she had "lost weight and looked great."

She has a friend who has been diagnosed with ED-NOS. The friend is constantly texting her about food and weight, and negative self-labeling. I know because I broke down and snooped through my daughter's phone.

I'd feel more guilty than I do, but I found a lot of texts between the two of them. I have not told my husband. Recently, when I told him, hey, have you noticed our daughter has kind of... stopped eating? he told me that she had a very healthy relationship with food, and I should back off. I plan to talk to him about it this weekend. I have emailed a few therapists, and am hoping to get her into counseling, soon, like this coming week.

My daughter has also struggled with anxiety the past few years. Being the oldest, she feels a lot of weight on her shoulders, real and imaginary. In the last few days, with this new information and confirmation of my concerns, I have been thinking about the parallels between ED and hoarding. I am a compulsive hoarder. Could my mental health issues be nurturing hers? Is this something I could have prevented, if I had put my foot down two years ago? Or got my own mental health under control years ago, before it could have impacted hers? She is still eating, she is not in need of hospitalization, but I know that things can spiral, so I am trying to play catch up now. I feel like I have been fiddling while rome burned. I just don't know what to do to help her grow into a happy, healthy adult. I don't want her to be depressed or anxious, or seeking control and stability from outside forces. I just feel lost. Help me help her? Please?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to work on recovery and be around dieting people/eat at structured times? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 01:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In December, I went to counselling and was told I either had an eating disorder, or at the very least disordered eating. I've started going to a support group every Monday.

My problem is, I am a 3rd year student teacher, and I've struggled with juggling eating and the school environment in the past, during my placements. First of all, it's a really structured time (being a school day), and for me, I can't eat large meals. If I get full, I feel so guilty. 

But if I get hungry and have to stay hungry for a couple of hours (eg a lesson), I then get into a cycle of telling myself and believing disordered thoughts about hunger. My current lifestyle is eating something small and healthy whenever I am hungry. Obviously this isn't ideal for a school environment. 

Over Christmas was a really stressful time for me because I couldn't just eat when I wanted to, and when we did sit down to eat, I'd get weird looks if I didn't eat everything. I don't know how to cope with that again for 6 weeks.

Second of all, in every school I've been in before, all the teachers are on diets (and especially when it's January). So every time I'm on placement, while I'm dealing with problem no. 1, I've got my peers, who I am supposed to be constantly learning from, saying how they 'shouldn't be eating this xyz' etc etc. It's not been a problem in the past too much but I've got a lot worse this past 6 months and I really don't know how I'll cope.

Thanks so much if anyone can give me any advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shout out to: New subreddit for Avoidant/Restrictive Food Intake Disorder, or Selective Eating Disorder /r/ARFID </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 22:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
We have a new subreddit for for those who have Avoidant/Restrictive Food Intake Disorder (ARFID), also known as, Selective Eating Disorder, food neo-phobia, or adult picky eating.

/r/ARFID

Picky eating is normally only associated as a phase of childhood, but the latest edition of the Diagnostic and Statistical Manual of Mental Disorders (DSM-5) has recently recognized that this disorder can continue on into adolescence and adulthood.

This subreddit is a place to discuss ARFID and related anxiety, express frustration, share tips, and help others gain an understanding of what this diagnosis encompasses.

If this sounds like you, please head over and help us create this new community! Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: 19 y/o, male, and new to all this - ARFID/SED/other issues? Avoidant/Restrictive Food Intake Disorder, Selective Eating Disorder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 02:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a 19 year old male college student who, after years of just assuming I was a "picky eater," realized that it's probably a bit worse than that and this is honestly the first place I turned to.

**First of all, I REFUSE to eat anything with toppings on it.** With few exceptions everything has to be completely and utterly plain. This basically means any kind of burger can only be the meat and the bun. If there's anything else on it then I will flat out refuse to eat it. 

I know in the rational part of my brain that this is absurd and I should just do it, but the few times I have actually tried to eat something new I legitimately had a physical gag reflex to it. 

**I don't eat vegetables, only eat a few 'approved' fruits,** won't dip my food in any kind of condiment or sauce.

**If it's not completely plain or it's food that is not on my 'approved' list, then I will refuse to even try it** despite my rational mind going "Dude, come on, you're a grown ass man. Eat the food." My approved list is very small. I'm almost entirely carnivorous. My 'approved' list basically comes down to this: Pizza and meat (no fish)

**I get severe anxiety when I get put in a situation where I might not be able to eat my plain hamburger or chicken fingers, which are my go-to food items.** 

I recently had to eat dinner with my girlfriend's family at her house, and I had to try new food. I had an anxiety attack and was (thankfully) calmed down by my girlfriend. I went down to try this new food I had never had. I took one bite and literally gagged so hard I almost threw up this food on the dinner table. I then took a few more bites, and ended up only eating like 1/3rd of the plate. **Because of this anxiety, I pretty much eat every single meal alone so I don't get judged.**


**In addition to this 'picky eating,' I do not eat enough. I don't feel hungry a lot,** and when I do, I get hunger for certain foods. If these foods aren't available, oh well, I guess I'm just not gonna eat tonight. I also never eat breakfast. **I often wake up reallllly hungry,** but if I try to eat in the morning then I feel nauseous and I have the same gagging reaction if I try to eat anyway. So, my breakfast is light and then at lunch, when for some reason, my body and mind actually allow me to eat food.

Guys, sorry that this is so long. I really feel like this is a pretty severe problem that I have though, and it is making my life difficult in more ways that I could have ever imagined. I'm losing weight because of it, and I think it is making me unhealthy. 

Any input or help I could get would be excellent. Thank you.

Does this sound like ARFID or SED? 

How can I not have anxiety around foods not on my list?

How can I become comfortable eating with others? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I think my best friend may be relapsing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 02:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My best friend suffered from an ED from which she recovered just before I knew her.

She also suffers from OCD and from talks with her I've learned that her ED involved a lot of calorie counting, binge/purges and compulsive exercise.

For the last few months I've noticed she has lost weight (still within healthy range) and her social media and text messages often include references to healthy eating, and exercise. She often is late to plans because she 'had to' go to the gym (direct quote multiple occasions)

I'm concerned she may be struggling again.

I was wondering a few things: 

1. Is there a way to tell the difference between ED behaviour and being committed to a healthy lifestyle? 

2. If she is relapsing - what are the best ways for me to support her? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to eat food you don't like </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 09:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm about six months into recovery and I'm doing pretty well, but I'm still having such a hard time finding things to eat. I've always been a picky eater, and liking so few foods makes recovery so much harder. I'm not doing it on purpose, and it really is just a burden at this point. Any advice on how to learn to enjoy more foods or open yourself to different tastes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I'm 24 years old and I'm an adult picky eater. I'm scared for my health, and I want to get better. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 09:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a 24 year old male who is an incredibly picky eater. For the last 2 decades I've lived in ignorance and thought this was something that I would eventually wake up and be over one day, but I'm afraid that my limited diet and (possibly self induced? I honestly don't know where this stemmed) phobia will one day kill me.

Until I moved away for university, I lived primarily on sandwiches with spread, bready foods like pancakes, and a few easy fruits snacks. The combination of limited options in a dorm dining hall setting and the embarrassment of eating in front of others introduced chicken and fish into my diet. Both still have to have some sort of breading for me to stomach. My girlfriend has started making homemade chicken fingers that aren't like I'd usually eat, and eating REAL chicken was a big step for me but I feel like I haven't made much more progress.

I avoid social situations that involve food because its embarrassing ordering my usual food at a restaurant and feeling like a kid. I get embarrassed when people edge me on and try to get me to try something. 9.5 times out of 10 its with good intentions, but I don't think they understand how hard it actually is for me. 

Lately I feel depressed, sluggish, I have aches and pains, I feel my sex drive deteriorate (causing other relationship troubles on top of everything else) and I believe that a large portion of this stems directly from my eating habits. 

I have no idea how to get better from this. I have no idea how to squash the fear and just branch out. I've never tried a vegetable in my life.

I want to be healthy. I want to get over this self inflicted negativity. If anyone has ever been in the same situation and has any tips, they would be greatly appreciated. 

Tl;dr: 24 year old scared about eating chicken fingers all the time, and i'm too scared to try anything new because my body always rejects it. Help me. Please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Girlfriend and I just dicovered she has an ED, how can I support her? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 03:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend and I are in our early twenties and I just discovered she has an eating disorder, AN. When she told me she said she just discovered she had it, maybe she was just telling me that to feel less bad. Anyway, the good thing is that she told me and recognize that she has a problem.

She told me she always thought she was not slim enough to have an ED and that she thought she was doing this for her job (model). But she now realize she is doing this for herself the most.

Our situation is a bit particular in the sens that she traveling a lot for her job while I stay to finish my degree, so I can't be beside her all the time to provide physical support. She can't realistically quit her job since it's a really good opportunity and very good money.

I've skim trough the already posted questions but it was hard to find something similar to my situation. The thing is she can't consult a therapist since she's never at the same place for long and even then she can get called on a job within a one day notice. Also one advice was to avoid the magazine, television, etc so it doesn't reinforce the idea of good looks but it's a little bit hard when you are the person in said magazines.

We have a kind of traditional relationship where I'm the pillar and make most of the decisions so she has no stress. I want to stay the strong rock she can count on. I have to admit that at this moment all of this is getting a little bit over my head and need some direction as how to handle it. I want to make is easy for her to slowly appreciate her body and to transition into a healthy diet after.

Thank you very much for your time and sorry for the sloppy English. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Previous or Current Inpatients With Strict Diets/Allergies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 13:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been battling with anorexia on my own ever since I began middle school, about a decade ago. While friends and family have expressed little concern at times about my habits, I've never actually sought out help or treatment. I'm getting to one of the worst points I've been in during this crippling battle and for once I'm considering seeking help at a mental institute or something of the likings. 

I understand most places require a pretty strict eating regime pertaining to those in need of recovery, but is there any sort of exception? I'm pretty passionate about remaining vegan and I'm not sure if I could go through with treatment if it meant changing so many predominate aspects of my lifestyle as I can recall it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Is extreme sleepiness and soreness common when recovering? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 02:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently I've accepted that I have a very unhealthy relationship with food, and that I need to change this. When I kept track of how much I was eating, it turns out that it was far, far too little - I think no one noticed because I would just not eat, then eat multiple servings or something and people would think I was clearly eating enough.

So... I've been eating more. I wish I could do this under the supervision of a medical professional, but that's really not possible for me. 

Though I sense that I generally feel somewhat more 'content' (maybe), the biggest issue and worry for me right now is that I'm extremely sleepy and sore the entire day. Is this common while refeeding (I've heard this is the term)? 

I feel like I should actually have more energy now that I'm eating more, but it feels like I was actually most energetic when I'd been restricting myself for sometime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Request: Looking for information, videos, and personal stories on the stigmatization of EDs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 13:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I'm a 3rd year nursing student currently doing a research project on eating disorders (mainly anorexia nervosa and bulimia nervosa) and the stigma society has towards these illnesses. My goal is to come up with innovative ways to slowly break down the stigma. I am wondering if anyone has come across any:

1) Videos pertaining the stigma of eating disorders 

2) Information or other media driven pieces relating to this


Or if you have a personal story surrounding stigma, please share. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 02:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful posts:

[Diet vs ED](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1l40q4/post_request_how_do_i_do_things_like_try_to_eat/)

[how do I approach](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/253fi9/request_there_is_a_girl_who_looks_anorexic_at_my/)

[is this an ED](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2rlqzv/request_i_dont_know_if_i_have_an_eating_disorder/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
