<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3132</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 22:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea :) 
Duolingo is pretty cool. Good luck in your studies! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 21:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is properly spelled 'ab intitio' which, in Latin, means 'from the beginning'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 17:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is early days but I feel comfortable and realise that it is not going to be 'easy' and I am prepared for the challenge.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 16:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Psychology was just introduced this year as a teacher-taught subject. It used to be online. So far, it is pretty good. A lot of memorization of studies, theories and terms. Exam technique is also pretty important. The teacher is horrible though :/ 

Yeah! History is great! We have not delved into any options yet, though I am sure my teacher has one ready. We have 2 exams till our first term is complete so the roller coaster of IB has only just begun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 15:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I moved from Australia (grade 1 at the time) to Dubai (placed in grade 2). I then magically moved up to grade 3. This is one of the wild occurrences of the Australian Education system. Most of my classmates are 16/17 and we are in IB1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 13:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IB ahaha! My HL's are: English Lang Lit, History, Psychology. SL's are: Physics, Math and French Abinitio. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 13:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are doing this one first. I guess we'll eventually get there :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Picture] How to pass IB History (we hope). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 07:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 09:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll keep an eye out, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 09:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah ok, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unusually quick shipping... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-01 23:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello all!
I came home tonight and rushed onto my computer to check my email. Much to my pleasure, I had been matched! I had also received to other email. One at 8:32pm (Dubai time) which stated that my SS had picked up my info and then one at 8:33pm which stated it has been shipped. I have never had this in an exchange before. Common or not?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 15:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the links! I will check it out :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Throwing Athletic Events Training anywhere in UAE? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 10:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am in need of a athletics/throwing events trainer or facility to train. I can't seem to find anywhere here where I can get that service. Anyone know anywhere or anyone who can help out? Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 18:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have the same wonderful guitar! It is solid and does the job very well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] The next best thing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 21:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted to leave this prompt considerably open as I would like to see what people can do with it. I was reading a newspaper article lately that asked this question to its readers and it kind of sparked to me that it would be an ideal prompt for this sub. 

I am excited to see some interpretations of any genre and style on here! Get creative and have fun! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 10:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I reckon you (anyone) would love Dolores Claiborne. There isn't that real sense of 'horror' to it but the story is told perfectly and encourages you to constantly turn its pages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 12:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is only hope!...and lack of $$. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 17:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Martin or Taylor acoustic. Been drooling over them for months! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 11:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I won a CD on the radio. 

It was Britney Spears.

Woo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Upcoming album... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 11:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello all, 

I have been out of the internet scene for a while and have been wondering what is happening with AVA. I remember seeing a post way back when stating that the new album would be called Halloween and would be released then as well. Now, David and Matt are gone and the album is called "The Dream Walker". Would anybody be able to kindly inform me of what is happening? Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> While packing the box I couldn't keep her away from me! All the way to Serbia from a German dog in Dubai! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 17:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 20:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dubai to US here! Should be awesome. 

Also for the pets exchange it is Dubai to Serbia! Can't wait! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 08:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Within the next week i'd say. We are just trying to get a cool poster for as cheap a cost as we can :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] [$$ Commission] Amateur (awesome) Dubai punk band in need of logo/poster. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 09:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello artists of /r/drawforme, 

I am one third of Dubai-based punk band, Legs. For the drummer's birthday, I would like to have a poster/logo drawn up for the band. 

There is nothing specific that I want in it, though a cartoon-esque approach would be great. We have attempted to contact local artists and given them examples of past blink-182 posters.

 Such as:
http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-qI17CNKr4GY/T5D979xLs_I/AAAAAAAAZ50/g-f3sIBL-G0/s1600/frank+kozik+blink+182+poster.jpg

http://411posters.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/07/kozik-blink-182-Luxembourg-2012.png

We don't require the posters to be as immensely detailed as those. 

Artists, feel free to take your own approach to this request. Post your sketches and/or ideas for this and I will PM whoever's ideas I find suit the band best. Also willing to discuss a payment. 

EDIT: The bands name is Legs and is typically written as LEGS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 09:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Watching the names Steven Spielberg, Brian K. Vaughn, and Stephen King come up in the credits each week reconfirms that Under the Dome is the underachieving child of prime time television. Its the kid whose parents are Oscar winners and Olympic athletes, who gave it every advantage, and yet its out in the student parking lot, huffing patio sealant, killing brain cells, and repeating ninth grade for the third time.

Too true... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
