<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3094</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-11 22:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've tried both ways, shorter and longer steps. Maybe I should use lighter dumbbells? I just assumed that I would be able to do a higher weight since it was a leg workout as compared to what I use with arms. I've had some experience with weightlifting, but I've never done lunges with any type of weight before this, they were just always incorporated with a warm up of some kind.  
  
I haven't tried split squats. I was hoping that if I did have to replace it, that I would find an exercise that still involved using some weight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-11 20:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm not crazy! I never thought about step-ups, thanks! Would I start with the same amount of weight I'm doing the lunges with?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone Else HATE barbell lunges? Or am I just doing them wrong? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-11 20:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently for my leg days, I do 3x8-10 on barbell squats, leg press, dumbbell lunges, and RDL. With the squats, leg press, and RDL, I push myself with weight each week and by the 8-10 rep, I'm struggling with the weight. This is where I want to be, and those lifts are all pain free besides the typical difficulty with the last few reps. Currently I'm squatting 80 lbs 3x10, leg pressing 90 lbs 3x10, and RDL 85 lbs 3x10. For the dumbbell lunges I use 15 lb dumbbells in each hand.  
  
Here's the thing. I HATE them. I feel immediate pain in my knees and hips when doing them., and it doesn't feel like my legs really get tired. I just stop at eight reps on each leg because I feel like I'm going to hurt something. I feel like I'm doing them completely wrong, and I've read up on form and watched videos about a hundred times. Am I using way too much weight? Or do I just need to stop them before I hurt myself? If so, what are some good lifts that will replace them?  
  
Any advice would be SO greatly appreciated. I feel like I'm not getting the most out of my leg days because of this.

Edit: In my title, I put barbell lunges, but I meant dumbbell. Way to go, me.  
  
Edit 2: I guess I should also mention that I am a 22 year old female.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 18:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't spoken to a counselor about this subject because they are extremely hesitant about promoting any type of serious exercise program for people who are recovering. If I express any type of negative feelings towards it, it tends to cause counselors to tell you it's a bad idea. I really think I'm ready for this, though. I've come a long way from 99 pounds and I think I'm healthy enough for this.  
  
Thank you so much for your kind words, I really do appreciate it.

I actually am working on cutting at the moment. I promise it's a rational and healthy goal! In that month of insane binging before I started lifting, I gained a lot of weight. I'm currently sitting at about 152 lbs and I'm 5'5. I don't want to cut a ton of weight, but 10 or 15 pounds is really want I want to lose.

Looking back on how strong I used to be playing softball, it is SO disheartening how much I've weakened and atrophied my muscles over the last few years. I can't do a single push up, or even think about doing a pull up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 05:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do see what you're saying, and usually starvation mode is bogus. However I do know that it is possible to damage one's metabolism and need to repair it. There's sort of a gray area in certain situations.  
  
I'm not sure what you mean by bending the truth...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 05:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm afraid it's not quite as simple as just "removing emotion". If it were, I don't suppose I would have been diagnosed with an eating disorder...It's much more deeply engrained. I'm sure it probably is simple for a lot of people.  
  
I'm honestly not sure how to take this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
