<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6210</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 02:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know how you feel. I've been binging after being binge free for almost a month. 

It's just 1 set back, you didn't ruin all of your work. Any weight you gain isn't real weight, just food and water weight.

Don't beat yourself up too much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 00:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there!
I'm subject6210! I've been struggling with disordered eating on and off for about abut 7 years now. I'm currently in my worst relapse ever. I used to really struggle with purging but this time I mostly stick to restricting. I've been restricting to under 400 cals for over 2 months now. 

I'm mostly likely going into recovery sometime in the new year. I'm excited and nervous. I want to stop living like this, but I have to reach my GW before I get admitted to the program. 

I'm 19, I'm a university student studying biology. I want to be a doctor. My life is pretty boring, it's mostly been swallowed up by my eating disorder.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 20:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't restricting, I was mostly recovered back then. My hair is extremely thick and wavy. I didn't have any lanugo. 

So I think once you hit your goal and start eating at maintenance, your hair will be nice and healthy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 07:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't the greatest diet ever, but I ate pretty healthy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 07:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was maintaining a bmi of around 15.5 I had super thick hair!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 22:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. I'm hoping that Christmas will boost my metabolism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 20:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom has, but no one else has. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 17:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Height: 5'8

*CW: 89lbs

*HW: 115lbs

*LW: 89lbs

*GW: 84lbs

*UGW: as low as possible

*WL:-15lbs

*BMI: 13.39

*Age: 19

*Genderexpression: Female

I didn't lose any weight this week, unfortunately. Plus I'm probably going to gain so much because of the Christmas binge that's coming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 17:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want someone to notice how sick I am. I want to look as sick on the outside as I am on the inside.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 03:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'm going to an ED clinic at my local hospital. I don't know if it'll be inpatient or intensive outpatient yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 03:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad to hear things are going well! I'm going into recovery in a few weeks, so I'm pretty nervous and scared, but I'm excited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 01:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cinnamon (147)

Lunch: 1/2 red bell pepper (11) celery (6) cucumber (8) and 2 egg whites (34)

Dinner: Rice cake with 1 and 1/2 tbsp of light peanut butter (155)

Snacks: Diet coke (0), vitamin water zero (0) and mio sport (0)

Total: 361 calories
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 17:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I keep telling myself. I actually wrote down a bunch of things to make me feel better about eating more for a few days </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 16:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm increasing my intake a few days before Christmas. I'm hoping that it will reduce the chances of a binge and of getting sick because I ate too much. I really hope that it will boost my metabolism because I just hit a plateau, but I'm terrified that it will instead make me fat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 02:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cinnamon (147)

Lunch: 1/2 red bell pepper (11) celery (6) cucumber (8) and 2 egg whites (34)

Dinner: Rice cake with 1 and 1/2 tbsp of light peanut butter (155)

Snacks: Diet coke (0), vitamin water zero (0) and mio sport (0)

Total: 361 calories
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 21:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This](http://imgur.com/a/YZlfx) is me from this week. I'm 3 lbs lighter than my last set of photos.

I didn't lose any weight this week, which makes me really sad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 16:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had what I call the "death talk" with my psychiatrist yesterday. He explained to me that I am risking my life and I could die from complications. It was kind of scary. 

Also, my sister just got in town for Christmas. We told her about my ed, and I'm worried about how she'll act around me. She's a psych student and I'm worried that she'll try to fix me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 06:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cinnamon (147)

Lunch: 1/2 red bell pepper (11) celery (6) cucumber (8) and 2 egg whites (34)

Dinner: Rice cake with 1 and 1/2 tbsp of light peanut butter (155)

Snacks: Diet coke (0) and mio sport (0)

Total: 361 calories
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 03:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love bruises! Unfortunately I never bruise, haven't had one in like 7 years. I'm kind of hoping that losing weight will make me more sensitive to bruises </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 04:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cinnamon (147)

Lunch: 1/2 red bell pepper (11) celery (6) cucumber (8) and 2 egg whites (34)

Dinner: Rice cake with 1 and 1/2 tbsp of light peanut butter (155)

Snacks: Diet coke (0) and mio sport (0)

Total: 361 calories
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Favorite zero calorie drinks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 04:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was wondering what people's favorite zero calorie drinks were? 

I like diet coke, tea, mio sport and water. But I'm looking for new ideas! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 19:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oatmeal, egg whites, celery, red pepper, cucumbers, and rice cakes with light peanut butter. That is pretty much all I eat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 05:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had the same thought! Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 04:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! It's really scary, I need all the bravery I can get </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 04:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I have a lot of support from my family which will be really helpful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 04:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I'm terrified, but I know it's for the best </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 03:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cinnamon (147)

Lunch: 1/2 red bell pepper (11) celery (6) cucumber (8) and 2 egg whites (34)

Dinner: Rice cake with 1 and 1/2 tbsp of light peanut butter (155)

Snacks: Diet coke (0) and electrolyte mio (0)

Total: 361 calories
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 03:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's really well written! Hopefully you get the help and support you need.

Also, I don't think anyone here is really pro-ed, it's just a term for people who aren't ready to recover </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 22:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have tried it, but I'm really bad. I have a few things that help with anxiety </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 22:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I'm really scared, but I know I can't keep living like this. So I have to give recovery a shot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 22:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I think I will hit my goal, only 5 lbs left, but Christmas will probably ruin my progress </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Possibly going into treatment earlier than planned </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 21:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was placed on a wait list for a treatment program at the end of November. During my phone interview they said that it would take 3-4 months for my assessment appointment and that I would probably start treatment in April or May. But since then I have lost quite a bit of weight and I have developed problems with my heart. I had to go to the ER last week because of low blood pressure/high heart rate. 

I got a call yesterday that now my assessment appointment is at the beginning of January. I think it means that I will be going into treatment much sooner than planned/expected.  This is making me really anxious. I really hope I can hit my goal weight before I go into treatment. This also means that I will most likely have to drop out of school next semester, which will suck a lot. 

Urg, this has made me so much more anxious about everything. I really do want to recover, but knowing that it's coming faster than planned terrifies me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 18:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I am an extremely picky eater, always have been. I rarely try new foods. Right now I'm only eating very few types of food </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 02:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cinnamon (147)

Lunch: 1/2 red bell pepper (11) celery (6) cucumber (8) and 2 egg whites (34)

Dinner: Rice cake with 1 and 1/2 tbsp of light peanut butter (155)

Snacks: Diet coke (0)

Total: 361 calories
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 00:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I eat between 360 - 370 cals a day and my bmr is 1272 cals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 17:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I danced a lot, and people said I have the body of a ballet dance, but I have absolutely no coordination and I'm super clumsy, so I just looked really awkward, not graceful. I had to stop because of an injury a few years ago. 

I went to high school with the ballet dancers who trained in the professional program at the local ballet academy. They were so tall and thin and triggered me everyday.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 17:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I noticed my weightloss in my stomach and thighs because that's where most of my fat is. I've always had a thigh gap and visible collar bones. My chest bones are just starting to peak out at a bmi of 13.39. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 17:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So beautiful! I used to want to be a ballerina so badly as a kid, I still do actually. I just never was a great dancer haha.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 16:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Height: 5'8"

* CW: 89 lbs

* HW: 115 lbs

* LW: 89 lbs

* GW: 84 lbs

* UGW: as low as possible

* WL: 15 lbs

* BMI: 13.39

* Age: 19

* Gender expression: Female </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 01:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! Welcome to the sub. 

I use this to be in control too and it does really help as a distraction from the horribleness of the world and depression </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 01:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cinnamon (147)

Lunch: 1/2 red bell pepper (11) celery (6) cucumber (8) and 2 egg whites (34)

Dinner: Rice cake with 1 and 1/2 tbsp of light peanut butter (155)

Snacks: Diet coke (0)

Total: 361 calories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 00:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you compare it to a real skeleton, he has a bunch of extra lumbar vertebrae, and he is missing his ulna and clavicles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 21:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big bones are a myth. But this photo is fake, he has extra bones and some are missing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 19:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm planning to binge at Christmas. I've never had a planned binge before, I'm excited and nervous </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 04:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cinnamon (147)

Lunch: 1/2 red bell pepper (11) celery (6) cucumber (8) and 2 egg whites (34)

Dinner: Rice cake with 1 and 1/2 tbsp of light peanut butter (155)

Snacks: Diet coke (0) and peppermint white chocolate tea (5)

Total: 366 calories

I got this new tea that has 5 cals per cup, and it actually really scares me to up my calories, but it's really good tea
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 19:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have really bad depression. And both my eating disorder and depression really feed off of each other and make it worse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 16:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you add me to the group? My username is labellemort </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 01:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, my jeans used to be tight, but now they are getting pretty baggy on me. Most of the time I wear loose tops or big sweaters with a huge blanket scarf.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 01:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cinnamon (147)

Lunch: 1/2 red bell pepper (11) celery (6) cucumber (8)

Dinner: Rice cake with 1 and 1/2 tbsp of light peanut butter (155)

Snacks: Diet coke (0)

Total: 332 calories

Edit: I had some peppermint white chocolate tea (5) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 15:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but they all knew about my ED </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 15:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love one! Great idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 14:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My doctor just said that the fact I was still losing weight was worrisome. I just didn't reply! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 14:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually wasn't feeling sick!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 04:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cinnamon (147)

Lunch: 1/2 red bell pepper (11) celery (6) cucumber (8)

Dinner: Rice cake with 1 and 1/2 tbsp of light peanut butter (155)

Snacks: Diet coke (0)

Total: 327 calories
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
