<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1637</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 20:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Capital, thanks. 

Forgive my ignorance, but I thought Windows 10 wasn't released yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What tablet should I buy for engineering? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 07:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I understand, the active stylus requirement is more a gimmick than anything. So I'm looking to get a cheap tablet to use for that and then have an actual computer. Any suggestions?

Edit: I think I must have been unclear. I realize that the active stylus is a gimmick, and I'm planning to get a real laptop in addition to a cheap usb tablet. But I don't know which usb tablets well fulfill the requirements, so I'm looking for suggestions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 02:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bread and water. I LOVE bread. Water's ok I guess. So long as I'm getting all my nutrients, it could actually be pretty great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 02:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey maybe Jesus was just offering some ahead-of-his-time nutritional advice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 00:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clarification: You *can* be tried again without violating double-jeopardy rules if significant new evidence has emerged. However, it is very difficult and costly to argue that and it's altogether cheaper to make sure you do it right the first time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 23:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Animal Crossing: New Leaf the sort of game into which I can sink hours at a time? Or will I get bored playing for more than half an hour per day? I know a lot of features are time sensitive, so will I have to wait until the right time a lot if I want to do things? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 23:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stand corrected, my apologies. I only really listen to morning edition, so I should have checked their website. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 21:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, step out of your internet bubble into the real world. Half the country is conservative.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 21:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no doubt that they always try to report the truth as objectively as possible, but they are biased in what they choose to report. For example, they talked for days about the SCOTUS gay marriage ruling, but when the annual March for Life turned out half a million people, they didn't even mention it the next day.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 09:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Much as I love NPR, they're far from objective. Their social-political news is almost as liberal as msnbc.

Their non-political shows, though, are fantastic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 06:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm looking into Animal Crossing: New Leaf. Never played an AC game before, it looks charming, but I'm afraid I'll get bored. What exactly is there to do in New Leaf, gameplay-wise? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 04:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Subs can do what they want. It might be sexist and invasive for *all* GW-type subs to have that rule, but since anyone can make a subreddit their rules are up to them. Some people can enjoy bodies without faces, some can't. It's reasonable to make a sub for either market. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 10:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taking tests.

I'm going into my Freshman year of college with over a full year of AP credits. 8 exams, 5's on all of them. 2300 SAT score. 

To compensate, I'm a colossal bonehead at pretty much everything else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 10:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same, Virginia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 10:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't mind an action-less experience, then you'll enjoy Story of Seasons. If you've never played a Harvest Moon game before, SoS is a good place to start. Take a look at Rune Factory 4 before you decide, I personally prefer RF4 to SoS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 08:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, this isn't even technically true. "Mitochondria" is the plural of "mitochondrion," so the truth is "The Mitochondrion is the powerhouse of the cell" or "Mitochonchria are the powerhouses of the cell." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 19:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point. I would say the admins were looking for a reason to ban fph as well as other offensive subs. They saw /r/fatpeoplehate doing things that could be construed as harassment, and they seized the opportunity to shut them down.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 14:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit should be transparent and honest about what they do. When reddit banned /r/fatpeoplehate, their biggest mistake was being dishonest about why. They claimed harassment, which wasn't unreasonable, except that it clearly wasn't why they banned it. Users could see through their political BS and tell that /r/fatpeoplehate was banned because the admIns didn't like it. The uproar was the result of reddit claiming to be a bastion of free speech and then banning speech they didn't like while trying to pass it off as harassment.

The problem isn't that they squashed free speech, it's that they were hypocrites. If reddit said "we ban whoever we want because this is our website," I would trust their judgement to use that power responsibly. But instead of asking for our trust, they gave themselves a set of rules and principles, and then failed to follow them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 21:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are Mexicans so great at basketball?

Running, jumping, shooting and stealing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 20:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Er, no, pretty sure it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 19:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it worth it? How much better is a New 3ds than a 3ds? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 19:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad to see fascist Romania getting some recognition, they're criminally underrated in the tyranny department. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 13:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Beidh Aonach Amarach](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3O6FjbbBmo0)

I like Trasna na Dtonnta and Sinne Fianna Fail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 13:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Desteapta-te Romane - The Romanian National Anthem](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zTwgwEHiWm0)

It sounds deliciously fascist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 07:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Losers don't fly flags** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 07:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a *modest* proposal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 13:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really... pizza slicers often don't cut all the way through. We use scissors all the time, quick and easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 12:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LPT: For pancakes and pizza, use a pair of kitchen scissors. It's way easier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 01:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I just wanted to stay in shape while still maintaining a snobby, pretentious attitude. Fencing seemed like the stereotypical "rich white guy" sport so I gave it a try. After the first few lessons, I realized that it was in many ways similar to chess, a game which I really enjoy. So, I kept doing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 13:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Want more quotes? Fine, here's the FULL context.

  Religious suffering is, at one and the same time, the expression of real suffering and a protest against real suffering. *Religion is the sigh of the oppressed creature, the heart of a heartless world, and the soul of soulless conditions. It is the opium of the people.*

 **The abolition of religion as the illusory happiness of the people is the demand for their real happiness.** To call on them to give up their illusions about their condition is to call on them to give up a condition that requires illusions. The criticism of religion is, therefore, in embryo, the criticism of that vale of tears of which religion is the halo.

 Criticism has plucked the imaginary flowers on the chain not in order that man shall continue to bear that chain without fantasy or consolation, but so that he shall throw off the chain and pluck the living flower. The criticism of religion disillusions man, so that he will think, act, and fashion his reality like a man who has discarded his illusions and regained his senses, so that he will move around himself as his own true Sun. Religion is only the illusory Sun which revolves around man as long as he does not revolve around himself.

Yes, the quote means something slightly different in the context of the paragraph. But the *following* paragraph Marx wrote has no summary more accurate and succinct than "Religion is the opiate of the masses."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 04:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing both areas, it's very well designed. I like it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 04:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally ridiculous, it's Moscow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/HarvestMoon, what is your daily routine? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 23:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Post your daily routine and the title of the game below! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 23:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, end the one you have going before a new one can start. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 23:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "religion is the opiate of the masses" -Karl Marx

Pretending that communism is not definitively and avowedly anti-religion is laughable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 22:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pop Island: Paperfield ($2.00). I also highly recommend the original, Pop Island, but I believe it is $8.00.

 Anyways, they're both amazing little capture-the-flag games, fast-paced and wild fun. You can play multiplayer, only one player has to own the game. And they're probably the most charmingly quirky games I've ever played, bar none. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 22:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd recommend Rune Factory 4. It has great characters, surprisingly deep combat, and a boatload of things to do and skills to master.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 12:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to qualify all the other responses, the Catholic Church doesn't have a totally clear vision of who or what Satan is. The interpretation is changed a lot. It's usually irrelevant to most doctrine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 12:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This quote has actually been hugely helpful in my religious life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 12:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> -Lord de Worde </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 05:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I'm guaranteed to be an *employed* one, I'd rather be a Lawyer. But since the market for lawyers is oversaturated, and there's always a market for doctors, I'd rather be a docter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 03:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Catalunya triumfant! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 03:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can line them up and hit several enemies at a time.

The charge attack, if you aren't familiar, hits the enemy with weak strikes very quickly for as long as you mash the attack button. They very briefly can't move after being hit, so they effectively stand still until you kill them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 03:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spear. The charged attack is fantastic, I can kill literally anything (boss monsters included) with a few charged attacks.

After that, I like the staff (magic attacks ftw) and the gloves (just for the feel of killing things bare-handed). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To simplify, left wing views support the population taking on some of the living costs of poorer citizens. So a wealthy right-wing person may be selfish. But a poor right wing person, who would have all the vantage of a left-wing system, cannot be characterized as "selfish." A poor left-wing person would be selfish, as they support an ideology that would effectively take wealth from others and give it to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 21:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point, but on the flipside he took the form of a Jew and made a very explicit point that he was there to redeem *all* mankind, that redemption was no longer limited to God's chosen few.

That could very easilt be interpreted as "Christ took the form of a *human* but he cam to redeem all *intelligent life*."

I think the real question we would have to struggle with is "do these aliens have souls?" which we frankly have no way of knowing besides divine revelation, so the practical question would be "is this life intelligent enough to understand the Word?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 04:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not quite. Independent organizations, like RAINN, set aside some of their funds to pay for the care of rape victims. When the rapist is apprehended, they then aid the victims in claiming damages. The rapist pays damages to the victim based on the amount of financial stress they endured because of the rape, and organizations like RAINN take their cut. Profits for everyone, except the rapist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 00:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The crafting materials sounds like an amazing feature, but it's a secondary feature. The fundamental mechanics, in the form of craftget more skilledunlock more recipesrepeat is unchanged and, frankly, not that great. I don't have a solution to this, but it is a problem that crafting systems are fundamentally pure grind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 20:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the subject of intelligent life on other planets: why not? What arguments are there against, say, baptizing an alien? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 19:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Always remember that you aren't looking for *things to say to the other person*, you're looking for *how to get the other person talking to you*.

That tip won't solve all your problems, but I find it helps a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 18:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Route 119. I'm a sucker for rainy places. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 18:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try /r/pokemonromhacks too, they'd get a kick out of seeing a good town design.

IMO, it's a nice little town. Maybe the red house is a *bit* of a walk from the rest of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 18:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RF4 is great. Characters are A+, farming is less in-depth but still plenty of complexity. RPG elements are pretty good, lots of choice in how you fight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 15:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ace, thanks mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 14:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where can I find the eu4_export folder? I'm not seeing it in Steam/steamapps/common/Crusader Kings II. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 14:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Used the last one, after the update. Thanks mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CK2-EU4 converter not up to date? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 13:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I finished a CK2 game for my Romania mega-campaign, exported the game but there's no mod available for EU4. Is the converter not up to date, or am I having a totally different problem?

EDIT: Solved, I was just being a doofus :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see the "one man, one vote" system is hard at work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [RSE] Is it possible to hack in "multi battles"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 22:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm talking about double battles with an ally. There's one instance of this sort of thing in RSE, when you and Stephen battle 2 thugs. Is it possible to add this into a rom hack without messing around in assembly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 00:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, maybe in the SPECIAL character creation we'll get to pick a backstory, i.e. pre-war profession, for our character.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 23:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not gonna lie, I love the drama. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 07:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, just hatched. Thanks again :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 07:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Egg received! Thanks a million, mate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 07:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! Sorry I underestimated the time it would take to be able to trade, are you still going to be able to do it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LF Machop Egg </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 06:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 00:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Simple, you chose slots over Blackjack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 05:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> k </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 03:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So... no downsides to drugs? Hell yes I'll take that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 03:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If reddit collapses I need someone to explain to me how tumblr works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 03:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Silly or not, damn that's a good song. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 20:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use console command "debug_mode" and mouse over Cagliaria. Its tag will show up in a tooltip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 07:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It brought new relevancy to formerly useless Pokemon. Several of those new evolutions were treasured members of my team (Electrive, Togekiss, Magmortar).

Baby Pokemon have always seemed kinda BS to me. They are useless in every way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 00:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally didn't dislike Gen4, I especially liked the new evolutions for old Pokemon. It did feel like a step down from emerald, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 00:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you on ORAS. Despite the fact that Emerald is my favorite Pokemon title, bar-none, ORAS felt like there was little to no improvement. Sure, it had an updated Pokemon roster, and mega-evolutions, but with the removal of the Battle Tower and Battle Frontier, it feels like a downgrade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 20:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah I think the original "When I remember that I hate the smell of leaves" was the shittiest gif to grace my front page. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 21:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, that explains it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 20:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> shit that's a lot of dolphins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has the converted been updated for Common Sense? If not, that would explain the wonky map conversion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Massive Orthodox nerf right there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 07:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This pretty much sums it up. I went broke recently, and I'm trying to save up money for college so I skipped Common Sense. I got extremely frustrated playing an Inca campaign when I had capped the monarch points and discovered that I couldn't develop my provinces. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 05:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, I think I explained my understanding poorly. I thought there were  2 things here, one of which was the objective moral truth of God and the universe, and one of which was *what our current best guess* is for the objective moral truth of God and the universe. 

Like, we acknowledge that we aren't perfect and that our understanding of God is certainly flawed, so we give our best guess while acknowledging that God is complicated and mysterious and that our understanding of Him is a permanent work-in-progress. *That's* what I thought doctrine was.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 04:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, thanks. I'll edit the post to clarify that. 

 As the Church gradually comes to understand doctrine

Could you elaborate more on this? I thought doctrine was the Church's *current* understanding of our faith. It sounds here like an objective, God-given set of policies that we must strive to discover on earth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A question about disagreeing with the Church </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 04:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, lifelong Catholic here, trying to get more involved in my faith. I'm a little confused about the morality of disagreeing with Church doctrine, and I hoped you all could help me out.

So, on the one hand there's the "cafeteria Catholic," who only subscribes to the beliefs they find convenient. We can all agree that this is wrong, it's not really belief if you can *choose* it. So in that case, disregarding Church doctrine is completely wrong.

On the other hand, Church doctrine changes. With the exception of those few times where papal infallibility has been invoked, just about all of our doctrines are subject to change as we develop a better understanding of God. For those doctrines to change, there has to be disagreement within the Church, right?

As far as I can see it, some people within the Church have to speak out against current doctrine if we are to develop a more accurate understanding of God. If people speak out against doctrine, calling for change, then some of them are bound to be right and others are bound to be wrong. So we should condemn Catholic dissenters not for deviating from official doctrine, but for being *wrong* in their deviation.




Somehow that doesn't seem right though. Can you explain it, or at least point me to a relevant catechism passage? How can one disagree with the Church and still be a good Catholic?

Thanks!



**EDIT:** /u/FiguredCo pointed out that doctrine does not change, but rather *develops.* Thanks!

**EDIT2:** One of /u/FiguredCo's comments mentioned a difference that I may not have made clear: I'm not talking about using some excuse for disagreeing with the church to act like a cafeteria Catholic. I mean a genuine disagreement about His truth, not just about what is convenient. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 03:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like I said, I don't want to get this argument off on a tangent. There is a time and place for a discussion on the evils of abortion, but it isn't a thread about gay marriage. 

I'm sorry about this, I don't like to end on a jade's trick but this discussion is making me too angry and I'm not sure I could stop myself from making personal attacks. So I won't be responding to your comments any more. I know, it's a dick move, I acknowledge that and I'm sorry that I don't have the emotional stamina to continue this debate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 02:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a waste of time to remind someone that this is a sin if we know from the start that it isn't going to help. Play the long game, make people understand the evidence before giving them the conclusion. We should be preaching to spread His word, not just because. 

As for abortion, I don't want to get too much into it because it's a little off topic, but suffice to say that it is a unique issue that we will never give up on. At least for other sins there is the chance of repentance, an aborted child doesn't get any chance to live and grow and their life should be saved at all costs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 02:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying it's ok to do it, I'm saying we shouldn't engage with a movement designed to make people hate religion. Ignore it, put our resources into bringing people closer to God through other means. If someone asks for the Church's view, we ought to give it fully and honestly. But we have to recognize that engaging with this movement is a waste of time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 01:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) the practice is a sin, that's what I meant, I'm pretty sure that's common knowledge

2) I am Catholic. When I said your church, I was implying that you are not Catholic.

3) We should try to get people closer to God. If they feel very strongly about homosexual marriage, the best way to change their minds is to let them reach the right conclusion. Getting into arguments might be fun, but it doesn't change minds. I don't want us to get bogged down in issues that the other side is very angry about and doesn't understand. We must always preach His Word, but we have to avoid focusing on the least appealing parts. Saying "the practice of homosexuality it's wrong" is morally correct, but if you're trying to change minds that's a stupid strategy.

Look, if you're trying to teach a history class, you don't start by listing important dates to memorize, you have to get people engaged. So, too, we have to inspire in others a love of God before introducing them to the less intuitive parts.

We have a responsibly to spread God's Word. We can't scoff and say "well we were preaching His Word, if they don't accept it that's their problem." We are all responsible for one another, we have to earnestly try to convert each person. There are no conditions to this. We love *unconditionally.*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 00:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This is a core tenant of our faith

Alright, I get that you think this is important, but we have to stop calling every tenet of our faith "a core tenet of our faith." Now every part of our faith is important, but some are important to greater degrees, like the divinity of Christ and the truth of His word. "Homosexuality is a sin" is not a core tenet of our faith.


 They were not good catholics if they were "driven from our faith" if they were driven because they were not allowed to sin or endorse a sin.

This is sounding mighty elitist. They sinned by rejecting the faith, but we should desire to welcome them back with open arms. We don't want to weed out the "fake Christians," we want to encourage them to be true followers of Christ. Our Church is the Church of all people. We *want* everyone to be a part of the Church so that the holiest men and women of our time can guide them to the path of righteousness. 

We do not want to drive people away just because you think they aren't good enough for your church. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 21:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm hoping it will bring the conversation to an end, or at least make it less talked about. There's so much more to our faith than these petty little semantics issues. And so many good Catholics have been driven from the faith because they feel strongly about gay marriage. It's cast the Church in a negative light to many Americans, and I hope we can move past this minor issue and be seen by all as the loving institution of His will on Earth that we are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 19:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hate crime is a subset of reactionary violence, I'm only using the must broad terms I can so as not to get tangled up in a petty semantic argument. 

My point is, rape and slavery are already illegal. Forbidding polygamy serves to prevent acts which are already criminal. Similarly, forbidding homosexual marriage could prevent hate crimes, which are already criminal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 19:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure similar arguments could be made against homosexuality, e.g. the decay of tradition resulting in reactionary violence.

For incest, I agree. But homosexual incest has no issue there, right? So homosexual incestuous marriage should be fine. Except then you've got a situation where homosexuals have greater marriage rights than heterosexuals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 19:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree completely here. The primary benefits cited by marriage are visitation and tax consolidation. 

Solution 1: let each hospital decide visitation rights case by case. Then we don't have hospitals saying "you can't visit because you aren't married. Hospital policy."

Solution 2: call all state marriages "civil unions." Heterosexual and homosexual. Now everyone gets the same rights.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 17:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first title was Rune Factory, so I'm going to suggest RF4 for the 3DS. It's a decent rpg, so there will be familiar aspects of combat and crafting. It's also easily one of the best games on the 3ds. 

Alternatively, you could get RF3. It's shorter, but has a lot more characters to interact with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 17:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good point. It's usually phrased as "homosexuals don't have the right to marry the people they Love," but neither do the people who are in love with a married person, or a close family member. I don't think I've ever actually heard a valid argument in support of gay marriage that addresses this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 06:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't connect with the characters yet, don't worry, new people will be introduced and there are some great character-developing random events. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 06:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the system, I wouldn't worry. I'm in the same boat as you, bought a 3DS 6 months ago, and IIRC there's only 1 N3ds exclusive that's been announced and I suspect that most games for several years are going to be old 3DS compatible.

As for Pokemon, I suggest you play Black or White. I recommend against ORAS until you've played the originals, though that advice may stem from my own nostalgia. Alternatively, you could try the 2nd gen remakes, Heartgold and Soulsilver. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 06:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want ONLY story, Phoenix Wright is a good choice. If you want story AND fun puzzles that make you feel smart when you solve them, look into the Professor Layton games. If you want both, there's the crossover but IIRC it isn't as good as any of the games in either trilogy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 17:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, you can't pick and choose beliefs, but let's not disregard the well-formed conscience. I believe, and I think a lot of people here are of the same mind, that as long as nobody tries to make the Church perform same-sex marriages I don't care what the state does about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 17:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah the stripe through the middle is to... I don't know, curvy? Irregular? I'm fine with straight lines and sine waves, but that design is just going to be a pain in the ass to draw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 22:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus fuck, *Russian roulette*? I thought Grindr was just like Tindr for gay men. Nobody gets shot on Tindr... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CMV: Being "on the right side of history" is not necessarily a good thing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 20:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Same music as Assassin's Creed 4? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 15:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got assassin's creed 4: black flag and one of the tracks sounded familiar. I thought about it and I'm pretty sure the exact same piece is part of the sunless sea soundtrack. Does anyone else know anything about this?

Edit: I checked, and it's similar but not identical. Sorry! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 05:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was ruthless enough. And madness isn't exactly a good quality.

It just sort of pisses me off how everyone spoke about "Wesley's employer" with such fear, and awe, and respect. And then we see him and his an awkward manchild whose only connection to his business is Wesley. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 03:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm kind of annoyed at how awesome Wesley was. He didn't even need Fisk, he clearly could have run the operation even better alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 03:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No yeah I do have to admit, the Nazis had style. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 22:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, yeah, I thought as much. I guess I'll get my computer elsewhere. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 21:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The T725 is $1600, the Lenovo is $1900, and the T935 is $2000. Price isn't a big issue, though, as long as I'm getting something for it. And yes, it is required to have an active digitizer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [USA] Fujitsu T725 vs T935 vs Lenovo Thinkpad Yoga 12 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 19:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm getting a new computer for college, and I'd like to get one from the bookstore for the on-site warranty. It will be used for medium gaming and programming for four years of college. 

The three options offered by the bookstore that might suit my purposes are the Thinkpad Yoga 12, and the Fujitsu T725 and T935. They all have nearly identical specs, save for the 12GB RAM for the T725 as opposed to 8GB in the other 2. Cost isn't a big factor, all 3 are within my budget. I'm primarily looking for high performance and hoping that this computer will still be adequate after 4 years. Which of these three would be the best option? Or am I better off passing on the on-site warranty and going elsewhere?

Bookstore links: [Lenovo](http://www.bookstore.vt.edu/ePOS?this_category=1746 store=109 item_number=C5049 form=shared3%2fgm%2fdetail%2ehtml design=109 __session_info__=jzKUy9UMaWAVBYAMaUaKozRFzecw6Ytnozlvupj6PSSUwyDeYHEOHREq8TBIIuwbOloHN%2bRLmCTY0qd23Tb%2fLTWYr4iTwVOQ5G8gxRfCO7LGhKWypK0UWXz0%2bA%2fDOB3bilfYcJkIHwvkqUEJGwSm2ua1DOzLOowo8Cv6ZulTh0noSdvU2zXwWll0WSEeqSmrM6QmRTkmEGePkHOcsKEZeJDWcyoJ2T2U), [T725](http://www.bookstore.vt.edu/ePOS?this_category=1746 store=109 item_number=C5044 form=shared3%2fgm%2fdetail%2ehtml design=109 __session_info__=jzKUy9UMaWAVBYAMaUaKozRFzecw6Ytnozlvupj6PSSUwyDeYHEOHREq8TBIIuwbOloHN%2bRLmCTY0qd23Tb%2fLTWYr4iTwVOQ5G8gxRfCO7LGhKWypK0UWXz0%2bA%2fDOB3bilfYcJkIHwvkqUEJGwSm2ua1DOzLOowo8Cv6ZulTh0noSdvU2zXwWll0WSEeqSmrM6QmRTkmEGePkHOcsKEZeJDWcyoJ2T2U), [T935](http://www.bookstore.vt.edu/ePOS?this_category=1746 store=109 item_number=C5046 form=shared3%2fgm%2fdetail%2ehtml design=109 __session_info__=jzKUy9UMaWAVBYAMaUaKozRFzecw6Ytnozlvupj6PSSUwyDeYHEOHREq8TBIIuwbOloHN%2bRLmCTY0qd23Tb%2fLTWYr4iTwVOQ5G8gxRfCO7LGhKWypK0UWXz0%2bA%2fDOB3bilfYcJkIHwvkqUEJGwSm2ua1DOzLOowo8Cv6ZulTh0noSdvU2zXwWll0WSEeqSmrM6QmRTkmEGePkHOcsKEZeJDWcyoJ2T2U)
EDIT: I didn't fill out the form because I felt it would be inappropriate given the nature of my question. If it would help, though, I'd be glad to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 04:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The entire Cowboy Bebop soundtrack is worth listening to. It's really something else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 00:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4 out of how many? I'm also kind of a maniac about solving all the puzzles :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 21:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the suggestion! I'll take a look at it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 21:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kid Icarus Uprising is a rail shooter, plenty of fun but not much content.

Animal Crossing: New Leaf is a life sim relaxation game, it has lots of content but you have to be patient to access it all.

If you want something to play for ~30 minutes a day, consistently, then get Animal Crossing. If you would rather be able to sink hours into a game until you've finished it, get Uprising. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 07:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, that's not a lot, but it is a story-driven game. Did you finish it? Any replay value? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 07:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the suggestion, I've been looking as ASUS and all their products look really nice. I'll check it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 06:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I mean is that it isn't weird to see phones at a social gathering, while books and gaming systems are decidedly solitary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [USA] Gaming, $3000 max. I want a real top-of-the-line piece, but I'm trying to avoid overpaying. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 06:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **LAPTOP QUESTIONNAIRE**

* Country of purchase: USA

* Budget range: $3,000

* Purpose (netbook, ultraportable, mainstream, gaming, desktop replacement, etc.): Gaming, programming. Hopefully should last through 4 years of college with a CompSci major.

* Screen size preference: 15", I guess. I'm not picky.

* OS preference (Windows/Mac/Linux): Windows

* Gaming requirements (example games and desired fps/settings): Assassins Creed: Black Flag at max settings. Crusader Kings 2 at 60fps after 400 years of game time.

* Other performance requirements (video editing, CAD, etc.): none

* Brand preferences and reasons (already owned accessories, familiarity, business compatibility): none

* Any particular style that you like (examples are great): 

**Which of the following qualities would you prefer? (Choose one, two, or balanced)**

* Long battery life -vs- Low weight -vs- High performance: Performance

* Build quality -vs- Low price -vs- High performance: balanced

* Low noise/heat -vs- High performance: Performance

**Which features would you pay a premium for?**

* High resolution screen: It would be nice, but not necessary

* A great keyboard: YES

* A great touchpad/mouse buttons: I'll use my own mouse, so no

* Great audio: No

**List any features that are critical:**
Not critical per se, but a touchscreen with active stylus integration is required at my college. I'm planning to get a cheap companion tablet for that, but if the computer has once that'd be nice.


Basically, I'm looking for a laptop that will last me all through college. My parents gave me a budget of $3000, which is awesomely generous, but I always feel bad about spending too much of their money. I don't want to blow it and fall for a stupid marketing trick. Can you guys suggest a few laptops that are really top of the line without being overpriced? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 06:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the difference with phones is that you are expected to bring them everywhere, whereas if you're planning to go to the bar it'd be silly to pack a book or a 3DS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 06:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frankly, yeah. Players don't need to be handed everything on a silver platter. I thought the little personality tests were nice. And anyone that didn't like them could look up the answers they needed to give to get the character they wanted. The choice was already there, they're just making it VERY obvious that the test doesn't matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 06:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much content is there on Professor Layton vs Phoenix Wright? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 06:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EDIT: Forgot my DSi games that I transferred over before buying anything

    1. Pop Island/Pop Island Paperfield (DSi)
Love these games, they're very charming little pick-up-and-play titles full of action and fun.

    2. Cave Story (DSi)
Still haven't finished it completely, but it's a great game.

    3. Etrian Odyssey Untold Demo
I downloaded this to try out the 3D feature, and it's good enough that I haven't deleted it. I've never really liked JRPGs though, so I probably won't ever buy the full game.


    4. Pokemon: Alpha Saphire

I pretty much bought by 3DS because this game was coming out. I loved Pokemon RSE and when I heard about remakes I NEEDED to play them.

    5. Fire Emblem: Awakening

I like Fire Emblem, but never bought a game until now (only played old roms on emulators). It got good reviews, so I gave it a shot. Well worth it, IMO.

    6. Rune Factory 4

Love the series, was itching for a Harvest Moon title, so I bought RF4. Words cannot express my fondness for the series, and this game.

    7. Super Smash Bros 4

This was a very recent addition, only about a month ago. Solid fighting game, a bit dull though. I wish I had some friends who have the game to play with.

My next title will probably be either Fantasy Life or Prof. Layton vs Phoenix Wright. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 02:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Abnormal" doesn't mean "bad." In a majority white nation, being black is abnormal. That much is, frankly, indisputable. Assuming that "abnormal = bad" is a misconception on the part of the receiver, not a miscommunication on the part of the speaker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 21:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try x-posting to /r/SunlessSea. Nantucket looks very similar to that game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 16:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That list is just an exercise in historical revisionism. Women have been oppressed and, thus, have had less of an opportunity to make a major difference. Rosa Parks was a political pawn in MLK's game, Harriet Tubman was a folk hero, Scagawea wasn't even American, Ginsburg, O'Connor and Anthony are still very controversial. Eleanor Roosevelt and Abigail Adams were influential, but they achieved that influence through who their husbands were, not who they were. And even still they made less of a difference than Alexander Hamilton.

Alexander Hamilton was more important to the US than any woman. That's not because women are lesser than men in any way, but because they had been treated as such. It's nothing but pure revisionism to say otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 04:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if they literally meant a "male pill" like a single-dose FtM sex change. And when they say "everything" they mean that they are going to secretly put this pill in the water supply and make EVERYONE a man.

I'm drunk don't judge me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 04:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, they should replace him with Aaron Burr. Because that would be *hilarious*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 06:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's actually a fantastic wingman tactic. "You're straight? Prove it." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
