<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5711</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 00:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the amount of guilt tripping makes me sick  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 00:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it has to do with the fact that government money is being spent on drugs not on food and shelter 

thats the only reason  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 00:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep i have NO one to turn to my grandmother is just like my mother 

my sister is her GC 

and i don't have any other family then that 

my wife also agrees with them 

I'm just a big bag of shit to them  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 00:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i to am a N- magnet 

i date them I'm "friends" with them 

my mother my grandmother my sister 
 
my wife 

there everywhere  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 00:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> have you seen something borrowed something new 

welcome to NMoms haven  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 22:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i personally think she looks fantastic 

but i think thinner is better 

and onto of that people have stopped realizing what normal looks like  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 00:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> personally i am 20 years old and I'm married the thought of getting married after i turn 25 makes me want to kill myself 

and i would have broken it off YEARS ago  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-04 22:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> vomit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-04 04:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no actually I'm in a wheelchair  have been since i was 10 and my benefits keep getting cut but theres are NOT being cut. 

They can lose some fucking weight i cant fix my spine  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unpopular Opinion Puffin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-04 03:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-04 02:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i know this is bad but i still think she's really fat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 01:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i cut myself from 11 to 19 

and my mother NEVER once cared she would just look at it and say why are you doing this 

im not a bad mother  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 01:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> she claims she's not a NMom riiiight
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Im married but i feel my high school bf was my soul mate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-01 07:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i started dating my high school bf when i was 13 till i was 15 he was 17 when we got together 

i am now married to a WOMAN and identify as a lesbian but i still think about my ex bf i have talked to him on and off for years 

i am happily married and love my wife but i feel that my high school boyfriend was and is my soul mate 

ps im 20 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-01 06:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So much wasted paint </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 21:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just picturing so many good things  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 21:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you eat all your food 

i will give you more food 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 05:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> please submit to /r/raisedbynarcissists
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-30 01:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes watching people actually do the sport is watching </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 23:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how do you love someone who hates you.

you don't  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hate people who refuse to watch the olympics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 23:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i am not a sport watcher and i don't like them much but i still feel people should watch the olympics.

all of the athletes work there entire lives to get there and for most on them this is the highlight of there life they will only get it once and i think we should be proud of them.

and along those lines my mother thinks that there should not be olympics because it is pushing a person to hard and stressing them out 

everyone gets a trophy mentality i FUCKING hate it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did we turn out so different </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 23:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i am so much different from my family not only in looks but personality and beliefs 

its like if my mother believes 1 thing i believe the poler opposite 

everything she thinks and believes i don't and that makes my sister the GC

but i am wondering why am i so different we were raised the same and she taught me 

how did i end up me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-28 04:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i disagree good use of the meme </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-28 03:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if your not ready to have a baby your not ready to have sex 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> my moms trying to kill me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-28 03:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my mother smokes in the house and our house has no windows that open I'm serious it used to be a restaurant so no open windows 

i cant breath in here at all it only smells like smoke theres no oxygen in here 

she just yells at me and tell me its her house and if i don't like it i can get out when i have been bring to but everything is very expensive  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 22:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i can eat 1 maybe 2 eclairs then i feel like vomiting  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 22:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when will they realize you need a certain BMI to have anorexia 

you could have EDNOS but its impossible to be anorexic and fat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 22:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fat people can be vegan and fat oreos i think are vegan so theres that  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to cut ties </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 03:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have been trying to cut ties with my mother but i keep talking to her hoping that one day she will actually change.

she never will but i don't know how to cut everything off or as much as possible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 00:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have seen dying fish flop around on my boat with more grace </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 23:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone with actual diagnoses anorexia 

this pisses me the FUCK off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 04:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How could she not understand why your upset </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 04:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so are we getting rid of it or what </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-22 20:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe she really is just a lazy person you can NOT change lazy if the lazy don't want to change 

you can try talking to her but i don't think that will help 

you might just be better to move on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-22 20:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did you tell her that you like laying around when you got together that was my problem

i am a homebody my wife is not and when we first got together she kept telling she hated to go out and didn't like people now 2 years later she complains i don't go out.

maybe you should find out if she's just has anxiety or maybe hates people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I got my ultimate dream and i hate it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-22 20:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my dream my whole life was to move to vancouver BC.
this past summer i got to move to bc ( not vancouver because my mother refuses to let me I'm 20) i moved to a small town ( HATE small towns) 

but i thought at least moving to BC would make me happy.

im in hell i hate being out here .

Health care is way worst .

the people are shitty. 

disability is terrible .

theres not a family doctor for 4 hours ( cant keep doctors around here). 

you have to drive 2 hours just to get to a hospital or a supermarket. 

i though moving out here would make me so happy its all i ever wanted. Now i regret it like you wouldn't believe and no i cant go back to ontario because my whole family located her there all happy out here and I'm miserable.

PS i cant move to vancouver with out my moms say even though I'm 20. because i don't drive and I'm in a wheelchair i will basically go where ever she will let me. she already said that if i move there she will not come see me and she won't take me there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-22 05:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my partner and i rent a room from my mother ( trying to move trust me) and its just a room for 600 a month </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-22 01:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i do agree i really love the sub but even my partner who loves fat logic who does have diabetes( since she was 10)  its kind of offend by it 

and i find it kind of obvious that i am looking at this particular site  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-21 06:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i hate the green text like i mean the colour its hard for me to read  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 22:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am actully in a wheelchair ( cant walk at ALL ) since i was 10 years old i have Muscular disability 

and do you have any idea how hard it is to get one of those spots it has nothing to do with the distance but you cant get the ramp out in small spots so you know what they can kiss my ass and walk farther because if i cant get one of those spots i cant go to the store e.g. if i need to go to the supermarket and cant park i need to go to another supermarket or come back later  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 05:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adele looks 40 !!! just saying  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think people are WAY to over sensitive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 00:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> with everything going on with fat shaming and Facebook and being politicly correct cyber bulling whatever i need to say something 

you all need to get thicker skin 

everyone is way to oversensitive and get offended at the drop of a hat 

people are to afraid to hurt anyones feels ever ones afraid to tell the truth and honestly i don't do that 

if your fat i will tell you your fat 

if your ugly i will call you ugly 

and so on 

everyone needs to lighten up and stop being offended at shit 

maybe thats because I'm generally a rude person that doesn't believe in being PC

and it take a lot and i mean a lot to make me offended </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 22:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> turtles swim like 20 hours a fucking day  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 02:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> im a chick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I love my wife but i HATE living with people </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 01:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i love my wife but i cant stand living with people 

i hate sharing my space with ANYONE 

i want to have my own privacy and have things my way 

i wish we could be married but live in 2 different places  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
