<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject758</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 05:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Orlando can't seem to catch a break. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 08:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My hair looks just like Coralines' now! Thanks! Maybe I'll post a pic tomorrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> dyeing over dark green hair, don't know what color to choose, please help! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 20:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had medium length tealish green hair for months now, and I really want to change my hair color to something else. Im on my way to a beauty supply store later. I bleached it about 2-3 times in January, before applying on the greenish teal color (I used special effects forest green and joico's green for about 5 months now). I really don't want to bleach my hair again and my roots are showing (my hair sounds like a mess, lol sorry) so I'm leaning in towards something more darker.

 I was told that reddish purple cancels out the green tones but I have no idea what to color my hair next and what it'll look like. 

Would I be able to achieve a blue black color without bleaching it again? I'll post pictures soon. I really need some hair coloring advice! Thanks.


(edit) heres what my hair looks like 

https://www.instagram.com/p/BExpll6ldsC/?taken-by=deann.u </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 20:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's like cotton candy! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 08:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a frozen calf/beef liver in my fridge. I oughtta try this, but pan fried. I still have some pomegranate molasses and some spices leftover to use, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 07:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u asked for it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 18:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is disgusting. I'm so sorry this happened to you. Something similar happened to me when I was a minor as well..if you want to talk about it, please message me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 09:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're right, I need to find things that'll be not detrimental for my health, I should try taking care of myself better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 09:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am really overwhelmed by all the support right now. In a good way though. Thank you so much guys. I really needed this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm feeling separation anxiety and I need people to talk to. (21,f) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 00:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I temporarily quit my job as a line cook to go on medical leave for a kidney infection that I'm recovering from. I'm feeling anxious without my boyfriend by my side and my life is really complicated, sort of lacking friends at the moment. I'm just at home, while it's a nice, warm and beautiful day and I can't enjoy it. I recently relapsed and everything's gone to poop. I don't want to cut myself right now and I am seeing my therapist tomorrow for a 2 hour session.

Just wondering if anyone could befriend me right now, it would be great. :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 05:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> many people mention Lana, Marina   the Diamonds also-
Meg Myers is an AMAZING artist that speaks deeply to me. 
Monster, Desire, Adelaide- brilliant songs. ^


heres some trip hop
Portishead- Roads, Mysterons
Mono (UK band that split up awhile ago)- Slimcea Girl, Silicone

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-26 03:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey. I was/am in your situation, you are not alone. Message me, we can talk. I really feel for you. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
