<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3132</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sticky rice soak time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 11:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there, 

I was supposed to host a Thai night today so I put my last lot of sticky rice to soak till I have to cook it. However, I have had to reschedule for tomorrow. 

What should I do with the sticky rice? Soak it till tomorrow night? Take it out of the water and refrigerate? Unfortunately sticky rice cannot be found anywhere here so I can't throw it out and put more on tomorrow (this was my last bag from Thailand).

Thanks in advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 23:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to Lulu hypermarket. Guaranteed that most foreign cereals will be found there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 19:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cook it with a little extra water. Not to the point that it becomes porridge like, but enough so that 'if' it dries out a little bit in the fridge, it will be alright.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 17:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.health-calc.com/diet/energy-expenditure-advanced


Woops, my bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 11:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find this to be the most accurate TDEE calculator. You can easily plug in the values for your exercise into it and find out how much you should eat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 08:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ALL DA OATS WITH SOME PB YUM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 14:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw some in the store today. They look/feel identical to the chat potatoes I buy. To track them I search in MFP "raw potato" and enter in my weighed out raw potatoes. Most potatoes are the same give or take 10 cals. When it is that small of a difference, it is not that important. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 06:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the weight raw or cooked? Might make a bit of a difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 10:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there! Good job so far. One thing to note, the 'grass-fed butter in coffee' combo does lead to weight loss when used as a meal replacement. It is called bulletproof coffee and also uses MCT/coconut oil.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 08:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oats are a good option. You could put all the ingredients in a container (even the banana- it should be fine in hot and cold conditions), and then you add room temp (or whatever is available) water when you want to eat. Mix it up and enjoy!
 I do this on longer school days and everything stays fine in my locker (which gets very hot some days). 


- 1 cup oats 
- Chopped banana or apple
- Scoop or two of protein
- Ground flax
- Handful of almonds, cashews, or walnuts


This is over 1000 cal and can easily be made more.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 11:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got it! Loved the snoo featured on the side!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I feel like I just signed my life away... [EE post] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 10:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our IB cohort (only 15 people) just signed off our Extended Essays to be mailed in the next few days. 

The five minute procedure of checking over the final print-out and signing it off was the most stressful 5 minutes (as of yet) in my IB experience. This is crazy to me as I finished my EE back in June, 2015. Finally, its weight has been 'lifted'. 


My advice to all in IB1, is to finish your extended essay ASAP. Many of my friends have been working on it over the past few weeks. And by 'working on it', I don't mean simple corrections. I mean hardcore essay writing from scratch. Much of their time has been used up by their EE delay, and as a result, their IAs during IB2 have been neglected. 


Anyways, good luck to you all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 06:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YES! Get it done. My school initially proposed a draft deadline at the end of Year 1. I followed this and managed to use my summer to go over it and make any necessary changes (minor). 

Over the past few months of Year 2, all my friends, who didn't follow the deadline, have been so absorbed in their EE that they have neglected study.  Get it done, comrades!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 14:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nuts are perfect for storing in a locker. Has your campus got a microwave? A container of oats is cheap and a great source of cals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 17:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your help! I ended up making 4 serves. It was great! The cooking tips worked a charm :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help with egg noodles and Khao Soi () </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 21:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello! I was lucky enough to be gifted some Thai cooking ingredients by a friend considering they are hard to come by in Dubai. Using these, I would like to make my favourite Thai dish, Khao Soi, for the family tomorrow. 

[Here are pictures](http://imgur.com/a/pYNCw) of the egg noodles I received (pen for scale). They are a dried variant and I am unsure if how to cook them and how large a serving size is. I am hoping to make 4-5 plates of the curry noodle soup.

Are these enough for that and how should I cook them? 

If need be, I will head to the shops tomorrow to hopefully find some fresh noodles though this may not be a possibility. Thanks in advance!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 13:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How'd it go? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 09:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you cook it plain? It tends to run quite boring that way. 

I like to change it up every time I make my oatmeal with whatever is in the fridge of pantry. Last night I had some mixed with a serving of Peanut Butter and some blueberries on top (add a little sweetener if you like it sweet). 

Another combo I enjoy is cinnamon and raisins with some brown sugar. Banana is also pretty good with cinnamon (especially if you cook it with the banana in it). 

If you are using quick oats, use a 2:1 ratio of water to oats (40 grams is a serving). Put it in a microwaveable bowl, set it in for 2 minutes (keep an eye on it though), take it out, stir, maybe add more water if you like it runnier, add any toppings (eg. I would add PB at this point) and then microwave for another 1-2 minutes. Top with more fruit, nuts, cinnamon etc. 

Maybe the texture isn't for you. Some people just don't enjoy it. Hopefully you can accustom to the texture, if that's the problem, and experiment with your own flavourings. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Modelling sand fall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 16:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there,

In regards to the volume of a cone (V=1/3r^2h), is anyone able to help me formulate height as a function of radius to then substitute into the original formula to get volume in terms of radius only? 

Thanks in advance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [High School French] Please help with my grammar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 06:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there. I am taking High School French and am currently writing drafts for a written assessment. The topic is on the climate/weather in France with a small comparison to Australia. 

My work is in its final stages and the teacher has told me that there are some slight grammatical errors that need to be fixed. I have endlessly scanned the document for corrections though I can't seem to find any. 

Would you please be able to aid me in editing/correcting these errors? 

[Here is a link to a GoogleDoc](https://docs.google.com/document/d/1gP_YH9eA-SVX8zW0xgHnHIPL53-HOYSbhOnVM-4qW6Q/edit?usp=sharing) of the assignment. 


Thanks!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 12:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, couldn't agree more! This is considered the more 'traditional' or 'old' part of Dubai that tends to be side-swapped for the modern buildings and attractions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 14:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeap year 1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 14:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ti-84's are damn expensive :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 14:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel you... I am in the same situation now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 14:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah! Good luck with that :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
