<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9229</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was everyday at the country club I used to work at.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grill is still awful  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's not a Jedi though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't think the tops came off these.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Black Chucks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 17:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. We used expired Kevlar plates at Basic training to get used to the weight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Demo derby  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I have to replace everything that is not the receiver more or less. It's a stupid one piece stock, no pistol grip, no feed lip, bayonet lug, incorrect gas block, etc and a parts kit would let me build it to the specs of a rifle I want.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bit of a random question, but could I do the same with an already assembled AK? I have a Saiga in 7.62x39 and got the idea to buy a parts kit and turn it into an actual AK instead of the abomination SAIGAs come stock as.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like the England comment. It's the same here in Ohio.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jokes on you. I have neither A/C nor radio </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My sherrifs department has an APC.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No disagreement there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well TIL.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 12:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. I live in a well off area with next to no crime and have gotten pulled over by one cop for speeding and then there are suddely like 3 police cruisers and 5 officers there. It's odd, but police in my town really have nothing else to do, so they latch on to every little thing. I know most of them and they're all honeslty pretty great guys as well. 

Also have been stopped for jaywalking before. Never ticketed though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 11:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't have the transmute spell and didn't bother to go find it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 11:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It still works well. I did it with SSE when it came out and it took about two hours of grinding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. I  bought a '95 for that exact reason. And rust, since it's the only year with a galvanized tub.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not involved with it anymore, but I used to love /r/falloutequestria. I didn't write anything, but I loved reading the stories people wrote. Some of them were bad, but for the most part, they were decent for fanfiction. 

It's a lot less weird than some of the stuff that comes out of the Overwatch community.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably the best year honestly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My high school coach just had us bring shovels to practice and we shoveled off the turf field.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. /r/falloutequestria. One of the stories is 1.7 million words. It's ridiculous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 13:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh. It was actually pretty terrible, seeing how it sunk and all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 13:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a gas line to a gas fireplace in the from above.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Freaking Rickon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It might kinda looks like a Cleveland class, but I'm not sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most are assembled in a factory by a combination of robots and people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 19:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope USA.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 19:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's my house (well my parents) and was done by a contractor a few years back. I'm not sure why they never argued with the co tractor about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apogando las luces? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 13:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few day late but it's because volume (well, mass in this case, since more mass=more water) is proportional to pressure according to the laws of thermodynamics.


q=mcT


Where "m" is the mass of the water, "c" is the specific heat (how much heat the water can hold) and "T" is the change in temperature. 


Q is energy, which in this case is equivalent  to heat. 


As such, when the energy of the system increases (adding the candle), so does the temperature. 

Of course it's not perfect, since the
It isn't a closed system (meaning energy/heat can escape, but it roughly explains why this is true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 13:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/starttrek is leaking  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 13:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like it used to be a loading dock with a doer next to it and they covered the loading dock first, installed the stairs, and then eventually bricked up the doorway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 13:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/notmyjob </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 13:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is when it isn't. We can't tell without context in this situation though, so it's probably best not to judge.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 13:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Orange is best tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 13:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do just because I like knowing immediately if something major happens (like a major terrorist attack I.e Paris, or natural disasters or something similar). And it takes less than a second to get rid of if I do that want to see it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How this piping was installed in my house. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 13:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 03:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...I have almost 80 hours with Sombra and didn't knkw that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 22:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love half doors on JKUs. It looks so much better than no doors.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I'm doing. It took me a year to read the first one lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 20:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks very good. I might suggest adding some tie down points along the sides, otherwise it looks like you may have some difficulty holding things in horizontally.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of an Xterras. Looks pretty OEM actually.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So expensive though. You can get a ex-military Humvee for about 1/5th of the price. Of course it's not as nice though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. Although Aston Martin doesnt have quite the reliability record that Corvette does.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 17:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure. They look wider in this shot than the standard Huracan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 17:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup same. Started the season at 1984  and maintained it for about a week and then dropped to 1400. Now I'm on the painful crawl up back to gold I gained 300 SR yesterday though. :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 17:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goddamn it. Everywhere I go. I can't escape /r/prequelmemes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 16:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds about right. Old wrangler's are death traps. I daily drive a slightly lifted '95 Wrangler and I could easily flip it if I wanted. Wind noise is horrible on the highway, ride quality is slow and awful (all leaf springs) and it gets filled up with water when it rains, even with a hard top and doors. 

That being said, I wouldnt trade it for anything. It's the most fun vehicle I've ever owned. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 16:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a 2.3l '97 as my first vehicle. That thing was awesome and was fast compared to what I drive now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 16:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> C7 if that counts. Or a C6 Z06.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 16:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drifting on public roads in the middle of winter in '97 2wd Dodge Dakota with bald tires and no brakes. I ended up crashing into a telephone pole and had to get towed out by my former (and now my brothers) '97 Ford Ranger.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 16:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *boboing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 14:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's good and all until people in the platoon start getting frostbite and hypothermia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 14:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow. That takes me back. I used to be obsessed with that place as a kid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 03:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. I knew exactly where you were talking about just by that description. It's been ages since I've been there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 02:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No lol. It was the Army </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 01:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did anyone else think that that one Imperial tech sounded way too much like Hera? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 00:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell no it doesn't. It just pisses people off and is just plain stupid. Like making everyone remove their cold weather gear when it's -10F because some jackass forgot their gloves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 00:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll put it in my YJ. Even more of a death trap than it already is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 00:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. That looks fantastic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 22:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dang those rear wheel arches look fantastic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 21:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup I voted for him in the primaries and was somewhat shocked he didn't do better. Still, he's been a pretty solid governor. I don't agree with him on a few things, but for the most part has done a good job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 17:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or in my case, this problem is fixed, but now everything else is still broken.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 17:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never said it worked particularly well, but it did work ok for what it was.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 14:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This crashed my Reddit app when I opened it the first time.

*I'm on to you* 

Also that's fucking awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 14:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trailers in general are a nightmare if you don't use them often.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 14:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the old first gens. They looks so 80's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 14:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They worked fine. This isn't a mod. It's an OEM option. It's more tractor than Jeep.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 02:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like someone stuck a Republic cruiser onto the front of a Eclipse-class Star Destroyer. Very cool.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 01:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ....how is that relevant? Because some people have a lot of money?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was an OEM Cj5 option.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say it one of her primary designs, given her ability to see critically wounded enemies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me as Sombra  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 17:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's ridiculous. Why not buy a Singer or other high end Porsche at that point? Hell, a Singer tops out around $400k according to their website. You could have two of them for that price and have it customized exactly how you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 14:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually that's California  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 14:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny you mention that model in particular. My grandmother has a Forester and is a terrible driver who also lives in PA.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is this? Subnautica references?! I'm happily surprised  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally nothing now, other then the ID number the government assigns you. (It sounds more dystopian than it actually is).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow that is beautiful. I think I have a new favorite early supercar  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that's what I've been thinking of doing until I can afford either a) a new tub or b) rust repair. I just hate the thought of Bondo. It feels like a makeshift solution to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that's true. I wouldn't even be concerned if I was replacing the entire tub. I can do that myself. (And some help from friends). I've already pretty much replaced everything on the tub (body mounts+added body lift, dash, seats, lights, pedal cables, hinges, shift boot, etc) Only major thing I haven't done is the windshield frame, which is probably the hardest (and most expensive) part to do. I can do assembly, I just can't weld for shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rust Repair on '95 YJ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I have a '95 Yj that I got a quote to get some rust fixed and they quoted me over $5000 just to replace the side/rocker panels. Now that's absolutely absurd, since that's more than I paid for the Jeep and about the same price as a whole new body tub. The rust isn't even that bad, except for a small hole on the driver side rocker and just a few bubbles on the passenger side. I don't have the time to learn to weld, and I'm looking for other options. I'd be fine with just patching the hole, but no shop will do it. They all want to replace the entire panel/paint/etc and won't do it. So I guess I'm asking what my options are? Any ideas?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 01:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has to be fun in some way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 01:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you mean YJ :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either way it's caused by the Death Star firing on Jedha or the poison gas exposure from Geonosis, neither of which are "natural". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To turn Anakin even more to the dark side. I mean shit, accidentally killing/losing the person you love has gotta create some serious anger and hate issues.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More than my Jeep YJ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been accused of being 3 (possibly 2) people so far with my username and that comment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm. Own a YJ that's never left Ohio since it was built in Toledo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Birth certificate sometimes, or just medical records. Also my (adoptive) parents know, I just never bothered to ask since I don't care.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no. They're on to me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could not care any less who she is. I am who I am. My biological parents do not make me the person I am today (except genetically) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 12:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So she's Tracer then? lol. The future got a little weird.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 12:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ding Ding We have a winner. 

It's the same thing with adopted kids (I myself adopted at birth, like Jon). My adoptive parents are my parents. I don't even know my biological parents and really couldn't care less. My adoptive parents raised me, so in my eyes they are my real parents.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 12:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's here in Ohio too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 12:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah, definitely. It's one of the reasons I want to build a FF Shelby Daytona Coupe  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jason Bourne did it /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 12:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's a race car that was made street legal.  Probably not very comfortable, but they're likely pretty reliable knowing the Ecoboost engine used.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 12:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And a company won't be profitable unless they have the best, or at least good products that people want to buy, so your point is somewhat moot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 13:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because what we have isn't actually capitalism. It's a pseudo free market with regulation set by the government. The government should just leave the economy alone (for the most part).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 13:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see no problem if these people are volunteering. They aren't being forced into it. They sincerely want to help people. It that so wrong? A mistrust of the government is healthy, but volunteering for the government is way different than being a slave.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 23:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We'll just sitting on some random parking lot it sure as hell isn't an original. They go for millions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 02:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much all of them to various degrees  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 02:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could see rail guns becoming a commonly used weapon. That is if we don't nuke ourselves to death first. The US Navy began sea trials of a naval railgun last year so it's an up and coming technology(military wise) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 02:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not too much. Really the main thing that matters is Calories in vs calories out. If you want to build muscle, eat more, of you want to lose weight, eat less.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 00:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /thread </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he'll see himself as sort of an adopted son. I mean he was raised by Ned since birth, after all. I myself am adopted and consider my adoptive parents to be  my actual parents since they're the ones who raised me, so I dont see why Jon would see it any different.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there another way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LW is complete crap. Those riveted on fenders look awful. The rest of the car isn't bad, but I'm sure it ruins the aerodynamics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 16:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's pretty badass. The body work between the bed and sleeper could use some work though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sombra kinda can when she EMPs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 14:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone has been watching too much Star Trek I think.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 01:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly Porsche would never make this. It would cut into 911 sales.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 23:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not possible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is that shithole of a sub relevant to this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 16:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just don't think Subaru really cares about car enthusiasts anymore. Other than the WRX (maybe the BRZ too, but thats more Toyota so I'm leaving it out) , their current lineup is kinda bland, and even the WRX is sorely in need of an update, but it doesn't look like Subaru cares about that ever since they got rid of the hatch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 15:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this point, its more like a dam broke rather than a mere leak.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 13:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably spray paint knowing North Korea /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 21:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I mean, it is technically true. A baseball traveling 70 mph won't kill you. A 1000 ton train traveling 70mph however will.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 19:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BFG A/T's are great. They aren't as good in mud as M/Ts but they still work very well. There's a good reason every other Jeep in /r/Jeep has them .  One of the YJs my family has has KO2s and driving it has convinced me that they are perfect if you don't want to switch tires whenever you go off road. I'm planning on getting a set for my personal YJ this summer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 19:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in Ohio. I was just stating my experience, which may not match up with everyone else's in the state.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
