<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1637</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overthewire Bandit: Passwords not working? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 07:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The passwords I'm getting for bandit aren't working. I can log into bandit0 with the password "bandit0" but I'm not getting any further. I tried copy-pasting the password from the readme, then I tried plugging it in manually, but both gave me "access denied." I even looked up the solutions online and tried to log into bandit2 and bandit3, but both times I just got "access denied." 

Clearly I'm doing something wrong here, since the passwords seem to work for everyone else, but I have no idea what it is. Advice/tips/solutions? 

EDIT: Well I slept on it, tried again, and the problem seems to have disappeared. Weird.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 02:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still, that's a pretty damn good rate. It probably survives the attack, and then you've got a *1/4 for 1*. That's excellent value for a one-drop.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 21:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you sac the artifact you control while this is on the stack? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 18:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a person has only a surface-level faith, then the deeper differences between, say, Methodism and Catholicism will be lost on them. A 6-year-old is going to get the same spiritual benefit out of a protestant sermon as a Catholic homily. 

It's only when you're mature enough to understand the nuances that these differences begin to matter. And many adults that claim to be religious don't really have a mature relationship with Christ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 15:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to make fun of protestants, but it's always lighthearted and I don't mean anything by it. For the most part, protestants are our brothers and sisters in Christ. Unless they have a strong, deep relationship with Christ, the differences between protestantism and Catholicism are minute and, frankly, insignificant. It doesn't mean anything more to go through the motions of Catholicism than to go through the motions of protestantism.

That said, it's not as though protestants are wholly equal in the truth of their beliefs. Protestantism rejects the tradition and apostolic succession of the mother Church, and rejects the Pope as the Vicar of Christ. The greatest issue with protestantism is that it completely rejects the *best* institution we have to help us find the truth about God: the Church. It hasn't been perfect, and at times it has been corrupt, but the Church is always more reliable than the judgement of one man. That's humbling to admit, and difficult, but it's true. 

As for major protestant reformers: Martin Luther I have a lot of respect for, he brought up some good points and rather than denouncing 1000+ years of tradition he asked to see them debated *within* the Church. I can't say I approve of running off to form his own faith, but I can respect his initial attempts to reform the Catholic church. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 02:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She essentially has 4 choices of ability when she comes down: Ramp, burn, card advantage, and removal. It's actually better than that, since you get to see the exiled card before choosing whether to cast. She's incredible, plain and simple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 02:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, a lot of these Energy cards are impossible to evaluate for Standard/Limited without the full spoiler. All we can do is consider them in a vacuum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 01:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Decent energy sink in limited. Otherwise, I doubt it'll see any play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 01:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Incredible value. Will absolutely see standard play. It's worth testing in modern naya zoo. If energy is strong enough, could see play elsewhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 21:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Norin the Wary will *love* this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 23:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could be cute in a UG spells deck with [[Jace's Sanctum]]. Topdeck manipulation + cost reduction, with a creature that likes instants and the top of library. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 23:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This could be cute with Devil tokens. If we see as many 2/3's as we have this past season, playing this could turn a board state with a few shitty 1/1's into a boardwipe that leaves a 5/5 flyer and gives you lots of energy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 22:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This + Devil Tokens could be a fun little combo if we see as many 2/3's as we had this past season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 21:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, each time you gain any amount of energy the ability triggers. So if you gain EEE, you get +2/+2, and then if you gain E, you get another +2/+2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 19:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wikimedia is the gold standard for decentralized, user-controlled services. Operating costs are covered by donations, of which they get plenty because they're providing an extremely popular service. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 07:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly I'm in the same boat. If I'm going to devote myself to someone fully, we need to be on the same page on a few things. I want to spend my time with someone who will help me grow in my relationship with God, not someone hostile to Him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 07:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After sleeping together for the second time, and having been an item for a week, we were lying in bed post-coitus and she said to me, "you know, I think the reason I liked you at first was because you remind me of my step dad."

I tell you, the last time I saw that many red flags was December of 1991. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 05:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a horny man, it is not in my interest to discourage women from having sex. I want them to have sex. However, it is in a horny woman's best interest to discourage others from having sex, because it reduces the level of competition.

That's not to say that women actively consider that as a motivation, but I can say anecdotally that I have censored myself on more than one occasion because I don't want to contribute to a prudish culture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 16:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How bout Cluelands? Monocolored, comes in tapped, when it enters the battlefield, investigate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 19:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Intellectual. I can fap if I'm sexually frustrated, but there's no cure for boring company.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 06:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a college Sophomore now, and I've noticed two distinct differences:

1. The level of competition is MUCH higher. A lot of these other kids are Poli Sci or International Relations majors, they often have access to some incredibly specific and in-depth research on the topics at hand. 

2. Delegates in crisis committees seem to be a lot more concerned with their *character's* power than their own. That is, in High School MUN all the "power moves" were about giving yourself more portfolio powers, more options when responding to crises, and generally it was more about appearing to be the most powerful delegate in the room. In college, a lot of delegates are content making their crisis notes all about how much money they're embezzling from the committee. The result is that they send tons of crisis notes that have little to no actual impact on the committee until they tell you about it afterwards. It's... weird. I'm still not used to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 05:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely, he's the most fun character in Twelfth Night. I've played him twice and I can tell you from experience that he's a lot of fun to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Standard] Mizzium Meddler against Bant CoCo? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 22:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[Mizzium Meddler]] doesn't really see play, but I feel like it's enormously strong against Bant CoCo. Bant mainboards 2 removal spells: [[Dromoka's Command]] and [[Reflector Mage]]. Mizzium Meddler is an effective counter to both. 

Against Reflector Mage, you flash in Meddler to eat the bounce and then you have it in hand to play during your opponent's next turn. 

Dromoka's has 2 possible ways to target a creature you control: Add a +1/+1 counter, and fight a creature. If the opponent tries to use the former to buff a creature, you can flash in Meddler and redirect the counter to it. If the opponent tries to use the latter, you can play Meddler and save your creature. Meddler probably survives the fight too, with 4 toughness. 

Mizzium Meddler seems like an awesome card against Bant CoCo, but I'm not positive what deck it could fit into though. UB Zombies doesn't need it. I hate to say it, but I think it's best fit would be in the Bant CoCo SB for the mirror match. Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 21:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The blood of the covenant is thicker than the water of the womb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 16:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was "shout out." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 17:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is exactly the answer I was looking for. Not necessarily a formal term, but something that sounds better than "fool's debugging." Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 16:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I'm trying to describe is slightly different, and I make the distinction because this doesn't work with a rubber duck. I have to put myself in a position where if I succeed, I'll make a fool of myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sometimes when I can't get something to work, I get someone else to watch me try do that when I succeed I look stupid. Is there a term for this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 16:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like, for example, I couldn't get my power washer to turn on. I turned the dial, pressed the button, and nothing happened. So I brought my supervisor over to watch me. I tried again, the exact same thing, and it turned on. I did this out of the superstitious belief that if success will make me look foolish, I'll succeed. I've been calling it "fool's debugging." Is there an actual term for this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 00:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I'm so sorry Mr. /u/_BEUFORD_. Please forgive me. I didn't mean to imply that I give a fuck what you think about me. Please, accept my sincerest apology. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 23:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha jokes on him I'm already hopelessly depressed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 23:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an uber-budget deck, I'm running like 10 or so creatures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 23:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was actually [[Contradict]]. I was playing Mizzix, so it's usually a counterspell with cantrip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 22:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know what? Fuck it, I am a bitch and a coward. But this guy's going to go to prison for up to 12 months, and he's gonna have a criminal record for the rest of his life. I don't care if I'm a "sniveling coward." This man crossed me, and I'm going to make him pay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 21:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I tried to explain this to him earlier: don't ask for blank checks. If he wanted to show me the card, then ask me if I'd counter it, I'd tell him the truth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 21:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't want to escalate the situation. If it was a full-on fight, I'd lose. The only winning move was to take the hits and then seek disciplinary action later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 20:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much exactly. It was like:

 "subject1637, do you promise not to counter my next spell?" 

"Uh, sure."

"I cast [some spell]."

"Counterspell." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 18:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, shit. I was expecting this response, but I didn't get it until after I filed the report. Out of curiosity, why not go to the police? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 16:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think so long as you trust his judgement, you can freely criticize his decisions. Like, there's a few issues where I disagree with Pope Francis, but when push comes to shove I'm going to trust *his* judgement over mine.

The Church could never grow closer to God if there were no doctrinal disputes within her. To other Catholics, we may freely debate the decisions of our leaders. But when we preach to non-Catholics, we must act as emissaries of the Church and speak for her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think I picked the wrong major. Again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 03:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So my first choice major was Comp Sci, with Physics as my second choice. I was rejected for cs and majored in Physics for a year. Then I applied for a transfer to CS with Computer Engineering as a second choice. Again, rejected, so now I'm in computer engineering. 

I'm now discovering that CPE is all hardware and almost no software. Worse, I'm gradually realizing that it's possible to get a job without majoring in engineering. WHY DID NO ONE TELL ME THIS?! I've always been told that STEM = employment, non-STEM = unemployment. I like programming, but if I had known that there was a market for Political Science majors, that's what I'd be doing!

But I can't really change course now. All my friends are tech people, and I've got a few promising opportunities for CS internships next summer. All my professional connections are USELESS if I want a government/legal job. I've got to slog through 3 more years of computer engineering so I can get into law school and do what I really want to.

And on top of it all, I don't even like the school I'm in. There's another school closer to home that has an excellent poli sci program AND a great CS program. The school I'm in now doesn't have any of the extra curriculars that I'm interested in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 21:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll see what I can do about making a screenshot album. I'm very proud of my work there and I think it turned out real well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 08:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dank? Check.

Christian? Check.

Meme? 

Lemme call my buddy, he's an expert on memes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 03:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want to be Bottom, ask to read for every character. All the men, all the women, all the lovers, all the faeries.

Jokes aside, I just closed a production of Midsummer last week (I was Bottom). I find it to be one of Shakespeare's most difficult works to understand and convey. In particular, the faeries always speak in a convoluted verse that makes the wording awkward to convey without singing "Twinkle, Twinkle, Little Star." Bottom requires very good comedic timing, and I found I had to practice and recite the scenes to myself over and over to get it right. But it's also an extremely rewarding role, because you can't *overdo* Bottom. There is no limit to the amount of energy and enthusiasm you put into the role. The hammier, the better, full stop. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 07:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely. Agil, Lisbeth, Thinker, Argo... I cannot believe that Klein is the *only* named character in his party. Honestly the show should've been about Klein's guild. A normal guy, albeit on the strong end of the spectrum, working through the world with his band of brothers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 07:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's dissappointing. SAO was *such* a cool concept, but they botched the main character and then proceeded to focus on him *exclusively*. I really wish the whole "players trapped in an mmo" idea had been executed well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 05:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol you try to take your Swadian Knights into battle in the mountains and see how weak the Rhodok Sharpshooters are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 16:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jamaica Plains is awesome for making a cramped cyberpunk city.

Egret Tours Marina seems to have a ton of potential to be a great settlement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 22:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely. These questions have answers, but they're so polarizing and so politicized that it's nigh impossible to approach them objectively. Which saddens me, because if we don't fully know what the facts are, we can't form comprehensive solutions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 20:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the flipside, we can't just dismiss biological determinism as an explaination because we fear being labeled as "racist." The reason that we *know* Africans are not genetically inferior to Europeans is that we ran a bunch of experiments with that hypothesis and, by and large, they rejected it. The only reason we can be so confident that Africans and Europeans are not genetically disposed to failure and success is that we were willing to ask the question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 04:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Avatar: The Last Airbender had a phenomenal world that I would love to see more of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 18:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm disappointed in the product but I totally do NOT blame Hello Games or Sean Murray for this. They tried super hard to control the hype and it's entirely on us for letting the excitement overwhelm us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 05:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vassal Settlements?!

ALL OF CALRADIA WILL KNEEL TO MY WARBAND
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 00:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Virginia. If it wasn't right to work, the union probably would've stopped it. Course, if it wasn't right to work I probably wouldn't have been allowed to completely lie in my application and interview. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 21:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **SIC SEMPER TYRANNIS**  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 09:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best financial decision is to go to community college for 2 years, transfer to a public uni, and graduate with a useful degree like Electrical Engineering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 22:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This title also works with the "that's a penis" gif. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] Meme magic is real. In fact, it's the only real form of magic that exists in the world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 06:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 23:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aah ok. I had Azura!Soleil so I didn't recognize her with pink hair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 22:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beautiful! If you don't mind me asking, who's the character on the far right? Is that Camilla? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 22:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I just read a lot of English literature. The company explained to me that unless I had a specific kind of insurance, I would have to pay out of pocket for any breakage that I directly caused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 11:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, can confirm. Schmergo is the author of the Dark Lord's Blog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 09:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nah you just saw the capital of ancient Phoenicia collide with a taxicab. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 09:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't have an issue with it being hard, it's just that a) I had only 3 weeks to work, so taking a fortnight to get used to it wasn't an option, and b) if I dropped something, I would have to pay for it.

I thought about it, and determined that there was a pretty good chance I would *lose* money by breaking something valuable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 07:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That question doesn't have a simple answer, because of how many variables are at play here. Does this man feel that sex is a deeply emotional connection, or a simple act of pleasure? Does the man live in a culture where sex is taboo, or a more open society? How attractive is this man? How many women does he see every day? How high is his sex drive? 

And after you take all *that* into consideration, it's still a matter of chance as to whether this man meets someone with whom he shares mutual attraction. 

Half of it is extremely personal to each individual, and the other half is pure chance. You can't realistically compare your anecdotal experiences to anyone else's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 06:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cruz would lose, unfortunately. He was very efficiently smeared by Trump and the Democrats that Clinton would be the favorite.

EDIT: It doesn't matter whether or not the attacks were true, or justified. All that matters is if they were effective, and they definitely were. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 05:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are these people on Trump's payroll? I mean, jeez, this sounds EXACTLY like what you would imagine a Harvard Republican Club denunciation of a candidate would be: elegantly argued, with flowery language. Appeals to the political elites (myself included, I thought it was lovely), but completely alienates the working class. The base is fed up with party leadership. A letter like this is only going to cement Trump's support with disenfranchised voters, and contribute to his reputation of being anti-establishment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 05:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it'd be a tall order for the Democrats to make Rubio look worse than Hillary. He'd have had it in the bag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 05:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope this is sarcastic. I would be moving heavy, fragile, EXPENSIVE things. If I'm too weak or too clumsy, it isn't just going to be hard. The job will actively COST ME MONEY if I fail. Classes start in 3 weeks, I can't go back to college broke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 19:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the greatest advantages in the Spirits archetype are 1) flash creatures, and 2) creatures with strong ETB effects. So I've been trying to utilize that, building a deck almost entirely out of creatures that fulfill the roles of other spells while also being aggressive, evasive bodies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I got my first job two days ago, and I'm quitting today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 13:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got this job for a moving company two days ago. I figured it would be a good way to occupy my time and make some money for school. I enjoy physical labor too, so all in all I was really looking forward to this.

Now I'm kind of an attention whore, but for the first time in my life I genuinely just wanted to keep my head down and do the work. So, naturally, I make a fool of myself a dozen times before we finish training. My grip strength is poor, my balance sucks, I have terrible form, etc, etc. I can't do this job. It's more physically difficult than I am capable of.

The other guys were nothing but encouraging and helpful, assuring me that even if I was "the runt of the litter," I was still "part of the family."

But I can't keep doing this for another week. I thought I could stick around until Friday, so I could be sure I was paid first, but I don't know if I can do it. So after I clock out today, I'm quitting.

I feel like shit about it. My first job and I'm not even capable of performing it. I've never been particularly strong, I don't work out regularly, but I've never been "out of shape." 2 years ago I biked 250 miles in a week, and I've only gotten stronger since. But this job is too much. I don't have the balance to carry a dresser twice my size without falling over. I don't have the grip strength to carry boxes that weigh 80% of my body weight. 

I think the worst part about it is how *nice* everyone is about it. I'm this scrawny, upper-middle-class white kid surrounded by bulky working class guys, but they haven't complained about me not being able to lift as much. They've accepted me, given me good advice. If someone had been an asshole to me at least I would be angry. At least I would have someone to channel all my bad feelings towards. Instead, I have no one to blame but myself.

Endrant. Sorry for the novel.

EDIT: I broke 50 lbs of ceramic plates today, so I quit this morning. I was only planning on doing this for ~3 weeks until I go back to college, but I think if I try to move any more expensive stuff I'll be losing more than I'm earning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 16:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edmund (King Lear) or Prince Hal (Henry IV). Richard III used to be a dream role, but last year I got to play him! It was awesome and so satisfying to check that off my bucket list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 13:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you think it's easier to change the body than the brain? The evidence suggests that transitioning doesn't make people happier or more comfortable with their bodies. Don't you think it's high time we explored the possibility of correcting the chemical imbalance in the brain? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 05:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!

Edit: er, those both link to the same article, which says that no controlled studies have been performed but that there is weak evidence in support of hormone therapy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 04:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  As a general rule though, reputable medical organizations agree that allowing a trans person to transition is the simplest, most effective, and most humane treatment for their gender dysphoria.

Have any studies been done on this? It seems like the most humane treatment would be to fix the chemical imbalance in the brain. Has any research been done into non-transitioning, pharmaceutical treatment for gender dysphoria? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 04:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is a pirate's *favorite* letter?

You might have guessed "R," but his first love was the C. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there any medical treatment for gender dysphoria that doesn't involve changing your gender? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 03:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it's not the most polite phrasing, but I'm not sure how else to put it. If a man has gender dysphoria and feels like he should be a woman, is there some sort of treatment that can make him feel more comfortable as a man, rather than transition to living as a woman? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 07:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this a RoboRosewater creation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 04:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plus that the First Crusade was started DIRECTLY IN RESPONSE to Muslim warlords restricting Christian pilgrims from visiting the Holy Lands. 

The 1st-3rd crusades were 100% justified, IMO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 01:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We should have a conversation about NATO's role in 2016"

"This is a conversation lol good talk bye." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 17:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, time to make Vault 88 into The Mechanist's Lair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 06:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who hates Jamaica Plains? It's one of my favorites!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 01:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know how sometimes when you exercise, and you're concentrating so hard that you forget to breath? It's like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 06:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mount and Blade: Warband. I'm only halfway through the list of mods I want to try, and the fundamental gameplay isn't old yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 17:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't want anyone interfering with your uterus, but I don't want you interfering with your child's body. Your rights end where another person's begin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 08:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same. After the low tech world of ATLA, LoK just felt like bad fan fiction. Then after a year I tried again and it felt like good fan fiction, and halfway through season 2 it felt like a proper sequel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 07:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly I consider Zuko to be the protagonist of ATLA overall. He has the most engaging and well-written arc of any character I've seen or read, with the possible exception of Walter White. And that final agni kai was a masterful conclusion to years of maturing that Zuko went through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 07:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. I met Father Hurley at your conference a few years ago, and I know he was a great coach and a good man. We attended your conference every year and Mr. Rauer would always talk about how much respect and admiration he had for Father Hurley. From one Salesian to another, I'm sorry for your loss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 07:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Johnson's pro-choice. Seriously I'm a libertarian on all fronts but I can't vote for a pro-choice candidate in good conscience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 04:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a video clip of this? I didn't want to watch the whole shitshow but I HAVE to see this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 12:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is Pendleton-act level corruption. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 12:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So no Cersei then? She was pretty into smoking septons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 12:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm pretty religious and I can say that was stupid on her part. It's one thing to tell a Presbyterian to get baptized Catholic so you can get married in the Church, it's another thing to say "you have to change your fundamental beliefs about the universe."

Some people think we can choose what to believe and that's just bizarre. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 11:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually have the exact opposite feeling. I can't get along with a person who takes every argument seriously, who can't argue just for the sake of flexing their debate skills. I grew up with lawyers, and my hobby is debate, so arguing is a huge part of my life and some people can't live with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 04:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Selfless Spirit is going to end up being *very* overrated IMO. It's going to depend heavily on the prevalence of destroy-/damage- vs exile-/sacrifice-based removal. Side note, it'll be an excellent GW tokens card for creature-heavy matchups. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 21:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That theory is supported by Freakonomics, which is part of NPR, which is culturally Marxist out the wazoo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 21:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is mostly what I'm thinking. Trump doesn't seem to care about the issue much, so I suspect he'll just nominate whoever the party will confirm and focus on issues he prefers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 21:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to point out, most people who ate strongly pro-life oppose IVF for exactly what you just mentioned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 21:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I literally will not vote for a pro-choice candidate. I like Trump's positions on a lot of issues but being pro life (or at least open to signing pro life legislation) is a prerequisite. 

There are a lot of voters who feel this way, single-issue voters who've mostly aligned with the GOP because of abortion. Pence as vp has done a lot to win us over but if Trump comes out as pro-choice then he's gonna lose these votes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 21:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm all for these things, but abortion still needs to be illegal. It's not like we can pour tons of money into anti crime programs and then decriminalize murder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 21:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the only logical reason to oppose abortion is if you believe the fetus is a person. He's said his "personal" stance aligns with his "Catholic" Faith, so that would imply as much. But if you believe a fetus is a person then abortion is *murder*.

It's like saying "I don't think the Jews did anything wrong really, but if it's what the people want I'll gas them!" It's just cowardly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 23:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how the 5th longest kill was shot with a fucking *machine gun*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 00:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Always Watching is too much of a beast to leave out. It has incredible synergy with Nebelgast Herald and Mausoleum Wanderer. Not to mention the possibility of Ojutai as a hexproof finisher. At the VERY least, you ought to be running 2 in the side for matchups that don't have Dromoka's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 17:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When her name is announced, No One should walk up to accept the award. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 20:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> America can publicly support a Kurdish state. We won't, because we don't want to antagonize Iraq and Iran, but it becomes a viable option in our foreign policy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 19:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm VERY suspicious of Brisela, not sure it's going to be consistently playable enough to win, but I am curious to see how it goes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 14:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who's BP? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 02:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Macbeth has ambition, but lacks talent. He botched the killing of King Duncan, so his wife had to clean up the mess. 

No, either Edmund or Richard III wins Round 3. They've got the ambition, the necessary absence of a conscience, and they're both experts at manipulating and scheming their ways to power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 11:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Capitalism** is a fun, simple game that holds a lot of fond memories for me.

**Caravan** is a deck building game from the video game Fallout: New Vegas. It can be played with one or more decks of cards, and it's tons of fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 10:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does and it should. But this is an argument that moral philosophers have been having for for decades. If you assume that a fetus is a person, then pro life is entirely compatible with libertarian philosophy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 08:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's like saying "banning honor killings is unnecessary government intervention." If there is one thing the government *is* supposed to do, it's keep people safe from those who mean to do them harm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 07:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, I've been swayed from Johnson to Trump because of the VP pick. I can't stand Trump, and Pence is mostly crazy, and I support almost everything Johnson stands for... but I cannot in good conscience vote for a pro-choice ticket. If Johnson would pick a strongly pro-life VP he'd earn my vote in a heartbeat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 09:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh sorry yes I meant U not B. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 08:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, these cards seem to work with Death and Taxes somewhat. Forces players to play off curve. Is there any history of a WB Death-and-Taxes like deck being successful?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 08:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I don't play Modern, but it's hard for me to believe that Mausoleum Wanderer gets a D-. It's a 1/1 flier for 1 that doubles as an on-board Force Spike. Can someone explain why it isn't good? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 04:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And when they don't give him permission, he does it anyways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 04:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that what Odin calls a tractor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 00:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The periodic table. I needed it for Freshman Chemistry and I never bothered to change it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 19:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean why not main board? It'd fit better than Selfless Soul. Soul might be better if he was running 4 Always Watching, which he should, but atm the deck needs card draw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 19:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Negate is better for the meta, because despite a very creature-driven top tier, the best spells to counter are non creature (Gideon and CoCo). But hopefully that'll change in the EMN meta. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 18:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not [[Bygone Bishop]]? All your creatures are 3cmc or less, and clues give you a mana sink when you want to hold onto your spirits in hand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 03:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Always Watching is a must-have, but I'd rather run [[Negate]] than [[Essence Flux]]. Much as I love the latter card, it's just more prudent to keep a counterspell for CoCo and Languish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 15:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting, I might give this a try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 08:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should be called Grand Wizards of the Coast for all this White supremacy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 07:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even in Limited, it's awkward. It has the same base stats as [[Erdwal Illuminator]] and costs 1R more, and dipping into another color is hugely limiting in a draft/prerelease environment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 03:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Libya? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 15:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much just a worse version. Though in standard the Spirit tribal might not be insignificant. [[Essence Flux]] and [[Rattlechains]] help dodge removal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoiler] Mercurial Geists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 15:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
