<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8657</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] I am relapsing after a year of being [binge]/purge free </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 11:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been struggling with a binge eating and purging disorder for almost 7 years. I am 30 years old now and it was almost completely absent, though the disordered thinking regarding weight and food never completely leave, until recently. I have started to binge and purge again for the first time in almost a year and I am beside myself with guilt, shame, and repulsion.

I believe this last set back could be due to my cycles. Do any other women here experience instability during/before their menstrual cycle? Perhaps I am not alone and this relapse is due to my body craving iron or something?

It always starts with me being unsatisfied with life and then eating to fill some sort of void, whatever that void may be. I am being treated for type two bipolar and that helps a lot because the sad spells don't come as often but this last one has me in its throws and, to my complete surprise, the eating disorder has come back full fledged.

What do you do when this happens?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to lose weight and not fall back in to old habits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 02:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey,

I'm a recovering ana/mia. It's been four years since my last major episode and, although I slip up here and there, most days I feel pretty safe in my recovery. That has, however, come with a lot of weight gain. Obviously, that's to be expected, but I'm a 5'7" woman and a little overweight. I just don't feel WELL, you know? I want to lose weight and get back in shape, but I don't know how to do that without extreme restricting and over-exercising. How do you lose weight in a healthy, happy way without falling back in to old habits? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I'm bulimic and am totally stuck being consumed by food </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 01:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm bulimic and I have been for about 4 years. Every day is the same, I'm consumed by food. I throw up everything that I eat. I go to the supermarket, to buffets, and buy food to eat and throw up. When my parents are asleep at night I stay up, cook and then do it all over again.

It's never ending. My body is constantly exhausted and all I can think about is food. My whole family knows about this. I've had counselling, a dietician, a crisis nurse and I'm still stuck.

I'm trying to recover. I've recently gained weight so my bmi isn't scarily low. My dietician has helped my keep down one food, cereal, so I try to use that to gain weight. But I feel I can't control anything else about this disorder. 

How can I stop this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Not sure if I'm ill/lazy/relapsing/something else... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 14:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I was hoping you might be able to help with some input. I recovered from my most serious bout of anorexia (with hospitalisation) about 7 years ago, but had a relapse about 1+1/2 years back that I felt like I recovered from (mostly on my own). Recently I've been feeling physically awful, and have also lost a bit of weight (other people have said so - I don't weigh myself). I keep getting illnesses and I feel exhausted all the time - like sleeping for 16 hours a day when I can kind of exhausted, and falling asleep sitting up at work a few times.

I can't tell whether this is a result of my body trying to repair the damage from my more recent relapse, if I'm generally ill, or just lazy. I feel like my last relapse wasn't that bad, and it's been so long since it happened, but I've also read other people say they suffered bouts of tiredness for up to 2 years following recovery.

I'm also not sure whether I could be slipping back into restriction and it's that which is causing the exhaustion. I have lost a bit of weight, but I don't feel like I'm restricting at all... I just wondered if anyone else had any similar experiences (of extreme tiredness/frequent illnesses like this) and what caused this issue for them.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Info: Center for Discovery Scholarship Offer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 22:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Center for Discovery, a residential treatment center in Los Alamitos, CA asked that we share information on a scholarship program they are offering. See below. 

************************************************
Our Company, Center for Discovery, is currently giving away 6 Scholarships for Residential Eating Disorder Treatments within the next 6 days. I have seen the passion and resilience of the redditors on this sub, and I feel that they would have a great chance at the scholarship. Please review the information, and, with your approval, promote the scholarship and help those in our community receive treatment that they may not have had the means to heal with. Thank you so much for your time

Link to Scholarship Site: http://www.discoveryscholarshipprogram.com/

Thank you so much for your time and have a wonderful day!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I can't tell if I am anorexic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 04:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Female, vegetarian. BMI in the "underweight" range. I want the answer to be no, but looking at the facts doesn't make me too confident. I skip meals, breakfast always and lunch when I'm too lazy to pack one to take to work or school, and then eat oversized meal with lots of snacks when I get home to make up for not eating all day. This past winter I lost a significant amount of weight because when I get busy with school and work, food becomes my last priority but I've yet to put it back on. I am happy with the way my body is currently, but not happy with the number on the scale mostly because I'm worried what others would think of it. I've tried getting my family to help with my eating habits but they're busy and don't notice if I don't eat. I don't relish eating, I love it actually, cooking too but I don't know. I don't think this is healthy either way.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Recommendations for an ED-friendly cookbook? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 03:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to purchase an ED-friendly cookbook for my girlfriend who is in recovery. Any recommendations? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Recovery] A food diary phone app for tracking recovery: Discovery in Recovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 13:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Music to support a friend with ED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 13:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A friend of mine (we are in a treatment centre together) has a severe and long-standing eating disorder. Unfortunately she must go home for two days soon and home is a massive trigger for her.

I am trying to find a piece of music for her that she can take with her as a piece of support. Essentially, the messages I'm trying to say are:
1) She is not her ED, I want her to keep remembering who she is distinct from the ED (Golden-hearted, there for everyone, a bit cheeky, perhaps pixie-like).
2) That while she's got knocked down before, she's always got back up and never given up the fight. There's a strength in her she doesn't always see.

Does anyone know of any music that fits? My own collection has come up dry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Low energy in early recovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 13:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm wondering if there's an explanation for feeling very low energy during early recovery and if so, how long it has taken for others to feel stamina and energy levels returning. Oddly, I felt more "pep" and even physically stronger when I was regularly engaging in binge/purge behaviors. Does the repair and recovery process even contribute to fatigue more than the actual Ed? I'm committed to recovery, but I do find this part hard. I like to be gently active most days to take the edge off anxiety but lately even my walking can feel like I'm dragging my tired self around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: When/how to trust intuitive eating? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 14:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been calorie counting for years now. I did it to help my ED and I used it to make sure I was eating enough through recovery and motivation. I recognize that I am obsessed with it and how to fit my numbers in everyday. I tried intuitive eating but still tracked my calories during the day and did not look at my calories until the end of the day to see how much I would typically eat. Everytime I intuitively eat, I eat much less than I am supposed to. I will lose weight rapidly if I continue to intuitively eat and I do not want that. I am asking, will I ever be able to eat normal? As of right now I have to track my calories to make sure I eat enough. Full disclosure: I am on thyroid medication and birth control because I have an overactive thyroid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Girlfriend too dependent for support </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 13:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend and I have been together for a while now but we just broke up.  I am someone who is easily affected by people's emotions and it was pretty hard for me to constantly support her through her ED recovery (I lost a lot of weight myself while dating her).  I would even go home after helping her through an episode feeling extremely anxious, a feeling that I have never felt before in my life.  I felt like she was too dependent on me for support, the people she used to go to before we started dating she no longer felt comfortable talking to.  She would even not talk to her therapist truthfully.  

I still love her with all my heart and talk to her everyday.  She wants to get back together, but disregarding my own hardships, I am wondering if taking some time off would help her recovery (which has stagnated and she has perhaps even been relapsing) or if I am enabling her by being with her? My original thought towards taking a break was with the intention of getting her to be less dependent on me for support and for her to have a wider network of people who can be there for her.  It was extremely hard for me to leave her because I don't know what will happen to her but I still care about her.  I hope she isn't reading this post but I'm going to therapy with her in a couple days so maybe that will help shed light on the situation as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Just realizing I'm suffering from some kind of ED. How do I go about fixing it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 13:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always ate a lot and my weight always fluctuates between normal and overweight, though during my school days people were convinced I was heavier. I just ate a lot of unhealthy stuff with my friends and healthier stuff at home and I didn't give it much thought afterwards.

Fast forward to 2016 where I'm pretty sure this got more serious. I eat mostly the same stuff (slightly healthier if anything) but my attitude towards food has become really unhealthy. I'm unable to eat without thinking about what I'm doing to my body, and sometimes I try to limit my intake of calories but it doesn't last long and I end up binge eating. It's not related to hunger, even if I'm full I will keep eating and when I'm stressed it gets worse. Sometimes at night I really have the urge to eat after all my meals are already over, so I wait until breakfast, but instead of falling asleep and eating after waking up like a normal person, I stay up all night so I can eat as early as possible, usually between 3-4am. Then hopefully I will fall asleep late enough that I will wake up at dinner time and not earlier, because some days meal times are literally the only thing I'm looking forward to.

I don't know what to do, I try to eat healthy, I get hungry, I eat more, then I end up binging. I try to make things better by exercising but after cutting back fast food and exercising for a while I actually gained weight so I mostly do it to trick myself into thinking binging won't be that bad to my body.  I want to stop but I can't help thinking about food all the time. What are the first steps I should take towards fixing this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Help with my ED (next steps) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 13:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi. I'm a male with what I think is anorexia. I'm always occupied with food and hate eating even a single cracker and I checked the symptoms as well. I matched nearly all of them. I used to train like crazy but over the past month or so, I can barely do anything since i'm so exhausted all day, everyday. In addition, my chest and heart also hurt like hell whenever I run now which is new. please, i need some help - what are my next steps? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I am never hungry and when I am I feel the physical need to vomit after. What's wrong with me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 11:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically the title says it all. Most times I'm not hungry but when I am I have the physical urge to vomit after. Also sometimes I get super painful shocks from my throat to my stomach that make me not want to eat because it hurts so bad. I don't want to vomit or feel this way. Most times I force myself to eat or have to smoke weed to make myself eat. This has been going on since I was about 13 and I'm 19 now. I don't know what is wrong with me or if I have an ED. I didn't know where else to ask this so sorry if I'm not welcome. What's wrong with me?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: What do you do when you find yourself tempted to relapse...? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 05:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been recovered (from anorexia) for four years now and even though I normally do pretty well, I do sometimes find myself tempted to fall back into old habits.

After recovery I was in the low middle range of a healthy weight and I was totally happy there! I was confident, felt beautiful, and actually felt thinner than I did when I was very underweight during my ED (body dysmorphia caused that, I guess). But recently I've gained weight and I'm now at the higher end of healthy and it's driving me insane. I think about it constantly, I feel huge, nothing fits, it's making me want to cut sometimes, I hate wearing fitted clothes (which is, like, my entire wardrobe), I can't even let my fiance see me shirtless, and it's affecting the way I feel about my value as a person too. I hate it.
I wish I could do it the healthy way without it being a huge hassle. All I want is to be able to lose some weight without it turning into a massive anorexia thing. The first time I had it, it lasted for almost a decade and it was miserable. So I'd prefer not to do that again...

So my first reaction was "Okay, I just need to lose the weight I gained and I'll be fine." Which is... normal, right? I think that part is okay, and I'm definitely set on getting back to my normal weight. But I'm not sure I'm capable of going about it the way you're "supposed" to because my first thought was to look at thinspo, make an account on a pro ED forum I used to frequent, berate myself constantly for being fat, and--of course--restrict heavily and exercise a lot. I guess I just feel like if I'm not doing those things then I'm not working hard enough, and some part of me still believes that if I'm not at a certain weight then I'm not worth as much or something. Like, I don't deserve to be happy until I'm back to that weight, because until then I'm just a piece of shit person with no value. Which logically I know isn't true, but sometimes it feels that way?

Also, one big problem I had when my ED was at its worst was the self harm it caused me to perform. I hated my stomach the worst (and that's my problem today) and I would often cut there because I hated it and I guess that's just how I took out my anger. I don't know, but I'm finding myself more and more tempted to do that, too. I haven't told my fiance that part because I don't want him to worry about me, but it's getting hard to deal with. Any advice for that too?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Nausea and increasing fats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 04:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had an ED for a number of years and for the last few years I've been in recovery. Recently, I started working with a nutritionist who told me I wasn't eating enough fat. So, I started to have a tablespoon of healthy oils with each meal. At first I tolerated it well and my skin and hair have been looking much better but lately I've been feeling really nauseous. Has anyone else experienced this? I also think it has to do with my cycle. Premenstrually my appetite increases and my digestion feels robust but in the first half of my cycle my appetite dampens to the point where I don't feel like eating but if I don't eat I get low blood sugar. Does anyone else experience these strong hunger cues that fluctuates over their cycle? Can anyone offer advice?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Eating more than others </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 15:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I'm currently in recovery and things are going on well, however, I struggle sometimes with the fact that I have to eat more than other people. I manage to push this fear away, because I know this is the only path for me to become healthy again. But, I fear that when I will be weight restored, I will still have this guilt for eating more than other people on some occasions, when others around me aren't hungry, or eat differently.

I have trouble accepting the idea that when I'm normal, I may sometimes want more than another person, as I've always felt that would make me abnormal or give me the body shape that I fear.

Has anyone had a similar experience? Do you have any ideas about how to push away the fear, or to get rid of these persistent ideas? Thanks for any help.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Put on a lot of weight binging now starting to restrict </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 11:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've been struggling with binge eating for several years off and on. Since this time last year I've put on a significant amount of weight from uncontrollable binge eating. Its gotten so bad that I've started purging again. But I've found a way to stop binging. I've been fasting and severely restricting my daily calorie intake. And when I do this I feel like I can control my binging. But I know it's unhealthy. 


Idk. I don't know how to find that middle ground between binging and restricting. I guess I was hoping for advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How do I fix my water-drinking habits? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 11:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over the past two years, I struggled with anorexia nervosa and became underweight. One of the things I did to manage hunger was to drink copious amounts of water. I regularly drank until my stomach was sloshing with water and I felt sick. After a while of this, it became that I was always thirsty and that I would have to go to the bathroom constantly.

Right now, my weight has been restored to the pre-ED weight and I am eating a healthy amount of food each day (although I still am neurotic and obsessive over calorie counts). However, I still have constant thirst and frequent urination. This time, I'm not drinking water to deal with hunger, but with thirst. I drink way more water than I did before my ED, but water just seems to go through me, and I feel thirsty again after an hour.

Did I break something with regard to my body's water regulation? Should I see a doctor about this?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: dentist help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 02:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been struggling with bulimia on and off for several years. I'm now at the point in my recovery where I am ready to see a dentist (I had stopped once I started purging), but I'm afraid. They're going to know my history with one look in my mouth.

When looking for a new dentist, is there something I should look for? Something I should say when scheduling the first appointment?

I have a lot of anxieties when it comes to dentists because of my past disorder so any advise would be greatly appreciated!!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: GAD and possibly disordered eating </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 02:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Backstory: I have a diagnosed anxiety disorder. It has caused me to restrict my food intake for many reasons: 

* physical stress reaction cutting my appetite 

* excessive and irrational worry about time management and money (skip meals to gain time/save money) 

* excessive and irrational worry about physical appearance (was at a healthy weight when GAD was diagnosed,am now slightly underweight) 

* feeling of control/ as a way to control feelings of guilt or inadequacy (ex: I beat myself over my lack of discipline; I will limit my food to "prove" I can have self discipline/control.) 

* Ashamed to admit it but simply to harm myself, as a "punishment" or a "test".

I've doing much better lately in general but my anxiety about calorie intake, physical activity and physical appearance has grown slightly stronger (especially if I can't go to the gym as its the case for all of August as I am traveling or if I can't control my food as much or decide to have an ice cream or a bigger meal for example.) My psych's take on it was that, since most things are going better, I am focusing my anxiety on something that I feel like I can control. It goes on and off and it isn't too bad as I'm not losing weight rapidly but I am terrified of gaining some as I fear I won't be able to control that and end up heavier than I'd want to be. It's not always worrying me but when it does it makes me very unhappy...

Tips on getting over that fear and guilt? When I go back to uni in a month, my anxiety will become much worse and I'm scared it will only add to the issue.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Help managing Binge Eating </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 02:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I go through cycles of eating too much then not eating at all. Recently I've been in the "eating too much" stage.
I feel hungry all the time. No matter how much I eat- even if I begin to feel sick, I'm never satisfied and it feels like I've eaten nothing. I've gained a significant amount of weight in just over a year and it's completely demolished my self-esteem.
I'm completely at a loss for what to do. I've tried changing what I eat and when I eat. My relationship with food has become so unhealthy that I only see food as a source of pleasure or punishment. I can't just eat because it's "dinner time". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My friends eating disorder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 02:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend has had troubles with anorexia and bulimia for years now, it was bad enough that a few years ago she had to go to Renfrew to get better, a year after that she looked healthy and she was gaining weight again, but recently, every time she eats, not more than 5 minutes after, she goes to the bathroom and she stopped gaining weight and rather lost more weight. I'm concerned that she's falling back into it and if she is, is there a way to approach this lightly? Thank you.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Girlfriend developing anorexia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 19:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I'll try to keep it short, but I'm fairly sure my girlfriend is developing anorexia. She has been rapidly losing weight this summer, and only allows herself to eat a very low number of calories each day, and says she likes to burn that off while exercising and then some. She does at least two intense workouts a day, usually running at least 8 miles or more for one of them. She tells me she constantly feels bloated and cries looking at all the fat she doesn't want in the mornings. She is at a healthy weight right now, but says she wants to keep losing weight. She also has told me on a couple occasions that she's made herself throw up after eating something with too many calories, like an avocado or pastry. I did try to discuss this with her once, albeit not very tactfully, and she got very upset and defensive, saying that she used to suffer from depression and anxiety and she wasn't that bad anymore. I'm not sure how to discuss this without upsetting her, but I'm very concerned for her health, she says she always has headaches and is getting back spasms that she didn't used to get. How do I approach this topic in a way that won't bother her or make her defensive? Thank you for any help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Anorexia vs. Anorexia Nervosa and what could trigger the first one </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 03:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Anorexia Nervosa is the eating disorder and Anorexia is the loss of appetite?

I am a female at a healthy weight, however I have recently lost a lot of weight in the last 3 weeks and it's starting to scare me. I feel like shit all the time. My head hurts, my body hurts, my heart is beating too fast. I am weak, but I am not hungry. I used to have a food addiction and used food as a coping mechanism for living with people I hated. I finally moved out and decided to only eat when I'm hungry... but I'm never hungry. I eat 3 small meals each day, and it satiates me, but I am losing weight and feeling weak.

What the fuck is wrong with me? I'm so scared. I want to be hungry again but I can't eat if I'm not hungry because it feels like acting on my addiction. Help.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How Can I Help My GF Realize That She Has Severe Body Dismorphia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 14:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm posting here out of desperation to try and help my GF realize she has major body dysmorphia. She is 35 and on the lower side of healthy weight. Thankfully she eats regularly, so I don't think she qualifies as anorexic. I think she is absolutely beautiful and nobody would ever think that she has weight issues. But to hear her talk about herself it's always extremely negative comments. Every morning when she gets dressed it's like this. She goes on about how her clothes are touching her funny, and nothing looks good on her, that she finds herself disgusting. It always ends up with her breaking down and crying hysterically. She says she doesn't want to go on living like this, and I can tell she's hurting horribly inside.

If I try to point out that she is not at heavy at all I always get the same "You're lying to me! I see what I look like in the mirror and pictures. Stop trying to act like this isn't a problem!" So it's obvious to me that what she sees of herself isn't what any other person sees.

I really want her to get the help she needs, but she won't even admit this is a problem. She thinks that I'm lying to her so that she'll "just accept being fat." Every time I press the issue we get into a big fight. And even if I don't say anything she has a mini-breakdown almost every morning.

What can I do to help her realize that her weight is completely healthy and that she needs to get help with these issues? I love her and want to help her through this, but I can't do anything until she realizes there's a problem. Any help would be greatly appreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How do you know if you're dangerously underweight? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 14:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because of a previous episode my family had to hide the weighing scales from me, and I haven't seen them in over a year. Now I've started losing weight recently. It wasn't intentional, it was just because I went on a holiday and had to restrict what I ate. On holiday I kind of knew I was underweight because of all the walking we did, and I got double vision a lot. 

But now that I'm back I want to remain at this weight, so it's caused bit of a 'relapse' in me. Once again, I've started restricting my diet when I just reached a healthy weight beforehand, but I am eating whole meals, if they can be called that. I'm definitely eating better than I was on holiday, so the double vision has mostly stopped now.

I ask this because just before writing I noticed some dry skin on my hand, and this was one of the symptoms my old eating disorder therapist would point out. But I don't feel anything drastically different. I have no idea if I should be worried, though, because I can't weight myself, so I can't say for certain whether I'm underweight. 

Any signs I should look for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Counselor isn't offering much help with binging issue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 03:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had a lot of issues with binging for about 6 years off and on. I've been on lately, having issues with binging almost daily again. And when I can get away with it I've been purging again.

I've talked to my therapist previously about having issues with binging and didn't receive much advice beyond "eat salad" which I guess can be helpful, but not really too much.

So I don't really know what to do. I feel like I'm losing control of everything again.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: significant others eating habits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 05:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there,

Have been concerned about my long time boyfriends eating habits lately and wanted to post to ask if I am worrying over nothing. Recently realised that if I am out he will not eat or if he does only eat pasta + something for flavour.

Many Thanks
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My wife has bulimia and is asking me to essentially take control of her life to help her recovery, but I'm worried it will create resentment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 01:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I (M/30) need help on the right path to help my wife (28/F) with BN. We have been together for 5 years and her ED has always been something that we are working on, she has gone to inpatient treatment and seen many therapists and nutritionist. Currently our insurance is terrible and we can't really afford any treatment options in a formal paid way. As for me, I have been a lurker here for a while, as well as attending some appointments with her and doing a lot of the research. I have come to terms with the fact that it is her problem, and that I am here to support her while giving the space needed, no finger pointing or shaming.

That brings us to now, she is going through a pretty bad stretch, and has now asked me to pretty much take over her life. She wants me to control her money, have all her account information, lock up all the food, and track her location when she goes out. I don't feel like this is a good idea because I will be the barrier between her and her comfort, and I can see her really resenting me for that. She has also stated repeatedly that she needs space, which I get and oblige her, that is why this idea doesn't seem good. 

Has anyone done anything similar? What are some alternative ideas? I want to have a good talk with her but I want to be very well prepared before I do so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My friend won't eat [19, F] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 03:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So my friend who I know online has told me that she doesn't like eating food. She says that just seeing food or smelling it makes her want to be sick, and now I'm really worried about her as I thought it could be the first signs of anorexia? This has only been happening since a month ago and she has lost weight. I've told her that she needs to see a doctor but she says she has no energy to do anything and always feels tired and wants to sleep. I've warned her about anorexia and that if she continues then she will lose even more weight. If anyone could post their advice then I will refer her to this thread and let her read the replies. Thank you for any help.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Research Study Request: Thoughts, Feelings, and Actions Study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 04:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Fear of eating lead to ED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 04:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure if this is the best place for me, because I don't have the traditional eating disorder - losing weight was a bonus, because I was incredibly overweight before all of this started, but my reason is I'm TERRIFIED of being sick, to the point where I won't eat for weeks on end, especially if I feel sick for some reason or if somebody in the house gets the dreaded sickness bug/norovirus. It's stupid, I know. I've lost a lot of weight very quickly due to my spells of not eating which can last four weeks at once, and going to doctors just prompts 'sign up for the local counselling service' which I have. It's taken a month just to have an appointment for consultation and then the waiting list will likely be very, very long, but I can't afford to go anything but the NHS.

I'm not really sure what to do or how to get help with this. When I am eating, I'll binge - I've always been a binge eater, but now I have restriction phases as well and honestly I'm just scared. I don't want to have An eating disorder. What more can I do? I'm in the UK, for reference, and my food aversions aren't helped because I'm on a special diet for my ridiculously bad and painful IBS, which is another reason I'm afraid of eating, especially new things.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Lost Appitite </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 03:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since I've developed an eating disorder along obsessive and compulsive exercise, even when I'm hungry I don't feel like eating. Even the smallest amounts of salad feel like too much. I don't understand it, but starving seems preferable. This is a new symptom. What's going on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to diet without getting pulled back in? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 03:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About two years ago I broke out of my eating disorder. I finally quit restricting, binging and purging but the result was for me to gain a lot of weight. I was largely able to keep from slipping back into the disorder before by not caring at all what I weighed or looked like and by not restricting anything I ate at all but now I've become obese and on top of looking awful and clothes not fitting it's just not healthy to be the weight I am. So I'm trying to lose it. The problem I'm running into is that when I actually care what the number on the scale says I fall back into restricting and purging. I can't figure out how to care enough about my weight that I stop gaining and lose it healthily but to not care so much that all that matters is losing weight. Is there a way to find a happy middle? Have any of you successfully dieted after an eating disorder? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: PhD Student looking for mothers with a history or in recovery from an eating disorder for research. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 03:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello I am a PhD student working on my dissertation. I am looking to interview mothers in recovery from eating disorders/disordered eating. Are you in recovery from and Eating Disorder (Anorexia, Bulimia, Binge Eating Disorder, EDNOS, etc)? Do you have a history of disordered eating? Are you a mother of a child who is at least 5 years old? Would you earn a $25 Amazon gift card by sharing your story about your journey of motherhood in relation to recovery?  Must be in recovery from an eating disorder for at least 1 year.  Must have at least one child 5-18 years old  Must be at least 18 years of age Participants will partake in an audio recorded interview for approximately 1hour. If you are interested in being interviewed about your experience please contact Heather Austin-Robillard. Heather.austin@ttu.edu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: This was my question? Sorry I don't know what to do </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 03:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please I don't know where else to go, but I need help controlling my eating. I can control it for sometime by eating healthy things and that isn't a problem for me, but then my parents will buy fast food and its almost impossible for me to turn it down. I soon as I eat it, I can't control my eating and will just eat a ton of food. I'm just looking for tips on how to control my eating and how to say no. I go to the gym and am trying to get fit ( I'm a normal weight. I don't need to gain or lose) but I fear my diet is just screwing me over.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to eat in recovery; starting out at "normal" weight. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 12:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good day or night to all madams and sirs. I am asking for some assistance in my most recent attempt at AN recovery, which started more or less yesterday.

I was a normal overweight man who ate without restriction (or thought) for the first 23 years of my life. Tackling my overweight after that, I was entrenched too deeply into the mindset of "the less I eat, the more efficiently I approach a normal weight", and got stuck quite badly in AN. The thing is, during all this time I exercised strength training with some intermittent cardio periods while still keeping a close eye on my protein intake, so my body was quite strong even though I starved myself in just about any other aspect.

When I sought therapy for my disordered thinking (compulsive calorie counting, food restrictions, extreme anxiety around unknown foods et.c.) I was not an extreme case in any way, but the ED started to impair my life quality. After a while I abandoned strength training, which meant I was "free" to not worry about macronutrients any longer, and picked up running, which I have realized I enjoy a lot more.

Everything was fine until I started working about a month ago (5 year CS student, never worked a full week before) and anxiety got the better of me, and I started, quite literally, to starve myself in response, living off nicotine gums and energy drinks throughout most of the week. I also realized staying drunk around the clock each weekend helped soothe my nerves.

Now I begun eating for real again yesterday, determined to kick my ED in the rear. As with other recovery attempts, it started with a sugar binge. Thankfully, as with my other binges, I have not restricted in response. The question I have is about how I should eat (general goals or recommendations) in my recovery, because the thing is - my weight is just about perfect. I have read that I still require a lot more calories than I would had I never restricted for bodily repairs. Is this correct? The hunger I feel is endless, and I am trying my best not to respond with eating sweets and treats since they are unlikely to give me the nutrients I need; those I eat only for psychological reasons and I still insist on eating balanced meals three times a day. The problem is that the bloat and trembling (possibly hypermetabolism) I feel are causing me a great deal of distress. I guess my question is whether or not I should accept that I will eat quite a lot in recovery or if I shouldn't and instead religiously eat my 3 balanced meals plus 0-3 snacks. I really want my body and mind to start trusting me again though, so I don't go more than 3 hours without eating, but that approach usually means I start grazing and run back and forth between the kitchen all the time...

I guess my question boils down to how a normal-weighted person who still has suffered from AN (to the level of multi-day fasts) should recover. All resources I find are (rightfully) aimed at more urgent cases where the sufferers are actually famished, which means there is not much guidance for me (therapists do not consider me underweight enough to warrant help beyond keeping a food diary and commenting on my lack of carbs...)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: tips on staying hydrated? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 12:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a hard time when it comes to getting enough liquids and it's a serious part of my disorder. I have a lot of trouble when it comes to consistent hydration. I would love if anyone has some tips on how to keep hydrated.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Personal and confidential information </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 12:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I apologize in advance for the length of the post and for any mistakes, I am not a native English speaker. This is the first time I am open about my problem, and I need to do this now, and in English, because it feels less 'real'.

I am 24, and I have always felt a little 'chubby', not fat, just a little bit plump. 4 years ago I decided to lose some weight. It quickly became addictive. I started with a healthy diet and regular exercise, and then, in an effort to "make it better, make it faster", I switched to a restrictive regime, where I would count calories and have panic attacks if the total daily intake exceeded a very small number. I also binged once a week, at night, and cried myself to sleep.

This had effects on every single aspect of my life. I started experiencing short memory losses. I was acting resentful and sour all the time. I started to stare at people's bodies and to mentally calculate their size, and then to compare it to mine. I remember one and a half year after I started, I looked myself in the mirror, passed my finger my ribs and thought "I looked like Christian Bale in the Machinist", and I was proud. I was proud of it.

I avoided many social events, either because they could be related to food, or because I was 'too fat' to be seen by people. Everybody suspected I had problems, but I always strongly denied, even if I recognized it myself from the beginning. It felt like I was "beating the dieting system", somehow.

Last year, I was selected for an internship experience abroad. Somehow, this triggered me a complete reversal. At first, I tried to stick with my habits, but in an effort to integrate with coworkers and to build a social net, I had to compromise. And I "remembered" how I loved to eat: long story short, I started to binge. To think constantly about food, to hope I'd end my working hours just to run to the first supermarket.

I gained most of my weight back, and didn't care about it in the process. But now... Now I am stuck into a spiral of self loathing and anxiety. I have all the drawbacks of an ED, but I am also fat now.

I hate myself for having failed. I hate myself for having thrown away all my effort. I hate myself because I used to be attractive.

And, I don't know what to do. I start my old routine, but then I am weak, and I binge. I hate it. I have daily suicidal thoughts but at the same time I don't want to die 'fat'. Really. I really have this thought.

I am sorry again for the long post. I needed to say it out loud, I needed to know I am not the only one. I need help.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Advice on gaining weight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 12:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What can I do to gain weight? I have tried and some of the time I undereat or overweight without realizing, mainly when I undereat. I cant seem to gain weight and I need help with getting my weight normal.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Getting to a healthier weight while recovering? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 03:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely cannot handle any kind of actual diet w/o being "triggered" I guess is the word? I am currently overweight, and would like to be a healthier weight. Some of the weight I gained while recovering was muscle, but other is not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Survey Request: Seeking adults with current or past eating disorders for online survey for doctoral research </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 11:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi everyone, here is a research study you might be interested in. Adults with current or past eating disorders (e.g., anorexia, bulimia, binge eating, compulsive overeating) are invited to participate in a University of Minnesota doctoral student research study on eating disorder recovery that involves completing a 10-15 minute online survey. Survey responses are anonymous. If you are interested in this study, please go to the survey link: www.surveymonkey.com/r/edrecovery. Alternatively, you can contact the doctoral student researcher, Nora Durkin, for more information at 612-625-1586 or umnedstudy@gmail.com. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Help with her </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 10:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My gf of about a year has been recovering from her Ed for about two years.recently something has triggered her Ed to get worse I was wondering if anyone has any advice on how to help her(we can't afford therapy)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Consent and Anorexia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 04:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am trying to understand consent in regards to mental issues in the United States.

My girlfriends anorexia has evolved to the point where she literally will no longer eat. She is going in and out of the hospital. She has suicidal thoughts.

I want to check her into a mental hospital, but she goes to the hospital and obviously improves. When she is conscious she immediately demands to leave the hospital, and due to consent laws the hospital can't keep her.

Is there anyway to override this consent. I have my girlfriend's dad and family on my side. Is there anyway to declare her unfit to make decisions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: experience at Timberline Knolls or Castlewood </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 04:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking into residential. Anyone with experience at Timberline Knolls or Castlewood?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I want to help, but not make her like like I'm helping </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 04:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She used to be picked on and bullied a lot growing up, now she has depression, anxiety, and an eating disorder. I think she's beautiful and wonderful but lately her insecurities are affecting our relationship and she's believes that I won't be able to handle all the negativity that gets thrown my way

I admit that it does become draining at times but I care so deeply about her that I want to be there for her and help her grow without being her crutch for happiness. I was thinking about taking her to the gym with me and helping her get into a healthy lifestyle that will help put her into a better mindset. I am not sure if that would help her or not because it may trigger her even more if she does get into this lifestyle if she feels like she's not working hard enough or if she has an off day or if she eats to much after a work out.

Tl;Dr How can I help her without her feeling that I'm trying to fix her? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How can I help my older sister with her anorexia? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 18:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My older sister is about to enter med school and she has been anorexic for about two years now, based on my observations. Everyone in our family is aware of her body/food issues but nobody knows how to help her. I really want to know how I can help her out. Some big advice I read suggested I ignore her issues and making certain topics "off-limits", and I was wondering whether that would be the appropriate course of action?

She has been seeing a therapist for a few years as well, but I believe her main topics there were about our parents' divorce. The therapist was not specialized for eating disorders.

Also, she has developed ostopenia.

How can I help her?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Others' expirience with therapy (BED) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 03:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the last several months I've found myself binging almost daily, and it's been more or less 5 months that I found information about a center in my town for the recovery of people affected by eating disorders - BED included - and collected their contacts, but I haven't been able to find the courage to call it and finally manage to see a therapist about the issue. I'm particularly afraid of failure: if I can't improve with the help of a professional, what else can I do? I also fear the fact that I may not fit the requirements to be allowed in the program. I'm also very emotional and I've found difficult communicating with my former therapist (that I saw in relation to other mental issues) without crying to the point of not being able to speak - the possibility of showing myself in that state to a stranger makes me very reluctant. Basically, I'm trying to get an idea of the possible approaches to the matter and therefore I'm looking others' knowledge about what to expect from therapy and maybe others' experience with it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: struggling right now, looking for some support </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 03:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi,

I am having some trouble at the moment. I have been struggling with anorexia for a number of years. I am in my twenties now and this year I actually feel like I want to live. I want to recover and be better. however after so much restricting food makes me sick. I am never hungry. I have researched and discovered this can happen to some people. my stomach seems to have shrunk and will not let me eat. it is painful and a disgusting experience to eat a whole plate of food. I have read that its important to push through this so that my stomach stretches but i have no support and my mind is telling me not to. just wondering if anyone has been through this as well to offer some hope or if they know anything about it because my mind (anorexia) is telling me its because i am too fat and need to start restricting again, and i know these are very dangerous thoughts didn't really know where else to come but here . thank you.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Weird thing has been happening lately, and I'm worried it's bringing back some old behaviors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 03:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, background, I'm 21F and have always been on the high end of a healthy weight. I struggled with disordered eating (intermittent restricting and purging, both by vomiting and exercising, but never regularly and I never really lost much weight from it) when I was younger (13-17ish) but have been more or less free of these behaviors for several years. I purged once last fall and immediately reached out to my old boyfriend, the only person who knew about my previous struggles, and talked through why I did it, and I haven't had a desire to purge since. I never had any sort of formal treatment, and I never told my parents or anyone except for the ex-boyfriend.

Now onto my current issue: recently, I've been getting nauseated every time I eat. It doesn't matter what I eat, it could be a salad or onion rings or half a pint of ice cream but I start feeling really sick, and I keep thinking maybe I'll feel better if I make myself throw up. So far I haven't but I'm scared it's becoming a conditioned response to eating (it also makes me not want to eat, and I don't like skipping meals as routine is very important to me.) Has anyone dealt with anything like this/have any tips?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Past body image issues are much better now, but I can't seem to keep a healthy weight and can't afford more food. What can I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 00:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have struggled with body acceptance since I was a child, my mother always placed high value on my being thin and would frequently make comments about my weight getting to the "point of no return". About 2 years ago I started to go through phases of being unable to eat anything at all because I felt I didn't deserve food and lost so much weight I hardly recognised myself. I am now past the idea that I don't deserve food and I'm eating a fairly balanced diet. I eat many food groups, however I restrict the type of meat I eat for ethical reasons and then that restricts how much meat I can buy for financial reasons. I try to eat three meals a day but I am still losing weight. None of my clothes fit and I look unhealthily thin.

I have seen my family doctor who assures me that nothing is wrong with me and I just need to eat more, "eat more!" that's the only advice I ever get... but the thing is; I can't afford to eat more. I am eating as much as I possibly can for my budget, I think my body is incorrectly digesting food and I can't get my doctor to take me seriously. 

I'm kinda scared because I feel weak and tired and I shake all the time and I honestly can't seem to gain any weight. I don't know what to do next because I feel like I'm doing everything I can and this is now out of my hands. I'm worried about organ failure if I lose much more weight but where I can't get my doctor to take me seriously I'm unsure how to solve my problem. Any advice?

**How can I remain positive and eat for weight restoration when I have financial limitations and past issues with body image?**

**How can I approach this topic with my doctor to make sure nothing else is causing my weight loss?**

(Mod note: please no mentions of specific foods or calorie/nutrient numbers) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How can I better support her? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 12:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend has been brave and courageous enough to open to me almost entirely about her eating disorder. She views becoming skinny as a challenge to become the skinniest, as it's the only she feels like she can do. She doesn't feel like she's important to anyone (and I try endlessly to show her how important and incredible and talented I believe she is), and in order to stand out, she needs to be skinny. She recently has started purging again (she hid it from me because she didn't like me getting emotionally involved). She doesn't believe she has an eating disorder, and believes it's just a dietary choice. I've tried encouraging her to create things for herself, like painting or drawing, or to go out in public by herself and just hangout. She's constantly thinking about how she thinks she's fat and how she knows she is, because she can see it. I can see her just fine, and she's very skinny. She has a goal to lose a certain amount of weight, and I told her I would support her getting there by working out, but she declined that. There's much more that I'm leaving out for time-sake, I just feel like I'm starting to run out of ways to support her to recovery. It pains me to see how much this consumes her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Advice for talking to an adult family member about anorexia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 04:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A family member (36 f) has been showing signs of an ever-worsening ED. At a recent family gathering, she ate hardly anything for lunch or dinner. She was always a very light eater, but it seems to be getting more extreme each time we see her. The only calories she really seems to take in are in the form of beer, so she's incredibly skinny but not yet completely wasting away. Because of this, it's easier for her closest family members (e.g. her parents, husband, sister) to deny that she has a problem. That said, I've been through similar things myself and see the warning signs all over her behavior. The salads she always ate in place of the meal that everyone else was having no longer contain chicken or oil   vinegar dressing - which was a light but somewhat nutritious meal. Now it's just a bowl of iceberg lettuce with some hot sauce, or something along those lines.

Her teeth are decaying, and in addition to the ED, she's a heavy smoker. She also had a stroke in her mid-20s due to a bacterial infection, and even though that was from a secondary cause, it still makes me very nervous for her overall health.

What would be the best way to approach a person in this situation about her behavior? She doesn't seem particularly depressed, anxious, etc. , although I wouldn't be surprised if there are things bubbling under the surface. Like I said, she's very thin but not to the point where she looks completely sickly because she has some extra calories coming in from drinking. I feel like my best bet would be to get one of her closest family members to intervene, but how can I best convince them that there's a problem? And what advice would you have for those people in regards to talking to her? (I have a feeling that if i suggest that they talk to her, they'll just say that she won't listen, which is probably true.)

Thanks so much in advance for any advice that you might be able to offer.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Recommendations for a book recommendation for my girlfriend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 04:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Do you know of any literature, book, story compilation, that serves as motivation for people fighting bulimia"? My girlfriend is fighting bulimia and started recently. She reads a lot but unfortunately , only reads about how to lose weight. I'd like to give her something to be entertained, that gives her hope that helps her with this.

I'd be very thankful for any support.

Best regards, Joo  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Unsure how to go about asking for help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 04:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a bit of info leading into my questions:

I'm in kind of a weird place with my eating disorder right now. I've been through a couple of treatment programs, the last one was about two years ago. I left it in a really good place, I was weight restored(-ish) and I had a huge desire to remain in recovery, but ever so slowly I began to relapse into restrictive eating, my team and I were able to intervene relatively quickly and I was able to pull out of that relapse out patient, without needing a higher level of care.

That was about a year and a half ago. Then, I relapsed again this past December and it was a little worse, I didn't really pull myself out of it until late January. Up until about a month ago, I was doing relatively well, then I relapsed again. I'm still in the midst of this relapse and it feels worse this time. I mean, I still know all of the coping skills that I've learned over the last few years, I still remember relearning how to eat "normally", I still recall what motivation I had at the time. None of that seems to matter, though. I feel stuck in this, it feels too overwhelming to deal with. I'm scared that I might need to go back into treatment and that I might not be able to do so.

I guess I'm wondering, can anyone relate to this? How did you overcome that relapse? How did you regain your motivation?

If you feel more comfortable, please pm me at /u/jljohnson92
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Please can someone just listen to me? The cycle is starting again and I can't tell anyone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 04:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Background information: Developed anorexia at 16, threw myself into recovery at 19 so I could do my degree. Been in 2 relationships since where food was largely cooked and decided for me as my partners were quite foody people.

More recently: Split up with ex of 2.5 years, moved to a new city and found myself very much on my own and having to take responsibility for food. I also started a job where I'm on my feet for most of the day. This coupled with living on cereal and anything that takes less than five minutes to microwave, I basically lost a bunch of weight unintentionally.

Very recently, I finally accepted that I needed to buy some clothes that fit because everything was starting to look a bit ridiculously baggy. Since then, I've been super fucking hyper paranoid about gaining the weight back. This has started me back on calorie counting, over exercising and then snapping into a binge. This triggers anxiety, which has lead to cutting as a "punishment".

My job is stressful, I drink a lot and I don't care if it's during the week or at the weekend. Most weekends I try and find places to go dancing and get trashed because it's exercise and it makes me forget about how fucked up my head is at the moment. I've joined two running groups during the week and will often go running alone as well. Originally I wanted to try and balance "normal" eating with moderate exercise, but I feel like I'm seriously losing control. I'm exhausted all of the time, I know I need to eat more but I'm scared about getting "fat". People keep telling me I look healthy and they're proud of how active and sociable I'm being, but it's all a really big lie.

I've been projecting all of this positivity about doing new activities and eating healthily, but more often than not now, I find myself binging and then self harming to stop the racing thoughts. This happened this evening, which is why I've found myself here.

I don't know what to do. Access to mental health services as a 24 year old in the UK is almost impossible unless you're at death's door. I'm tired of being tired, I'm tired of my fucked up relationship with food. I don't have a degree to aim for any more, just working and working and working until I run myself into the ground.

I desperately want to care about cooking for myself and I want to stop freaking out about what I'm putting into my body or feeling too full.

This is such a messy confession but I really just need some support. I think if anyone close to me knew I was falling back into this hole, they would be heartbroken. Also, it's the most difficult thing to land on someone unless they say something first. I don't want to get to that point.

Sorry for the long post. I'm tired and I feel extremely sick and depressed. 

I have a huge amount of gratitude in advance from any thoughts or advice anyone can give.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: is this behavior an eating disorder? If so, what would it be called? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 02:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have depression and anxiety. I also have a moderate to severe vomiting phobia.

I have been overweight to obese to class 2 obese, I have used a very restrictive diet plan to get back down to overweight, and have put most of the weight back on and am obese again.

When my stomach is empty, I feel nauseous. The vomiting phobia comes into play here, so I eat to calm that feeling. I also eat when I "deserve" rewards - happy day, sad day, but most often stressful day.

Until now I have believed the food behaviors are a symptom of the other issues. But recently I've realized that I don't just eat, I eat defiantly. I pick the least healthy things intentionally. I eat too much, almost daring my body to rebel by vomiting - thinking that maybe if I finally cross that line the phobia will teach me a lesson.

If I think of a food that sounds good, I cannot relax until I have eaten that food. It begins to feel obsessive.

I am in therapy, but for several reasons it does not seem to be helping. I have a consult with a psychiatrist next month.

is this behavior an eating disorder? If so, what would it be called?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I'm afraid if I'm not being super restrictive I'm going to gain weight. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 02:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For over a year now I've been dealing with overly-restrictive eating habits that eventually led to binge eating, and in the last few months I've taken steps to work on it. I stopped counting calories, which has helped a lot, and I'm trying to break myself of the habits I developed such as being obsessed with low carbs and weighing myself often.

I just started an internship a week and a half ago, and right before I came here I had been going out to eat a ton with friends so I gained a few pounds. I had been trying to lose weight, got very close to my goal weight, but last time I weight myself, I had gained about half of that back. I hated seeing that number, but could accept that it was temporary and I would go back to my normal eating habits soon.

So I started my internship, and here I'm extremely active, hiking between 5 to 10 miles a day in the desert. I'm trying to trust that I'm hungry because I'm so active, but the amount I'm eating scares me because I'm so afraid I am going to get fat. I don't have any full length mirrors, so I can't analyze my body and convince myself that I'm skinny, and I don't have a scale so I can't see my weight and reassure myself that I'm not actually gaining weight.

I think the main thing is, though, that I don't want to need to see a number on a scale to trust that I'm fit and attractive. If I were to step on a scale right now and it showed what I weighed the last time, it would ruin my week.

I'm just so aware of everything I'm eating, how many carbs I'm eating (because I'm sweating a lot and doing physical labor), and I feel like my body feels so huge right now and I don't know what to do. I feel like I can't trust myself to just eat in a way that comes naturally, because I'm going to end up getting bigger.

Are there any ways to gain trust in your body and eating habits? Ways to lessen the importance of seeing a certain number on the scale and stop using my weight to validate my self-worth? How do I stop being afraid to eat?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Experience with "Unrestricted Eating" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 11:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello readers. I have a few questions running through my head, and am primarily (not only) looking for people with similar experiences.

I am a quasi-recovering male anorectic (healthy weight) in his mid-twenties. This last weekend was the third in a row I used alcohol constantly Friday evening up until Monday morning in order to avoid eating. I had also had two days last week, Wednesday and Thursday, where I got through work (CS engineer) on energy drinks, diet soda and nicotine. Needless to say, the pressure from being new at work got the better of my recovery and I relapsed harder than I ever had.

My wife (10 year relationship) found me passed out on the toilet (I snuck in there to drink out of sight) and needless to say, she was devastated. That evening I ate heartily (she almost force-fed me) and fell asleep immediately after. I slept for fourteen to fifteen hours, then got up for work, bringing with me a large breakfast. After all, I needed to get through work severely hungover.

I have been aware of the concept "unrestricted eating" (I know some webpage touts "guidelines" for it but it was only this concept I found any grain of truth in) for quite a while, but was always very afraid of the binge-eating risks, but having almost botched my first good job, turned into a semi-drunkard, and nearly smashed my relationship in one go I felt desperate. I set out on what would become a three, maybe four day binge journey like one you have never seen. I have been overeating like crazy, somewhere along the lines of a weeks worth of food over the past three days. It feels as if I ate like a marathon-runner post-contest.

My rationale isn't (wasn't?) different from what I had gleaned from the internet. Restriction is nigh impossible for me, and the supposed meal plans or whatnot my dietitian and psychiatrist set up for me only left me hungry and, well , feeling even more restricted. I followed these meal plans for a long time, damn it! They were fishily skeptical about eating any junk food at all as well... The last 1.5-2 years have really messed up my views on food, so in my ire I wanted to hammer into my brain how stupidly simple it is. "It's food, c'mon"! Somehow prove to myself that I am allowed anything I want, at any time, and to illustrate to myself why non-ED people actually keep these things in moderation. I also wanted to hijack my ANs stealthy way of working against my weight-gain efforts.

Needless to say I am now feeling the unavoidable anguish and anxiety that follows such an out-of-control experience. I was prepared for it, and hell yes I am ignoring it -- i.e. I am not restricting as a consequence. Been there, done that cycle.

But I am at a bit of a loss here, and I was wondering if you out there have any experiences to share on this? Can it work? Should I only keep it to a few days, to let my body restore the damage (n.b. not underweight at all)? Should I eat anything I want at any time or should I rather keep a "solid, healthy baseline" and only go by pure intuition past that point?

I know I am taking a huge risk, but as I said I am kind of desperate. Keep in mind that in my country at least, any help you get if you are not underweight is amateurish at best, so I am kind of left to my own devices. This "test" or whatnot is not something I recommend either, the psychological effects are... Tough, but of the kind I can manage. I just seem to have some form of issue with restriction in itself.

TL;DR: Restricted for a long time. Still normal weight. Relapsed and almost turned alcoholic, wife found out. Got desperate and tried unrestricted eating for three-four days. Wondering about other people's experience with this.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How can i get treated and why is it so hard to get treatment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 10:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Twice I have tried to get into IOP programs and both times they have insisted i enter their residential programs. I tell them I can't. I have insurance, but I can't take weeks/months off for a residential care. I have two dependents and a couple months inpatient will leave all three of us homeless. Today I was told they wouldn't treat me at a lower level than they feel I need, despite the fact that this means I get no treatment at all.

So how can I find either PHP in evenings in Chicago area or an IOP program willing to help me when everyone is insisting I do residential? If residential is the only treatment they are willing to do, then i can't get treatment? This seems horribly wrong to me. How can they refuse to give me any treatment when i'm finally at a point where i'm admitting i need help? I simply can't go live in a treatment facility for months. Please, please offer me some suggestions!!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Personal and confidential information - how to avoid changing from one ED to another </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 15:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am 24[m] in recovery from AN.I have been in the recovery for 1.5-2 yrs. Originally I was obese then started losing weight due to a change in lifestyle post college, and i continued that trend into a very dark and unhealthy place. I just recently made the decision to stop weighing myself and counting calories/nutrition. It was becoming just as obsessive in my mind as not eating was during my darkest days. I am safely within a healthy weight range again, but i have recently started binge eating to a ridiculous degree. I would like some advice so I wont move from one eating disorder to another, aka anorexia to binge eating. I have difficulties recognizing when I am actually hungry even after a year of eating properly. I am scared of both eating too much and not enough, and i am finally in a healthy enough place mentally to deal with my issues. Maybe some of y'all could help me out with some advice?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: (19/M) Are any of you men suffering from an ED? Has gender affected your experience? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 04:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At times, I feel ostracized and invalid as the only male identified person in local support groups. 

I suppose I'm turning to the Reddit community for additional advice, support, etc. Does anyone have any advice for me?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How do I help out my well-meaning, albeit uninformed grandmother? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 04:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all  My eating disorder could best be described as exercise bulimia, with occasional restriction. I no longer vomit and I've never done laxatives or diuretics, but my health has suffered due to the compulsive exercise -- mostly in the form of disrupted menstrual cycles/amenorrhea. I am not underweight, but I guess on the lower end of normal. On the outside, I look like a fitness fanatic, which blends in seeming normalcy with my (at times self-effacing) perfectionism.

My grandmother has been the most stable, supportive figure in my life. She took me in on various occasions while I was growing up when my home environment was just too toxic, and we share a close bond to this day. While I still relied on financial aid and loans, she and my grandfather nearly put me through college and were the home I went to during breaks from school. Needless to say, my gratitude for them and their positive influence in my life is ineffable.

However, after two years of struggling with an ED, I had to come clean, and was met with disbelief. My grandmother's reaction was not one of shock or sadness, but... disappointment that still stings. "I don't see how you can have an eating disorder, you just seem like you have it all together." I always felt like being the perfect child was the only way I could pay them back for taking care of me when I had no one else. I graduated a year early with high honors, and didn't want to project to them an image that deviates from that. I always wondered if they would still love me when the confident, ambitious honors student was revealed to be a facade to hide the lowkey depressed, somewhat nihilistic pothead who struggles with an eating disorder and abandonment issues.

But even after the cat came out of the bag, lo and behold, despite all that the ED inner voice told me, she still loves me. But her confusion indicated that she doesn't seem to understand how eating disorders work. Example: "I think you should drink less coffee. All that caffeine is probably why your appetite is so poor." While, yeah, coffee is certainly one of my vices and I'll admit to having used it to blunt my appetite... the issue is so much deeper than that. If I cut out caffeine, I'd still be bulimic.

I guess the question is if anyone would happen to know any resources -- preferably books over website as she isn't too internet-savvy -- that would maybe enlighten her knowledge of eating disorders, and maybe arm her with the knowledge of how to be a support? I know she wants to help, but I'm afraid she just doesn't know how. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Adult mushing food </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 04:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My question for this subreddit is that I saw someone at my in law's parents mushing her food into a paste before proceeding to eat it (chocolate cake). Is this part of an eating disorder? I've never seen an adult act like this at the dinner table and I'm curious to learn more but can't seem to find anything about this behavior. I commented on it at the time and was told to just ignore it, so you don't need to post that kind of answer, thanks!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Do I have a binge eating disorder? History of problems </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 03:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realize ya'll can't diagnose me, but I'd like to know whether there is a possibility.

So, I'll start off in sixth grade. In sixth grade was my hospital trip because of dehydration. Before the hospital trip I NEVER drank water (because I hated the flavor). I didn't eat very much. My meals were probably the equivalent of a regular person's snacks. I knew I would get in trouble if I didn't eat at home, so I did. Some nights though, I purposefully said I was full as an excuse to get out of eating. I was obsessed about my body image and weight. I weighed myself everyday, and thought I was fat. I really wasn't though. (I was about 4'10. I realize I can't say weight, but I looked online and for my height, it said I was underweight). I sometimes went on my dad's treadmill, for a long time on a fast speed to try to lose weight. My dad told me to stop, and I did, though doing so felt like torture. In December that year, I had a Kidney Infection due to severe dehydration. I also had severe constipation. In the hospital though, they didn't ask about my diet or whether I was eating enough. Most of the nurses I spoke to told me be quiet because others had it worse. Yes, I know others have it worse, but that doesn't mean I shouldn't get help. They forced me to eat food before I could go home. It was extremely hard, partially because they put IV tubes in my arm that gave me water in my blood 24/7, partially because, well, I thought I was fat. I relented though and finally ate. The next day I got my first period. Right after I got out of the hospital it must have started, because I only got two hours of sleep because I was discharged at like two in the morning. I've always thought that the reason it started right after was because I was given so much water and I was forced to eat and I finally wasn't dehydrated. I'm guessing my period started late though, due to malnutrition, as that apparently happens to some people with eating disorders.

The next year after that, my parents made sure I drank enough water. My diet in terms of food was about the same, I mean, I ate a little bit more each meal, and my constipation was not as bad. Since my period started, I gained a lot of weight.

Now zoom to now. Now I'm the complete opposite. I've had a few times this month where I've eaten so much food at a time and I feel like I can't stop. I don't vomit after I eat, though. I feel so guilty afterwards that I try to diet, but I can't no matter how hard I try, possibly because I was in the hospital for not eating enough. My eating issues scare me. Could I have had a different eating disorder in sixth grade than in eighth grade?

I used to go see a counselor, and when I spoke to them about my concerns involving food and weight, they said that so long as I had an apple each meal (as an example) than that I'm fine. But I don't think living off an apple or just one food per meal is healthy.

Thank you for any and all help!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Binge drinking water </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 03:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently it has come to my attention that my water drinking is becoming a problem, and I know that sounds absolutely absurd but I've repeatedly gotten reprimanded at work for how frequently I have to urinate, I haven't slept longer than a couple hours at a time in months because I get up to pee or drink more water, and my family is always complaining about me drinking all the water in the house. I even recently got blood work done and my doctor was concerned because my sodium level was low due to my water consumption. 

How do I take control of this? I feel really alone in this matter and when I discussed this with my doctor all she said was essentially as expected....drink less water.  But it's soooo difficult to deny yourself something as innately necessary and seemingly harmless as water, but I presume one could say the same for food. 

I even have trouble eating enough calories because I HAVE to drink a shit ton of water with all my meals, unless it's soup/fruit.

The only way I can describe why I do it is for one,  it cleanses your palette, a lot of the time I feel like I need to wash my food down, it helps me swallow, my mouth is frequently dry, I get tired if I'm dehydrated, and....it's....comforting? I feel like I sound insane but it's almost as if I cannot go to sleep without a belly full of water.  

I need help because when left to my own devices I drink so much I have difficulty walking. If anyone has any experience with this please direct me how to go about seeking help for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Academic Study: Seeking participants for a study on self-injurious thoughts and behaviors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 03:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are a Harvard University research team currently working on a study looking at people who harm themselves. The primary goal of the study is to better assess self-injurious thoughts and behaviors.

If you are interested in participating, you will complete an online screener to see if you qualify to participate. If you qualify, you will complete a variety of questionnaires online and then you will be contacted 2 weeks later to answer some more questions.

For completing the first part, you will be paid $15 in Amazon gift cards. For completing the second part, you will be paid another $15 in Amazon gift cards. Unfortunately, if you have already completed an earlier version of this study (Harvard SIB Study), you are not eligible to participate in this updated version.

A few important things to know about the study are: 1. The study includes questions regarding self-harm. Some people may feel that talking about these topics is difficult and may find it to be triggering. 2. All information collected will be kept confidential and private. 3. Participation is completely voluntary. 4. The link we provide will send you to a website asking you a few questions to see if you qualify to participate. 5. If you start to participate and decide you no longer feel comfortable or you are no longer interested, you can end it without any penalty or punishment. 6. We will provide links to treatment resources throughout the study. 7. This study will include only participants from the U.S. who are 18 years and older.

Please PM me at /u/ResearchAtHarvard if you are interested in participating. Once you contact us, we will send you a link to the screening questionnaire to see if you qualify and to tell you more about the study.

Thank you for your consideration! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: What are the long term health effects of binge eatingbesides weight gain? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 03:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been binge eating for nearly six years, but I'm at a healthy weight. Between binges, I eat healthily, with a caloric deficit that's not huge, but enough to get me back to my previous weight before I binge again. If you looked at all the food I eat in a week, it would look okay. Except that I concentrate all the junk food and a gigantic chunk of the calories into a two-hour window.

Since I always promptly lose the weight I gain, what are the other long term effects of binge eating? How does this affect my health? Or is my diet equally as healthy as it would be if I were to eat the same amount of food spread out into sane portions?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My eating problems </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 03:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello there. 21 male here. My situation has changed quite a lot of times throughout my life, so I'll try to summarise it all in here. I'm not sure if I'll do that, but I can try.

Basically, I think I have some kind of eating disorder. I'm not sure how to call it, and fortunately it has never affected my life much enough to cause any serious problems.

tl;dr (as a summary - written after the last paragraph appeared): I'm thinking of food all the time, and can't help it!

Let's start from the beginning (sorry for any chaos in the text): I always used to be a little bit chubby. This must have been the first reason of my problems. I was never very fat, but always had the biggest belly. In any moment of my life, the fat used to be located on stomach and butt areas and a little bit on thighs, and when I was wearing t-shirt and pants, you would say that I look like a normal, healthy child (as now I'm 21 and so to say well-build and some people even 'expect' me to have a six-pack because of my muscles, and I have never had one).

The family of my mom always had a healthy attitude towards food, i.e. some of them were overweight, but never really cared about it too much, never ate too much, they were able to leave some food not touched. My mom's mother cooks just enough portions to make you full, but you wouldn't overeat from what you had on your plate.

That was, however, never the case with my father's family. They all love to eat. And it's very typical for them to eat huge amounts of food, especially the comfort food - fat and stodgy. When they finish, they want more, and if there's something sweet to eat - they are always eager. What's funny, most of them look great. They do have some fat - just like me, usually on their bellys - but they also do not care. They all move a lot. The problem however is this stupid attitude - that whenever you end your meal you have to feel STUFFED.

Now back to me. I used to spend every weekend at either of my grandparents. The manner was alternating - once at father's family, once at mother's. My family is very kind and loving, which has one serious drawback - they could never say 'no' to my cravings. I could stuff myself with anything that was available, and if there were no sweets they were ready to buy something for me while shopping.

I think, that the influence of the father's family had a great impact on me. I always heard 'eat as much as you want'. I taught myself to say that 'I'm hungry' when I had only a small craving for something.

Because of the fact I felt unattractive I went to the gym at the age of 16. Had no diet, only tried to eat better (couldn't develop good habits in a house, where the was always something unhealthy), but still changed a little bit. When I went to the new school I was still overweight tough. In the second class (I was 17 or 18) I went on a diet. I did it by myself and despite of constantly stopping it, and then re-starting I lost several kilos, felt much better, and from then I have to say - I am considered as well-build person - with muscles, only some fat, and generally in good shape. Everything's perfect, isn't it? Unfortunately, not.

The problems I had with maintaining the diet were the episodes of overeating. For instance, while going to the family (no matter what part) I had problems with controlling myself. When I ate one piece of a cake, I couldn't be stopped. I was able to eat about 10 pieces of different cakes - and even more, but then I had an upset stomach, which 'helped' me to restrain myself.

Throughout the next years I lost weight, and gained it. Never became fat anymore, but still not satisfied with my appearance. Started to 'bulk' (gain muscles) than again wanted to 'cut'. I could never decide. I enjoyed eating clean and counting calories, but eventually I was always eating some individual pieces of sweets/sliced meats, and finally I even started to eat things that are not tasty while eaten from the fridge - for example cold (but of course cooked!) potatoes, some leftovers, etc. I am then telling myself, that it's a healthy food, and I need to eat to maintain muscles etc (excuses?)

I had a period of time when I was 'cutting' and heard of cheatdays. It was the worst thing that happened to me. I had an excuse to do the 'cheatday' once a week. I used to eat sooo much then, that I'm still confused, how was (and probably still am) I able to do it. Once, after eating the comfort food dinner, I went with my gf (don't have any problems with attraction etc anymore, so it's not the case), and she bought me a pack of cookies 'just for me'. I ate them all. She did it purposively, as she knew I was restraining myself, and wanted to please me while my cheatday (she knew about this invention). Ok, no problem. BUT. I came home and guess what - ate more. I ate the whole pack of crisps as I was not hungry AT ALL. In the halfway I felt bad (stomach), but still ate. I felt like I was gonna throw up (fortunately I never did after overeating).

Ok, next problem: again my family. My mom doesn't eat much, so there's no problem. But my father still has those habits from his family home, and he eats everything, what he would like to stuff himself with. When there's a chocolate bar, it disappears in one hour. My brother (15 yo) helps him, mom eats a bit (like a normal person), and I used to eat it too. Right now, I can restrain myself from eating sweets most of the time, but I realised, that I have some sick thoughts like 'I need to eat it, as later there will be none left for me'. I believe it occurred because of those habits from my father's family.

As I said, I don't eat much sweets now. I don't eat much pasta, nor bread. Occasionally I eat some sweets or fast-foods. I think it's not too much. BUT. The problem is my mental attitude. Well, three things here: a) when I eat something unhealthy, I feel like there's no sense in restraining myself anymore (the day is already ruined, so why should I bother) and then I eat more and more. I go around the house, looking for unhealthy, and tasty things, even though I now it's overeating now, and I should control myself, but can't. I don't eat too much, as I don't buy it myself (and what my family buys, immediately disappears)

b) I DO NOT feel guilty. I look good, and eating too much doesn't change much. But still I know I shouldn't eat when I'm not hungry. And still I do eat. Don't know what to do about it!

c) last, but not least - I think of food ALL THE F** TIME. I have exams now. Should focus on studying. Yet, I can focus on it only occasionally. When I'm not sleeping, I'm thinking of eating. That's stupid and makes me feel bad about myself. I think we've finally reached the most important part. I do not enjoy life anymore, as everything I can think of is food. I go to the party - where's the food? Go to the uni - what could I buy myself? I'm dating someone - I want to go home and EAT. EVEN IF I'M NOT HUNGRY. This state started about one-two years ago. Cannot remember when and how. Since last two years just cannot enjoy life. And I do not enjoy eating anymore either.

I also think, that I'm kind of trying to stuff my life with eating. However I DO HAVE hobbies, I DO HAVE passions, and still cannot focus on them. When I'm reading, I want to eat. When studying - even interesting things - I want to eat. Crazy. I do sometimes have those moments of relief. Then, I feel like I don't have to eat. I don't care. I'm engaged in some social situation, or doing something that's my hobby. Also in the gym, and right after it (the only moment when I know that I should eat) - I just don't care. When I hear of people who can forget about the meal and therefore skip it I just can't believe it. How is that even possible?

Sorry for so long post, I've tried to finally settle it all. Hope that you will understand me, and help. Should I see a psychologist? Maybe someone had got rid of that kind of problem? Please, help!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Help shifting meals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 03:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my 20s I was bulimic. I got help, and now it only creeps back once in a while. (I'm 50 now.)

For about 5 years in the early 2010s I was very poor. I could only afford to eat once a day, was eating very little and not nutritious foods.

Today I'm financially in a better place and am eating much better. My problem is that I'm still stuck in a rut with eating once a day. This means I'm eating a boatload of calories at one time. That much food at once makes me want to start purging again.

I sometimes see a registered dietician. I've asked her for help but she keeps harping on -what- I eat, not when and how.

Please help. I have no idea how to stop this habit and go back to eating like a normal person.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Post requesting information regarding binge drinking water </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 11:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Advice Needed - Bulimic Girfriend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 10:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Have I crossed the tipping point from disordered eating into an eating disorder? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 10:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a 22M who's on the border between healthy and overweight. I got up decently far into overweight during college, but have recently been trying to get back down. However, I've been struggling with my diet. I've been so hungry all the time during my diet that I've fallen into a pattern of overeating occasionally, feeling sick, and throwing up. I don't particularly like throwing up, but I feel sick when I overeat and it feels like something my body is supposed to be doing. It doesn't hurt that I usually end up with a lot of free calories for that day while still feeling full, but that's where I'm getting concerned. None of this seems extremely out of the ordinary to me, but my partner has expressed some concern over the number of times I'm nauseous or outright sick in the evenings, and I'm starting to worry. Is this developing into an eating disorder, and does anybody have some constructive mental strategies I can use to head this off at the pass? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Do you have any lasting side effects from your ED? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 16:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suffered from anorexia for about 4 years. I'm recovered now but I have some lasting side effects from it. This includes hypothyroidism (slow metabolism)- messed up my metabolism from restricting so I have to take medicine for the rest of my life.

Also I feel like my IQ has dropped, I have a Masters and Bachelors in Law and used to be really bright and articulate. Now I have a bit of a social stutter and don't feel as sharp; things take a bit longer to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I am underweight for my height and hate the feeling of being full. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 16:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have nothing against food, and I love eating, but I hate the feeling of being full. I also can't eat unless I'm hungry. If I try to eat breakfast, sometimes I'll throw it back up and the other times I feel gross all day. Very rarely will I finish a full plate of food. I eat until I'm no longer hungry and then stop. The problem is that sometimes I won't get hungry for a day or two and won't notice, then I'll eat. i'm "not hungry" which is still not a whole lot so I'm down a full day's worth of calories. Do you guys recognize this or know any tips for combating it? This is the first time I've reached out about it anywhere. I'm a young-adult male if that makes a difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I think i'm developing an eating disorder rapidly (21/m/UK) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 02:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was made unemployed in November.

I binge eat every night before sleeping, eating a lot of calories in a very very short amount of time, I eat when i'm not hungry and I feel awful after I do, I tell myself I'm not going to do it but I do anyway.

I will literally open pots of cream and custard and just chug them, etc ... whatever shit my mum buys.

I need to stop, my weight is ballooning.

I'm thinking about going to a doctor but I fear they will tell me that its just willpower in stopping, its seriously an uncontrollable urge, I tell myself i'm just going to get a drink and suddenly i'm eating.

How do I stop? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How did you first realise you had disordered thoughts/an ED? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 02:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I have disordered thoughts about eating. I realised it when I remembered that I never used to think about food this much or feel guilty about eating.

I think I've had them for the past few months, but they come and go. For example, if I am busy/hang around with friends a lot, then I can distract myself from having thoughts about what or how much I eat. But by socialising, I end up comparing my body to other people's.

And when I'm alone, all the guilt and body-hate comes out and I just want to starve myself, but because of lack of willpower, I never do completely. I think about food a lot - how many calories are in the foods I eat, what recipes I could do, but never do.

I try and be healthy - do a couple of workouts a week, walk everyday, try and cook healthy things that I won't feel guilty eating, but I'm lazy so it doesn't always happen. Therefore I end up feeling guilty about not working out enough/eating some junk food. But it's probably a blessing that I'm lazy and lack willpower, otherwise I'd be starving myself.

I don't know if thoughts like this are serious or if they warrant some kind of therapy or if I just need to change my attitude to food.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Recovering, but I've always been a picky eater. How can I branch out and get the variety my body needs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 01:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am three years into recovery and have been an extremely picky eater my entire life. Now I am doing great and have healthy eating habits, but know that actually eating a variety of foods is an important step to keeping my body healthy, especially as I get older. 

I am of course in no way wanting to restrict or change the quantity of my diet, just trying to be more kind to my body! 

Wondering if anyone has tips on how I can do this? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Having digestive issues after an eating disorder. How can I fix it so food doesn't make me sick? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 01:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last year I had a several month long episode of anorexia and bulimia at the time and I am concerned it has permanently damaged my stomach. A lot of times before I eat I get very nauseous and afterwards I remain nauseous. I can't handle too much strong food that is very fibrous, like certain vegetables and smoothies. I usually throw those up involuntarily. 

Is there any way I can correct this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My friend is acting strange and I am worried she has an eating disorder. I am in high school, how can I help her? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 01:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
For context, me and my friend (let's call her Allison) are both 15 and haven't been close friends for too long--maybe for a year, and aren't too comfortable discussing really personal things with each other, but I really care about her.

My friend has always been the quiet, more aloof and secretive type of person, who never really talks about herself to others. She really admires models, and is constantly on her phone looking at pictures of really, really underweight models and she likes art, and when she draws it's mostly underweight girls. When she's with me or our other friends, she always acts normal, but never really talks about herself; for the past year or so she's stopped eating lunch and instead goes on her phone while we eat. 

She always critisizes how she looks and about she's too fat (when she's easily underweight) when the topic is brought up but always says "I'm fine," even though we found her with scars from self-harm last year. We brought her to the school counselour, she denys everything and is extremely defensive about everything, and does anything she can to change the topic; visiting the counselor is something I've ruled out as something that can help, especially as she's a really stubborn person who thinks that nothing's wrong, and therefore resents us everytime it's brought up or we try and do something about it. 

She never actively brings up the topic, either, so I know it's not for attention. It's something we've already accepted we can't change ourselves, so it's been pretty normal for the past couple of months.

Today, me and a couple of friends went to hang out for the day and from the morning to the night (~8am-8pm) and she didn't eat a thing. We took some pictures together, and I let her look at them on my phone with the agreement that she doesn't delete anything, and she spends the entire time staring at her arm that she thought was fat in a few of the photos, even zooming in and screenshotting it so that her arm was the only thing in the picture. When I took the phone away from her because she was literally staring at a screenshot of her arm for a long time, she said accused me of breaking our agreement and said "just because I'm not as persuasive as (other friend) doesn't mean you can just push me around like this" when I'm notoriously known as being a doormat and would never have any intentions of pushing her around :(( I gave her back the phone with the agreement that she doesn't send any of the photos to herself, and she promptly distracted me to takes pictures of the photos with her own phone so she could go back home and stare at her supposedly fat arm. Everytime I told her she didn't look fat she responded with something like "Are you saying that what I think doesn't matter?"

This day was a bit of a wake up call, because honestly her condition has been at the back of my mind for a while since she always acted normal. But I'm worried again now (on long school days when we go to school at 6am and leave late, she's taken to bringing those small packets of condiments like soy sauce or mustard that you can get at a local store and just eating those for lunch), and I have no idea what I can do as a friend. 

I'm sorry for the long post, I just don't know what to do and it's really making me worried.

**How can I help my friend when I know she won't really open up to me about this?**

**What do I need to know as a teenager with a friend who may have an eating disorder?** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to recover "normal" eating habits after a long time of neglecting to eat enough? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 01:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't had the habit of eating regularly since middle school, and now that I'm kind of trying to get out of, well.. not eating for long periods of time, I have no clue at all where to start with things. It's been years since I would make breakfast in the morning, or make lunch for when I'm out, or make a coherent dinner. I just don't know what to make, or how to make it, or when to make it-- Does anyone have any tips or anything to pick up the habits and stuff?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I don't have a typical ED, but it's hard for me to keep a healthy weight and bring myself to eat. What can I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 01:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always been a small size my entire life because of my fast metabolism, but my therapist believes I developed an ED a few months ago. The ironic thing is, I love food. I could eat everything in the world and not gain any weight. 

Recently I've been under a tremendous amount of stress and I haven't been eating. I'm not purposely not eating to lose weight because I'm already very small, I was actually trying to gain weight but eating hasn't been my main priority in the day. They're concerned with my weight because I've lost a significant amount in the last two months. Now since I haven't been eating, I have lost my appetite completely and I get full easily. If I do eat, it's because I know I have to eat at least a little something for the day.

I've been trying to put a name to what I have, and my psychiatrist   therapist can't put a name to it either because they don't specialize in eating disorders. I'd just like to start helping myself get better.

What can I do to eat enough when I have no appetite?

How can I make sure to prioritize eating when I am stressed?

Are there professionals or treatment approaches that can help me with this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Book suggestion for an older sibling of an anorexia nervosa patient </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 05:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you guys! I would love some reading to do in order to better help my little sister, who is currently in treatment for a loss of control (not body image) related anorexia disorder.

Thanks so much in advance!

Kim </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I think I have an eating disorder and I want some advice on where to start with treatment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 23:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a 24 year old male, and I feel like i might have an eating disorder. I have never had any issues with body image or felt like I was overweight at any point in my life, my problem seems to completely physical. I almost never get hungry. Ive gone days with heavy restriction, and restrict on a daily basis. 
    
I have a lot of stress in my life, particularly over the past year when my problem seems to have gotten much worse. I have lost a scary amount of weight over the past year, which is causing comments and concern.

I am seeking advice on how to get help. I want to see a doctor but I'm not sure what kind would be most effective for my problem (nutritionist, psychologist, general practitioner?) I am unsure because my symptoms don't seem to fit the description of a "typical" eating disorder. 

Any advice will be greatly appreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Is recovery actually possible? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 03:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made a longer version of this on another site, but, since it says keep posts short, then I'll leave out some details.

I have anorexia, and it started in school when I stopped being called the 'skinny' girl (which I'd always been called beforehand.) It hadn't been a compliment, just an observation. But when some other girl started being called the 'skinny' girl, and this stopped, I started restricting my diet.

I never got help for my anorexia until last year. I literally begged for help when I first found out I definitely had it. I started reading up on it. I thought I was the only person in the world that had these thoughts and felt that way. Obviously I knew of anorexia, but I had no idea that people had the exact same thoughts that I had.

But I was turned away from getting help because I never fit the 'criteria.' I wasn't underweight enough to be classed as anorexic. I was still in the healthy BMI section. It was only last year, around exam time, that I got help. My BMI  was low enough and I was given help INSTANTLY then, like, within the same week. I'd been asking for years before that. It did help, at first.

But, even a year later, after being discharged from the ED team, I still have anorexia. I feel as if I will always have it. Food will constantly rule my life. I plan my day around food. I eat the same things everyday at the same time. Whenever the plan is broken, or something comes up, I get distressed and seriously shout and complain at those around me. My 'dinner' is 3pm. I HAVE to eat at 3pm. So much so that I won't stay out after 3pm. I tell friends and family that I have to be home at that time.

I've started weighing myself again. The first time I said it was only to see if I was still a healthy weight. Then I weighed myself again to see if I'd maintained the weight, and not put on anything. Now I weigh myself everyday to ensure my weight never changes. I actually get panicky before I step on the scales. I think, 'if I've gained weight, then I'm going to cut out a desert from my dinner,' or, 'if I haven't gained weight, then I can treat myself.'

I wish so much that I had never started looking at calories. I'd maintained a healthy weight before the whole thing started, and I'd been eating normally. Now I can't even remember the normal things I used to eat, or when I used to eat. I feel as if I will never be capable of changing my diet, as now I 'know' what I am eating and how many calories I'm consuming. If I change my diet, then I'm so afraid of eating more calories, of instantly putting on more weight.

My parents had to hide the scales from me, and whenever they went out of the house I'd tear their room apart looking for them. I used to walk EVERYWHERE, I'd walk miles, just so I could burn off the calories I'd eaten. I don't think this behaviour will ever change...I can't even imagine my life before this thing took over.

Is recovery actually possible? Will I ever be able to go through a day without thinking about food? Will I even be able to change my diet and eat normally? How will I cope? Does anyone have any inspiring stories?

Sorry, this kinda turned long again, but I just wanted to give some context for my questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I have anorexia I think and I have a lot of trouble even being able to talk to a therapist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 12:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm truthfully just looking for any help I can get please bc I don't even know how to fix this at all. My moms worrying for me for a lot of reasons right now and this ones been going on for so long that idk how to fix it. I don't want to say how old I am bc people will think I'm too young to even be here but only in elementary school now and I know I probably won't even get taken seriouslyl bc I'm not even a teenager yet. But I really need help bc I have a lot of trouble with therapist and don't even know how too talk infront of them at all anyway even.

Like I've had it ever since I can even remember. And it's especially dumb for me bc we have this really amazing lady we pay to cook and do groceries for us bc both my parents are doctors at a really big hospital and don't have time. We always have all this truly delicious food she works truly very hard all day makeing for us and I can't even taste it with out needing to throw up. That's how dumb I am.

I don't look that sick from it I don't think just really pale maybe. But my doctor thinks it's not letting me grow properly. Like I look the same as when I was 6 pretty much and am not even close to 5 foot yet. And I've been doing dance and gymnastics my whole life and their truly very important too me and I've had to be kicked off 3 times already bc I can't pass my physical bc of this. Which is truly humiliating bc I'm the only person who has this problem in elementary school already.

I don't care about the way I look at all. I'm really shy and scared of ppl anyway I always eat lunch in my teachers room. I hate being called pretty which is dumb bc that's a nice thing to say to a girl but not if that's all she hears. Like I hate myself for it bc all of my family are truly amazing ppl like my mom my dad my Oma and Opa are all really amazing doctors and both my older brothers are in premed and actuall medical school already. Like I want ppl to want to be friends with me for being smart or good at something not for being pretty... But ppl probably think that's all I care about bc I'm anorexic but I don't care about it even a little and I work truly very hard at school and my parents even pay for me to go to this truly amazing private school that costs even more than my brothers college which isn't even in this state and costs a whole lot so I can be as smart as them. But I'm not I'm not even smart enough to eat even.

 

And I truly wish I wasn't like this I always have been like that ever since I was 3 or 4 at least. Bc it was so important to my dad that I be really really really skinny bc that's what was gonna make me worthwhile and make ppl like me or not. And would help me hide my food from mom so it looked like I had ate it. Like I would have the lady who cooks for us pack me a lot of lunch and just threw it away before mom picked me up. And then I could just say I wasn't hungry at dinner.

But mom dindn't think I needed too bc everyone in are family is really skinny already and we have really good matabolisms and we will be skinny even if we ate. And that being skinny isn't important at all anyway. Like she'd always have real serious talks with me about it bc she worried a ton bc of it but he didn't want me to so I didn't eat but idk how to explain it to mom bc I wasn't allowed to tell her.

 

And he got way worse making sure I didn't eat too much and on the nights mom wasn't there would just r like drag me by the hair to the bathroom and shove his finger down my throat until I threwup. And he just kept doing it every night mom wasn't there. Even when I started not eating anything anymore and he was trying to teach me how to myself so I could even when mom was there but I couldn't and he just shoved my head into the toilet and held it there wich was really humiliating and disgusting but I should of tried harder. And like I never learned how but it got to the point it is now where my body just makes it so I throw up when I just try and eat even if I don't want it too at all anymore.

Mom wanted me to see a therapist really badly but dad and me didn't want me too bc I think we were worried about getting caught for the other stuff we have to do together. And like when I was 6 I had done something to hurt myself on accident and mom finally made me see one. But dad told me a lot of things to make me really terrified of talking to therapists. Like even now that I know their probably were all made up I'm still too scared to talk to them even if I really should for my mom.

 

I had to talk to one for 3 times last month bc of trying to of trying to kill myself and couldn't even talk to him by the last time bc I was very scared bc he kept asking me the same questions me and dad had practiced how to answer like a million times and I answered them how I was supposed too even but he just wouldn't let it go at all anyway even tho I answered them the right way even.

And like me and my mom thought maybe it would be easier to talk to a girl therapist and she spent like forever finding a really good one for me and I saw her for the 1st time last week and mom even took work off to be there for me but I was so nervous I had done something really dumb the night before and tried to hide it from my mom but ended up fainting there. Her office is right next to the hospital my mom works and idk for sure bc I only woke up for like a real little bit only and I was really very dizzy but I'm pretty sure my therapist who I don't even know yet had to drive me to the hospital so mom could be in the back seat with me and keep me from dying and I haven't asked mom yet but I know she probably hates me for it and won't be my therapist anymore for it. And idk how too even fix myself alone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My girlfriend used to binge eat and has self image problems </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 15:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello,

So about a month or so ago, my girlfriend told me that she used to binge eat and had actually stopped about 10 months ago (we've been dating for 7 months). I didn't really say too much in return, I've known that she was critical of her body but assumed that she'd gotten better and that it was over.

However the other day, she saw a picture of herself on facebook that she thought was unflattering and got really upset. She tends to get emotional when she's on her period so that might have been it, but I've never seen her so sad before and it really hurt seeing her like that. I tried explain how I thought she was beautiful (I genuinely do, not only is she beautiful to me, I know that other people think she's very attractive and in all honesty she has nothing to worry about when it comes to weight).

I'm still not sure I reacted the right way, but that whole thing got me a little worried about how she's doing with her eating disorder that she used to have. She's been exercising a lot more lately and she counts her macros with an online trainer - she has one cheat meal a week, usually with me, but otherwise she plans what she eats very specifically. I've heard that these can both be signs of eating disorders?

I was the only person she's every told about her eating disorder, not even her mom or best friend. I don't think she's ever gone to see a therapist, and I really think it would help. Are there any suggestions as far as

1) how to be there for her as her boyfriend - when she gets upset in the future should I reassure her that she's beautiful like I did before or just tell her I love her and be quiety? 2) how to help her to get help - I understand it's not my role to be her therapist or caregiver, but the fact that I'm the only one who knows it's an issue I think puts me in a position where I should try and help her to get help if she's having problems 3) Are there triggering things I can avoid in conversation?

Thanks everyone!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Adderall masking the symptoms of an ED? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 15:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was 9, I was diagnosed with severe ADHD, and I was put on Adderall. Long story short, nearly every day since my diagnosis, I've taken Adderall. I usually get my prescription filled every month, but because of a mistake made by my insurance company, I won't have Adderall until next week. The day after I ran out, I started having insane urges to eat; I can only describe it as an instinctual urge to eat anything I can lay my hands on.

I haven't really had any ED related behaviors in the past, I do count calories and use a food scale (I lost a lot of weight when I was 16). However, I've always attributed this seemingly obsessive behavior to behaviors typically present due to asperger's syndrome, which I have.

I'm beginning to think that the appetite reducing qualities of the Adderall have masked an eating disorder, and I've falsely attributed my obsession over calorie counting to Asperger's syndrome. When I get my new prescription of Adderall, I'll reassess the situation, but the possibility of having an ED scares the shit out of me.

I want to talk to my parents about it (I'm still in High School), but I'm scared shitless that they'll either brush it off or think I've gone completely mad. l feel like I'm losing control of my body, I'm depressed, I can barely fit into my clothes anymore, and the only friend that I have is currently on a 2 month vacation. I'm at a loss about what to do. Any help? Suggestions? Online Resources? Really, anything at this point would help. Thanks in advance.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Overweight, dieted hard a year, got anorexia along the way, can't feel satiation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 15:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Used to be overweight, dieted hard for a year, got anorexia along the way, struggling with satiation.

Not clinical anorexia, ED-nos I think it's called (realized today that the term existed), or simply over-restrictive eating.

So basically what the title says. Started a hard diet at quite low calories per day at the start of 2015, followed it more or less consistently until jan. this year when I started to realize my relationship with food was down the gutter. I was in a bad place, but reacted quickly to the signs (with some help from my wife), so I did not reach an alarmingly low weight. I am in regular contact with a therapist (she has been relatively helpful; CBT) and have had contact with a dietitian (useless; he told me that I need to eat more and complimented my diet). However, my mind is in a really bad place.

Since I am not a dire case I do not get much more help other than in terms of "try to add a sandwich to your dinner" or "try to gain some weight". My therapist has made me aware of some of AN's trickery which has helped a bit, but my anxiety is still very real and very, very strong. I try to eat solid meals every day, snacks in between main meals, but I have issues with knowing how much I should eat, since no one seems capable of giving me guidance on the matter other than "eat more".

Certainly the most prevalent issue is that I seem to be unable to feel satisfaction after a meal. Since I eat healthily, quite a lot of lean meat, whole-grain bread, oatmeal porridge, eggs, nuts etc. and am painfully aware of roughly how many calories I consume (compulsive calorie counter - it was my first warning sign) I feel like I'm eating the right amount. My stomach gets physically full, often uncomfortably so, but the feeling of satisfaction never occurs. I have tried all kinds of combinations, even a few careful attempts loaded with saturated fats and sugar, and nothing seems to work. If I eat until I do not want to eat anymore, I easily overeat (or feel like I do - i eat A LOT), and I am still yearning for a snack two-three hours later... I do not want to transform AN into BED, but I still want to eat enough to feel satisfied...

So does anyone here at CC have experience with this? Part of my problem is that most information on anorexia and recovery diet-wise (rightfully) concerns dire cases, with individuals that are underweight or even famished. As I do not fall into this category I am at a loss for a recovery strategy. I still experience typical ED behaviour that would likely diminish if I just felt satisfied: wandering around the grocery store daily staring at candy, sweets and treats (or even foods that I usually eat), day-dreaming about food, anxiety in face of ordering out or unprepared meals with friends, incapability to treat myself to "bad" (I know they're not, but you get the point) foods: candy, cookies, cakes, desserts, many condiments or sauces etc... Even though I fight hard and actually eat them. It just seems as if my body will not accept anything less than gorging.

I have heard about the "eat whatever whenever" approach but I feel like it's a bit dangerous as I have binged a couple of times before (4 times, 5 months since last time though). Though I have been wondering if I haven't really let my body repair enough; many AN recovery plans involve eating a whole bunch of calories for that purpose, not only for weight gain. That's where my dilemma enters; I do not really need to gain weight, at least not that much, else I wouldn't be that tentative towards just eating more. I want to establish a way of eating that I can carry with me for the rest of my life, so that I don't have to bounce between gaining and losing...

Quick info about me in case you wonder: healthy BMI (smack in the middle I think), 25 years old, male. Jogs for a couple of hours a week, works as a CS engineer. I used to lift weights but recently realized it destroyed my self-image so had to toss it. I have nothing against it but I personally can't manage it and stay sane, it seems.

Thanks for reading! I can be quite verbose, for which I apologize.

TL;DR: Used to be overweight, dieted hard for too long, got anorexia along the way but stabilized at a healthy weight. Can't feel satisfied after a meal despite being healthy. Looking for guidelines for AN recovery when not underweight.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Exercise guilt? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 02:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I may have some type of ED associated with exercise addiction and could use some advice.

Due to a developing health condition, I'm unable to complete my former exercise routine, which I have been doing without breaks for many years. I used to be obese and worked really hard to get to a healthy weight, and I'm worried that I will get out of shape.

To expand further, the issue is that I count calories and knew how much I ate versus burned off. Now that I can't burn off as much through exercise, and I've been having trouble eating less to compensate, I'm constantly worried that the net effect is a calorie surplus, which will decrease my lean body mass. I often feel like I don't deserve to eat certain types/amounts of food unless I can get a good workout in.

To make matters worse, I'm starting to get anxiety with the simple thought of working out. Before I even get started with my workouts, any slight fatigue or body ache and my mind panics; I become anxious that I won't be able to start or finish my full workout and that I'm going to fail yet again. On top of that, when I see other people exercising, I get really jealous and feel guilty that I can't be in their shoes. These thoughts never came into my head before!

Has anyone else felt this way before? How do I break out of this vicious cycle? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My sister and I are thinking about going to the same treatment center... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 02:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will be my third time in treatment, her first. She's definitely going to this center, I have another option. We have a six year age difference (I'm older and we are both adults. I'm 25f and she's 18f.) and her ed is related to mine. Mine is (as far as I know) totally unrelated to hers. Would this be detrimental to our recovery? I think it could be good because I never see her (I live in the US, she lives in Europe) and also because family therapy would be much easier. I also think it might be comforting for her because she's never been to treatment before. But, I can also see this going very badly. I would love thoughts and opinions.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How do you deal with people bringing up actions in that past that were due to an ED? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 19:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you deal with people bringing up actions in that past that were due to an ED? My friends joke about how I used to eat using behaviors. 

I've gotten much better about food, but these types of comments always make me anxious, and I can never eat when I'm anxious or stressed. I don't want them to know about the ED. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My girlfriend told me about her eating disorder but doesn't want to recover. What can I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 19:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So recently my girlfriend who is at a healthy weight told me she has bulimia. She said she really didn't want to tell me and has never told anyone before. I've tried to talk to her about recovery but she's convinced that she has it under control. 

She is a frequenter of pro ED sites (which I made clear that I don't approve of) and she insists that she has it under control. She keeps saying she'll stop when she reaches her goal, (which is unhealthy), that she experiences no symptoms, and absolutely refuses to seek help, recovery, or even begin to change. 

It's stressing me out beyond and I don't know if I can help her or just give up. How do I get her to realize that she's going to kill herself like this or encourage her to get help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] How do I know if I'm at a healthy weight? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 05:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have had a love/hate relationship with my body for years now. Sometimes when I didn't like how I looked I would just up the exercise and lower the food. It was never very extreme so I never thought I had a problem. I was very close if not at underweight the entire time. I was always the "skinny" girl and I loved it. It became part of me. My mother would complain about how thin I was and then call my butt too big within the same day. I have no basis for if I am healthy, overweight, or underweight (for me). 

Only within the past few years have I been "happy" with how I look. I am well within the healthy range now. I got married and subsequently put on "happy weight". I haven't been able to workout like I did because we moved so far away (no gym near). I love that I have boobs now, but that is about it. It changes day by day if I love it or hate it. Realistically I haven't gained much at all, but to me it feels like the world.

Days like today I just want to restrict. I just think, well if I restrict for a few days then I will be fine again. I want to be back at the weight I was. My views are so damaged I don't know what body was genuinely more healthy/attractive. I had things I loved/hated about both. 

How do I get past this? How can I see myself how I am able to see other people? How can I figure our if I actually should lose weight? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] I've got a history of purging and binging, and I'm moving to a new town soon. What can I do to get a handle on this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 05:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few years ago I was in a bad spot mentally and physically. I had my tonsils and wisdom teeth out in the same month, and was pretty sick. I was admitted to the psych ward for self harm and severe depression two years ago. Around this time I began purging and just barely eating. I saw a nutritionist who wasn't very helpful. Just gave me some pamphlets and said that I needed to gain some weight. At this time I was on the low end of healthy weight. Before all this happened I was pretty heavy).

So I stopped purging. I didn't feel like it was an addiction, but I miss it still. Anyway, my doctor and the nutritionist both told me to gain weight. And since then, I've gained and gained. I'm now at my highest weight ever and am classified as obese. I am a pastry chef, so food is constantly on my mind and is a HUGE part of my life.

Tonight my mom told me I need to lose weight. I'm so hurt by this. I know that it's the best thing for my body, but I just don't know what to do. Food is my comfort. I'm moving 6 hours away from my mom and everyone I know on Sunday.

What can I do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Seeking advice about sister's eating disorder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 02:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 15-year old sister has become way too skinny over the last couple of months up to the point where it's disturbing. After every meal she is complaining about how she ate too much, while in reality she didn't eat much at all. I don't know what to do or say to help her get over these delusional thoughts. I tell her all the time she doesn't eat enough but I don't know if that is the right way to react (it's just my natural reaction). I'd like to know how we as a family (my mom and other siblings) can get her to eat more/workout less (she works out for several hours every day and she even starts crying when we want to go on a holiday because she won't be able to workout for a couple of days) and get a healthy weight/body again. I don't know if that qualifies as an eating disorder but it looks like it to me. Also, something clearly needs to be done.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I think my housemate has bulimia and is lying about it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 00:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So about a month-ish ago, I started noticing that my housemate had started making herself throw up some nights after drinking. I thought it was a little concerning, but she was open about it so I didn't think about it too much. Then I started hearing it happen almost every night she went out, and a couple times I heard it during the day. The day thing only happened about 3 times, but it was enough for me to start to really worry, so I talked to her about it and just expressed my concern.

She completely denied it, said that she makes herself throw up only when she's drunk because it makes her feel better, blah blah blah. She denied it ever happening during the day, but I literally share a wall with the bathroom and can hear everything. She's a very good liar, but I've lived with her for 3 years and this is completely new behavior. I don't believe her, but I know that you can't force someone to get help if they don't want it. We're both seniors and graduating in a week. She's moving across the country after college, and I'm worried that it's going to get much worse. I feel so helpless. Should I tell her parents? Her sister? Her future housemates? I'm really worried about her, but I don't know what to do.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Advice with over eating </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 00:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi I wanted to post a message to the subreddit if this is acceptable.

I've been over eating for years now, I'm disgusted with how fat I've become and I've got a little boy, and I really want to be able to keep up with him but I'm struggling already.

I know I have a problem I accept that. I wanted advice on how to get help/ things I can try to make things better. I eat in secret, I'll try and grab bits of food when people aren't looking, finish up my partners leftovers when cleaning the dishes,. Grabbing a pasty when I get the milk on the way home. I know simply put I need to stop eating, but I eat without realising it. I'll be half way through something and realise what I'm doing. I feel like a scavenging dog like I have to eat.

If anyone has any suggestions if be delighted to hear. I'm trying to think before picking up food, but any tips would be really appreciated.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: seeking Volunteers for Vanderbilt University study on risk factors for suicidal thoughts and behaviors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 12:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> STUDY ADVERTISEMENT Our research team at Vanderbilt University is currently conducting a study on risk factors for suicidal thoughts and behaviors. The primary goal of the study is to better understand what thoughts, feelings, and experiences motivate suicidal thoughts and behaviors.

We are interested in recruiting people who use this website to participate in our research study. Participation is completely voluntary. If you are interested in participating, you will complete an online screener to see if you qualify to participate. If you qualify, you will complete a variety of questionnaires online.

The study will involve four online assessments over the next month that should take about 40-50min to complete and you will be compensated up to $70 in online gift cards to Amazon. A few important things to know about the study are: 1. The study includes questions and images regarding self-harm, suicide, and other unpleasant images. We strongly emphasize that some of the images included are extremely graphic suicide-related images. Some people may feel that these images are very disturbing and may find them to be triggering. 2. All information collected will be kept anonymous. 3. Participation is completely voluntary. 4. The link we provide will send you to a website telling you about the study. Once on that site, you can decide whether or not you want to participate. 5. If you start to participate and decide you no longer feel comfortable or you are no longer interested, you can stop at any time. 6. We will provide links to treatment resources throughout the study.

This study will include only participants who are 18 years and older. Here is a link to the study website: https://my.vanderbilt.edu/tapresearch/.

Please send us a private message at /u/VandyTAPstudy if you are interested in participating. Once you contact us, we will send you a link to the screening questionnaire to see if you qualify and to tell you more about the study. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Upset stomach after eating? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 02:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm slowly working on increasing my food intake and I've noticed I get really nauseous after I have a "normal" meal or snack. Of course, this makes me not want to eat because I feel crappy afterwards and it's making it more difficult to get myself to eat something...

Has anyone else experienced this and does it eventually go away?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 01:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, I was just reviewing post comments and noticed that you mention weight in your post. While weight is important to medical professionals, this subreddit aims to provide more casual support without providing opportunities to compare (e.g. listing weights, calories, exercise numbers). 

Can you please edit your post to remove those numbers?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I have had anxiety for years and my food/body obsession is getting worse. How can I manage this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 01:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I have never been officially diagnosed with an eating disorder, but I have been diagnosed with an anxiety disorder which has been ongoing for years. I have always had a very negative body image, constantly feeling fat and unattractive, however never really lost substantial amounts of weight.

Last summer I got it into my mind that I was going to lose weight, and started using myfitnesspal to track everything I ate and every bit of exercise I did. At first I seemed to have a normal relationship with it but it quickly developed into an obsession, to the point where I would severely restrict for days after I ate even a little over the minimum recommended calories, and I wouldn't eat back any exercise calories. I starting running frequently and walking everywhere. At the time it didn't feel like that much of a problem because I felt I could easily maintain it, and I was losing weight very quickly. Between August last year and January this year I dropped significant weight, and I was never huge to start with. I am very short (4ft11) and started at a BMI just over "normal" and now have a slightly underweight BMI.

I started to realise something might be off when I started getting dizzy and developing huge surges in my anxiety, and experiencing feelings of depression/suicide regularly. I kept having panic attacks and not really being able to do anything. Thoughts of food, exercise and weight have consumed my mind and I am so scared that I will gain weight if I lose control.

I forced myself to stop tracking calories a couple of weeks ago, and I have also stopped running because I felt it was only making it worse. I think I am getting better but I am so scared to gain weight. I know this makes me sound crazy, but I am not a vain person, I just don't know why this suddenly bothers me so much.
I also have huge anxiety issues relating to doctors/medical staff/anything to do with hospitals or doctors surgeries. I have had unrelated medical problems for years (very personal problems) and have had very bad experiences with doctors. My boyfriend forced me to go to the doctor a few weeks back and they booked me into appointments for blood tests, but then I got letters saying they had to cancel them and I had to go back and re-book :( I just can't bring myself to go back and get help for it.

I guess what I am wondering is what are the best ways to overcome the obsession when you're afraid of gaining lots of weight? I keep getting slight urges to binge eat, but nothing of a huge problem at the moment. The dizziness and anxiety is going as long as I eat more, but I also feel like I am eating too much. I am still stuck in my past 'chubby' junk-food loving mindset, whilst simultaneously struggling with being underweight. I don't know what to do. I feel so silly for feeling like this.

**How can I recover normal eating without resorting to binges or freaking out?**

**What can I do to keep my anxiety under control while trying to get well again?** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: What are some of the harmful side-effects that bulimia has on your body? Can I heal my body from these? PLEASE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 02:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been purging, not after every meal, but after really big meals for the last ten years (about 2 or 4 times a month). I know have stopped this behavior since December of last year and I feel I'm finally getting over it.

But now I'm suffering from acid reflux and heartburn, and I have extremely strange bowel habits. These are the main reasons I stopped purging as I thought they might be linked to that. I have a very sensitive digestive system, meaning that I poop about 5 times a day (normal, no diarrhea) and I feel the need to go to the bathroom whenever I eat something. I think I might have IBS, which only started about two or three years ago.

The acid reflux is pretty bad too. I'm in pain almost every day unless I take a Nexium or something similar.

I've had two endoscopies in the last year and the doc said everything was fine, there was nothing wrong with my throat, esophagus or stomach. He just asked me if I had puked recently (which I had). Now I'm thinking that maybe I should get a colonoscopy.

My question is, could these "symptoms" be related to my vomiting? If so, will I get better now that I've stopped? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Relationship with exercise? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 02:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been in recovery from AN and overexercise since 2010, and my eating has improved a lot, but I still have a horrible relationship with exercise.

A little background: all the members of my family are extremely athletic and active, and somehow I feel like I didn't get that gene or whatever. I've never enjoyed exercise at all, though I used to play some sports very casually as a kid. Once the ED hit, it started as "be healthier!" as usual, including exercising more often, and then spiraled quickly.

I've been pretty much weight restored in the "healthy" BMI range for the past 5 years, but the ED thoughts and urges are always still there and I still go to therapy and stuff. I haven't exercised in the entire time I've been in recovery, mainly because I just don't feel the need or desire to, and when I force myself to do it, all the negative feelings come back. Even things as simple as walking make me start to obsess over calories and numbers and stuff. I never feel better afterward, and a lot of times if I do anything extremely aerobically strenuous, it's so painful both physically and emotionally that I honestly feel like I'm going to die.

My medical doctors (who specialize in ED) have all told me it's okay not to exercise, and with this recommendation plus my own... lethargic nature..? it seems pretty straightforward.

The problem comes in with my family and the rest of society. My family is always urging me to exercise and basically telling me that I'm lazy for sitting on my ass all day. It's been like this since I was a kid, and I won't deny that it contributed to a lot of my ED problems at the time. I don't literally sit all day; realistically, I get up and do chores, play with my dog for a bit, send my younger sisters to their extracurricular activities and all the like. I just don't "work out" like the general population does, and I'm definitely not active compared to the rest of my family. And for some reason my family thinks that's unacceptable. And on top of that, we're flooded by the media with all the ~benefits~ of exercising and stuff, and I've been trying to use tools from therapy to resist the urges and help myself when I get triggered, but it's hard.

I don't have any medical issues that aren't caused by ED, if that's of any relevance.

I guess my question is, are you guys at a point where you can exercise? How much do you think it depends on your own nature and personality and inherent energy level? Is it okay not to feel the need or desire to exercise?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I accidentally triggered my gf. How do I fix it and regain her trust and comfort? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 14:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend of 1year currently has a full blown ed. I have always been very careful about how I talk to her about the subject, but tonight I accidentally and unintentionally made her really upset by commenting on someone else's body, and I should have seen it coming but I didn't. She tricked me into talking about it and the person actually looked ok and normal, but in my girlfriends eyes she looked skinnier than her (which is not true), which made her upset because she now thinks she looks completely healthy and normal and "not skinny" enough to even think about recovery. She completely lost trust in everything I say and thinks anything is a lie just to defend myself or comfort her. I feel absolutely horrible. How do I regain her trust and comfort? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Sick but not "Sick"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 14:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been purging excessively -I normalized it but the doctors said it was a severe amount- for three years (huge weight fluctuations of about 7 in BMI in a matter of two months and it's just gross). I was diagnosed last year, but I've gained weight (being monitored) and my bmi is around the upper end of "healthy". I feel like I can't be sick anymore since I weigh so much, and the only way I can seem to self-validate what I'm struggling with is to purge more. 

Any advice?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: What to do after an argument with my bulimic girlfriend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 14:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly, I let my frustrations get the best of me and I said things that hurt my girl, things that I read in the FAQs that I should never fucking talk about but I did. I should have been a better man but I let the ED be the focus of our relationship and she hated it. She hates it that I talk about it with her. It frustrates me that I can't talk about it with her but now I realize that I am not her doctor and that I am her boyfriend, her best friend.

If any of you have ever been hurt by your SO and have argued before regarding ED, could you please chime in and give some advice? How can I make things better? Please tell me I did not destroy our relationship... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
