<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8986</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 06:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine is "I wanna die". I'm not suicidal at all but i just say it. It rolls off the tongue, or something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 08:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find the same with avocado, especially avocado nigiri. 

This is [another recipe](http://thursdayswithwanda.com/2014/06/26/vegan-tuna-salmon-uni/) that I haven't tried but I would love to when I have the time and resources! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 05:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah, coconut curries! I made that for her before and she loved it. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 20:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's kind of a fucked up thing to say when I was just asking for recipes. It's not like they don't exist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 19:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She doesn't want to be vegan, I just want to cook for her and since I'm vegan, I want to cook food we can both eat. 

We've tried explaining things to her but she has her own diet and it's not my place to change it. It's basically similar to paleo, so it isn't too extreme. It just becomes extreme paired with my veganism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 18:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No rice, and she doesn't eat potatoes really. Thinks they're too "carb heavy" (same with bananas).

But, that's not to stop me from eating them of course. I just want to make food for her to show that she doesn't have to eat lots of meat. 

She does eat nuts, like almonds, and stuff like that. I made kimchi that she loved. I know there's a few websites that are vegan and gluten free that might help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Favorite recipes without legumes or grains? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 18:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be traveling to my MILs place in Hawaii, and want to find recipes I can cook for the both of us. She isn't vegan but doesn't eat grains and legumes. That is kind of what my diet is based off, so it's hard to think of 2 weeks worth of food. 

I'm guessing salads, lots of fruits (we'll be in Hawaii after all), and things of that sort. I made zucchini boat pizza things that were pretty good. 

Id love to get as many recipes as possible, as I'm not completely sure what ingredients I'll have available to me when I'm there. 

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 17:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite ice cream sandwich place sells their sandwich for $2, and the vegan option is $4 :( double the price! I would've gladly paid like 50cents more, but double the price is insane! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 08:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not that the term "natural" should ever mean anything, anyway. The naturalistic fallacy is used against veganism often. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 05:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Planning to go into Occupational Therapy, and have an interest in working with eating disorders. No idea how to involve ethics into it... tricky!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 17:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if we could determine it by how many pounds of meat were sold? Although that seems really hard to find out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 08:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you prevent them? All produce in the fridge? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 08:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going on a cruise (Norwegian epic) next year and looked into their vegan foods. Seems like they're pretty accommodating! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 00:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the other hand, I think it could be a conversation starter, to tell the background of the antlers.  

For instance, I went to an animal sanctuary that was selling peacock feather earrings (from their own peacock). I think that would be a great convo starter, if someone compliments them, and you tell them about your trip to the sanctuary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 00:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basquiat, a black bun :) He's doing really great. Was doing a bunch of binkying the other day (I just found out what that was!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 07:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vegan for ethics here, too. It's helped me, although I went vegan after I considered myself quite recovered. 

I didn't realize not accepting unexpected foods was part of the ED until you said it. It seems so obvious now but that's something I still do, I'll try to stop. It's funny how I have to be told that behavior isn't what normal people do (it's happened so many times with different behaviors). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 06:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it House Rabbit Society in Richmond by any chance? I just got a foster over the weekend there, so just curious! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 06:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in a similar position. I just joined a club at school and we volunteer at the city's animal shelter. I joined the social committee thinking I could suggest vegan food for the events. The chair of the committee just said "lots of people, like myself, like meat". It baffles me that people can't consider not eating meat for one meal. There will be vegan options but it just makes so much sense to have it be vegan (I even suggested all vegetarian if it's a cost thing). It just tells me that a lot of people are animal lovers because of how it makes them feel, more than how animals feel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 10:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if I've even tried the organic, but I like pasteurized store bought carrot juice more than the freshly juiced kind straight from the machine. I feel like it's creamier or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 08:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh that stuff is sooo good! It's what I get when I feel like splurging (I'm wild, I know) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 05:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a great staple! They also last a while (compared to raw meats) when in their unopened package, so I always have a few packages in my fridge. Usually their sell by date is about a month or two after I buy them. If you have the package open, use them as if it were raw meats (within the week). 

[This](http://imgur.com/a/JKPnb) is a nice BBQ tofu recipe from /r/vegan. I've eaten it just like that, but something I've been loving lately is putting it in summer rolls with whatever leafy green I have on hand, and maybe some sliced carrots. Rice paper is pretty cheap, I think 50 of them for a couple of dollars. I can get maybe 8 rolls out of a block of tofu. If you don't want to bake or don't have access to an oven, [this](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vxHAbIddCXE) recipe is also great on how to pan fry. Make sure you get extra firm or super firm tofu! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 05:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is basically my grocery list (minus fresh produce) as a vegan, except I'd substitute the eggs for tofu. I usually see tofu for $1/package and you get about 40g protein per package. Eggs are about $5 per dozen where I live so it makes extra sense to do so, IMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 19:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another fun way to make it is to dehydrate it after you boil it, and you get seitan jerky. Soo yummy :) And way too easy to eat protein. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 08:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can eat a higher amount of protein rich vegan foods, so it's actually easier for me to eat more protein. Like, it's really easy to eat lentil soup but when I ate meat, eating 6 oz chicken breast felt like a chore. Realizing I don't need to force myself to eat it was super relieving! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 08:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Waiting for the page to load, I was trying to come up with what a thighbrow could be. I was expecting a new shaving trend where you would leave a strip of hair above the knees. Made me laugh. Maybe some girls would try to draw in their thighbrows with eyebrow pencils. So great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 03:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The yoga journals page was helpful, especially using the strap (although I just used some string). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 03:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Very thorough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 01:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! What do you mean by curve forward? Do you mean like kind of keeping your chest forward? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 00:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's kind of like separation anxiety in kids. We get attached to people (significant others, friends) like they're our parents or our safety nets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 00:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's really good to hear. My teacher had us do it on day 1, and explained proper alignment, but I suppose I'm used to the approach of being warmed up. The only thing I can think of is that other students in my class are part of university sports teams, so have more strength (she teaches yoga for sports, as well as vinyasa).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is chaturanga dandasana supposed to be "easy"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 23:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm taking a beginning vinyasa yoga class at my university, and the teacher has us go into chaturanga on the way to upward facing dog, partially for safety issues to help avoid back injuries. I seriously can't get into chaturanga, or even close. I can't do it on my knees. The thing is, I know I'm weak in that area because I can't do regular push ups, either. But, that seems common (especially among women), so why do I feel like she's treating the pose as if everyone can do it already? It's not a rolling admissions class, so day 1 is day 1 for everyone. I'm worried I'm missing something. Or, am I just unnecessarily comparing myself to others?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 18:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Refurbished Blendtec blenders are under $300, something I'm saving up for. Plus, you can make so many things, like soups and vegan cheeses! Seems totally worth it IMO. I'd skip the juicer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 17:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tahini, salt, thin it out with water.

Cashew cream.

Goddess dressing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 07:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't heard of Unilever until a video, I think it was posted on Reddit about a month ago, about some unethical practices by Unilever in a city in India (I think) in the tune of Anaconda. After that, I was getting all these ads from them. So weird. I don't buy that many products from big names (like the ones by Unilever) so luckily I don't purchase from them, anyway. It's too bad Ben   Jerry's is under their label as they're coming out with a vegan ice cream soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 06:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you try on both the women's an men's equivalent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 06:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Women's sizes are smaller (narrower) than men's sizes. Try them on in a store. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 08:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't say Sapphire is like that, though. Garnet and Ruby do seem to be very "hands-on", though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 05:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want to stretch it out on the cheap, add TVP. It's soy based. Sounds a bit strange but a package will last you forever and it's like $3 where I live. Also a good substitute for ground meats in general (it's what's in soyrizo). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 04:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Similarly, I've been making granola and it's been enjoyable especially since it's been hot lately where I live. It's basically similar to what I put in oats, but baked for 15 min. 

Ive been doing rolled oats, peanut butter, maple syrup (or cheaper alternative), molasses, almonds, chia seeds, and dried fruit. Mix together, spread it on a cookie sheet, bake 15 min. Take it out and it'll still be soft, but it'll harden once it cools. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 03:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, I was watching a vegan bodybuilder on youtube somewhere who said that the reason he went vegan was because Rastafarianism. I have no idea if a significant portion of Rastafarians follow the diet, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 03:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely. I think what's frustrating about it is that people that eat those types of meat are SO close. They're proving that they care about animals, but are going about it the wrong way. I think that a lot of people are kind of a lost cause at this point, but people who eat "free range" are saying they want to help animals, and are against cruel slaughterhouse conditions. So close! 

On a similar note, I really want [this shirt](http://www.compassionco.com/product/vegan-unicorn) but I don't think I have the vocabulary to explain myself if someone confronted me, and the shirt asks to be confronted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 03:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im surprised Jamaica was vegan unfriendly, only because I've heard about Rastafarians being vegan. Although, I know very little about Jamaica. But I guess that's like judging America with the fact that we have 7th Day Adventists, which most vegan Americans aren't anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 03:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found that I could only be vegan when I felt more on the recovered side of my anorexia. But, something that really helps with me now is that if I relapse, I am not allowed to be vegan. So I have to stick with my recovery to prove that I can be recovered and vegan. Perhaps it's something that you can strive towards! 

I do know that there are tons of people that are recovered or battling EDs in the vegan community, though. 

Have you talked with a dietician about this (as opposed to just your therapist)? I wasn't seeing a dietician when I went vegan, but I found that mine was very helpful when it came to my specific eating habits. 

IMO, eating vegan at home is pretty simple, but it's harder to not restrict when I'm out. Maybe you can be vegan at home, and omni or vegetarian with friends? This also depends on where you live-- I live in an area where vegetarian food is very easy to come by. 

I also had the side effect of feeling less guilty about eating while vegan, which was a huge part of my ED, even though the guilt stems from different places. You could also just try it out for a few weeks and see how you do. You have to be SUPER honest with yourself and your therapist/dietician, though!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 02:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was waiting for this video since they mentioned it in the vegan soul food video a few weeks back. Pretty disappointed. I was expecting it to be like Vegucated (which, of course, has it's own issues) where they would explain why people went vegan, and maybe spoke to more experts. 

I think veganism is a topic that can be very controversial (and Buzzfeed loves clickbait) so I'm surprised they didn't go that route. They didn't really go over the ethics at all, only to show the one girl talk about how it's possible to eat humane meat (which we should know is BS). I feel like people who are uneducated/unaware about the ethical side of veganism would fall off the bandwagon sooo easily. They focused on the health aspect of it, which is such a weak argument IMO. Even when they asked about yummy vegan food, they just mentioned vegetables... I mean, she couldn't even mention vegan ice cream? 

I guess I was expecting more because they've been putting out more vegan-themed videos lately, so I would have thought that there were some vegans in their production team.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 07:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ice cream, maybe mayo. The YouTube channel, So You're Dating A Vegan, did them. Maybe more taste tests too? I would check them out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-06 19:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you're into topping from the bottom? Dominant masochist? Just because you're into being the recipient of pain doesn't mean you're submissive. It's just how you are. I would talk about it beforehand, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-05 22:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a buzzfeed (sorry) video that shows that it's actually a cavity forming, not bubbles popping.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TIBydD49-xM

edit:
It could also be [crepitus](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Crepitus). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 19:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a cookbook based on Japanese vegan cuisine! It's called [Kansha: Celebrating Japan's Vegan and Vegetarian Traditions](http://www.amazon.com/Kansha-Celebrating-Japans-Vegetarian-Traditions/dp/1580089550). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 07:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you tried researching your professors? The style of mine was very laid back. He taught us how to have easy to read notes, and spent a lot of time talking to us about anxiety. Know that most of your classmates feel very similarly! So many of my classmates talked about how they were nervous, and I was surprised because a lot of them seemed so confident. Also, something that's nice about these general ed classes is that you'll never have to see these people again, even if you make a fool out of yourself. Another thing you might want to consider is taking it with a friend if that's a choice you have. You might not have less anxiety but you'll have someone to tell you that you probably didn't do as poorly as you think you did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 08:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't kimchi use soy/fish sauce? You could look up the percentages with those recipes. I don't go by percentages so I don't know myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 07:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was a vegetarian, became anorexic (not severe) for a few years, became more anorexic for a bit (rock bottom?), recovered. Had to eat what I didn't want to, became defensive about needing animal products. Never looked up to vegans, but I had (still have) many vegan friends and just thought they were unhealthy because Fitness and Recovery! I was always looking ways to gain weight, and eating tons of protein. Low carb was also part of my anorexia. Then had a moment of realization while watching cute pig videos that the taste of pork wasn't even that good. A year later, realized that it wasn't logical to discriminate what animals deserved to suffer based on cuteness, and also realized that i was "allowed" to be vegan and felt this cool sense of independence and autonomy from it. I suppose it's a similar sense of "control" as anorexia, but I can do it in a healthy way. Recovered and happy about what I eat. There's a great sense of guilt that eating disorders give that veganism takes away, too. I should have it not matter whether food makes me feel guilty or not, but I'll always have some weird thought processes but it doesn't affect how many calories I eat, so it's fine! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-30 21:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe intense was the wrong word, so not more fiery... but whatever their personalities are, they become more of that personality. So it could be like, very peaceful instead of peaceful, etc. But I did think that, and that's why I said that it could just be that their increased size makes them seem that way, like how a calm elephant would probably seem more calm than a calm mouse (or aggressive big dog is scarier than aggressive small dog, etc etc). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-30 19:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw that too, also food being eggs as I know chickens can get nutrients back by eating their eggs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-30 18:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True about that being like Sugilite, but I feel like the more gems fuse, the more intense their personalities get. Sugilite was 3 gems fused, whereas Ruby+Amethyst would just be 2. Although I could be wrong, and their size and strength just makes more of an impact.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-30 08:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, that reminds me of a time I told my coworker I was bi. She told me I couldn't be, because I had a boyfriend (so I would be straight I guess?)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-30 08:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> High school seriously is hell! Understand that this isn't going to be forever. I very rarely hang out with people from before college. One thing that I was told that stuck with me is that in high school, you get made fun of for sticking out and people want to avoid it. Once you're out of there, uniqueness draws friends in. Know that the things that make you unique, like being vegan, will make you friends in the future.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 19:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A couple of days ago I asked if any of the cookies were vegan and they responded "no, the closest thing we have is gluten-free." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 07:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My loaf of bread has milk :( I usually don't buy bread, but I've been hearing about avocado toast and wanted to try it. Didn't realize! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 21:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was also that show with Tila Tequila, who is bisexual. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 18:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem with "make her stop" (as mentioned in an above comment) is that she could lose her job, or lose a promotion, or whatever. 

I'd say if it's worth it to pursue a relationship with her, find another job first. Emotions get involved way too easily, and her manager could take it out on her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 18:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically, a "strict vegetarian" eats no eggs or dairy. A vegan doesn't use any animal products (leather, wool, etc). A vegetarian who eats eggs and dairy are ovo-lacto vegetarians. But the common usage of the term vegetarian is ovo-lacto vegetarians. I would do a tofu scramble anyways, because it's just as easy. Maybe add in some soyrizo for flavor. 

OP: you can also check out /r/vegrecipes and /r/veganrecipes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 03:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kombu, too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 02:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roast them!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 12:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like you're saying you're vegan for health reasons... While eating top ramen. I'm only judging a little bit :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-23 16:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since you're saying you have an eating issue in general, maybe you also need therapy? I don't want to be presumptuous but if you mean you are a binge eater, you might want to look into that, too. As well as following the advice of others here, a dietician and/or therapist can help you if you need the extra support. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-22 06:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. Sets off my anxiety! Adderall doesn't, though, but my heart races on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 06:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooh thanks! I went to the Gentle Barn about a month ago :) haven't heard of the other. I'm always looking for stuff to do!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 06:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great! I spend most of my time in LA so I'm bound to head that way sometime. I'll keep it in mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 06:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love hearing about the one in Big Bear. Do you know if there's a website that has a list of places like this, including sanctuaries? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-20 06:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched this a bit ago and one girl on there, Gaby, had written on her tumblr that she went vegetarian after the video. It was worded as "so far, I haven't eaten meat" kind of thing, though. I think I have seen her eat meat in a newer buzzfeed video, the taste-test type videos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-20 00:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you've been eating tofu a few times a week, it probably is something else and not soy. Since its only been a few days, maybe you got sick? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 22:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're renting an apartment, the lease is usually for a year minimum. For subleasing, that's kind of up to whoever you're renting from. I've asked for money in advance (for 3 months in the summer) because I was moving and didn't want to deal with mailing checks. Very importantly, though, was that I was friends with who I leased my apt to so there was more trust. Finding month-to-month is pretty rare, and whoever is renting to you might be gone for a certain period of time and would rather rent it all out at once. If you're uncomfortable with it, I would just look elsewhere. I would at least ask why you would have to pay in advance - could be a scam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 11:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool! Good to know. I haven't made it in ages since I like the added nutrients in the store bought stuff :P  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 04:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only made it in a high speed blender (a blendtec) and it turns out thicker than the store bought stuff, for me. I think the blender has a lot to do with it... I imagine if your blender cost less than $200, it's not doing a good job. Maybe soak it longer like a day? Also get the skins off of the almonds, and make sure the almonds are raw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 12:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking depression, too. Both my SO and I deal with adhd (and have had depression) and can be messy, but we do have a desire to clean (even if it doesn't happen), unlike OPs SO. I would have suggested something that works for us is doing chores together but separately, so double the amount gets done (you do dishes while I do groceries/laundry/etc) but that wouldn't motivate OPs SO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 06:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try adding the spices to the onions and add them to cooked lentils and cook together a little. Also try adding some water to the onion pan to get all of the spices out. Seriously a game changer... Also try adding tomato paste with the spices and onions. Soo good. A little extra work but worth it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 02:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard that being a minority (gender and sexuality in your case) can help with empathizing with the abuse towards animals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 01:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like velveeta? I found this recipe to be pretty good for that. http://plantpoweredkitchen.com/recipes/recipe-vegveeta-dip/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 23:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In case you didn't know, naan is often made with yogurt in the dough so you might want to check in the future! Looks yummy, though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 20:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can't find a butter alternative, you can try making it. This is coconut oil based but I haven't actually made it. Although she's the same lady who makes Miyokos Vegan cheeses :) I just use coconut oil and salt, though!

http://youtu.be/GHQGGAY0vo8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 19:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For written out directions, go on their website and use google translate. It translated pretty well for me, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 06:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try blending vegetables. I don't really like her, but fullyrawkristina on YouTube has a few dressing recipes that look good (but haven't tried). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 05:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, I'm not too strict on bone char and small things when I eat out (but that's just me). I don't know the exact website since my bf ordered it, but it would be one like this: 
http://www.bubbleteasupply.biz/bubble-tea-tapioca-pearls

I would also try Asian stores or if you have a Chinatown near you. Also, don't forget the straws! I asked a friend who works at a boba shop where they get their boba, and they used a website like the one above but drove to the warehouse to save on shipping. I live in LA so that's a more doable option, though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seitan Jerky - (German video but easy to follow) Just made it and seems like a great addition to a "B"LT but also great on it's own. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 04:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 03:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zucchini noodles (spiralizers make the job super easy if you like it). 

Little pizza boat things- cut the squash in half, scoop out the inside (optional), put on tomato sauce, diced pizza toppings (onion + mushroom is good), veg cheese or nutritional yeast and salt on top. Oven for ~20 minutes. 

Inside of veggie burgers.

Stir fry.

In curries.

I eat so much squash.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 02:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have boba all the time. You can make it yourself (order it bulk online) but the last 2 boba places I went to said they can replace the milk with soy, and the other said all of their drinks were non-dairy (although I wonder if they're saying non-dairy creamer, which often has casein). The stores I go to usually have non-dairy flavors, like juice-based drinks, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-14 06:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're in the US, have you tried Trader Joes? I think that's where I've found them the cheapest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 23:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard that local can be worse for the environment. Some arguments being that produce should be grown where they grow the most abundant in the world (it would use less water, etc). Also, more gas is used to bring smaller amounts of produce to where they need to be with local. But I wouldn't know about the human ethics because I do know the laws of growing in America would generally be more strict (as with other goods from overseas). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 18:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes!! That's when I found you guys! It's so great seeing you guys grow! I remember spending that summer watching all of your videos from day 1. Crazy that it was only 9k at that point! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 04:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One I've been giving my dog is bananas! We've been using them as pill pockets. Also, using nut butters inside of Kong balls if you want to be fancy and something that lasts a couple of hours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 05:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get the kind you can slice, fry in a little olive oil and add salt and nutritional yeast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-09 03:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a great restaurant! Love this plate. Huge portions, especially for a vegan specific place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 05:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard vitacost is good. Free shipping over $50 and I see people advertising them with other discounts. I just use Amazon, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 04:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea! Plus, their dried fruits have great compact packaging for travel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 06:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My college- granted, in a very liberal area (berkeley)- is super veg friendly. There's always a salad bar, and all of the vegan dishes had green handles. Even for burgers, we could get portobello mushroom patties. Almost everything had a vegetarian (at least) alternative. If there wasn't someone serving the food, there were usually tags on the labels saying what it was made from with common allergies and animal products. Their website also had labels with all of the food served for that day. 

I have no idea about your college, but I've also met a ton of vegan and vegetarian people and made friends with and I didn't even do anything animal related (though I might next year).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 20:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, ok :/ I saw some seitan at the grocery store that had 70g for the whole package (typical tofu sized container) so it might not be too bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
