<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject845</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 07:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pupper in his happy place. Perfection.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 07:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kodaaaaaaaaaa. Stick with one 'a' though. Don't want him getting bullied.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My happy niece </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 07:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a gift for my boyfriend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 06:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My boyfriend and I just celebrated our 6 month anniversary. We're both 18 and he's away at college while I'm still living with my parents and attending community college. He's a huge PC gamer and anime watcher. He's on the quiet side, a funny loser, and loves rap/hip hop. Long distance really sucks for us, but I get to see him at least once a month when I go up and stay for the weekend or he comes back home to visit. I'm not exactly flowing with money right now, but I'm willing to spend what I can on him. I loved the idea of [this](http://www.littleriot.com/pillow-talk/) gift, but obviously, it isn't available for purchase yet. He mentioned getting matching necklaces, but I don't even know where to start looking for that. I'm traveling to Israel for an entire month next week, so maybe I can find something there? I'm totally stuck on what to get him.
 

EDIT: I also thought of maybe getting him something car related, like maybe a car accessory since neither of us have our licenses and spend money seeing each other. We're both working on it and hope to have our licenses and a car by the summer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 06:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey. Added you. Let me know when you'd like me to come over.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 03:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll add you as soon as I can. FC: 1435-4340-5493 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 03:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My boyfriend and I just celebrated our 6 month anniversary. We're both 18 and he's away at college while I'm still living with my parents and attending community college. He's a huge PC gamer and anime lover. He's on the quiet side, a funny nerd, a foodie, and loves rap/hip hop. Long distance really sucks for us, but I get to see him at least once a month when I go up and stay for the weekend. I'm not exactly flowing with money right now, but I'm willing to spend what I can on him. I loved the idea of [this](http://www.littleriot.com/pillow-talk/) gift, but obviously, it isn't available for purchase yet. He mentioned getting matching necklaces, but I don't even know where to start looking for that. I'm totally stuck on what to get him. 

*edit: I also thought of maybe getting him something car related, like maybe a car accessory since neither of us have our licenses and spend money seeing each other. We're both working on it and hope to have our licenses and a car by the summer.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
