<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6446</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 18:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being vegan is generally a choice made by an adult....I've never heard of a vegan baby... but im guessing the parents wouldn't consider there own milk an animal product?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> R/feminism im high...but is this *ucked up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 08:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok so I was a bit high when reading this article  just a warning***

http://m.motherjones.com/politics/2015/07/planned-parenthood-abortion-the-war-is-over?utm_source=nar.al utm_medium=urlshortener utm_campaign=FB 

Am I crazy to be disturbed by the multiple mentions of the physical appearance of the doctors and patents involved?  

"A petite woman with a blunt haircut and a round face"

"A state senator sporting pink running shoes"

"She wore a waffle tee that showed off an intricate tattoo on her sternum"

 "I find her by the clacking of her heels"

"Miller is feisty, with a sharp blond bob"

I'm honestly a bit torn, the article was informative, and the topic incredibly disturbing,  and it seemed that the author was pro choice, but I felt uncomfortable reading about hairstyles, and fashion choices, of these women, in an article about their battle for women's rights. I was confused as to why it would be seen as relevant in any way. The author shouldn't (and probably dosnt?) care about the physical appearance of the doctors, or patients, and the people reading this article shouldn't (in my opinion) care about there physical appearance of them. So why is this information included at all?

I cant tell if im being too picky or radical about this, and I was a bit stoned when I read it, but it was so strange to see random comments about appearance, scattered throughout an article about something so important, and disturbing, that seemed to be written by an author passionate about women's rights. 

So what to you guys think? Am I reading to much into this? Or is there something wrong with it? 

Thanks and sorry if I sound crazy :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 05:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't decide if Creepy or awesome.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 05:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cranberry sauce...don't judge me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 03:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can always tell because I get horny as fuck a few days before and really clingy/emotional :/ barf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 23:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are so incredible! I would love to learn how to do this? What kind of glass work is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
