<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6210</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 16:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my goals. I love the androgynous look </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 04:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I am in Canada. The wait times are horrible, I'm getting into the program relatively quickly compared to other people. The average wait time in my area is 6 months to 2 years! People are waiting years for treatment, it's horrible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 04:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. A date would help so much, just so I would know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 04:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg, we totally are! I think we're one of the nicest subs ever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 03:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely ate like 2000 cals worth of peanut butter yesterday. I couldn't stop! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 01:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: nothing

Lunch: Campbell's tomato soup to go (120)

Dinner: nothing

Snacks: Diet coke (0), mio sport (0) and sparkling ice (0)

Total: 120 calories

I'm sort of fasting today. I had to have the soup because I had to get a blood test today. I'm feeling alright, drinking lots of water and diet drinks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 00:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried this new zero calorie drink called sparkling ice. I liked the lemon lime flavour, the kiwi strawberry flavour is ok.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 00:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lost the water weight I gained because of my binging, so I'm able to wrap my fingers around my upper arm again which makes me happy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 00:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doctor's appointments

Eating something that I didn't plan or know the calorie count of

Peanut butter cravings

Being home alone for too long </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hate doctors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 23:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As many of you probably know, I'm currently waiting for a spot in a treatment program. At the beginning of January they said I would get in in about 3 weeks, now they are saying I have to wait another month. But at the same time, they are saying that I could get the call any day. I hate waiting and not knowing when I'll get in. The uncertainty is killing me.

They also want to keep tabs on my medical status, so I'm going to doctors appointments every week and getting blood work every week (I'm starting to look like a junkie). But I've noticed that I tend to binge on days when I go to the doctor's, which really sucks because I have so many, (on average I have 3 a week). 

 I hate this. I hate my life. I hate myself. I hate our ridiculous wait times for treatment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 20:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should check out /r/proed, it's much more active than here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 17:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't consider it a sports drink because it doesn't have potassium or sodium, which are the electrolytes that keep you hydrated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 17:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sports drinks are probably better than vitamin water. Most have low cal options, I use mio sport. Coconut water is also good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 04:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad to see you posting again! Keep us updated on your situation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 04:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today has been an absolute shit show. I was originally going to fast, then I decided to just restrict because I had a killer headache and a bunch of stuff to do. But I ended binging and purging 4 times today. I don't know how much longer I can keep doing this. I absolutely hate it. I just want to starve. I hate myself. I really want to cut right now. I am definitely fasting tomorrow and taking laxatives tonight. 

Does anyone ever read these? I know I do... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 20:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best time to weigh yourself is first thing in the morning after peeing. Most people do it naked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 01:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cocoa (147)

Lunch: Egg whites (60) and 1 wedge of laughing cow cheese (22)

Dinner: Shirataki noodles with vegetable broth and soya sauce (26)

Snacks: 2 wedges of laughing cow cheese (45) with 4 saltine crackers (51), 1.5 tbsp of light peanut butter with 2 saltine crackers (26), diet coke (0) and mio sport (0)

Total: 498 calories

I had the biggest urge to binge and purge all day, but I've resisted it until now. I think I will be able to resist until I go to bed tonight. I'm planning to liquid fast tomorrow and Tuesday.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 01:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't really achieve anything in January. I mostly maintained my weight. My frequency of binging and purging increased. I did start the process of going into recovery which I'm mostly happy about. 

My goals for February are to read more, watch less tv, reduce how much I binge and purge, smoke less and vape more. My only real hope for the month is that I will finally get my spot in the inpatient program. 

It's also my birthday this month which is stressing me out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 21:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get them for less than 1.50$ per pack </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 19:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get mine from an Asian supermarket </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 19:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have IBS too! It sucks, I find that probiotics really help with my digestive issues </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 19:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I'm hoping. I just have to keep fighting the urges to binge and purge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gained weight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 18:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck, I gained weight because of my binging. I don't know my weight, but I know I gained because I can't wrap my hand around my upper arm anymore. I feel so disgusting. I just want to die. I look so horrible and fat

I really want to binge right now, even though it's counter productive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 17:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm doing a liquid fast tomorrow and Tuesday, might go longer idk yet. Good luck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 16:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly hate how many food ads there are! Sometimes the food looks absolutely disgusting, other times it looks so delicious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 02:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal and egg white "pancakes" (83) with 1 tbsp light peanut butter (80)

Lunch: Egg whites (60)

Dinner: Shirataki noodles with vegetable bouillon and soya sauce (26)

Snacks: 6 cups of sugar free jello (30), 3 wedges of laughing cow cheese (68), 6 soda crackers (77), diet coke (0) and mio sport (0)

Total: 424 calories

I didn't cave into my peanut butter craving yet, hopefully I won't for the rest of the night. I'm so into these sugar free jello cups, I ate all of them, I love them. 2 days binge free which is nice because my binging was out of control, hopefully I can keep this control </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 02:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel the same as 15 lbs ago. I think I look the same, but people say I look different </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 00:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does it taste? Is it as good as regular pb? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 00:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have any pb2, I've heard good things about it, but I'm a bit weary of it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 00:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to do a peanut butter mono too!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Craving peanut butter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 23:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really craving peanut butter right now, but I know if I have some I'll binge. I might be able to work it into my calories for an evening snack, but I just want to eat a whole jar. Why must peanut butter be so delicious and addictive? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 23:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most hospitals have a gift shop where you can order flowers to be delivered to the patients, so if we know what hospital he's staying at we can order flowers or something. I would love to chip in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sugar free jello cups </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 21:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just discovered these sugar free jello cups. They are only 5 cals per cup, I could eat the whole pack for just 30 calories. I've been looking for low cal jello cups forever, but I was looking in the wrong section of the grocery store. I'm pretty happy that I found them. 

I also bought laughing cow cheese wedges that people keep raving about on here, I'm excited to try them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 20:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty good actually. I'm still getting urges, but I'm fighting them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 19:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't binged in a day and a half, which isn't a lot, but I've been binging like crazy lately so this is good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 05:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit! I hope you get better soon. I would be really sad to see you die </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 04:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's wrong? Why are you on an IV, if you don't mind me asking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 02:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cocoa (47)

Lunch: Oatmeal and egg white "pancakes" (83) with 1 tbsp light peanut butter (80)

Dinner: Shirataki noodles with vegetable broth and soya sauce (26)

Snack: Celery and cucumber (22), diet coke (0) and mio sport (0)

Total: 358 calories

I haven't been posting my daily intakes because I've been binging like crazy for the past while. I need to lose this weight as soon as possible. 

I might have another snack later depending how I feel, I'll update if I do

Edit: I had 2 saltine crackers with 1.5 tbsp of light peanut butter. I feel so hungry because of all of the binging I've been doing. Hopefully this goes away soon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 01:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coconut water is good. I use mio sport, but any sports drink is good, most have low cal options. Also, salt is important </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 21:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peppermint tea is a god send for pretty much any digestive tract issues </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 21:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make sure you are getting enough electrolytes, it's pointless the drink water if you aren't getting enough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 19:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really, she has a weird relationship with food, but she eats healthy and normally. She is just super tiny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 17:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're from the prairies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 08:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love raspberries, only 1 cal each, other berries are good too. But idk if they are in season. An apple or orange would be good too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 07:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have some fruit, something low cal but sweet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 07:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't brush your teeth after purging. You'll remove the enamel that has been softened by your stomach acid. The best thing to do is to swish around water mixed with baking soda to neutralize the acid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 05:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't work out, haha. I drink mio sport, but Gatorade or any sports drink would work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 05:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a heart problem too. I started fainting occasionally when I was young, but my doctors never found anything wrong with me. Now I'm pretty good at knowing when I'll faint and I can avoid it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 05:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also having electrolytes is super important. It happens less now that I drink more electrolytes and increased my salt intake.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 05:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I couldn't have explained it any better! I feel so awkward after every interaction, including online. I usually delete my posts before posting them because it feels so wrong and awkward. Mosty of my interactions with people are online now, but I feel so awkward because I suck at writing and I never know if anything I write makes sense or is grammatically correct

I don't exercise, so I can't comment on it removing the awkwardness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 05:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I compare my chest bones and wrists to my mom's. Her chest bones are very prominent and her wrists are tiny, she wears baby bracelets.

I also used to compare myself to a girl I would see around my university. Her jeans were tiny and so loose on her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 05:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could be low blood pressure, dehydration, low heart rate or an ocular migraine. 

It happens to me quite often. I usually just lean on something or sit with my head between my knees. 

Make sure you are drinking enough water </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 19:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My urges to self harm have been through the roof these days, probably related to all of the binging I've been doing. I've been able to resist up to now, but I have no idea if I can resist much longer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 06:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a few guys who are active in this sub. Some great male thinspo albums were posted recently. Everyone is welcome here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
