<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3259</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 11:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like travel kind of gives you somethings for the rest of your life. It gives you the memory and experience imo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 11:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talking animatedly and engaging in real conversation. I tend to laugh and smile a lot while talking to guys and am a very nice person to strangers. I've had instances where people have thought I am interested in them simply because I am nice to them and do three things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are you currently looking forward to in your life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 11:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's share some good news! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's a song lyric that accurately describes your sex life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 05:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 05:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This makes me miss winter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 04:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spitters are quitters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A seed already started to sprout inside the apple I ate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 12:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 21:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cook and bake as a hobby but don't eat the finished products myself. I do it for my family and then eat my own meals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 05:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it made perfect sense. I have bdd too and am so confused by it TBH.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Body dysmorphia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 05:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand how people can see a completely different image of themselves versus reality </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the worst name you've heard someone bestow their child? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 04:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: suddenly becoming aware we are doing a mundane task and forget how to do it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 03:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 03:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those who don't signal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Parents of Reddit, what is the hardest thing you've seen your kid go through? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 03:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 03:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Introverted. I'm on the fence about it. I enjoy being alone and doing stuff by myself but find I get lonely and depressed. I want to be more out there but just don't have the personality to do that, and some people take that as me not liking them...which is frustrating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 03:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Top soil </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What injury you brushed off turned out to be serious? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 03:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best time to book an all-inclusive vacation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 02:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going on vacation the second week of April. I haven't booked the trip yet and want to know how long I should wait to book. I've noticed some prices I was looking at have gone up. Will they go down closer to the date?  


Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: why do I suddenly become aware I am walking or driving and sort of "forget" how to do them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 21:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 04:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah they are so good frozen!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 22:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree...it's a shame:( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 17:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try eating something that offers a lot for little calories. You can air pop some popcorn and add coconut oil and stevia to create a salty and sweet mix. Keep fruits and vegetables in your house.  If it's not there then you can't eat it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 17:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 17:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope you enjoy it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 17:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always wanted to try a dole whip.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 17:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the suggestion! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 17:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll try that! I just used mangoes because of their amazing texture while frozen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 03:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 03:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 02:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a fan of caramel corn but it's interesting how you used the walden farms caramel. I find their products are usually a hit or miss (but mostly the latter). You should try out their salad dressings. 

My mom gave up sugar for lent and loves caramel corn so I'm gonna try this out for her. Thanks for the inspiration! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An alternative to banana "ice cream"... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 02:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been seeing a lot about the whole "freeze a banana and blend it thing" and offer an alternative to it for those who don't like bananas or want something different:

Frozen mangos. They. Are. So. Good. 

I literally eat them from frozen because they have a really silky texture and won't hurt your teeth. I buy the frozen chunks from walmart ($4.97 CAD) and blend it with stevia, water and a squirt of no sugar drink mix. It comes out like sorbet and is surprisingly filling. 

It has only 90 calories for 3/4 cup of the pieces but 21g of sugar so it's a good treat to have if you're craving something sweet. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some good travel websites to book an all-inclusive vacation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 10:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My budget is under 1000 CAD and 3.5-4.5 stars. I'm flying out of Toronto and am looking for a reliable booking website that is cheap too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This guy's brake light </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 01:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Calorie intake when food is purged. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 07:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been searching the web for a clear answer and there's always two sides to it. 

I just want a clear answer: let's say someone binges on 1000 calories. Immediately after, they go and throw it all up until nothing comes up. Are all the calories gone? Will they gain weight?

Is it just the food that's actually in your stomach that turns into fat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 03:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a simple lemon cake that's just a vanilla cake recipe with added lemon zest, lemon juice and yellow food colouring. 

I made lemon curd by heating sugar and flour, adding lemon zest, juice and water and then cooking until thick. 

It has a simple buttercream I flavoured with lemon and coloured yellow. 

I made fondant with marshmallow and icing sugar which turned out less than stellar, but still got the job done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lemon cake with lemon curd and buttercream...a little lopsided, but tasty! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 03:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 06:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The second one looks right  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 06:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cute!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 05:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it's for a summer job so it would be sunny or rainy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 05:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! It feels awesome to be able to make this and tell people that everything is basically from-scratch!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Accepting that I can't have kids </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 03:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was little I used to watch a show called 'A baby story.' I oohed and aahed at the miracle that life was and became enthralled with the thought of being a mom one day. I used to stuff my shirt so it looked like I was pregnant. I then 'gave birth' to my baby(a stuffed animal) and fed and rocked it. 

Somehow life always has a way of screwing up your dreams. As I grew older, I struggled with being who I was. Mental illness broke though in my teen years and shredded every hope I had to be a successful person apart. I could no longer function as kids my age did; I couldn't sleep, barely ate or even left my house. Depression had me in an iron grip. 

I soon realized that mental illnesses run in my family. As does heart disease and horrible genetic acne. I came to see that if I do have kids, they would end up exactly like me. They would have to suffer what I suffer through. They would hate me the same way I hated my mother for having kids knowing all the genetic disadvantages that'd be passed down. They'd be forced to be raised by a mother who can't even take care of herself. 

In the end, is this really sad? I don't know. I guess there's something in every woman that makes us want to be a mother one day. Unfortunately for me, I just can't see myself as a mom anymore. I can't raise a kid that will end up hating their life: wishing they were never born. 

I just can't do it. But it's okay to dream...

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 00:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry for the horrid quality of picture. 

I used giadas  recipe for dough: www.epicurious.com/recipes/food/views/pizza-dough-237338

It's super easy and fast. Didn't even use my stand mixer. 


Cheese:
Bring to boil two cups milk. Add 1/4 cup white vinegar and let stand for 10 minutes. Add salt and put into a cheesecloth for 45 minutes. Form into a ball and store in fridge until you use it. 

Sauce:
Saut one minced onion and two cloves chopped garlic in oil until browned. Add one can tomato paste, one can tomato chunks and one jar tomato sauce(I used my sauce I made in the summer). Bring to a boil and add salt and herbs. Turn down heat and simmer for 2-4 hours or until reduced significantly. 

Roasted garlic:
Cut top of garlic bulb off and peel outer layer. Drizzle with oil and salt and wrap in foil. Bake in oven for 1 hour at 400 degrees. 

Pizza:

Preheat oven to 500. Oil a pizza pan and punch dough down. Spread dough and bake in oven for five minutes. Take out and layer garlic, sauce and crumble cheese on top.  Bake for addiction all 5-10 minutes or until golden brown under neath. Broil and take out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the best pizzas I've ever made. Homemade cheese, dough, sauce and roasted garlic. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 23:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some good sites to book all inclusive vacations? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 19:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 20:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel you on so many levels. 

My acne started at age 10 and I began wearing concealer and people would comment on it.

If I went without makeup my grandmother would say "what's on your skin?"

My boss even said "you've got some acne scars on your face"

Like as if I don't realize this! This is something that causes me immense emotional pain every day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 20:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Betty Crocker oatmeal cookie recipe...which can be found on their website. 

I subbed coconut oil for butter and added 1/2 cup shredded carrots and 2 tsp ginger.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Carrot and ginger oatmeal cookies! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 15:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Freshly baked soft pretzels </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 22:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 19:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 06:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha true! But a very delicious pizza cake
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 06:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> www.kingarthurflour.com/recipes/chicago-style-deep-dish-pizza-recipe

The reason mine is so deep is that I used a small pan and only made one with the dough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deep dish pizza- it was inhaled 5 minutes after I took this photo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 00:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some cheese bagels I made today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 00:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I made some cheese bagels today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 00:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 00:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem! Try Alton Browns soft pretzel recipe and instead of shaping them into pretzels just make mini bites! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 05:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They may look ugly but these are the best oat squares I've ever made. 

Recipe

1 cup coconut oil
1 medium ripe banana
1 tbsp fruit jam
1   1/2 cups sugar
2 eggs
1 tsp baking powder
1 tsp baking soda 
Pinch salt
1 cup flour
4 cups oats
Cinnamon to taste

Preheat oven to 375 f. Combine all ingredients and place into greased square pan. Dust cinnamon on top and place in oven. Bake for 30-40 minutes and cool. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something people complain about in life that can easily be fixed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 05:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 20:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually when hosting parties that just involve drinks and apps you can do whatever you want to. Include a cheese platter and pair it with some wines that compliment each cheese. You can make some mixed drinks as well. 

If you really want to impress people, you could make some homemade pretzel bites with a beer and cheese sauce. They are so simple to make and you could easily double the recipe. 

As for sweet, one of my favourite party snacks are rum balls, which there are numerous recipes for online. You can vary the flavours which is always good. And to stick with every thing being mini, you could make mini cupcakes and decorate them with your initials. 

Sorry if I couldn't be any more of a help. I recommend searching on Pinterest for some easy and fun recipes and ideas. 

Congrats and good luck!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 00:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.bettycrocker.com/recipes/oatmeal-raisin-cookies/8a07726c-0056-4953-bd57-5fbb7b285bd9

Omitted the raisins and added peanut butter and chocolate  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
