<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3094</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 23:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess my situation is more that my body learned to maintain on an extremely low calorie diet for a long time. Whereas some women can eat 1500-plus calories a day and lose or maintain weight, I was basically gaining on 1300 calories. What I want to do is jump back into eating around 1650 calories a day and lift, so I can gain muscle and strength, and I'm trying to find out if my body will catch up to that, or if it will just cause me to endlessly gain.  
  
I'm at the point now where I've gained more than I needed to, because I really dove back into recovery and eating and enjoying food. I would like to lose a few pounds, but I have to make sure I can do it with a healthy amount of nutrition and calories.  
  
It's a hard thing to explain, and I'm rambling I think. Haha. Thank you for your advice! I'm glad you're past your sick years. :) Also, thank you for your offer to talk. I may PM you when I figure out solid questions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 23:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I'm really more looking for anecdotal stories than anything - people who have been in similar situations and what their experiences were. I saw a nutritionist during my recovery, but it was more for gaining back the weight I needed to gain. Thanks for your advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 22:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Compared to the macros I was following before, 59g of fat actually seems like an insanely high amount. I'll see how I feel for the first couple of weeks, and then I might up my fat some. 242g carbs just seems RIDICULOUSLY high to me.  
  
My strength isn't just dreadful, but it's not the best either. Squat 1RM is 105 lbs, bench 1RM is 70 lbs, DL 1RM is 115 lbs. The IIFYM TDEE calculator (which I understand is just a broad estimate) pegged me at 2207 for six days of exercise a week. (I lift five days, and do cardio on one of the rest days.) Not sure how close this is, but if I follow that, I'm currently at a 4,406 cal deficit per week. the 31minutes PDF recommended being at a 4000/week cal deficit, so I figure that gives me a little wiggle room. Am I wrong on that?  
  
Thanks so much for your advice! It's all extremely helpful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not new to lifting, but I'm brand new to IF/LeanGains. Take a quick look at my macros? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 21:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently switched up my nutrition to IF/leangains, and I'm curious as to whether I calculated everything properly. I've read everything I can find, and now I just want to make sure I haven't gotten lost in all the information.    
  
I'm a 23 year old female. 5'6", 156 pounds. Not sure on body fat, but I'm sure it's not a pretty number.  
  
From what I read, I calculated my macros to the following numbers.
Lift days: (5 days a week) 1758 calories - 117g protein, 242g carbs, 36g fat.  
Rest days: (2 days a week) 1172 calories - 117g protein, 44g carbs, 59g fat.  
Does this seem correct? I opted for a cut. I plan to fast until 12 pm, and my eating window will be 12-9. I will be doing fasted training in the morning, and incorporating BCAAs and fish oil. Any comments are welcome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not new to lifting, but I've changed up my nutrition. Critiques/suggestions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 17:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently switched up my nutrition to IF/leangains, and I'm curious as to whether I calculated everything properly.    
  
I'm a 23 year old female. 5'6", 156 pounds. Not sure on body fat, but I'm sure it's not a pretty number.  
  
From what I read, I calculated my macros to the following numbers.  
Lift days: (5 days a week) 1758 calories - 117g protein, 242g carbs, 36g fat.  
  
Rest days: (2 days a week) 1172 calories - 117g protein, 44g carbs, 59g fat.  
  
Does this seem correct? I opted for a cut as opposed to a recomp. I plan to fast until 12 pm, and my eating window will be 12-9. I will be doing fasted training in the morning, and incorporating BCAAs. Any comments are welcome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 00:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually do enjoy jumping rope, which is why I'm looking to see if it's a good alternative. I just find treadmills and ellipticals boring.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
