<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6681</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 04:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a male, it's definitely my chest. No matter how skinny I am I always concerned about the man boobs. ugh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else worried about Thanksgiving? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 04:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm wondering if anyone else is worried about thanksgiving or the holidays in general? I know this doesn't apply to my american readers, as we have thanksgiving early here... but are you guys worried for it next month? What about Christmas? 

 Not only will there be absurd amounts of food - but there will be SO MUCH SOCIAL EATING. I struggle with eating infront of other people a lot. This is not going to be fun.

Also, to add on top of all of this. I've been away at University ever since September and haven't seen a lot of my friends/family for over a month. When I left "recovery" I was at 135 ish and now i am below 120. I am afraid the people in my life will notice the difference as they are well aware of my eating habits ever since I got hospitalized... 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 20:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost at the 72 hour mark of my fast. All the water weight is gone + some more. I also have an appointment with a new therapist in an hour... im very very nervous. But I know that its the right thing. 

Breakfast: Skipped

Lunch: Skipped

Dinner: Skipped

Total: 0 calories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 21:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I currently haven't ate anything in just under 24 hours. I've been avoiding the scale as well... Oddly enough the laxative did absolutely nothing so I will probably take another one tomorrow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I screwed up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 04:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh yes - a good old rant. I need one of these.

Recently my track record has been pretty good. I recently did a 7 day fast, and I did another weekish of 500 calories only. Things were going well. 

Today was suppose to be only 500 calories... I'm at Uni and have to eat in the dining hall. Luckily there is a calorie and nutritional information available online. So everyday I always plan out exactly what I am going to grab before I go down there.

Today I was going to grab a tofu and spinach dish. Surprisingly it was low in calories but high in protein.  I went down, and ate. It wasn't until after I was finished eating that I realized I grabbed the WRONG dish. I looked back at the online menu and I ate about 200 or so more than what I thought. In my mind I /completely/ ruined the 500 calorie day and had a mental breakdown.

I wasn't able to get any work done. I just felt so out of control. For SOME REASON I thought Oreos would help me emotionally. Holy fuck that was a bad idea. I ate probably around 2-3000 calories worth of junk food in my hysteria. Then I thought it would be a good idea to step on the scale.

10 pounds. 

I gained 10 fucking pounds.


I worked so hard for a month to lose 15 pounds.......


The rational part of my brain knows this is just water weight and I most likely only gained a pound or two from this whole dilemma. But still I am so dissapointed in myself. I showed a completely lack of self control. I DESERVE to be punished for this. So here is my game plan

1) I took a diuretic (Flush out salt   water weight)

2) I took a laxative (Flush out water/food weight)

3) I'm going to fast for 5 days.


Im hoping the diuretic and laxative combination will help get rid of the water weight ASAP. I know it doesn't get rid of "real" fat weight, but It'll at least make the scale seem normal.  My hope is that the 5 day fast will help me burn the actual weight I put on and maybe a little more... 

Does this plan sound reasonable?

I usually don't do the Laxative thing but sometimes you gotta do what you gotta do.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 19:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interested </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 19:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm keeping to my 500 calories diet really well! It's almost been a full week. Weight loss is a little slower than if I were to fast but that is okay! 

Almost everyday I complete a 24 hour fast, since I eat my 500 calories in the same 1 hour window each day. 

Breakfast: Skipped

Lunch: Tofu and Spinach (450 cal), Orange (60)

Dinner: Skipped

Total: 510 Calories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 21:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woohoo~

First day of October and I am below 120lbs!! Finally broke that plateau. This must be a sign of good things to come

Breakfast: Skipped

Lunch: Potato and Curry (260), Almond milk (110), Banana (105), Lettuce (10) 

Dinner: Skipped

Total: 485 calories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 19:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So lately i've been eating less than 500 calories a day. For the last three days my weight has not changed and I think it might be partially due to lack of BM (TMI). So...... today is going to be 500 calories of beans. Hopefully thats enough fibre. If not, Tonight ill use tea and laxatives. 


Breakfast: Skipped

Lunch: Beans and Edimame (480)

Dinner: Skipped

Total: 480 calories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 19:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This 500 calorie a day thing is working pretty well. No weight loss today.. but if I am consistent I know it will show on the scale eventually. 


Breakfast: Skipped

Lunch: Mushroom Pilaf (250), Almond milk (110), Cauliflower (30), Banana (105) 

Dinner: Skipped

Total: 495 Calories  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
