<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5127</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 20:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright! Message me and let me know how it goes! :) good luck  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 20:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meds can help reduce the thoughts though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 20:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think both are helpful. Don't worry about all the questions. Ask as many as you'd like.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 19:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd  skip the hospital and talk to a doctor about meds. I've been on all of em xD it's all about finding the right amounts and combinations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 19:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I was admitted for the first 2 times. The group stuff is complete bullshit that doesn't help anyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 19:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's different depending on why you're admitted. It's very controlled. You go to group therapy sessions for most of the day, and honestly it's the most annoying thing ever. In my honest opinion it's all bullshit. I've been to a few different places and its all the same. It's nothing like in the movies. I thought it was a waste of time but its different for everyone. That's just how my experience was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 19:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been in a psychiatric unit...I don't think they really call them mental wards or anything like that anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 14:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the prettiest cat I've ever seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 04:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The smell of sulfur usually tags along with something demonic or unholy. Be careful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 21:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was thoroughly disturbing but the band is great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 18:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do. I feel like its probably fairly common in this sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 02:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What?! You're adorable! You be quiet! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 01:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't a clan. It was player on player </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 19:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish they would change it back to the way it used to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 16:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was that game called out in the middle of the wild? It's underground. You duel people and you have that little teleporty thing? That was my favorite thing to do. I miss the old runescape  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 02:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so glad people go out there and help them 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 02:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I'm in the U.S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 19:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds fine and dandy but I don't think there are any shelters around me. I still need to research emancipation more because I'm not sure how to go about it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 19:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right. Thank you. Like I said, I've recently filled out a shit ton of applications but unfortunately I can't get there by foot. I've been trying though. Thank you for your advice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 19:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you Teesh 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 15:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have brought that up before and they just laughed and said yeah right. I wouldn't even know how to go about it anyways. I did just get a job though. I don't know if that would help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 15:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. That made ms feel better. It just takes a toll on you after awhile, y'know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 15:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see a counselor weekly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 15:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right. Thank you so much. I go to counseling weekly and it really helps. I've brought up emancipation before but they just laughed at me. I don't really have anyone to stay with so I just kind of deal with it I suppose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-04 21:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in counseling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 16:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never be afraid of who you are. Killing yourself would result in more heartbreak and pain than you coming out anyways. They're your parents. They'll love you no matter what, even if they don't agree with your sexuality. Don't be afraid to DM me if you need anything! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 15:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I distinctly remember my first time. I was so young. I was going into 5th grade and it was summer. I've always been bullied, I think that's what caused the buildup. But I also didn't get along with my parents. One day it was particularly bad of a fight. I went into my room, locked my door, and cried for an hour or so. Something sort of snapped in me and I reached over and grabbed scissors off my nightstand and started sawing away at my right forearm. It was surprisingly deep. Right after I had finished and cleaned up the blood, I was confused as to why I did this for I had never heard of people harming themselves in such a way. But I felt this sense of calm and peace roll over my body and I quit crying and laid down to sleep. That was how my 4-5 years of selfharm began. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 14:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More like Hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-30 19:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's Venus Angelic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-30 15:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would a teabag be covered in blood? xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-30 15:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u/teenagehate18 we must do this! Also, can anyone translate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 21:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am so glad things are working out for you dude! That sounds amazing. I don't blame you for leaving. I won't ever have a job that involves me sitting behind a desk or filling out paper work and such. Keep on keepin on:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 15:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. I mean what I asked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-28 21:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you get started on this, as opposed to leaving a corporation? What made you decide this is what you'd rather do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-28 19:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When were you diagnosed with Down syndrome? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 17:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've lost your muchness, Alice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-24 15:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u/teenagehate18 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 01:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bipolar 2, schizoaffective disorder, major depression/anxiety, PTSD, EDNOS. Also BPD which is a sort of recent diagnosis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 01:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally agree with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 23:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same with Mussolini and Napoleon. It's unfortunate but that's just how it usually ends up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 23:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't we eventually just end up where we are now? Government is always going to be corrupt. Yeah, there are some good guys but the majority is not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
