<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3132</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can't decide on program to start as a beginner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 16:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello all. I am Female, 16, 45kg, 168cm and looking to put on some muscle. 

I am interested in the future to compete in powerlifting though realise I need to put on some mass and strength before then. 
About a year ago I weighed 65kg and was doing lifting at a local gym with a bodybuilding coach but school got in the way. So, I guess I have some (very slight) experience. 

I need a program to follow. I am only able to work around a 3 day per week schedule. Is there any program you recommend to follow?

I do know that eating is a large part of this process and getting my nutrition underway is currently being monitored by a dietitian who is adapting a meal plan for when I start the program. 

I want to look good naked too. Thanks all.

(I have referred to many FAQs and forums but still can't decide) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Training program while gaining weight (F,16) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 16:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 06:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends how you cook them. If you sautee them for a few seconds with some salt/pepper/other seasoning, they are alright and are not 'soggy'. If you really cook them down, that's a whole other story. When I do this, I keep them with rice or quinoa, so they kind of soak up the moisture of the veggies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 07:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sometimes roast sweet potatoes like this but never tried mashing them after. Will try next time! Thanks :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 07:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I store 2-3 days in the fridge and the rest in the freezer. I don't think there would be anything wrong with chicken after 6 days, though I freeze because of the rice or quinoa possibly drying out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 07:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a lot of recipes online! Otherwise, just give it a go with some of your tried and tested 'hits' :) Good luck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 07:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So far, so good. I did boil mine prior to mashing which I have noticed leaves them to excrete a little liquid when reheating. Someone below said they only roast them in the oven and then mash. Next week will try that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 18:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure about the others but I eat the same for lunch all week, and dinner will be the same (but diff to lunch). I might switch around vegetables, spices, proteins and rice/card options. 
For me, it is easier to do this as I am also sharing a fridge/freezer with 4 other people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 18:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will definitely try this next time. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 18:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in Dubai, UAE. We rent our current house and the landlord never really allocated a 'laundry room' or cupboard in the house. Probably because most local people here will hire a maid who has the washing appliances in her bedroom (pretty horrible). 
It is pretty handy to have in the kitchen though :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 16:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sticky and mushy. Kind of like overcooked rice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 16:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am currently in the second-ish week of recovery from an eating disorder. I am seeing a dietitian who is helping me by allocating a very specific meal plan that will allow me to gain weight at a healthy rate with clean food. The reason I meal prep is because the dietitian recommended it as a means of avoiding thinking about the food/portioning/calories and being able to avoid eating. 

With meal prepping I am eating on a consistent schedule portioned meals without wasting time weighing/cooking everyday. I still have to focus on school work etc. 

I also love to cook and it is lots of fun to unwind by going to the shops on a weekend afternoon, coming home and cooking. It keeps my mind off other things :) 

Also, I love my mum's cooking and enjoy it for other meals in the day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 16:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wo ho ho... who said I microwaved it? The fish ones are the only ones I don't pop in the microwave :) The beef and chicken ones I do as they have mashed sweet potato, which is BY FAR better served warm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 15:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha.. I thought my 'slang' might've thrown someone off. I meant it in the same manner as someone who just won a battle or challenge. Kind of as though I destroyed the challenge of week 2 of my first time meal prepping :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 15:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep 2 days worth in the fridge after the cook. The rest I freeze and take out the night before and put into the fridge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meal Prep Sunday: Week #2 = DESTROYED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 10:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IB Physics SL plea of desperation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-26 16:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all!

I am in a slight crisis. During IB1 I endured physics SL classes from a teacher, that I realised later, I couldn't learn from. IB2 has well and truly begun and I am stumped. The class is behind in the syllabus and I am attempting to work ahead into chapters the class is yet to venture into. 

At this stage I know how to use the formulas and I know my definitions... BUT I just don't UNDERSTAND it. The theory, the science, the physics. It doesn't really make sense. 

What would any of you guys suggest doing to be more efficient in my home-learning? Any books I should get, tips I should know, things I should do? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 08:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I will do steamed. Thanks for your help :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 08:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely forgot about cauliflower! Thanks for the suggestions. I will make sure to incorporate them :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 00:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regular asparagus here is quite pricey. Baby asparagus is sometimes cheaper. I was thinking about brussels sprouts but can only get them frozen. Yay or nay? 

Thanks for the suggestions :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greens veggies: What and how? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 20:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello Preppers! 


Tomorrow is my prep day (being a school student)... so I am spending a little time tonight to fix up a shopping list. 

I am currently seeing a dietitian who is supplying me with a very choice-limited meal plan so I can avoid thinking too much about food and the quantity of it I am eating. The only choice on there that I have is that with both lunch and dinner, I can eat unlimited green vegetables.

I love my veg, all of them. Especially broccoli. So I am sorted for that. Yet, one can only eat so much broccoli. 

What would you guys suggest to fulfill this element of my dishes? He said to pick the lower carb, fibrous green veg. Thanks.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 12:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about Rosemary? Lots of lamb roast recipes out there that make the two SHINE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 07:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there! Thanks for your kind words. I really appreciate it :) It is unfortunate to hear about your diagnosis, though I hope you were able to recover well. 

I will make sure to keep in mind the idea of little snack bags with nuts to carry around. They'll be helpful at school, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 10:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much! I find that the tupperware is not that great in the microwave so I might go look for some new ones at Ikea soon. 
The cayenne gives it a little kick :D
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 21:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks amazing! This is 5 lunch days for one person, right? Do you keep them in the freezer or fridge? I am going to be meal prepping for one and will do 4 days at a time but don't know whether my food will keep till the forth day in the fridge.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
