<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject758</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 12:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am currently in therapy but my therapist is in Japan, I was seeking help for it/went to treatment but I got kicked out because I wasn't following the rules. Currently, I'm at a healthy weight (everyone thinks I'm all better now lol) and I'm ambivalent towards recovery. I know that if I relapse, I'd lose a lot of valuable things in my life but I don't know if I care enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am a bulimic 19 y/o girl that just binged. AMA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 12:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm also suffering from food poisoning from this past week and I have been diagnosed with a handful of mental illnesses. Currently, I feel like shit and I need a distraction. 

Ask away! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 11:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A simple way would be stir frying it with minced garlic, salt, pepper and then adding sesame oil, sesame seeds, and minced green onions on top at the end. Usually I let it sit in the fridge till it gets cold and I have it over hot white rice.

They're also fantastic in Pad Thai. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-28 01:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well, I have CIGNA and I know how you feel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-12 07:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> gummy worms and reeses peanut butter cups </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-12 05:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHO'S THAT POKEMON?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Me [19 F] with BPD+ED dating my AVPD boyfriend [23 M]. I think our personalities are starting to clash. (semi long description). (trigger warning) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-07 09:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-05 23:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally my goal! Thanks man. I need to check it out. My stats are almost the same as Jennette McCurdys (even the same height,around 105-110 lbs) I just need to tone up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-05 23:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find that snacking on fruit really helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 07:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The third one, holy shit, I wish I had her body :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-25 11:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> arrest me officer 
-swoon- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 14:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have the same one.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
