<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6210</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 18:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well reddit gifts does gift exchanges all year round. I don't know if they would help us do a secret Santa due to the nature of our sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 18:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'm actually getting treatment quickly because of my low body weight. Some people wait 2 years for treatment in my area  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 17:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really want to go into inpatient, but the wait times are really long. So I'll probably end up doing intensive outpatient instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 02:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cocoa (147)

Lunch: Simply egg whites with 2 tbsp partially skim mozzarella and sriracha (60), celery (6), red bell pepper (11) and cucumber (8)

Dinner: Whole wheat tortilla, 1 tbsp pizza sauce, 1/4 cup partially skim mozzarella, 1 onion slice and 1 slice of spicy salami (168)

Snacks: Diet coke (0), mio sport (0)

Total: 400 cals

I decided to increase my intake because I need more variety to what I eat and I couldn't get that at the level I was restricting at. It just lead me to binging, so hopefully the new flavours will help stop the binging. I'm also starting to take walks with my mom and my dog in the evenings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 21:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a while, any food that wasn't part of my strict meal plan would trigger a binge. But I'm working on that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 20:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it is. I guess the opposite of feeders... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 20:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also thought we could do some sort of secret santa thing, like other subreddits do.

But this is a great idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 20:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This](http://imgur.com/a/YZlfx) was me a few weeks ago, [this](http://imgur.com/a/o9Kuu) is me now.

I'm pretty sure I've gained weight which makes me so fricken angry. I've been restricting to below 400 cals and I'm still not losing weight :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 20:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup! I've gotten asked for nudes, they kept asking even though I said no. 

Also I became friends with a guy who doesn't have an ed, but like to talk to girls who have them. It's really weird and kinda creepy, but he's really nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Increasing intake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 02:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking of increasing my daily caloric intake to around 400 cals, because I need more variety in my meals. But I'm worried it will decrease my weight loss, especially since my weight has plateaued these days. So will this make me gain?

Also if anyone has any low cal recipes I'd love to hear them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 00:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cinnamon (147)

Lunch: Simply egg whites (30), celery (6), red bell pepper (11) and cucumber (8)

Dinner: Whole wheat tortilla, 1 tbsp pizza sauce, 1/4 cup partially skim mozzarella, 1 onion slice and 1 slice of spicy salami (168)

I decided to make a modified version of /u/faebun 's poor man's pizza for dinner. It was delish

Snacks: Diet coke (0), mio sport (0)

Total: 370 cals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 00:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, 18 days. He said I could text him, but he isn't great at replying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 23:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My therapist is out of town for a few weeks. This is probably one of the worst times for him to leave because so much stuff is going on in my life right now. I just hate not being able to talk to him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 21:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm making a modified version of this for dinner tonight! Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 21:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use mio sport, but it probably has aspartame. I've heard that coconut water is good for electrolytes and pretty low cal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 04:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you looking for people to research? I'd love to help you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 01:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Overslept, so I missed it

Lunch: Celery, half a red bell pepper, cucumber and 1/4 cup simply egg whites. (55)

Dinner: Vegetable bouillon, celery, carrots and 1tsp soya sauce (32)

Snacks: Diet coke (0) and mio sport (0)

Total: 87 cals

So I binged yesterday, I'm guessing I had around 2000 cals. That's not horrible, but it isn't great either. I'm glad I missed breakfast today and that I had less than 100 cals. I bought ephedrine today, well pseudoephedrine, which I hope works as well. So I'm going to try an EC stack tomorrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 19:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will the show make sense if I haven't seen previous episodes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 18:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the kind words </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 07:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much for the kind words. You really helped me!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 07:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. I'm safe, I wish I could die, but I can't commit suicide </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 07:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 07:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Canada, we have really long wait times for health care. But it's free!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 01:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still have fat I can pinch at a bmi of around 13. You will always have pinchable fat on your body </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 00:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's cream to put on your hemorrhoids, you can buy it at any pharmacy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 19:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hemorrhoid cream. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 19:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have hemorrhoids. I just use preparation H on them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 01:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cinnamon (147)

Lunch: Simply egg whites (30), celery (6), red bell pepper (11) and cucumber (8)

Dinner: Rice cake with 1 tbsp light peanut butter (155)

Snacks: Diet coke (0), mio sport (0)

Total: 357 cals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 23:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How was your inpatient experience? I'm probably going in at the end of the month </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 18:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, but right after I posted this they kicked in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 18:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, brand new. But just after I posted this, they kicked it. I'm just worried about what will happen when the second dose I took will kick in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Laxatives not working? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 18:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this is pretty tmi, but I haven't had a bowel movement since Christmas. So I figured I would take some laxatives to get things moving. I took 2 ex lax last night before going to bed (about 12 hours ago), and I'm still not having a bm. I took 2 more just now. I have never taken laxatives before and I've been drinking plenty of water. I really want to poop today because I'm getting weighed tomorrow and I don't want 10 days of poop affecting my weight. Any advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 05:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cinnamon (147)

Lunch: Simply egg whites (30), celery (6), red bell pepper (11) and cucumber (8)

Dinner: Rice cake with 1 tbsp light peanut butter (155)

Snacks: Diet coke (0), mio sport (0)

Total: 357 cals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 05:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone is welcome here! Hope you find the support you need  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 03:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you should try probiotics! You can buy them at any pharmacy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 02:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are thinking about recovery, then that might be a sign that you are ready for it.

I know I am. But ultimately it's your decision. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 01:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cinnamon (147)

Lunch: Simply egg whites (30), celery (6), red bell pepper (11) and cucumber (8)

Dinner: Vegetable bouillon with celery and carrots (27)

Snacks: Diet coke (0), mio sport (0)

Total: 229 cals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 01:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to drink mio sport, it comes in a little bottle and you add it to water. 0 cals per serving </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 18:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome! Glad to meet you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 07:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you aren't vegan, egg whites are great for protein and low cal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 05:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cinnamon (147)

Lunch: Simply egg whites (30), celery (6), red bell pepper (11) and cucumber (8)

Dinner: 1 cup brown rice (170), soya sauce (15) and 1 cup broccoli (30)

Snacks: Diet coke (0), mio sport (0)

And then I fucking binged. Urg I am so angry with myself. I don't even know why I binged, I wasn't even hungry. I want to purge, but I'm trying not to. 

Total: ????
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 01:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too! I wear so much clothing all the time, or else my hands go numb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 01:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wear leggings underneath everything, I'm so sad that I couldn't find fleece-lined ones, because that's what I wanted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 01:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, same thing here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 23:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just started losing my hair recently, I'm actually kind of glad because I have crazy thick hair, so now it's becoming manageable.

I've experienced most of the things that you mentioned </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Side effects of your ED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 22:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all know that ED take a toll on our bodies and change them. I'm wondering what people have been noticing changing in their bodies because of their ED. Some are positive, others are negative.

I have starting developing lanugo, I'm losing my hair, I'm developing sores on my body (similar to bedsores), I'm having trouble going to the bathroom (tmi), I get really light headed and almost pass out every time I stand up, I'm always cold, if I don't wear enough clothes my hands will go numb and my blood pressure is really low and I have a rapid heart rate

The positive ones for me are losing weight (obvs) and my hyperhidrosis (excessive sweating) is gone. 

So what are the side effects you've noticed?

Edit: added more things </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 22:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to reach my ugw before going into recovery, then my next goal is to recover and quit smoking. These aren't really new years resolutions because I'm not starting them at new year's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 16:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are drinking enough water you shouldn't be retaining water </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 05:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not even a guy, but that was super inspiring! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Make sure to get enough salt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 22:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I just wanted to remind/tell people to make sure they get enough salt. I often see people recommending people to have more potassium, but salt is just as important. It helps to keep your blood pressure up and helps to keep your muscles, nerves and heart working.

My doctor always emphasizes that I need more salt in my diet when I'm restricting. So I just wanted to let people know that salt is super important and can keep you healthier as you restrict.

I like to put inot my egg whites. Salted cucumbers are really good too.

Plus salt has no calories! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 17:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not too sure. I think it's just how it affects me. I've smoked for about 5 years and I only had the munchies for a 1 year period when I was recovered.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 17:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so glad I don't get the munchies when I smoke weed, because I'm a daily toker. 

I'm sorry to hear about your binge, but you can lose that weight quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 16:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have my assessment at the ed clinic next week and it's making me really nervous. I'm just really anxious about it. I know I need to recover though but I also want to reach my goal. Plus it doesn't help with my anxiety that I won't know my weight until my assessment. I'm worried they'll think I'm still too fat. 

Plus, I've been really depressed these past few days and I don't know why. I just don't know what to do with myself anymore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 06:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cinnamon (147)

Lunch: Simply egg whites (30), celery (6), red bell pepper (11) and cucumber (8)

Dinner: Vegetable bouillon with celery and carrots (27)

Snacks: Diet coke (0), mio sport (0)

Total: 229 cals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
