<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8657</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Any advice on body dysmorphic disorder? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 11:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> im 17 and i have major body issues. ive found myself eating less and less. i love food but i feel so guilty when i eat a lot of it. i usually don't have breakfast. and it's because i think im fat, ugly, i don't see myself as beautiful. i found out about BDD and started reading about it. 

i read people will constantly look in mirrors and spend so much time fixing their hair and makeup. they try to avoid pool parties. this sounds like me. i hate wearing tank tops because i think it makes me look fatter. im always wearing sweaters, or slightly baggy clothing. and im so cold all the time. 

recently i weighed myself and i can remember feeling so much guilt because i had been eating more and more with friends and family. it really impacted me. i felt like i had failed myself. i constantly think about losing weight, my makeup, my hair, clothes, etc. but i haven't gone to a doctor to see if i have BDD. i don't know how to approach my mom about this. i like to think i can get over it but it's really starting to damage my mental health.

im asking for advice because ive never talked about my body issues with others and it's not helping.

do I fit BDD? what should I do if I do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How can I help my girlfriend who has an unsupportive family? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 10:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  My girlfriend has AN and she is losing weight from not eating, going to the gym and purging. I'm 18 and she's 17 now and and has had it on and off since 14 or so and her parents were extremely unsupportive when it first came around. They brought her to dietricians only to not listen to the professional and their nutrition plan because they felt that it was not enough so they kept trying to stuff her with food. They threatened her that if she kept losing weight or if they caught her purging that they'd kick her out and send her back to her home country. They think it's some kind of teenage attitude problem as opposed to an actual illness and it  upsets me greatly. The parents and her grandma all call her names and tell her she's manipulative, ungrateful and asks why she can't be normal.They gradually just kind of forgot about it and let her on her own.

 Once we got together, I started to talk to her about it and since then we've met the school counsellor, but not much has happened as it's only 20-40 minutes each week. I'm always there with her and even then she leaves things out. Like, after I eat at a takeaway or whatever and she's there with me (not eating) and we go to her place, her parents ask if she ate and she answers that we ate at takeaways even though it was only me. I've found bread and other food items stuffed in drawers in her room which were given to her by her mum to eat but instead she just hides it. I've asked her to ask her parents to look for a person to talk to, but they never did so I found one myself and paid 300 dollars for an hour and she absolutely hated it. The person just went off and said that she's killing herself, she needs to be hospitalized etc just started really roughly and my girlfriend couldn't handle it so we crossed that off. My gf is in her home country now with her family and they went to a person there together only to be told the same thing they heard last time and it ended with the mum crying and the father shouting and getting angry at her. It's taking it's toll on her. She gets frequent stomach aches, punches her stomach when she's frustrated or feels 'disgusting' and I've notice scratch marks on her legs and arms. I'm really worried. I read that dealing with AN is difficult and requires a lot of support from the family to overcome but I don't think any exists here. 

Sorry I couldn't keep this short and it being all over the place, I had to get this out there. She made me promise not to tell anyone I know so it's been sitting with me.

How can I help her? What should my next step be when her parents are unsupportive?

edit: Post by /u/feladirr </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Selective Eating Disorder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 12:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I seriously struggle with this and don't even know where to start. I constantly feel embarrassed going out with my friends and not being able to order off the menu. If I could conquer this, i would lead such a more enjoyable life. Whats the first step in getting this fixed?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Relapsing, I can't afford therapy and I'm terrified of my behaviors/weight gain - how do I help myself? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've struggled with disordered eating off and on for over 10 years. Over that time I've gone through separate periods of solely restricting, then solely binging   then binging and purging. 

I was discharged from a partial hospitalization center 2 years ago and thought I was in the clear. I struggled occasionally throughout that time but am now back to binging on a regular basis. 

I've gained weight and feel terrible about myself. The only thing that numbs this pain of hating my body is food. It's not yet to the point where food is ALL that I think about but I do think about it quite a bit   always eat food if I'm offered it even when I'm not hungry. I can't keep any food that I like at my house because I will eat it ALL when no one is around.

I know therapy is a very important part of my recovery, but I can't afford it. I'm so mortified of my weight gain   behaviors that I can't talk about it to anyone, so I thought I'd start here for some support.

How can I help myself?

Any advice/encouragement would be helpful. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I need to accept that I've relapsed. What are my next steps? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 12:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in treatment for anorexia in high school. After treatment, I still struggled with disordered eating and thoughts through college. I was finally doing better; for about 5 years, I was eating normally, often in excess. I gained a significant amount of weight, and currently am overweight.

Dieting has always been hard, because I find that when I try to log calories, I instantly fall into the rigid, controlling methods that led me to anorexia in the first place. I was doing OK this time. I was logging calories without being crazy. 

Then I skipped a meal.

Then I skipped a meal a few days in a row. 

I just binged and purged for the third time this week, and I looked at myself in the mirror and realized that I need to get a handle on this before I spin out. 

I feel so much shame telling my family and friends that I'm in this situation. I'm living alone, in a city where I don't know anyone, and I don't know how to get support here without telling the people I love and, inevitably, letting them down.  

I need to accept that I've relapsed. What are my next steps? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How do I react when my girlfriend starts talking about restricting or purging? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 12:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all, I wanted to say that this subreddit is very helpful and it's been a wonderful resource to me in helping my girlfriend with her eating disorder. My girlfriend is 19 and she has a combination of anorexia and bulimia that tend to cycle between each other (sometimes she goes through periods of restriction and then she will have periods of binging and purging)

I have been helping her deal with her disorder for more than a year now and there's one thing I've had the most struggles dealing with. How am I supposed to react when she tells me about her plans of restricting? Every once in a while she will show me some diet plan she found on the internet that suggests restricting to crazy levels. When she talks to me about it, she acts very happy and excited about her new "diet". What things should I say to her when she does this? I typically try to say that her choice of eating habits are hurting her but she only says "no I need to do this to be thin" or "I don't care I have to do this". I haven't been able to find a way to talk about this with her without making her angry or anxious. Anything I say seems to hurt more than help. I love her more than anything else in the world and I can't bear to see her do this to her body. Any advice would be much appreciated. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I only eat at night and I want to change. Help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 15:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last several years I have had trouble with eating throughout the day. I averagely went to bed around 4am and got up around 2pm, and typically only ate later in the day.

Right now I go to bed around 8am and if I have nothing to do that day, I get up at 5pm. I eat everything (not overeating, tho) starting at 2am and ending when I go to bed. I know why, it's a mental thing. I am scared of getting hungry throughout the day, so I just push everything I eat later and later. The later I get up, the less time I have to go without eating until night and I can eat. Also, when I know I am about to eat, or have food with me, it's all I can think about. I have separated food and my life. It's subconscious, I don't literally think these things to myself, but I have thought and reflected a lot and this is what I've come to. I really want to change. But I am soo scared of moving it up. Every night when I tell myself, 'tonight's the night, just 30 min' I just can't. Or i move up my first meal and wait an extra 30 min for the next.

Please help me, I hate this lifestyle now, I want to eat breakfast, and go out to lunch, and naturally get up early and go to bed at night.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Dealing with comments from roommate about food? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 15:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm home for the summer right now, but when I'm living with my roommates most of the year, the one girl's comments about food really upset me. I'm a healthy weight. I am mostly recovered from my eating disorder (bulimia. started recovery about 1.5 years ago...), but I still get into overeat/restrict cycles. I know I eat too much when I'm stressed; it is something I am trying to work on. It's not binging per se, just eating large-ish meals. When I was in treatment, they told me a meal this size was a "normal" meal, but I'm still not sure I believe them.

Anyways, even when I'm not eating "a lot", my roommate makes comments about what I'm eating a lot and it makes me so upset. She'll say "omg, don't eat x, it's so bad for you!". More often, if I go to make lunch or something, she'll ask me if I'm actually hungry. If I order something at a restaurant and I'm thinking I might finish it, she'll make a comment to encourage me not to finish.

Even writing this puts me on the verge of tears. She does not have an ED/MH issues herself (we've openly talked about this before. She feels like she can't understand the MH issues so many of her friends have because she has never experienced a mental illness). She knows about my ED-history now, but hasn't for most of the time we've known each other, and finding out didn't change anything.

I don't know how to cope. I don't want to say anything to her because she sees mental illnesses as "weaknesses" and thinks people can just "get over" them if they choose to. Like it's easy.

How do I deal?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Realising I might have an eating disorder and looking for advice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 00:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apologies in advance for the length of this post. I'm looking for some thoughts or advice, if possible. First up a few details about me - I'm 29, and I'm a trans woman. I've never been anything other than quite thin, but a few years ago I began to get really self-conscious about my size. This was before I was able to get on HRT and I had some pretty major issues with my body (most of which are slowly resolving themselves after nearly 2 years of HRT).

Most relevantly I hated where weight went on my waist and my belly and made me feel bulky and so, so masculine, and it killed me inside. So I always kept myself fairly thin, but never such that it was a problem. Eventually I started cutting right down on what I was eating to try and be thinner. For a while I kept a spreadsheet to keep track of what calories I was taking in and always aimed to have as few as possible. I liked the sense of control over my body it gave me after feeling for years like it betrayed me. I'd never had that before.

So I eventually got to a point where for months - more than 2 years, if I'm being honest - I was barely eating. I'd go days without a proper meal. I'd be happy about losing weight and want to be even thinner and convinced myself that this was totally normal. I was always hungry but I just ignored it. People would comment on how thin I was, and my family would always be trying to push food on me. I'd say I ate loads and I didn't know why I was losing weight and I think I believed it, I just didn't let myself consider that other people had a very different relationship with food. Looking at photos of me from then I look so unhealthy.

I realised a few months ago that I was seriously underweight, and I've been trying to work on raising it back up. I still sometimes feel ill at the thought of food, so I'll ignore the hunger and not eat. I know that I should eat more and I'm forcing myself to and I'm trying to. There are days occasionally when I barely eat anything and other days when I'll really push myself and I'll do really well - and I am slowly putting weight on, even if I'm still underweight - but it's far harder work than I think it should be or seems to be for other people, and I'm beginning to realise I might have some variety of eating disorder. If anyone has any thoughts or advice or any idea where to go next with this then it would be so very much appreciated. 

I want to put weight on and get back to being healthy again but I really think my relationship with food and eating is holding me back and I don't want it to any more.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Coming to terms with BED..how do I get help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 16:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has come to my attention that I seriously need help. I started binge eating in 2011, when I was in an emotionally and physically abusive boyfriend. He limited my calories and told me what I could and couldn't eat. We were in this relationship for about 3 years until I broke it off. 

I still continued to binge eat when I was stressed, but I have become aware of how frequent it has become.

I currently live at home with my parents, and when I'm home I'll binge a lot within a span of 10-30 minutes and I feel absolutely disgusted with myself afterwards. After I binge, I purge. I know this is so unhealthy and I hate myself for doing it.

My parents don't know that I do this and I am so scared to ask them for help. I want help, and I need help. I don't know where to start. What do I do? How do you stop binge eating? How do you stop purging? How do I stop self-harming myself? I need help.

Thank you guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I am visiting home for a short window of time and am worried about my sister, how can I help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 23:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've come home for the summer from college and I'm really concerned about my sister. She has a history of eating and body image issues - I'm not sure exactly what as she is quite secretive about it but she's started opening up a little more about it recently and I believe she used to have orthorexia which has now morphed into anorexia, or something like that. 

She went to college this September but had to come home at Christmas because she couldn't cope, she got extremely ill and underweight and developed anxiety. She's doing a bit better now and has regained a little weight but I'm still really worried about her.

She eats regular meals but a lot of the meals are very restricted - she is clearly not getting the calories or nutrition she needs. 

What concerns me more is her behaviour: I've been home less than 2 weeks and she's already had at least 3 meltdowns (maybe more but I've lost count) when she hasn't been able to go food shopping on time, when her exercise time was delayed by 5 minutes, when her cooking time was delayed by 5 minutes... really little things that she doesn't seem to be able to cope with at all and just breaks down into hysterical crying and wailing. These incidents seem to revolve mainly around her scheduling of food and exercise related activities and she gets upset when her schedule is disrupted.

She is a really difficult person to live with (negative, rude, tries to control everyone according to her schedule, these hysterical crying fits over tiny things, she is sensitive and very easily offended.... she has a difficult personality, and has treated my mom like crap for years), part of which is due to her illness but partly it's just her personality. Even so, she's still my sister and I care about her. but I have no idea how to help her when she won't accept help. She won't take any criticism or advice and she has refused to even consider seeing a therapist. She's 19 so our parents can't force her to go.

Can anyone give me some advice? I'm only home for holidays so seeing her behave like this has shocked me. I'm also not at home for much longer before I leave again so I am especially at a loss. How can I help her? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I suspect my girlfriend has an eating disorder. What do I do and how can I help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 15:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive currently been with my girlfriend for 6 months, and i love her so so much. I care for her so deeply, and i can tell we'll be together forever. She's struggled with depression, suicidal thoughts, anxiety, self-harm and body image issues in the past, and she has since stayed nearly 2 months clean of self harm, but still gets recurring bad thoughts. 

She basically will call herself 'fat' all the time, and point out all of her own 'flaws' in her body and bring herself down, and she refuses to eat much when we're out. She's told me that she hates eating, and that her mum wont let her leave the house until she's had breakfast, after which she claims she is full. 

She is kinda obsessive about food as well, as in she talks about it quite a lot. After shes eaten lots of food in one day, she feels bad and she always says bad things about herself and her body. she always talks abut how she works out, and she told me she avoids hunger cues. She's mentioned things about purging after meals, but this as a long time ago, but its still very likely that she does it. 

My question is what do i do? How do i support her. I tell her daily that i love her and i wouldnt change her for the world, and thats shes beautiful, but she just goes on about how 'ugly' and 'fat' she is. It does upset me a lot when she says the things she does about herself, and it does frustrate me when she wont eat, but i tend to hide these emotions from her otherwise she'll get upset, which gets to me as well i guess... i just feel so useless. I just dont know what to do... i feel like its my responsibility to get her on her feet again, but i know it isnt. 

She refuses help of all kind. Believe me, all her friends, family and myself have strongly persuaded her to get help, but she wont. She's still under 18, so her mum is taking her to see a psychiatrist about her problems, but a referral From a doctor hasnt been made yet. And no, breaking up with her is not an option.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Recovering from AN - how can I reintroduce fear foods and have eating feel "casual" again? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 17:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My doctor told me that reintroducing empty calories will improve my relationship with food and help me get to a healthy weight. 

I'm currently eating more, as requested, but I still over-analyze the process of eating these "fear foods." I'm making waaay too big of a deal about it. I make such a big deal about it that I fear my relationship with food is still damaged. 

Is there any way to make eating feel casual again? My goal is to get to a state of sensible indulgences, but I fear I've forgotten how to do it on my own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How can I help support my SO in recovery from BN? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 17:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To give a bit of background we've been together for about 4 years and have been living together for almost 3. We're both almost 22 years old and about to finish university. We live together in a flat (roommate situation? for you americans) with a 3 other guys and as a flat we're all pretty close - almost like family you could say.

She's been struggling with BN on and off since she was about 14 I think. The severity comes and goes, and for the 1 and a half years she's been doing really well and keeping everything under control. However, she's just started her Masters degree and the stress of it all has really taken a toll on her mental health.

She is adopted and by all means to an outsider her situation is as perfect as anyone could hope for. Her birth parents were too young to keep her, hence the adoption. Her adoptive parents (I'll refer to them as her parents) are great! Very supportive and loving family. Its only the 3 of them in the immediate family, but their extended family is also very close and supportive. Her relationship with her birth parents is fine - they come from a different walk of life so understandably there can be some frustrations with everyone not seeing eye-to-eye, but its nothing extreme or unhealthy. Thats a bit off topic, but I'm sure her adoption is what ultimately caused (?) her ED. Also she has 2 younger birth sisters about 10 years younger.

I'm really sorry for the long wall of text - theres a lot of factors that go into this.

She's mentioned before that the pressure to fit in with such a "perfect" family is constantly looming, and having a family full of fit and healthy people (while her birth mother is probably an unhealthy weight) puts a lot of pressure on her to stay thin.

Thats pretty much all of the background I think. Now on to more recent things.

She hovers around the unhealthy/healthy BMI (as do I - naturally).
She is quite short.
She is very active - intense sport 3 - 4 times a week.
We eat healthily. She is a great cook (and loves it). No junk food.
Masters degree has caused her B/P behaviour to start again
Her parents are now more involved - they knew earlier, but everything was under control back then
She (we) has just started a bit of counselling (half because she wants to/half because we want her to)
I can see its helping her cope with the stress of it.
Its getting worse.
Our flatting situation can be a bit toxic at times for someone with an ED ("Females should be thin!", "She's too fat!" behaviour). It was never extreme, no one genuinely has those views but the jokes still understandable hurt. To counter this, we agreed to talk to the main culprit (nice guy, very understanding), and he has stopped. He shared that he has had family go through the same thing. Because of this, he and my SO started talking to help her cope. Ultimately this made everything a lot worse. He's not the most positive person and has troubles of his own (unrelated) and I fear his outlook may have reinforced in my SO that life is bleak etc.

Ultimately, she is very intelligent. I tell her she is beautiful, and that I don't mind if she puts no some weight. I try to point out that because of her lifestyle she will never be overweight and its not really something she needs to worry about. On a logical level she knows all of this, but that is of course why this is a disorder - her behaviour is illogical. She knows the damage she is doing to herself, and she knows how much a normal person should eat but that doesn't help her BN.

I just don't understand why.

I understand that it isn't a choice for her, in the sense that she chooses to binge and purge. I understand she can't just stop her feelings. I understand that by eating little, sleeping little this makes her mentally unhealthy and fuels the fire of BN, and I understand that it is a cycle.

I don't know what to do anymore. What can I do to help? I've tried sitting back and letting her come to me for help. I've tried being a bit more forceful on the off chance it might be a bit of a phase (I hate saying phase, because its not the right word, but I think you understand what I mean). And now I'm trying to take a bit more control of her eating habits which she has been quite receptive to.

She respects me a lot and we have a healthy relationship, so I told her I will be around her when she eats. We will (try) keep meal times to breakfast, lunch, possible afternoon re-fuel), and dinner. She can eat what she likes and I will step in if I think its too much/becoming a binge.

I'm hoping some of you who may have gone through this, or experience ED from any angle might be able to help me, help us.
I really appreciate any input. How can I help my SO? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Pregnant and in recovery from EDNOS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 23:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am about 12 weeks, nearly 13, pregnant with my second child. Through my first I did not suffer from any eating disorder. I have been extremely sick and I am on medication for my morning sickness, and as a result I have dropped an unhealthy amount of weight.

My biggest problem right now, is worrying about the future. I'm eating whatever I can, when I can to try to put on weight and get nutrients to my baby. My ed doesn't seem to be affecting me much. I'm worried about after the baby is born. 

Will seeing my new body make me freak out and throw me right back into restricting and purging? How can I combat this and ready myself for the changes I am going to face? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Missouri Becomes The First State To Expand Insurance Coverage For Eating Disorders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 00:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Orthorexia in the Chicago or Midwest in general. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 17:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a master's candidate at Northwestern University/Medill finishing up my degree in longform health reporting. For my final story, I would like to write a piece that profiles someone who has struggled with orthorexia. 

I think the condition deserves much more attention and I would like to profile someone because I think a more personal story will resonate more with readers. 

I would love to speak with someone about their experience with orthorexia who is either in the Chicagoland area or in the Midwest in general, as I can travel. 

Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: What can I expect my body to go through when I stop being bulimic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 23:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been bulimic for over 10 years but I have decided I cannot do it anymore. I want to stop, however, I am extremely fearful of gaining weight when I stop purging. 

I am working extremely hard on limiting myself from binge eating. I have gone 4 days without throwing up and have kept my calorie intake relatively normal. Even in those 4 days, I feel like I have gained a lot of weight and it's terrifying me. 

Is my metabolism permanently destroyed? What can I expect my body to go through when I stop being bulimic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I am overweight with BED, Should I actively try to lose weight? (19F) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 19:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
I have had BED since I was a child and have struggled with my weight since I was 11 years old (currently 19F). I am sick of feeling ashamed in my own body and don't know what to do to further recover. 

Every time I try to lose weight it turns into a miserable failure of binging and ultimately hating the gym. However when I just try to stick to my recovery I feel like I am never making any progress. 

My therapist always said that if I focus on my recovery, eating to my hunger, and healthy body image, then the extra weight i have will come off naturally overtime. I can't help but be worried that my weight is going to keep going up and that I will ultimately be in a place I cannot recover from. 

This year I gained some pounds from being really stressed at college, going on birth control, and a failed relationship. This weight gain has pushed me into a more unhealthy range and has made me seriously consider changes I need to make. 

Should I try to diet, which has always led to failure?

Should I listen to my therapist?

Please help reddit!! 

TL;DR : have BED, weight keeps going up over the years despite recovery efforts and therapy, should I actively try to lose weight or focus on healthy body image and let the rest happen on its own? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Answers to Important Questions! Please look here first! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 18:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are many, many gems of posts on this subreddit. Please use the search box and limit your search to /r/eatingdisorder. Try different words, and you will find your answers. 

Below are some of the FAQs and responses.

**How can I help / talk to my friend or loved one?**

 * [Phrasing](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/37pbn3/request_help_phrasing_support_for_my_cousin/)

 * [How to talk to her](https://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/3a86tt/request_girlfriend_has_had_ed_behavior_for_20/)

 * [How to be there for loved one](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2ajwpb/sharing_some_of_my_personal_experince_on_how_to/)


 * [How to eat with gf who has trouble eating in front of others](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/254vp9/request_how_should_i_behave_when_my_girlfriend/)

 * [How to talk to gf after she purges?](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/wbowc/how_do_i_act_around_my_bulimic_girlfriend_when/)

 * [How to help my teen](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2ok24n/request_parent_needs_treatment_options_for/)

 * [How do I tell my parents?](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1s7exr/request_how_do_i_tell_my_parents_i_think_i_might/)


**Trying to recover from Binging, and/or BED.**

 * [BED is ruining my life](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/3b8vqo/request_bed_is_ruining_my_life_how_can_i_get/)


 * [Things that worked for me](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2dc4rb/recovery_sharing_ziploc_bags_and_other_things/)

 * [Cycle of overeating and undereating](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2f0p7y/anorexia_to_binging_its_not_about_will_power_its/)

 * [Want to stop binging](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/24wtxz/request_what_do_you_do_after_you_stop_purging_but/)

**Do I have Anorexia?**

 * [Dieting or Eating Disorder?](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1l40q4/post_request_how_do_i_do_things_like_try_to_eat/)

 * [Anorexia or just bad habits?](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2l4n2p/request_do_i_have_an_eating_disorder_anorexia_or/)

 * [Guilty feelings and weight loss](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2d4x6r/request_underweight_and_feel_guilty_about_eating/)

 * [Am I too close to see it?](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2guh23/request_my_bf_accused_me_of_having_an_ed_do_i_am/)


**Trying to recover from Bulimia.**

 * [How I recovered from bulimia](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1d62ip/post_request_i_got_better_30_years_of_bulimia/)

 * [AMA on recovery from BN](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1uob3k/ama_on_recovery_2_years_ago_i_recovered_from/)

 * [I want to stop the binges and purges](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/36ayxn/request_i_have_bulimia_and_i_cant_stop/)

 * [Teeth help](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1wvg5m/request_teeth_recovery_after_bulimia/)


**Terrified of what's going on, what can I do?**

 * [Should I seek treatment](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1smp3r/request_to_pursue_treatment_or_not/)

 * [Is therapy worth it](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2uaq8m/request_is_therapy_worth_it/)

**Trying to recover from Anorexia.**

 * [How do I decide to recover?](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2gafly/request_how_do_you_decide_to_recover/)

 * [Is therapy worth it](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2uaq8m/request_is_therapy_worth_it/)

**Can't stay away from websites with image content, pro-ED content.**

 * [Why are some attracted to these suffering-inducing sites?](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1nno7v/post_request_ex_has_an_ed_need_advice/)

 * [What can I do to help my gf stay away from them](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1y583g/request_my_gf_21_is_secretly_active_on/)

**I don't look sick enough to get help.**

 * [I don't look sick enough](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/39dcbx/request_i_am_not_well_but_i_dont_look_sick_how_do/)

 * [I feel need to get worse to get help](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/33thpm/request_feeling_a_need_to_relapse_without/)

**Misconceptions about people with Eating Disorders**

 * [Myths about people with EDs](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/3aqyz7/request_what_are_common_misconceptions_about/)


**Intuitive eating and Unrestricted eating**

 * [Why intuitive eating isnt a good place to start](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2rkt6s/request_how_does_one_distinguish_between_feeling/)

 * [Why unrestricted eating may be necessary for restrictive disorders](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2f61ky/request_thoughts_on_totally_unrestricted_recovery/)

**Body image issues.**

 * [10 Will Powers for Body Image issues from NEDA](https://www.nationaleatingdisorders.org/10-will-powers-improving-body-image)

 * [Fearing mental health due to possible weight gain](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/148ipq/twelve_ideas_to_help_people_with_eating_disorders/)

 * [Issues with body image](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1w5ywl/request_issues_with_body_image_distortion/)

**What are some recovery apps?**

 * [Notes on Recovery Apps](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1z013o/list_of_mobile_recovery_apps_please_let_us_know/)

**What are some good books?**

 * [Books](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2y4jma/request_have_you_read_any_books_that_helped_with/)

 * [Bulimia Self-Help Manual](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/175vv7/post_request_found_a_self_help_manual_that_was/)

 * [Success with Brain over Binge](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1d62ip/post_request_i_got_better_30_years_of_bulimia/)

**Other Peoples Comments**

 * [Unwanted Comments from others](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/29jy2f/request_people_always_commenting_on_what_i_eat/)

 * [Dealing with others comments and shame](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/345faa/request_how_do_i_get_over_the_shame_of_having_an/)

 * [Lunch with Co-workers and their Dieting discussions](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2j56wn/request_how_to_handle_lunchtime_with_dieting/)


**Success!**

 * [Recovered from BN](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1d62ip/post_request_i_got_better_30_years_of_bulimia/)

 * [You can beat this thing!](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1k9vgu/post_request_just_sharing_a_little_you_can/)

 * [Ive been fully recovered](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/24l9cl/ive_been_fully_recovered_for_an_entire_year/)

 * [Recovery, and changing the little ED habits](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/316929/request_do_those_little_ed_habits_ever_go_away/)

**Pregnancy**

 * [Pregnancy and fear of relapse](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2xewal/request_25_weeks_pregnant_and_afraid_of_relapse/)


**Articles**

 * [Most are unaware eating disorders are fatal because death records specify heart failure, etc.](http://www.bbc.com/news/uk-northern-ireland-26227243)

 * [Reproductive problems from BN and AN](http://www.sciencecodex.com/eating_disorders_often_associated_with_reproductive_health_problems-120673)

 * [What causes eating disorders](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/35y23q/what_causes_an_eating_disorder_article/)

 * [Negotiating the holidays](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/148ipq/twelve_ideas_to_help_people_with_eating_disorders/)

 * [Dying to be Thin, a very worthwhile 1 hour PBS documentary](http://video.pbs.org/video/1865661292/)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How can I help my sister with her binge eating? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 16:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talking to her (she's 20, just as reference) about it just makes it worse. She ends up binging after being confronted, or after having been to therapy. We (family) have tried bringing it up a number of ways, just letting her know we're there and offering support if she wants it, but the mere mention of food basically makes her binge eat for days.

We recently got her to realize she has a problem and she started going to therapy, but it's been making her worse. She gets home and binge eats way more than usual.

She is young and packing on the pounds and it's really worrying, what can we do to help her? She does want help but I don't understand this situation at all. We're worried about both her mental wellbeing and her physical health.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: BED is ruining my life, how can I get better without therapy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 00:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've lived the last 6 years with what I would consider 'disordered eating', very obsessed with my body, purging, restrictive calories, incredibly intense exercise. 

However in the last month I have developed what I can only consider a serious case of BED.

I can't go three days without a moderate to serious binge and have put on enough weigh to make me want to not leave the house. I feel suicidal, I'm trapped. I can't afford to see a therapist but I feel like this is destroying my life.

How can I recover without therapy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: how to reconcile being overweight and having an eating disorder? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 17:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was diagnosed with binge eating disorder last summer (but through therapy I learned that it probably started about a decade ago). I'm significantly overweight, and sometimes it's still difficult for me to "accept" that I have an eating disorder because of my weight.
Logically, I know that fat people can have eating disorders. But there's this hurtful idea in society that eating disorders only happen to thin people, or they make people thin. It just makes me feel like an outsider among people who have EDs, and like I'd be lying if I said "I have an eating disorder."

Having an eating disorder and being obese feels like a contradiction, and I'm not sure how to reconcile it. 

How do you deal with doctors? How do you deal with friends and family and explain the problem? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Gaining weight too fast due to bingeing so often. What kind of insurance should I get and what kind of doctor should I see? - Sensitive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 15:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
I grew up outside the US and was getting antidepressants from my parents outside of the US, last year in November I dropped the medication because I wasn't seeing a therapist and felt that I didn't need them anymore.

With medication my bingeing episodes where occasional and not as severe but now I have been having them very often to the point that i've gained weight, my clothes don't fit me anymore, not even my work out clothes, and I can't afford to just change my wardrobe.

I have been seeing a therapist once a week but I keep on bingeing and gaining weight.

After doing research I feel like I can benefit fro Vyvanse while I get back to my regular weight but as not being grown in the US I do not know **which insurance would be good to get and what kind of doctor should I see?** I live in Texas if that matters.

I understand eating disorders don't go away overnight but the weight gain has made me feel so depressed that I have contemplated *suicide* (not that I even want to die but it is a recurrent thought that I can't avoid). I honestly just want to disappear until I go back to who i was 6 months ago. 

I feel trapped and lost. Any suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Terrified of gaining weight   obsessed with the way my body looks. It is affecting me negatively. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 18:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like I ate too much yesterday, ended up coming home and feeling very bloated, and overweight. Kept looking at myself in the mirror and grimacing and picking apart my looks.

Generally on Thursday mornings I wake up early and exercise, but this morning when my alarm went off, I just...didn't get out of bed...and then the second alarm went off and I just...stayed there...Now I'm sitting on Reddit, trying to tell myself I should get my homework done but I keep getting distracted by watching episodes of Seinfeld on Hulu.

And the overpowering thought in my head is about how much of a loser I am for not getting up and just doing some quick exercise. For eating too much last night. For worrying too much about food. For worrying too much about the clothes I wear and if they're going to make me feel fat or look fat or not.

I'm feeling very depressed and upset with myself. It's hard to keep going like this.

How do I deal with these issues? How can I relax about my looks? 

How can I learn to accept myself as I am? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Stuck in a binging cycle, eating dominating my thoughts, dealing with shame </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 16:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've really been struggling with my eating lately and it's starting to dominate my life, thoughts, and actions again, though in a different way than before. I'll explain and I hope you can give advice for overcoming this binging cycle.

I have a history of restrictive eating. I was hospitalized. I did inpatient. *As a man who's never been underweight, my anorexia has never felt "real" to me.* I try to distance myself from it when possible, as it's been a source of shame to me. I got better enough to live and feel normal but I never fully recovered all of my physical and mental normalities. 

*This shame really has me in its grip lately.* Eating around other people, especially if I'm eating more than them, causes me shame. Eating outside of my routine causes shame. I can't feel normal when eating. That being said, lately I've been eating more and eating what I think is enough for me.

*However, nighttime binging for me has run wild in the last few weeks.* I'm devouring everything in sight almost every night as soon as everybody goes to sleep. I've binged before in my recovery out of hunger, and I know what it feels like: I get ravenous, I lose control, I just need to satisfy the empty feeling in my stomach. The binges lately have felt different. I'm more in control and I don't feel as hungry. *With past binges I've wanted to stop and I couldn't. Now, I want to keep going.* I think a lot of this has to do with the shame I mentioned earlier: around others, I'm afraid to eat a lot and am very particular about food. 

Now, alone and away from judgment, I can eat whatever I want. I also get emotional satisfaction from this nighttime eating. I have no friends or job, as I'm home for the summer from college. I have an emotional void that night eating fills. It gives me something to get through each day.
I'm finally realizing that these binges might not be triggered by hunger and this terrifies me. I don't want to go from one end of the spectrum to the other. I'm lost and just hope somebody out there can give me some guidance or wisdom.

How can I reduce the obsessive thoughts around eating?

How can I stop the binging at night cycle?

How can I learn to deal with the shame around eating in front of others? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Trying to recover from AN. How can I give up counting/cope with losing control? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 15:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am currently trying to recover from AN without a treatment team, just my mum. I am still counting what I'm eating with an app, although not restricting, but I really just want to be able to eat without my phone, but even the thought of not knowing gives me major anxiety and I'm scared of loosing the control. 

How can I ween myself off counting or to just stop cold turkey? How can I deal with the loss of control? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Is browsing fitness websites hindering my girlfriends recovery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 06:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend is recovering from ABN for about a year now. She has been extremely slow in increasing her calories and actually started eating less after she started getting help, although the purging stopped immediately. She is now eating approximately what a normal-weight woman would require to maintain her weight, sometimes less, but exercises quite a bit. She browses Pinterest for exercise pictures, along the lines of "get you summer 6 pack in 30 days" "exercise to slim your legs" and then below the headline is a series of exercise routines. The text is usually accompanied by a picture of an athletic female.

My issue is, while having an athletic body is not a bad thing, I can't articulate why constantly browsing these sorts of things is bad for her and hindering her recovery. She almost misinterpreted something I said so she thought I was implying she didn't have a nice body and she shouldn't be trying to achieve these picture perfect bodies, but luckily I managed to nip that thought before it fully formed. Can anybody tell me if actually browsing these images and fitness plans is damaging? How can I articulate this to her without upsetting her? I know that exercise is a form of purging, but the exercise she does now is a healthy amount for any regular female of her age and I am focusing on trying to encourage her to eat more to enable her to exercise without feeling exhausted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: What are common misconceptions about people with eating disorders? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 22:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I'm hoping to give a speech about people afflicted by anorexia, or maybe eating disorders in general, in my communications class. The point of the speech is to refute common misconceptions that might hurt the anorexic community; like generalizations, assumptions, or myths.

I've done a bit of research around the internet but I think it would be a lot better if I got some actual opinions from people with first hand experience or common knowledge from the ED subreddit.

Anyways, what do you think are some common misconceptions about people with eating disorders?

Thanks in advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 15:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful posts:

[Talk to cousin](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/37pbn3/request_help_phrasing_support_for_my_cousin/)

[Approach someone](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/253fi9/request_there_is_a_girl_who_looks_anorexic_at_my/)

[Talk to roommate](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2lgrru/request_request_for_advice_on_how_to_talk_to/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How can I be supportive of my friend who I suspect has an eating disorder? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 23:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a friend who I believe has been purging at some BBQs I've hosted. I'm friends with both her and her husband. I want to be supportive and avoid things that maybe triggering for her. 

I'm unsure if I should say anything. I'm thinking I should not as it is not my place. Should I perhaps talk to her husband? I assume he knows. It would be to let them know I'm aware. I do not want to "fix" her, I just want to provide a non-triggering comfortable environment.

How can I help her?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Undiagnosed Bulimic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 16:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just really need someone to talk to. As of 24hrs ago I'm new to reddit,

Since about 17 I've been overeating and throwing up after I eat, like a bulimic but I've been too chickensh*it to confront it. Breaking up with my bf, I've had experiences likened to a panic attack but not diagnosed because I'm too afraid/broke to see a real doctor. Now as a 22 year old I've been to a shrink once this past semester and never gone back. 

What do I do? My boss, (now ex)boyfriend and friends have told me to go back to a shrink. I feel so alone and don't have time for a shrink or s.o to "rescue me". Should I follow their advice to see a shrink? Is there something else I should do? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 15:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful posts. Keep in mind, OP, you did not distinguish from recovering from AN type disorders or BN type disorders.

[Counting calories in recovery](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2k265i/request_is_it_counter_intuitive_to_count_calories/)

[Ways to manage intuitive eating?](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2llr9e/request_quitting_calorie/)

[How not to worry](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/31m3ji/request_how_to_not_worry_about_calories/)

[Tracking with MyFitnessPal](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/25362g/request_concerned_about_risks_of_tracking_my_food/)

[You can do this](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1k9vgu/post_request_just_sharing_a_little_you_can/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Is tracking calories a healthy thing for those in recovery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 15:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is tracking calories a healthy thing for those in recovery? 

Does it depend on the person, or is there a general consensus from the nutrition field on the best way to detach from disordered habits? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Vyvanse for BED - How to keep it from going far? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 07:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was one of the people in the study testing Vyvanse as a treatment for binge eating. Being part of that study also helped me realize I had ADD, and once the study was done I went through testing for ADD so I could get the Vyvanse prescribed to me that way. I stopped taking it for several years when I decided to try to have kids, but I am back on it now. I have been doing wonderfully for the past five months, but now I am starting to see myself leaning towards anorexic behavior and it is frightening.

For anyone else who had this happen, what did you do to help yourself from going down that road? I don't want to go off it and start binging again, but I cannot bring myself to eat enough anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Girlfriend has had ED behavior for 20 years and is very easily triggered over things I consider minor. How to help her get better without making her feel worse? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 02:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend has dealt with binging and restricting for nearly 20 years. She experiences the feelings of being overwhelmed about things I have come to consider 'normal parts of being an adult.' Most recently, she graduated from a clinic for others suffering similar issues. She struggles with her body image and has the most severe shame-spiral reactions I've ever seen in a person.

 I'd like to be able to have conversations about the hard stuff, and I'm okay if I have to ease into them, but I know that if I ignore the conversations for her benefit, I will grow resentful of not being able to share my feelngs.

We practice "I" statements, such as "I feel," or "I worry when." I ask her if she wants me to listen or solve first, so that I can provide the most helpful attention. We go to couple's counseling to have smarter people than us point out things.

It's been a few months since this situation was revealed, and I'm feeling like I'm losing my mind because she's still lying about little things and it is causing me a lot of distress - I don't want to go home and see her; I'd rather forget about her when I'm away. It's very frustrating.

**What are some methods I can use to approach her without triggering her, or tripping the shame-threshold of no return?**

**How can I support her without sacrificing my own wellbeing and happiness?** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Long history of body image problems and disordered eating. Is it possible that I have BED or compulsive overeating? How can I bring it up with my mentor? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 02:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys. I need some help figuring out what's going on with me and how I can get help. I've been struggling with my weight almost my whole life, beginning since about 3 or 4 where I remember my family always making comments about my weight. It started with comments like "you need to lose weight so boys will like you," and "you'll be pretty when you lose weight." At the time I was a good swimmer, so my parents would make comments like "to swim better you need to lose x amount of kg."

I grew up with the message in my head that said "you're too fat, you need to lose weight, you'll only be beautiful and worthy if you lost weight and were thin." When I was younger, I would try to restrict what I ate, then ended up binging on everything I wasn't allowed to eat (but was in the house, anyway). It was like my parents gave me the order to lose weight, but at such a young age I had no idea how, and I snapped under the pressure.

My first successful attempt at weight loss was on exchange in Japan where I restricted and exercised excessively. I lost an unhealthy amount of weight in one month. Nobody said anything because I was losing weight.

I came back to my home country and put on double the amount of weight, and it has just been rising ever since. I feel like I'm trapped in a cycle of diet - binge- fail -diet - binge - fail that I can't get out of, and the only result is that I just keep getting bigger and bigger.

Few years later, I've moved to Europe and I live on my own in a student room. My relationship with eating is out of whack. I was on a popular diet for six months and lost weight, but then I cracked and ate everything I could find, gaining the weight back. I share a kitchen with a big building and I sometimes just order take out or eat in secret if there are people in the kitchen, because I'm so ashamed of being seen eating. I buy a lot of food I refused to eat on the diet, and just binge on them in my room. It's much worse in times of stress, for example I have exams now, and I'm going back to my country for the summer - I'm scared that people will see that I'm still fat.

All I want is to be a normal weight. I want to stop gaining weight, I want to stop feeling so ashamed about eating food, I want to stop binging. I'm in DBT for Borderline PD and I think because I stopped doing other self harming methods, my eating has gotten much worse. However, when I tell my mentor about these feelings, they just get ignored.

tl;dr: **I think i have compulsive eating or binge eating disorder, and I want to know what I can do to get better. How do I bring this up to my mentor and get appropriate help?** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Question - might my friends have eating disorders? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 12:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know two people who always go to the toilet straight after they eat, even if it's very little proportions. They have both made comments about their weight in the past, despite both of them being very skinny. They do tend to portion control to a large degree. I understand it could be a fast metabolism but do you think in any other situation, they could be trying to lose weight or have something that borders on a eating disorder? Is there something I should do or say? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to help my anorexic sister when she won't help herself? What can I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 17:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

Hello, So last summer my older sister ( mid 20s, F) had a painful bone surgery to correct an old injury. As a result, she was couch ridden and nauseous from painkillers for months. This caused her weight to plummet dramatically since she had no appetite and any food she had to eat made her feel sicker. Shes average height and went from a healthy weight to very underweight in 3 months. 

All her bones protrude in an unhealthy way. She has always had a naturally thin body shape but hated her some parts of it before. She now likes being underweight. 

She was convinced to go to a nutritionist who wanted her immediately hospitalized. But my sister is smart and knows how to manipulate people, and she swore she would stick to a prescribed eating regime. She is stuck at home with my parents, however, and they tell me she has not followed the doctors advice to eat multiple small but healthful meals throughout the day. She only eats a few select foods, and although healthy, she's not eating enough to look or feel healthy.

When my parents call her out on not eating enough, she lashes out. When I was home for the holidays, I was shocked at her skeletal appearance. She has literally wasted away to nothing. I struggled with eating issues a few years back, and told her that the stomach pains and loss of your period are not worth looking skinny. I told her I was terrified that her heart will give out if she doesnt get healthy, and she told me to shut up. 

She has been to a few doctors, who tell her that she is severely underweight but since none have said shes in imminent danger of death she thinks shes healthy. My parents are at a loss as to what to do, and Im 1000 miles away. 

To worsen the situation, she has recently been getting into modeling. Modeling has always been one of her dreams, and now she has the emaciated look that the media portrays and it is terrifying in person. She just had her first photo shoot, and I dont even recognize her in the photos. I expressed my concern for getting into modeling when her health and body image are already fragile, and she insists shes fine.

She overexercises.  I think her exercise regime is hurting her even more. Her body is probably eating itself.

The main problem is that she likes the way she looks now. When she posts photos on social media, her girlfriends make supportive comments. She has bought a new wardrobe of smaller clothes. 

Luckily Im not alone in concern for her, since some of her friends have messaged me privately saying theyre worried about how skinny she looks, and I tell them to tell her that instead of me.

TL;DR: I dont know how to help my sister when she likes how emaciated she is and is getting modeling jobs for her new body shape. I dont want to lose my sister. How can I help her see that she is killing herself?
Thank you for reading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Survey: Latina college   graduate women needed to participate in study on eating disorders! (repost) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 19:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

Hello,

I am a Latina graduate student completing my dissertation on the topic of disordered eating behaviors, current relationship styles, parent-child relationships, and perception of the thin ideal portrayed in the media. I am specifically looking for Latina female college and graduate students to participate in my study, which will help expand the (currently very limited) research available in the area of eating disorders in the Latina/o community. I would very much appreciate your support in sharing my dissertation survey information! I would be happy to provide you with more information regarding this study. It has been approved by Pacific University's Institutional Review Board (IRB).

If you are a self-identified Latina woman who is 18 years or older and are currently enrolled as an undergraduate or graduate student at a college or university, please help me out with my dissertation research! Clicking on the attached link will take you to a brief (15-20 minute) survey. Im interested in looking at the relationship between the way you relate to others in close relationships, your relationship with your mother or female caregiver during childhood, eating behaviors, and your perception of media messages about body image ideals.

At the end of the survey you can enter into a drawing to win one of five $20.00 Starbucks gift card! The results of this survey are anonymous and your responses will be kept confidential. Please share this on your page or with friends that may be interested. Thanks!

http://edu.surveygizmo.com/s3/1725287/Dissertation-Survey

Please note: For those of you already visiting this site, a recruitment post has been created to provide you with more information about this study. When accessing this site to review the study details, it is recommended that you first review the policies of this site. We want you to know that while we, as researchers, will not have access to anyones data that uses our page nor do we have any plan for collecting that data, it is possible that this site may be collecting that data.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 02:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful posts

[Not-Exercising guilt](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/25qg9d/request_exercise_guilt_guilt_from_exercising_less/)

[Hunger hormones and how we're wired to survive](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2f0p7y/anorexia_to_binging_its_not_about_will_power_its/)

[Weight gain](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2b1tl1/request_questions_fear_of_being_mentally_healthy/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Recovery from 10+ years of exercise addiction. How to deal with recovery, weight gain, and being almost 30 and dealing with this issue? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 02:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Hi Redditors,

Just wanted to relate what I'm going through and see if anyone has some words of wisdom. I currently fall into more of the ED-NOS category and I've found it really hard to find information/resources on the internet to help me understand what is happening.

Long story short, I struggled with anorexia in my early teens, and recovered fairly well throughout high school. When I went off to college, though, my moderate exercise routine became an obsession, and for the past 10+ years I've consistently upheld an extremely rigorous and time-intensive exercise routine. I won't get into too many details here, but exercise was exhaustive and intensive, often combined with restrictive eating and intermittent fasting.

Over the past few months, I've experimented with recovering on my own. I had a revelation while traveling around 6 months ago, and decided to cut exercise out of my life cold turkey. I'm sick and tired of being a slave to exercise, and my fixation on working out has truly, in retrospect, had a hugely negative impact on so many aspects of my life. I see other people living relatively more normal, healthy, balanced lives, not depriving themselves or beating themselves up with crazy amounts of exercise, and I recognize that I really want to live that way as well. I also want to have time to do other things, and be able to commit myself to people, relationships, other experiences, and my career, instead of just being focused on my workout all the time. Since this revelation about 6 months ago, my only forms of exercise have been low-intensity walks with my dog, and gentle-moderate yoga. A far, far cry from what my life has been like for the past decade.

It has been tremendously difficult to figure out how to feed myself properly without my usual intense exercise regimens, and over the past 6 months I've really been experimenting with how and how much to feed myself. I have zero hunger cues, so I often feel like I'm stuffing myself, even though I know that the reality is that I'm not meeting my ideal daily intake for food. That said, I really do feel like my body is blowing up. Presumably this is a result of so many years of stress and semi-starvation on my body, but I'm already well within the "normal" BMI range and heading rapidly toward the high end. I am not binging or purging at all, just trying to be reasonable about what I eat and make healthy, sane choices.
I'm feeling really frustrated about what feels like a massive weight gain in the past few months, especially because mathematically it doesn't compute. However, I know that a big part of recovery can sometimes mean weight fluctuations and water retention. I guess I'm just really surprised because I am by no means anywhere near underweight, yet still my body seems to want to hold on to everything so hard.

What is recommended for recovery from exercise addiction? 

How do you deal with the weight gain?

What helps best when struggling for 10+ years and goning through multiple recoveries? Especially for those recovering well into adulthood (I'm close to 30 years old)?

I really appreciate any advice. I haven't been able to find much information on what to expect on my recovery from exercise addiction.

Kind thanks for those of you who have taken the time to read and respond to my post. Your comments mean so much to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Is there such a thing as "overeating" in AN recovery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 20:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey everyone, I was thinking about writing a long post about my background, but I find it better to just divide it into a TL;DR post.

Point 1: I love food

Point 2: I'm afraid of eating too much food

Point 3: I'm underweight and was told by my parents and a doctor to gain more weight

Point 4: I'm eating a lot, but just not quite enough to gain weight. I know I can eat more and more, but I'm afraid I'll go off the deep end. I'm still afraid of food (counting calories) even though I'm consuming a lot more than I used to.

Point 5: I've been following this trend of "weight gain" for about 2 months, but my weight has been stagnant/slowly declining for the last year and I have yet to see any progress.

Point 6: My dad is overweight and I fear that I will become like him if I keep following this lifestyle.

Question: Is there such a thing as "overeating" in AN recovery? I've been trying to pinpoint the perfect number of calories for me to eat, but I'm completely ignoring my hunger cues and am avoiding sweets because of it. I feel like I'm living a healthier life, but I'm not sure if I'll ever make any progress this way.

Question 2: If I do go off the deep end and finally start gaining weight, will I be able to stop? Will I be able to slow down the weight gain once I reach a healthy BMI, or will I gain a new eating disorder and become overweight? I want food so much right now that I feel like I'll get addicted once I start eating food carelessly again.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I am scared of my restrictive behaviors and I want to get help - where do I start? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 22:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A little background I am 18 year old female and have struggled with my body ever since I was 13. I am currently underweight. I didn't want to admit that I am sick, but it's time to face my fears. I hate/love my body. 

Some days are really good for me I will eat a normal 3 meals and a couple snacks, but other days I will only have maybe one meal and drink a lot of coffee and this will go on for a couple weeks. I had my first accident of not eating and passing out. It scared me a lot and I realized I need help. That lasted a couple days and now I am back to hardly eating anything. I came to this site for help and to see if any others have been in my situation before.

What is the best first step for me to take towards getting help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: SO with ED and depression wants to start exercising with me - Not sure if it's a good idea? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 15:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My SO has an eating disorder and depression - she wants to start running in order to "get in shape". However, she is already slightly underweight and I'm afraid running would push her to a dangerously low weight. 

Beyond that, I'm afraid she wouldn't know where to stop. On the other hand, exercising is often listed as a great way to help with depression and would probably help boost her self confidence. We go on walks together fairly often, but I'm not sure if it counts as exercise enough to her - she really wants to run. 

I want to do whatever I can to help her with the depression, but at the same time I don't want to make the eating disorder worse. 

I would really appreciate any other advice you guys could give me as well in order to help. Thank you in advance.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sharing: My Interior Design senior thesis on a Recovery Center </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 23:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thought you guys might be interested in my senior thesis on a Eating Disorder Recovery Center. We did 6 months of research (which I came to you guys with some questions), and 3 months of designing. Thank you so much for your help!

[Here's a link to my thesis on issuu](http://issuu.com/heathergaboury8/docs/thesis_book_final)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Advice/support about healthy weight loss </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 23:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to post the following to gain some advice or insight about healthy dieting for someone prone to ED behavior.

I've never had a full-blown eating disorder, but I've been unhappy with my body/weight for as long as I can remember. In my early teens, I began using some really unhealthy restrictive eating habits, working out daily and always monitoring the scale. I forced myself out of these habits in high school, because I saw a documentary about anorexia that scared me shitless.

I'm 22 now, and a bit overweight after college (though definitely still at a healthy weight). I've gotten really into the gym and want to trim down in a healthy manner, but every time I start to lose some weight I'm tempted to "speed it up" via not eating. It's so easy to slip into unhealthy restrictive eating.

Is it impossible diet/lose weight in a healthy way once you've got an ED kind of mindset? Does anyone have any tips for how I can healthily diet without it being so triggering? If not, support is welcome as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I am not well, but I don't "look sick." How do I know if I'm sick enough for help? How do I stop feeling like an impostor? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 02:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a 29yo female at a healthy weight. I've recently realized I've been using food and restriction as coping mechanisms since my childhood, and my situation is getting progressively worse.

A year ago I noticed I had put on a lot of weight after an injury had prevented me from walking (or leaving my house, really) for 2 months. I started dieting immediately, lost some of the weight I intended to lose in a healthy manner, then began restricting a lot. I restricted to an unhealthy amount for some weeks, before starting to binge. This was last february; come march, I was bingeing and purging on a regular basis, generally at least a couple times a day (sometimes as much as 4 or 5 times). I managed to start restricting again for 3 weeks, then skipping meals, then fasting for a couple of days at a time. And then the b/ping came back. I'm now trying to at least avoid purging, but I feel sick all of the time and I'm so scared to gain back weight I feel like (no kidding) killing myself.

On the outside, though, I don't look sick. I'm a very normal, average woman, on the high end of a normal bmi. I feel unworthy of help when so many people with "serious" eating disorders are so much thinner than I am. I feel like an impostor, and I'm too ashamed of my fatness to ask for help. I don't have the resources to look into counseling, and there are no free services available for this type of issues in my country (that i know of), but even if there were, I could never bring myself to be subjected to ridicule because I complain about purging and restricting when I'm not particularly thin.

So far I've admitted to my problem with only one person close to me, who urged me to seek help, but I can't. I just can't. I feel hopeless and ashamed of myself. I see mysellf as a disgusting glutton without an ounce of self control, and a part of me still mantains (despite the evidence to the contrary) that I should be able to recover by myself, in secret. That I should be able to just "turn it off".

I guess this came out as an incoherent rambling, so, to cut it short...

**Is there a meter to judge if someone is sick enough to deserve help?**

**If yes, do I have a chance of resolving my issues by myself and move on without becoming a joke for some professional looking to help real sufferers?**

Thank you in advance for your help. (Sorry for any mistake- english is not my native language.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: What strategies have helped prevent you from bingeing in poisonous food environments? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 21:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 22/f, recently diagnosed with BED, and in a very peculiar situation that involves near-unavoidable contact with many of my trigger foods. I am currently on a cycling journey with 28 other young adults across the country. Our team feeds us breakfast, lunch, and dinner, and many of the foods are ones that require a lot of self discipline for me to be around. We eat meals as a team. Because of this, I've had three total binges (each progressively worse than the others) on this trip thus far-- and want to hear from you all- what has worked for you when you've been put in environments around your binge foods -- to prevent from bingeing? I buy greens regularly to increase satiety and to round off my meals, as well as leave the eating area when I'm done. Anything helps! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: What kind of treatment for the uninsured? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 16:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm fairly certain I have an ED (I think it to be AN). My entire life I've always been a picky eater but as of this moment I've started to notice that it has cost me relationships, as soon as some acquaintances found out eating habits I would hide from them only eating in isolated places as to not be judged. I am extremely skinny and have lost whatever muscle I used to have. I've noticed an increase of hair growth (everywhere but on the top of my hair which has actually started to recede a lot), dry skin, but most importantly I seldomly have an appetite and when I do it makes me feel noxious to eat.

Anyways I'm a baller on a budget and don't have an insurance. My family has some money but they aren't very convinced (when you have been around me for most of my life and never thought to mention "Hey, maybe you're AN" it makes sense that you were only aware as I was). 

Just looking for some advice and maybe an idea as how much 30 day inpatient was for those of you that had it?

What other suggestions for helping myself? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I need advice on if I should seek counseling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 20:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
I've never been diagnosed with ED but I've had some nasty bouts with anxiety and depression. Currently I'm trying desperately to gain weight as my husband and I are trying to conceive, and it has been impossibly difficult. 

I've never eaten much and it is generally very healthfully. However, I tend to just not eat. In December, after some difficult marriage troubles, I became very underweight. I've gained some weight, but am still underweight. 

Whenever I eat I feel physically sick.  Understandably that makes me not want to consume the necessary calorie/day diet I need to put on weight. 

I've been to my GP and they can find nothing wrong with me. My husband has suggested I try counseling for an eating disorder. 
However, I am not afraid of gaining weight-if I could snap my fingers and be my goal of a healthy weight, I would. But I feel as if I have a hangover every time I eat. 

Do you think I should seek ED counseling? Do you think it could be a benefit (that perhaps this is psychosomatic) or since I don't have the accompanying mental symptoms that it would be a waste? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: In Los Angeles and Starting an EDA Meeting. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 15:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
There are not a lot of Eating Disorder 12 step groups on Los Angeles and being a 12 Step guy, support groups don't do it for me and OA doesn't either.

Does Anyone else want to start a Eating Disorders Anonymous Meeting in Los Angeles?

Has anyone started a group like this elsewhere and how did it go?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Am I on the verge of developing an eating disorder? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 11:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I'm a 20 year old female. I'd really like some advice about whether or not I have an ED. I don't particularly want to talk to my mom about it unless it's serious, because she's told me she had an ED when she was my age and would probably freak out. (She is a wonderful mother.)

Basically, I'm just terrified of gaining weight. I weighed a little more than average two years ago and lost that, and that really isn't enough. I cry thinking about my body and I log the calories on everything I eat. I restrict my calories greatly but then will feel bad about myself and eat a lot, then restrict, etc. I work out almost everyday, though I still feel like I'm not at the right weight. I do not purge.

If someone asked me what the worst thing that could happen to me was, I'd say gaining weight (disregarding anything happening to my family).

I am at a healthy weight for my height, so can I have an eating disorder? Or is this just a matter of a bad self-esteem?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to talk to a male friend with suspected ED? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 23:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My partner (M) and I (F) suspect that his roommate (22M) has bulimia. He tries to cover the sounds by briefly turning on the shower or the sink. I also suspect that he has used some type of laxative (some red liquid?) as he offered it when my partner had indigestion. 

He has dark circles under his eyes, gaunt face, usually wears baggy clothes, and has lost a lot of weight. My partner has tried to talk to his roommate about it, but he has always denied it. I'm worried that if no one talks to him about it now, it will never be addressed. 

He is a Latino, first-gen college student with little financial resources - how do I approach him about this? Should I approach him? I've known him for 4 years and we're friends, but really only surface level. I don't want to ignore this problem, but I don't know how to approach it. I'd appreciate any advice. Thank you so much for your help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How can I help my sister who is relapsing? My parents say they've given up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 21:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To preface, both my sister and I have been going through weight problems and were frequently shamed by our parents as we were growing up due to our weight. 

My sister has always been fairly skinny. She was an athlete in high school and used to exercise frequently. When she left high school it took a turn for the worst. She stopped eating a lot because, from what she told me, many of her peers would tease her about how she ate a lot of food. her condition has been deteriorating and last summer, she actually attempted suicide. She was sent to a help facility. She was eventually released from after she told them what they wanted to hear. 

After she got out, she started making an effort to intake enough food, but when she left for college in the fall, she fell back into her old habits of not eating.Throughout the year, my parents have been trying to help her, but she gets angry with them and confides with me about how oppressive they are to her. I've tried to tell her that maybe my parents are right, but when I do, she becomes angry that I'm against her. 

She came home this week for my high school graduation and seeing her state made my heart sink. She looks very sick and underweight and she looked extremely weak. My parents recently told me they had given up and had no idea what to do for her because she wouldn't ever listen to them. 

I'm really concerned for her health and I really don't want to give up on her because she's my sister and I love her. Anyone have any ideas on what I can do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My girlfriend thinks she's recovered, but she's not--how can I help her realize this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 06:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My gf went into self-guided recovery for her anorexia around the time we got together (3 years ago), and she considers herself recovered now. She doesn't have the eating disorder she had before, that much is true--she's now a healthy weight, and she claims she doesn't consciously restrict. And she no longer identifies as someone with an eating disorder, which in itself is a big step.

She still has unhealthy body image about 50% of the time, calling herself or specific body parts fat when she clearly isn't and they obviously aren't. If I try to reassure her that she's not fat, she tells me she doesn't believe me and that my opinion of it doesn't matter. If I try to get her to compare her body to other peoples' bodies to show that she's not fat (ie, "you don't think I'm fat, right? well I'm bigger than you, so you're not fat either, then, right?") she says the way she evaluates her body has nothing to do with the way she evaluates others'. She also claims that her assessment of herself as fat or not has nothing to do with her self-esteem/sense of self-worth now. I don't know if I believe that or not.

She also still exhibits behaviors, particularly during times of stress. In fact, I might go so far as to say it seems like her eating disorder resurfaces during times of stress. She claims she "can't eat" when she's stressed out. She frequently skips meals and/or eats "meals" that nutritionally and calorically don't qualify as a full meal, and she'll get mad at me if I try to tell her it's not enough. Again, she claims that she's not restricting or even trying to lose weight. I can always tell when she hasn't had enough to eat, because she's very irritable with me and mentally slow/foggy, but she's completely unreceptive to any feedback in that regard. I know that she used her eating disorder as a coping method for stress/anxiety and depression, and it's my theory that she unconsciously falls back on these coping mechanisms now, but can't see it because she's convinced herself that her eating disorder is over.

She doesn't count calories or monitor her intake or weight anymore, but she's really not as recovered as she thinks she is, and I really worry about her. Since she gets mad when I voice my concerns about it, how can I gently guide her to the realization that she's got a lot of recovering left to do?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How can I help my girlfriend push past her fears? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 01:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, my girlfriend is fighting to recover from anorexia, but she's having some really severe trouble, and I can't find anything very helpful in the previous discussions. So, I was hoping for some advice.

She's 23, suffering from anorexia, shes currently at a very low BMI. She recovered (physically) once before in a programme at the hospital, but immediately returned to low weight and unhealthy behaviours. 

She talks all the time about how much she wants to recover, but is paralysed by the fear of taking too much food, eating abnormally, becoming fat, and she say that the voice in her head is too strong no matter how hard she tries. Right now her and I are living with her mother in the hope that it could be a safe space for her to recover.

But recently, I've learned that she is obsessed with her (very thin) mothers portion sizes, and body shape. At every meal she eats less than she wants to (this she admits) because her mother has eaten far less than her. She finds herself unable to take eat something if her mother isn't eating one too. She also obsesses over what her mother eats when she is away.

She's very conscious and rational about the fact that she needs to become healthy, but she is having terrible problems actually doing any of the things she talks about

How can I help her push past her fears? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to listen to my girlfriend who had an eating disorder? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 01:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, my girlfriend is 19 and i'm 21. We're far away from each other at the moment so it is a little more difficult. i've known my girlfriend for a long time but we have been together for a year as last month. She had an eating disorder through high school, she would starve herself, make herself throw up and often pass out. She went to programs and for a few years there was a lot of frustration among her family because of her eating disorder. She is feeling better about herself now a days, she doesn't do any of the behavior which caused the eating disorder but often she will be hard on herself for eating something bad which i can easily talk to her about and make her understand one thing doesn't change everything. Often she tries to talk to me about how bad she feels about herself a week before her period and she'll 1 or 2 days where she is down and she dislikes aspects of her body through out the day. She tries to tell me what she hates but i just get so frustrated because i can't do anything. I get so so angry (not at her but at the fact that she hates how she looks sometimes.) I don't want to get angry anymore when she tells me this stuff, i just love her so much and i can't help it. How should i go about helping her when she is feeling like this? How should i go about listening and what is the appropriate way to react?

Thank you, i just really want to help and i don't want to continue my behavior because it's not helping anyone.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Is it ok to make my daughter clean up her messes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 01:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 15 year old daughter has developed an eating disorder over the past few months. Aside from the things the hospital recommended (not let her go into the bathroom 30 minutes after she eats) what are some other things I can do?

It seems like every time I go into the bathroom, there is puke on the floor, or all over the back of the toilet seat/rim, or in towels. Is it wrong of me to make her clean it all up and punish her for not cleaning it up if she doesn't? I am not sure how to go about this, but I am getting tired of cleaning up vomit everyday.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Cold Turkey on Exercise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 11:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I have been in recovery for an eating disorder and seeing a therapist since March. We have made some good progress but I realised I transferred my control from food to exercise. For the last few weeks I have been working out many hours per day, running many km most days and binging as a result. 

I had a bit of a breakdown on Sunday and having seen the psychologist yesterday we decided I should take a week off. (At least). I am petrified.

I haven't done any exercise for 2 full days and I feel so guilty. The voices in my head are strong and telling me I'm a lazy so and so and I'm worthless and telling me not to eat because I don't deserve it. It's day 3 today and I feel so bad and this is so hard. 

Any advice ? any stories / experiences / thoughts would really help....
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How can I help my friend? Her parents don't want her to seek help! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 03:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To begin, I'm not exactly good with words, so I apologize if this is written poorly and I hope I still make my point very clear. 

My friend has been dealing with (I'm very new to this subreddit so I don't know the acronym) compulsive purging for about two years now. She's had a long history of trying to go cold turkey on and off, but that really hasn't been working for her, as you might think. 

She's talks to me every day about how she feels like it is spiraling out of control and getting much worse and I'm getting really concerned for her. The worse part is, we are both high-school aged kids, so the help she can seek is very limited.

Her parents have a very stubborn and gross mindset that mental illnesses like depression or eating disorders (and even allergies) are just people overreacting and don't actually exist. She outright told her parents about what she has been going through, and her parents told her that they not only don't want to spend the money, but they'd be embarrassed to have their daughter seek help for something like that. On top of all that, she's undergoing surgery in a few months, and she was told (by her parents) that the surgery could be effected by her eating condition. 

She's very scared, but she's also very timid. She told me she'd much rather keep purging than confronting her parents. What can I do for her as a concerned friend?

TLDR: My friend is a compulsive purger, but her parents don't want her to seek help. How I can help her?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: What kind of ED do I have? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 03:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am over weight and hate it. I decided to start losing weight and in addition to eating healthier and more moderately, I have started to throw up after "bigger" meals.

I am not anorexic, I don't binge like a bulemic. Is there a word for me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seeking Study Participants, Harvard University </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 01:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are a Harvard University research team currently working on a study looking at people who harm themselves. The primary goal of the study is to better understand what kinds of thoughts and feelings motivate different types of self-harm, including intentional overdoses with and without wanting to die as well as other types of self-harm without wanting to die. We are interested in recruiting people who use this website to participate in our research study. Participation is completely voluntary. We are recruiting worldwide. If you are interested in participating, you will be asked to complete an online screener to see if you qualify to participate. If you qualify, you will complete an online survey lasting 30-60 minutes. The study will take place online you will be compensated $10 in online gift cards to Amazon. A few important things to know about the study are:

~ The study includes questions and images regarding self-harm as well as other unpleasant images. **Some people may feel that these images are disturbing and may find them to be triggering.**

~All information collected will be kept confidential.

~Participation is completely voluntary.

~If you start to participate and decide you no longer feel comfortable or you are no longer interested, you can end your participation without any penalty or punishment.

~We will provide links to treatment resources at the end of the study.
        
~This study will include only participants who are 18 years and older.

Please [send us a private message](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose/?to=WebGameStudy) if you are interested in participating. Once you contact us, we will send you a link to a screening questionnaire to see if you qualify. If you qualify, you will be provided with more information about the study and a link to the assessment if you are interested in participating.

---

Edit: If you participate and find any discrepancies between this post and what you do, please notify the mods on this subreddit.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not diagnosed, but struggle with body issues and I'm terrified of gaining weight. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 17:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a 16 year old male, and for the past year I've had significant struggles with body image. For my entire childhood I had been heavier than everyone else, but not overweight to the point that I needed to lose any. 

However, over the summer I began to restrict my eating in an effort to lose weight. It helped a little, but I lost a massive amount of weight when I got the flu and couldn't eat for a week. Over the course of a few months with the combined restrictive eating and illness, I lost a significant amount of weight in a few months. I was aware that this weight loss was unhealthy but I finally felt okay with my body when really I shouldn't. 

My physician and my parents told me that my weight was in a really low percentile for my age and that if I didn't gain more weight it would be bad news if I got sick again. For most of the schoolyear though I became even more obsessed with nutrition labels and calorie counting and not gaining weight. I literally had to look at the nutrition facts of EVERYTHING I ate but I thought I was still eating healthy.

 I started to realize the damage I was doing to my body though around March when I needed to count the number of calories I ate for a health assignment. I forced myself to eat more than I usually did but still clocked in below my recommended amount. On a regular day I was probably getting significantly less than that. 

I've seen the errors of my ways and I'm now eating more and I'm eating 3 meals a day almost every day. However, I'm still terrified of losing weight. My parents want me to gain some weight but it sounds repulsive to me. 

Even though I would be a healthier weight the thought of being fatter sounds horrible to me. I need advice on how I can accept my body and how to cope when I start to gain the weight back?

 Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Help with sister </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 19:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Need advice on what to do about my sister who is both anorexic and bulimic. She's at a dangerous weight and mentally she isn't the same person. I've tried talking to her but she shuts off at any mention of her problem. She has 2 kids and I'm terrified of calling CPS, because either her ex will get them (absolute loser that can't take care of himself) or my parents (they drove her to this, we believe our mother has munchausens. plus she absolutely hates them and we are planning on moving out by august).

Other information- shes 31 and been dealing with this for a year at most. And she had this same problem when she was 16 -18? she was eventually placed in a live in rehab. So there's at least a 10 year gap where I don't believe she was suffering from these problems.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Can anyone recommend any free ebooks or resources (besides NEDA) to help me in my recovery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 17:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm getting married in a few months and going through various "life stressors" and feel like I'm beginning to relapse back.

Does anybody have any good places to get free ebooks or pdfs besides the generic NEDA, etc? I have several different hard copy books but would like to read them before going to bed on my iPad, while my fianc sleeps. 

Thanks so much in advance!! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Trying to help a woman that I love. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 02:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've been looking around the internet for some help but I figured I should have started here in the first place. This may be a little wordy but please bare with me.

Background: I'm in love with a woman with an ED. She is the most compassionate, intelligent, and beautiful person that I know and she has been struggling with her body image and eating habits for at least five or six years now. We're both in our mid-twenties and we go back about 9 years. We've lived and worked together for a year before college and then fell somewhat out of touch until about a year ago. We still tell each other everything and we are slowly rebuilding our relationship and working back to a point where we are best friends and lovers. I'm going to marry her one day. I've known about her struggle for a while and I'm still somewhat lost on how to help her.

She has a pretty messy family life and has fallen out with her dad and one of her siblings. She has also dealt with depression.

What I know about her ED (please correct me if I'm misinformed or just being ignorant on something, I'm trying to learn as much as possible): She is very upfront about her struggle. She fully acknowledges that she has an ED and has sought help in the past but just moved to another city and she's hesitant talk to any professionals about it. It has been at least a year since she has last talked to a therapist. Based off of what I've seen and what we've talked about, I know that she is extremely unhappy with her appearance. She doesn't look unhealthily thin but I know that the physical and psychological toll can be hidden. She was never heavy, overweight, or anything resembling that. She regularly under-eats or skips meals which seems like anorexia(?) and consistently talks about how much she hates her body. She regularly tells me that she needs to lose weight and sometimes says it is because she wants to impress me. That freaking kills me.

Sorry about the extended background info, but I want to make sure I give enough context before I ask a whole bunch of questions.

So here are my biggest questions:

1. **Where is the line between pushing her too hard to get help and letting her do things at her own pace?** I don't want to push her away and seem callous but I'm scared that inaction will become too comfortable and nothing will change. I was pushing very hard for her to see someone again and she told me to stop until she at least moved to her new place (she just got there this week).

2. **How do I show her that I love her body without seeming patronizing?** She is absolutely beautiful, top to bottom. I mean drop-dead gorgeous. I love everything about her body but I'm worried that she thinks I'm trying to fight the ED and not genuinely attracted to her.

3: **I'm a pretty skinny dude. Is my size making things worse?** She's both shorter and skinnier than me but I still think that she has this idea that a girlfriend should be significantly smaller than the boyfriend. I've actually been gaining a few pounds intentionally to see if it helps.

Thanks in advance for any advice, resources, etc. I've been really torn up about this whole thing and I'm just looking for some perspective. Any advice helps.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Do I (15m) have an eating disorder? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 02:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a history of depression, including lots of self harm and multiple suicide attempts. Around October of last year I had been without hurting myself in any way for about a year and three months, when I started self-harming again. I'll leave out the details, but I ended up being admitted to a mental hospital.

After leaving, I became very conscious of my weight (I've always been sort of fat), and I restricted how much I ate. Between November and now, I've lost a lot of weight as a result of eating very little most days, and not eating at all some days. I've never purged, but I've tried.

I weigh myself almost everyday, and I get really upset when I noticed I'm up a pound or two for whatever reason. I'm at a healthy weight now but I'm still trying to lose weight, and I'm still eating very little except when I'm around other people for an extended period of time so I'm expected to eat.

Do I have an eating disorder? Or, I guess, does it seem likely?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Is this an ED or am I just convincing myself it is? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 14:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

I'm 22F, with a history of mental health issues (anxiety, self-esteem, depression) and a long term chronic condition. I'm fairly short and used to be, in my teenage years, pretty rounded. My parents said it was puppy fat, but I think they knew different.

When I was about 17/18 I started changing how I ate. I said it was because of health stuff. I'd eat really small, inexpensive lunches. My argument was that I was allowed to keep all my left over dinner money. People started saying how much better I looked. I kept pushing for more weight loss.

Aged 18 I was diagnosed with an anxiety disorder. I was having daily panic attacks over being less than perfect. About failing. About letting people down. I started running: I'd run to reward myself, to punish myself, to break the monotony of life, to have a break from work. Sometimes I wouldn't eat properly before running, or after running. Aged 21 I was diagnosed with depression. Again, fueled by my self-loathing, my insecurities etc. Age 22 I was diagnosed with a chronic medical condition: I spent time at home, being fed by my mother, living on steroids. I gained weight. I was finally able to move out and get my life back in order.

But I've found myself falling back into the same habits. I don't binge, I don't purge, I'm a healthy weight for my height. But I feel like food is one of the constants I have. When my day is bad, I know that food is something I can do for myself. That I can control it.

I work in a highly stressful field. Things go wrong daily, hourly. It's a field where you can't be perfect, because perfect doesn't exist. There are too many variables to be perfect. But I find myself striving for perfect. I can't be perfect because of my anxiety, because of my job, because of my depression, because of my chronic condition. But maybe people will like me because I'm skinny. At least being not as fat as I was will make my life seem more in order.

I weigh myself regularly, get sad if I eat too much. Get sad if I gain weight (even if it isn't real weight, it's that you've just drank a pint of water weight).

I'm going to make an appointment to see a counselor about my anxiety and depression (I've realized that bouncing from relationship to relationship to make me happy isn't good enough). But I don't know whether to talk about food. It sounds stupid, but I don't know if I really have a problem or if I have convinced myself that this is an issue. That I am actually just a normal, anxious 22 year old who just wants to look and feel better, or if their is something more to it.

(To add to this, if my work thinks that I'm mentally unstable, they take me off the job. Yay for another anxiety inducing issue!)

TLDR: anxious, depressed 22F, not sure if I've actually got a problem or that I've talked myself into thinking it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Help phrasing support for my cousin? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 11:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shes's(16) been admitted to hospital for anorexia and self harm. I'm(20f) wanting to give her some moral support but I'm unsure how.

I was raped by our cousin when I was 6, then by the next door neigbour at 15, and I've been self harming since I was about 10-11. I don't think she knows any of that as our family has a very hush hush mentality about anything bad.

I haven't seen or talked to her for a few years, but I want to be able to give her some support if she feels so inclined. I want to be able to tell her that I can relate to how she's feeling, but I don't want to make it about me, so I'm unsure how to even mention the eating disorder, as I've heard many people don't want to even hear those two words. How do I go about writing something supportive without stepping on any toes? Any help is greatly appreciated.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> California Woman's Descent Into Anorexia, in Her Own Words - ABC News. Trigger warning images, numbers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 16:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Survey: Latina college and graduate women wanted to participate in dissertation study on eating disorders! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 02:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Hello,

I am a Latina graduate student completing my dissertation on the topic of disordered eating behaviors, current relationship styles, parent-child relationships, and perception of the thin ideal portrayed in the media. I am specifically looking for **Latina female college and graduate students** to participate in my study, which will help expand the (currently very limited) research available in the area of eating disorders in the Latina/o community. I would very much appreciate your support in sharing my dissertation survey information! I would be happy to provide you with more information regarding this study. It has been approved by Pacific University's Institutional Review Board (IRB).

If you are a self-identified Latina woman who is 18 years or older and are currently enrolled as an undergraduate or graduate student at a college or university, please help me out with my dissertation research! Clicking on the attached link will take you to a brief (15-20 minute) survey. Im interested in looking at the relationship between the way you relate to others in close relationships, your relationship with your mother or female caregiver during childhood, eating behaviors, and your perception of media messages about body image ideals.

At the end of the survey you can enter into a drawing to win one of five $20.00 Starbucks gift card! The results of this survey are anonymous and your responses will be kept confidential.
Please share this on your page or with friends that may be interested. Thanks!

http://edu.surveygizmo.com/s3/1725287/Dissertation-Survey

Please note: For those of you already visiting this site, a recruitment post has been created to provide you with more information about this study. When accessing this site to review the study details, it is recommended that you first review the policies of this site. We want you to know that while we, as researchers, will not have access to anyones data that uses our page nor do we have any plan for collecting that data, it is possible that this site may be collecting that data. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: self-help (books, web resources) for binge eating? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 00:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello :) I want to start trying to tackle my occasional binge eating and restricting, and I was wondering if anyone has any good resources they can let me know about? Like a good book or website that guides you through how to deal with binge eating?

Reason why; I gained a lot of weight last year when I was very depressed. I just ate far too much all the time to cope with my depression. The extra weight ended up having physical impacts on me in that my hormone cycles are all off and not working as they should - to the point that I got paranoid and suicidal one week each month. :(

I've made a start, I've lost some weight and am feeling better. I'm still borderline obese though and I want to lose weight and learn how to eat healthily for my health, because everyone in my family is obese and sick and I can't let that happen to me.

So, I've done okay. Since march, I've been eating better than usual. Even if it's only making small changes here and there. I'm cooking more and consuming healthier food. But; I had a lot of binging episodes. Probably at least one weekly.  I struggled to eat my meals yesterday (but I still did!) and I'm worried the restricting/binging pattern I had as a 14-18 year old will return. I never got help, because I was always overweight, and none of the doctors believed me when I said I had trouble with food, and that my trouble was restricting, not the binging.

Most information I have seen is just restriction or binge/purge type disorders - neither of which apply to me. So I would be incredibly grateful if you can share your resources for binge eating - any useful books, worksheets, or websites would be great :) It's also really hard to tell what's good and what's not when your new; so I'd love to hear what has worked for all of you :) tl;dr I have worked on most of my body image and self perception issues through therapy - i feel better about myself, mentally healthier and now i'm trying to lose the weight i gained when binge eating. i'm doing well so far, and am eating healthier than ever but i notices some old binge/restrict patterns coming back. I would like some self help resources if you know any :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Is there anything that I can I do that'll help me eat normally? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 15:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
To give a brief summary of what's happened to me. For most of high school I'd been on the thinner side (probably slightly underweight) caused from the fact I'd spent so much on my computer gaming and consequently skipped meals inadvertantly.

Towards the last few years of **secondary school my mother passed from cancer**, I lost the few friends I had and fell in depression. The depression hadn't got really bad, but I only barely passed my final year. I had nowhere near the scores to get into university, but I didn't know, and still really don't, have any idea what I want to do.

For whatever reason I decided to be healthier (I wasn't even unhealthy to begin with, I just didn't get out, and was use to years of missing meals because of gaming to early hours, sleeping in, and so on), but since I knew nothing about doing so, I started walking, then later running everyday. It helped with my mood regulation a lot, but because of my poor knowledge I under-ate and only ate how I thought was healthy.

Since I'd been at a lower weight for a few years, you can imagine **my weight plummeted**
without me even noticing. I suffered from a lot of the psychical symptoms but hadn't attributed it to the weight loss. I hadn't noticed the weight loss itself and was used to family members commenting on my weight because being thinner before losing a lot of weight. But on the coming Easter I over-indulged, which I wasn't worried or stressed, or anything about, I'd done it every Easter that I can remember as it was special since I never had the chance to eat treats at home because of my sister's allergies.

But I think **because I was so underweight that it threw me into months of binge eating** everyday, causing havoc on my digestive system, extreme bloating and brought back my depression. It scared me so badly because I had no idea what was happening. I just spent months in anxiety and physical pain. But because I hadn't had any ED related thoughts or anxiety, I didn't attempt to make up for the over eating in any way.

I hadn't seen a psychologist in over a year (I'd seen two over the two years prior), but went to see a different one because I had no idea what was happening to me. While I don't feel she helped that much (didn't help to build a healthy relationship with food, or eating normally or anything), it allowed me to vent a bit (but didn't quell my fears in why I was over eating) but lead me to the path of my current job I've had for about a year.

The over eating stopped once I got on track with a part time job, but only (which I didn't realise at the time) was because I went back to two meals a day because of my hours always being early and thus I went to bed early missing dinner.

So as you can imagine again, I lost all the weight again (which I didn't even notice again, which surprises me because it scared me when I saw images of myself so gaunt). Although Easter came around again and I'm now in the same predicament again. Luckily this time I did did research and quickly find out why it was happening, and how much I had needed to eat versus how much I had been eating.

Which brings me to now. I've been binge eating everyday since Easter, par one or two days where I couldn't eat or was only able to eat one meal because I felt so sick and had constant diarrhea. I'm struggling really hard to get myself to eat three meals with snacks all of which reaching the intake I needed (so not to undereat). I'd unknowingly restricted certain foods when I was underweight only because I thought they were unnecessary or unhealthy. But knowing what I know now, that there isn't anything unhealthy or bad, that isn't all moderation (which made sense with every other part of my life, helping my thoughts and mood regulation to do with my depression).

But **the binge eating now is putting my job at risk** because I'm calling in sick too much and I'm worried my boss thinks I'm going out, not actually sick, etc. I'm gaining weight so quickly I'm worried I won't able to come in because I won't fit in my clothes anymore. **I'm in constant physical pain** and **really anxious** and **I feel like I could slip back into depression**. I'm angry and I yell at my father a lot. He's the only one I've told everything I've been through.

I'm scared what's going to happen. Getting a job for the first time helped me so much, with the social aspect, confidence and money. Most people got their jobs in high school, and later went to university. But I finished poorly, which didn't worry me too much I just focused on the next step which lead me to the job. But I scared that's going to all fall apart. I'm trying to work on getting a hobby and finding friends after not having any at all for years but the binge eating has thrown me over.

I'm really happy I've regained the weight back, not only because I like the way I appear more, but because it's brought back my libido and I feel so much more energetic. **But I can't seem to eat normally** no matter what I try and the stress and pain is excruciating, especially since it's everyday.

I don't know if this is even the right place to ask this because **I don't know if I've ever suffered from an ED**, but I've noticed a lot of similarities in the physical symptoms, but never had any disordered thoughts or was weight/body image conscious. The only thing I think I might of had was orthorexia, I don't even know if it's considered an ED.

If I don't do anything, is the binge eating going to taper off eventually? Is what's happening to me a normal part of returning to eating normally? (I've read from those who've had anorexia and had the same thing happen to them during recovery, but I don't know if it's the same for me) **What can I do that'll help me not binge or restrict?**

(I'll just mention in case it's important, but I'm a male).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I have been binging and purging for a year and I don't think I want to tell anyone. I need ideas for how to get help (in Canada). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 05:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over the past year, or maybe more, I have been binging and purging. It's difficult for me to admit, but I understand that it is what it is. It's beginning to consume my thoughts, and I fear for what might happen.

What I'm wondering is, what are my options. I don't really want to "come out" to anyone. 

What avenues are available to me (specifically in Canada)?

Thank you for your time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Triggers at Home </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 04:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hiya. So, I was diagnosed with severe EDNOS last year and had a really rough go of it - but I've been on the recovery track since about February and today I'm just trying to maintain my goal weight. I have up days and down days, and a few things still set me off sometimes (eating in front of others, eating certain foods, etc), but all in all I can feel my relationship with food getting close to normal-ish again.

I'm home from University for the summer, and that means being around my parents. My mom has a history of anorexia and eats very, very little. She also makes a big show of when she is full after small meals (puffing out her cheeks, talking about how stuffed she is and how she could never eat any more) and comments about what others are eating (like if a portion looks large or if something is unhealthy). All of this happens more often when she is stressed - and, just our luck, things are stressful at her job and at home right now for reasons that I won't explain here.

As you've probably guessed by now, her behavior REALLY bothers me and makes me anxious about food. I feel fat and uncontrolled around her. I feel guilty for eating at all - today I'm pretty sure she skipped dinner, and we all went out for froyo after but she refused to have some. Half of me is running around in circles in a nervous panic, vowing to restrict better tomorrow, and the other half is trying to just stay calm and on-track.

Any advice for how to handle this? Should I talk to her, or just make more of an effort to avoid her at meal times? How do you deal with a close friend/family member with eating habits that trigger your own ED?

Many thanks.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 16:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful posts:

[Recovery sharing, Zip Lock bags and other techniques](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2dc4rb/recovery_sharing_ziploc_bags_and_other_things/)

[Self-Esteem](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/search?q=self+esteem restrict_sr=on)

[Hunger Hormones](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2f0p7y/anorexia_to_binging_its_not_about_will_power_its/)

[Brain over Binge, excellent book and workbook](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/35697y/book_suggestion_for_bed_bulimia_brain_over_binge/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 16:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully [helpful posts](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/search?q=do+i+have+anorexia restrict_sr=on sort=relevance t=all). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Diagnosed, but doubting it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 15:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Due to some pretty heavy physical and mental issues in the past 6 months, I've been going to doctors, psychologists, been put on anti-depressants, and finally today I was at a psychiatrist to make a diagnosis: He said depression and anorexia.

But I'm having doubts. It's true that I am very preoccupied with my weight, and that it's one of my primary goals to not gain weight - I'm very physically and mentally weak atm, so I've scaled back to have as few goals as possible, and I've settled on staying in school and keeping my weight under control (since I used to be morbidly obese). I used to have so many goals.

I don't think it's unreasonable to want to control my weight after all that work, and most slim women do control their weight, even if it doesn't require as much mental effort as it does for me.

The 'stress' it causes me might as well have been on something 
else, I don't feel like my emotional turmoil is because of food and weight, it just so happens to be one of the things I focus on right now. Like, I could have been perfectionist or obsessed with a number of other things, I would feel the same, but the diagnosis would be different.

So I feel like the anorexia diagnosis might be 'distracting' and misleading to the underlying cause of my physical and mental issues? I feel like as soon as the psychiatrist heard that I had lost a lot of weight, and did not want to gain any, he completely equated that to all my symptoms. He's asked me to write down everything I eat for 14 days. I don't know if he thinks that will prove anything?

Can doctors misdiagnose anorexia?

Could a restricted diet contribute to my mental and physical issues? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: BED Help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 13:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel as if I've tried everything as far as attempting recovery is concerned. I've been in therapy since I was an adolescent and I feel like I'm stuck in this vicious cycle of restricting, purging, and bingeing.

I went a year restricting. I lost so much weight I was on the verge of hospitalization. I was given a clinical diagnosis of malnourishment. Then I'd have occasions where I would finally break down and eat, and then subsequently I'd purge out of guilt.
Now I guess I'm what you would consider a normal weight, but I'm far from recovery. I'm completely obsessed with food, consumed be self-hatred, and an uncontrollable urge to eat. At times I eat to the point of being nauseous and bloated but will continue to eat anyway. It all feels so familiar, I've been going through this "cycle" for years now.

Restrict   purge. Then binge and binge and binge. I'm so sick of this, I feel like I've done every exercise, read every book, and quite frankly feel like I've exhausted all my efforts. I feel like I can't stop. Like I'll never have a healthy relationship with food. Sometimes I wonder if its even possible to recover from this. 

Does anyone have any advice/insight they could give? Anything would be greatly appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How often do you have to exhibit disordered behaviors before you know something is seriously wron </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 13:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Skipping one meal doesn't mean you have an ED. But what about purging? How often do you have to exhibit disordered behaviors before you know something is seriously wrong?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Do I have anorexia? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 13:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It started with just being self conscious about my weight. In 2012 when I moved to college, I started eating healthier since I was living with my aunt, so I lost weight. I've never been overweight, or even chubby, I was normal but I got thinner and people noticed it, which made me feel really good about myself. A year and a half later I moved to live alone and downloaded a calorie counting app, so I started losing weight consciously and willingly, just by counting the calories. My family and my boyfriend have told me that I look way too thin now, but when they say that I kind of feel good with myself, even though they intended to tell me I looked sick. Obviously none of them know that all this weight loss is intentional, and since my career demands me to stay up all night sometimes, I blame it on the stress. My concern here is, I've lost all the weight I planned to, but I'm afraid I could gain it back again so I keep eating small amounts of calories daily. I don't want to lose more weight, but I am really afraid of getting heavier again. I can't eat certain foods without worrying after or while I do so, and actually (Despite I know it's only mental) feeling my butt getting full of cellulite after I eat high-calorie food. I'm not happy with my body after all this weight loss, I'm only happy with the numbers. I wish I could care less about my food. I'm afraid to be actually anorexic, because I've heard you can have anorexia even if you don't look like you do. I sometimes eat a lot and then feel very bad about it. 

Do I need help? 

How to be happy with my body and not worry about my weight?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Helping Someone with an Eating Disorder: Advice for Parents, Family Members, and Friends </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 19:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 02:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful posts:

[Body image issues](https://www.nationaleatingdisorders.org/10-will-powers-improving-body-image)

[Pro-Ana sited and problems](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/s9411/do_you_know_anyone_who_has_ever_been_addicted_to/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 02:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful posts:

[Recovery sharing, Zip Lock bags and other techniques](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2dc4rb/recovery_sharing_ziploc_bags_and_other_things/)

[Hunger Hormones](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2f0p7y/anorexia_to_binging_its_not_about_will_power_its/)

[Brain over Binge, excellent book and workbook](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/35697y/book_suggestion_for_bed_bulimia_brain_over_binge/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 02:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful posts:

[Reasons to recover from NEDA](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2wte4j/nedawareness_week_three_reasons_why_you_should/)

[How to want to recover](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/21ktfa/request_how_can_i_start_wanting_to_recover/)

[reasons to recover](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1emjg9/post_request_reasons_to_recover/)



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woman who Battled Eating Disorders Leaves Legacy of Words </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 02:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I think I want to recover from my ED, but I have a hard time really feeling committed. How do I get unstuck? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 00:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all, I am struggling with finding the willingness to be committed to my ED recovery. I have suffered consequences both physically, emotionally and spiritually and have been through several treatment episodes. My first treatment episode was twelve years ago and my last was almost four and I am twenty five now. I am currently in a relapse and struggling to gain and maintain a healthy weight.

I feel completely stuck at this point. I think I want to get better. I feel horrible but still struggle with being completely willing to do what professionals suggest. More importantly, I am not sure how honest I can be with myself.

I still find myself getting defensive over things that are stupid and I think I lack the faith that I'll be completely okay. I have currently begun (re)attending a 12-step group for my ED and I see people who seem happy and willing but for some reason I don't believe that will be me- which is not rational.

What has been the catalyst in your willingness to move past resistance in dealing with your eating disorder? 

Is there something I can do to feel more ready and committed in recovery? 

Any words of wisdom please! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I have bulimia and I can't stop binging/purging even though I hate it. Techniques to control binges? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 00:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I technically have bulimia but honestly I see it more as a binge eating disorder because I honestly hate throwing up and i avoid it for as long as possible. 

I sense its more of a binge eating disorder because i can not literally help my self around food because i know i have a way to get rid of the food via throwing it up. It honestly disgusts me how hard it is to control my self i can go all day eating healthily and then its in the am's and there i find my self surrounded by plates and wrappers. 

How can I control my binges? I do not purge after normal meals, only when I binge, so I think I need techniques to prevent binges. 

How can I handle the urge to throw up after I binge?

 Thanks
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Is my ED the pinnacle of my issues or a result of my issues? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 01:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll keep it short as to not ramble on.

- I developed anorexia aged 15 after my brother's suicide

- After 5-6 months I transitioned onto bulimia, it was officially diagnosed and I was under mental health services. I was not at a healthy weight.

- For the last 8 years thereafter (I'm now 24) I've had lengths of time bulimia-free with lengthy relapses in continuous cycles, but I am a healthy weight

- Aged 19 I was diagnosed with a personality disorder

- I'm currently having a bulimia relapse which started in January

As I've grown older I've questioned why I was one of the few who develops disordered eating, and furthermore - was it because of my personality disorder or my trauma aged 15? Predestined or by chance of events?

I'm incredibly lonely, and suicidal. Ive struggled my whole life with making friends (most likely because of the personality disorder), my job is a very serious job, and demanding mentally and physically. I have a long term relationship but my other half has bipolar and it can be toxic at times. I also have a gym obsession. My SO has a demanding job which leaves me quite lonely. All of these things are relevant as my bulimia almost comforts me in my times of sadness and anxiety. On the flip side, knowing the seriousness of bulimia adds to my anxiety, but it's the only way I know to settle the rest of my negative feelings.

I've tried many prescription drugs over the years and I'm happy to cope without them, or at least try to. I've exhausted all therapy options, but I'm on the verge of blowing my lid.

I don't wanna be like this any more.

Will I ever break free from it without damaging all aspects of my life? How will I manage, and what could I do to help myself?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Trying to recover from anorexia-- how to not succumb to pro-ana sites and pressure from those around me? Seems impossible. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 17:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would really appreciate some support. 

I am girl from Russia battling with her anorexia. And it is so hard for me because in Russia the anorexia community is enormous and it is even considered to be beautiful. 

How can I not succumb to the pressure to be anorexic?

What do I do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Not diagnosed but obsessed with weight gain/food-is this a problem? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 13:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lost some weight after taking Zoloft for 6 months. Because of the crippling nausea and weight loss, I stopped taking the pills. 

I have been off of Zoloft for about 6 months, however my appetite never quite came back the way it was, and sometimes I experience lingering feelings of nausea. Does not hinder my ability to function though. 

I noticed that recently I've been overly concerned about gaining weight and am at a lower weight.

I do not eat breakfast, but usually eat something small once at work, and lunch later. I eat dinner occasionally however as my boyfriend is out of town and I hate cooking, I haven't really been eating dinner. And this is fine by me. I am pre-occupied by the size of certain body parts. I know that I look like a 12 year old because I have an extremely flat chest as well, so it can't possibly be appealing to those around me. BUT, I can't bring myself to eat more and gain weight. 

So, my question to those who think they may have an answer, is whether or not you think this is an issue. I do not count calories or have eating rituals, nor do I see fat in the mirror, but I am almost obsessive about food and what I do or do not eat. Usually I will restrict eating if I'm feeling depressed.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Relapsed and didn't eat for some time, started eating again made me sob </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 06:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have had anorexic tendencies for the past five years. I was officially diagnosed when I was hospitalized a year ago. Things got better, I wasn't "recovered", but eating a meal didn't count as a binge for me. Now. I'm worried I'm relapsing. I didn't eat for an extended amount of time, and after fainting, I decided to have some plain food, which made me sob. I'm becoming so afraid of eating, to a degree completely unfamiliar with me. Is this normal relapse behavior? What should I do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Considering intensive outpatient treatment. Is it worth going even if it means losing most of my income? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 04:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was recently admitted for an overnight stay at the hospital and since then I've seen a dietician, a therapist, and a psychiatrist. I was diagnosed with an unspecified eating disorder about two weeks ago.

So now they want me to go into an intensive outpatient eating disorder program. It'll be about 4-6weeks (or however long I need it), Monday thru Friday, from 8:30am-5:30pm. It's about a 40min drive one way from where I live. If I do it, I would more than likely lose my job (I'm a student worker on a college campus) because I would have to take those weeks off. I would also lose about half of the money I get from the VA (veterans affairs) for education because I wouldn't be able to be enrolled in classes (I have to take at least one on campus class for full benefits). Overall, I'd lose the majority of my income for two-three months, and my job.

My question is: is it worth it? Is it possible to actually get better/manage this or would I just be wasting my time/money? I want to get better, I'm tired of feeling like, this but I don't know if it's worth everything I'll lose?

Also, does anyone have any experience with this type of program in general? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How can I try to help with weight restoration without getting lost in calorie counting? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 04:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over the past few months, I have been restricting without tracking my intake.

Now, my parents have forced me to start gaining weight. I want to gain weight, too, and I've started tracking every single thing I eat to make sure that I'm eating enough.This makes them happy, but it makes me miserable. I miss being able to eat things without having to track, and now I won't even eat something if I don't know its caloric value.

How do I stop thinking about calories? it doesn't matter what my perspective of food is (good or bad), calories will never not be on my mind. I have forgotten how to eat for pleasure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Causes an Eating Disorder article </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 15:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **What causes an Eating Disorder**

Eating disorders are complex illnesses with a genetic component that can be affected by a wide variety of biological and environmental variables.

Eating disorders include a range of conditions that involve an obsession with food, weight and appearance.  The obsession is often so strong that it disrupts an individuals health, social and familial relationships, occupations and daily activities. It is estimated that over 10 million people in the United States suffer from eating disorders such as anorexia, bulimia, and binge eating disorder, and the statistics are growing.

Research on the causes of eating disorders is constantly evolving, and we continue to gain increased insight into risk factors that may contribute to the illness.  However, the answers remain multi-factorial, and they reflect a complex combination of biopsychosocial factors that may intersect differently for each person.

**Several major risk factors for eating disorders are outlined below.**

**Genetics**

Increasing numbers of family, twin, and adoption research studies have provided compelling evidence to show that genetic factors contribute to a predisposition for eating disorders.1 In other words, individuals who are born with certain genotypes are at heightened risk for the development of an eating disorder. This also means that eating disorders are heritable. Individuals who have had a family member with an eating disorder are 7-12 times more likely to develop one themselves. Newer research is exploring a possible epigenetic influence on eating disorder development.  Epigenetics is a process by which environmental effects alter the way genes are expressed.
Temperament

Some of the genes that have been identified to contribute to eating disorders are associated with specific personality traits. These aspects of personality are thought to be highly heritable and often exist before the eating disorder and can persist after recovery.2,3 The following traits are common among people who develop an eating disorder but all of these personality characteristics can exist in the absence of an eating disorder as well.4,5

    obsessive thinking
    perfectionism
    sensitivity to reward and punishment,  harm avoidance
    neuroticism6 (emotional instability and hypersensitivity)
    impulsivity, especially in bulimia nervosa
    rigidity and excessive persistence, especially in anorexia nervosa

**Biology**

Even in healthy individuals without eating disorders, states of semi-starvation have been shown to trigger obsessive behavior around food, depression, anxiety and neuroticism that promote a continued cycle of starvation7.  Additionally, brain imaging studies have shown that people with eating disorders may have altered brain circuitry that contributes to eating disorders.8,9  Differences in the anterior insula, striatal regions, and anterior ventral striatal pathway have been discovered.  Problems with the serotonin pathway have also been discovered.10,11 These differences may help to explain why people who develop anorexia nervosa are able to inhibit their appetite, why people who develop binge eating disorder are vulnerable to overeating when they are hungry, and why people who develop bulimia nervosa have less ability to control impulses to purge.
Trauma

**Traumatic events such as physical or sexual abuse** sometimes precipitate the development of an eating disorder.12-14 Victims of trauma often struggle with shame, guilt, body dissatisfaction and a feeling of a lack of control.  The eating disorder may become the individuals attempt to regain control or cope with these intense emotions. In some cases, the eating disorder is an expression of self-harm or misdirected self-punishment for the trauma.  As many as 50% of those with eating disorders may also be struggling with trauma disorders.  Its important to treat both conditions concurrently in a comprehensive and integrated approach which is why The Center for Eating Disorders offers a specialized treatment track for women and men with eating disorders whove also experienced trauma.
Coping Skill Deficits

**Individuals with eating disorders are often lacking the skills to tolerate negative experiences.**  Behaviors such as restricting, purging, bingeing and excessive exercise often develop in response to emotional pain, conflict, low self-esteem, anxiety, depression, stress or trauma.  In the absence of more positive coping skills, the eating disorder behaviors may provide acute relief from distress but quickly lead to more physical and psychological harm.  Instead of helping, the eating disorder behaviors only serve to maintain a dangerous cycle of emotional dysregulation and numbing feelings.  Effective treatment for the eating disorder involves education about and practice of alternative coping mechanisms and self-soothing techniques such as in Dialectic Behavior Therapy.
Family

The family is an integral system in the healthy development of a child and can play an important role in the recovery process. Unfortunately, in the past, parents were often blamed as the sole cause of their childs eating disorder. As more research is done on the diverse contributing factors discussed above, it becomes more and more clear that this is not the case.  While stressful or chaotic family situations may intersect with other triggers to exacerbate or maintain the illness, they do not cause eating disorders.  Its also important to note that some family dynamics, which were once assumed to be precursors to an eating disorder, may develop as a response to a family members struggle with an eating disorder.  The Academy of Eating Disorders (AED) recently released a position paper that clarifies the role of the family in the acquisition of eating disorders. The paper points out that there is no data to support the idea that anorexia or bulimia are caused by a certain type of family dynamic or parenting style. Alternatively, there is strong evidence that family-based treatment for younger patients, implemented early on in their illness, leads to positive results and improvements in conjunction with professionally guided family intervention.  While parents and families are not to blame for eating disorders, they can play a role in helping kids establish a positive body image, one of the most important protective factors against eating disorders.
Sociocultural Ideals

**Our medias increased obsession with the thin-ideal and industry promotion of a perfect body may contribute to unrealistic body ideals in people with and without eating disorders.**15,16 An increase in access to global media and technological advances such as Photoshop and airbrushing have further skewed our perception of attainable beauty standards.   In 1998, a researcher documented the response of adolescents in rural Fiji to the introduction of western television.17,18 This new media exposure resulted in significant preoccupations related to shape and weight, purging behavior to control weight, and negative body image. This landmark study illustrated a vulnerability to the images and values imported with media. Given that many individuals exposed to media and cultural ideals do not develop clinical eating disorders, it may be that individuals already at-risk, have increased vulnerability to societys messages about weight and beauty and, perhaps, seek out increased exposure to them.
Dieting

**Dieting is the most common precipitating factor in the development of an eating disorder.** In the U.S., more than $60 billion is spent every year on diets and weight-loss products. Despite dietings 95-98% failure rate, people continue to buy dangerous products and take extreme measures to lose weight. Restrictive dieting is not effective for weight loss and is an unhealthy behavior for anyone, especially children and adolescents.  For individuals who are genetically predisposed to eating disorders, dieting can be the catalyst for heightened obsessions about weight and food.  Dieting also intensifies feelings of guilt and shame around food which may ultimately contribute to a cycle of restricting, purging, bingeing or excessive exercise. 9.5 out of 10 people who lose weight through dieting gain back all of their weight within 1-5 years; half of them gain back to a weight thats above their starting weight. More worrisome though is that dieting is associated with higher rates of depression and eating disorders and increased health problems related to weight cycling. Intuitive eating and the health-at-every size paradigms are recommended as alternatives to diets for people looking to improve their health and overall well-being. 
References

1. Thornton LM, Mazzeo SE, Bulik CM. The heritability of eating disorders: methods and current findings. Curr Top Behav Neurosci. 2011;6:141-156.
2. Wade TD, Bulik CM. Shared genetic and environmental risk factors between undue influence of body shape and weight on self-evaluation and dimensions of perfectionism. Psychol Med. 2007;37(5):635-644.
3. Wilksch SM, Wade TD. An investigation of temperament endophenotype candidates for early emergence of the core cognitive component of eating disorders. Psychol Med. 2009;39(5):811-821.
4. Tyrka AR, Waldron I, Graber JA, Brooks-Gunn J. Prospective predictors of the onset of anorexic and bulimic syndromes. Int J Eat Disord. 2002;32(3):282-290.
5. Klump KL, Strober M, Bulik CM, et al. Personality characteristics of women before and after recovery from an eating disorder. Psychol Med. 2004;34(8):1407-1418.
6.  Cervera S, Lahortiga F, Martnez-Gonzlez MA, Gual P, de Irala-Estvez J, Alonso Y. Neuroticism and low self-esteem as risk factors for incident eating disorders in a prospective cohort study. Int J Eat Disord. 2003 Apr;33(3):271-80.
7. Keys, et al.  The biology of human starvation. (2 vols). Abstract online here.
8. Kaye WH, Wagner A, Fudge JL, Paulus M. Neurocircuity of eating disorders. Curr Top Behav Neurosci. 2011;6:37-57.
9. Kaye W. Neurobiology of anorexia and bulimia nervosa. Physiol Behav. 2008;94(1):121-135.
10. Bailer UF, Kaye WH. Serotonin: imaging findings in eating disorders. Curr Top Behav Neurosci. 2011;6:59-79.
11. Lee Y, Lin PY. Association between serotonin transporter gene polymorphism and eating disorders: a meta-analytic study. Int J Eat Disord. 2010;43(6):498-504.
12. Dansky BS, Brewerton TD, Kilpatrick DG, O'Neil PM. The National Women's Study: relationship of victimization and posttraumatic stress disorder to bulimia nervosa. Int J Eat Disord. 1997;21(3):213-228.
13. Inniss D, Steiger H, Bruce K. Threshold and subthreshold post-traumatic stress disorder in bulimic patients: Prevalences and clinical correlates. Eat Weight Disord. 2011;16(1):e30-6.
14. Reyes-Rodriguez ML, Von Holle A, Ulman TF, et al. Posttraumatic stress disorder in anorexia nervosa. Psychosom Med. 2011;73(6):491-497.
15. Hogan MJ, Strasburger VC. Body image, eating disorders, and the media. Adolesc Med State Art Rev. 2008;19(3):521-46, x-xi.
16. Spettigue W, Henderson KA. Eating disorders and the role of the media. Can Child Adolesc Psychiatr Rev. 2004;13(1):16-19.
17. Becker AE. Television, disordered eating, and young women in Fiji: negotiating body image and identity during rapid social change. Cult Med Psychiatry. 2004;28(4):533-559.
18. Becker AE, Burwell RA, Gilman SE, Herzog DB, Hamburg P. Eating behaviours and attitudes following prolonged exposure to television among ethnic Fijian adolescent girls. Br J Psychiatry. 2002;180:509-514.
 
**From: The Center for Eating Disorders
Request Information
Online Self Assessment
Evaluation Process**
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: What are the long term health problems for a person after recovery? What should I watch out for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 15:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
For several years in high school I was underweight due to anorexia, but now I've been at a healthy weight and with generally healthy behaviors for three years. I still have compulsions to overexercise or not eat enough when I'm stressed out but I don't give into them and haven't for quite awhile. 

My doctor at home knows my history, but my doctor here at university does not because I go to a different doctor most times I have an appointment about anything because that's how the student health center works. 

Basically, I'm wondering what I need to worry about? What kinds of health issues could I be at high(er) risk for than people without this history? What should I look out for?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Overweight, transgender, depression, anxiety, is what I'm doing an eating disorder or dieting? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 15:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm diagnosed with **severe depression and anxiety**. Which may impact this a little.

I am **overweignt.** I'm **transgender male to female** if that applies at all, so my whole life is a crazy mess essentially.

I dont really eat if I can help it. Its not like I need to starve, I just dont want to eat too much. I know what I usually eat is terrible for me so I try to reduce portions. I'm losing weight. Which makes me happy for sure. I try to weigh myself each night to keep track of stuff. I dont think its a problem, I think its making me waaay healthier.

So what my dad said. He just asked me if I was eating and I said yes and all that. He said alright and I asked why he asked and he said I sleep too much and seem sick. I mean yeah, **I sleep a lot.** If you leave me in bed I'll sleep from 8pm to 8pm the next day. But thats just because I'm a **teenager** and I'm depressed and there isnt anything else to do. I don't feel very sick.

Once last month I did throw up. Like on purpose. But it was once and we went out to eat and it was a lot and its not that big of a deal. I've not done it before. I wont do it again unless I eat like a shitton which I never will.

I mean I'm blatantly overweight, I cant have an eating disorder when I'm not even a healthy weight yet, or can I? 

 I just want to lose weight and this is how I'm doing it and it's worth it.

   






**So what makes it into an eating disorder vs just dieting?** 

Is it more the intensity like how much you worry about it? Or the methods, like dieting or just binging or purging.

Just because I know I have binged and purged before and I'm not really thinking I have a disorder as much as I'm really focused on losing weight. Or like hyper restricting intake like avoiding eating at all vs eating 'healthier' foods?

I suppose for example : somebody prefers to not eat and they are overweight, so losing weight is logical. It may be kinda unhealthy but would it be worth it?

Or if somebody worried about calories and weighing themselves a lot, and based their intake on losing weight very quickly vs carefully, is this an eating disorder or dieting?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to help my girlfriend eat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 21:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello Reddit, I love my girlfriend a lot and want to try to help her get over her eating disorder. She's at a healthy weight and doesn't seem to have huge body image issues. She does think she's kinda fat though :( 

Anyways, we're going through a tough time financially and haven't been able to keep buying weed(which is legal here, WA state) and now she can't eat anymore. Apparently solid food feels really gross in her mouth and she can't get it down. It makes me sad to see her struggle like that and I want to help.

Does anyone know anything helpful? I just don't really know what to do. I could try to get more weed, but that's not a real solution to the problem. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I think my friend may have an eating disorder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 10:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was sexually assaulted by his ex girlfriend of 2 years last year, and experienced a very traumatic breakup. As a result he suffers from anxiety, and it has manifested in anorexia - has no appetite, he 'forgets' to eat, or says he doesnt feel hungry. He eats a small amount once a day. I've asked him about it and he says he doesn't have an eating disorder, but i know he used to suffer from one, when he would work out at the gym and overexercise (I'm not sure what this is called) I'm recovered from an ed which was triggered by similar circumstances and I'm really worried about him. What can I do?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Questions on partner's non-purging bulimia and CAT </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 15:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend has been diagnosed with non-purging bulimia and is 9 weeks into cognitive analytical therapy (CAT) for it. I appreciate that these are still relatively early days for the treatment but so far she doesn't seem to be getting much if anything out of it.

My concern is that she may have misrepresented (**lied about**) her condition to the therapist from the beginning, which might make the whole thing a waste of time - or even damaging. I feel I should have been involved in some way in the initial sessions to ensure the therapist got the full picture. At the start of the process I was trying to give her space and privacy to deal with the issue herself - she hates talking about it - but now I think this might have been the wrong approach and I'm not sure what to do.

As I see it, there are two behavioural aspects to her condition, plus a third that may or may not be related. The first is very occasional **binge eating (without purging)**. The second, constant, aspect is a **phobia of any food she feels is fattening**. Finally, I think she has an unhealthy relationship with **alcohol.**

The foods she feels are fattening include major food groups. She's very bright and, intellectually, she knows that this is totally upside down nutritionally, but she remains phobic of these foods to the point where the prospect of eating them makes her **panic** and break down. This happened most recently in a restaurant last night when we the food arrived with an unexpected "fatty" sauce on it. I discreetly ate both meals to avoid the waitress asking if there was a problem (which would have freaked her out even more). After we hurriedly left, she started crying and comparing herself negatively to the other "skinny" women in the small restaurant - who were, objectively, a very similar build to herself.

The **alcohol issue** isn't quite as clear cut but is definitely worrying. I know alcohol / substance abuse is often linked to eating disorders. She doesn't get drunk every day. She never gets black-out drunk. It doesn't affect her ability to function. She can go a couple of weeks without a drink without suffering (although this is rare). But she does drink a significant amount almost every day, irrespective of whether I'm drinking (usually I'm not). If we have a bottle of spirits in the house, it will be gone in 3 or 4 days without me touching a drop - sometimes without me even knowing it was there. She feels she needs a drink before bed to sleep well. We've discussed this - she knows I'm concerned about it but she doesn't accept she has a problem. I have at times resorted to secretly pouring a couple of shots of spirits from the bottle down the sink to try to limit it a bit (she doesn't know about this).

I should say that her weight is perfectly healthy - although of course she doesn't perceive it that way. She doesn't purge, her sometimes **inadequate food intake is balanced out in calorie terms by her alcohol intake** and she exercises most days. Her diet isn't terrible - but she has a limited and unvaried diet.

Before she began therapy, her perception was that her only real problem was the **bingeing**, because it makes her gain weight. From my perspective, that's actually the least of her three issues - because it's so infrequent. I'm much more worried about the constant **excessive diet control**, **body dysmorphia** and **alcohol issues**. I'm pretty sure she will have minimised these points when speaking to the therapist, and I wish I'd been invited to attend an early session to give my perspective. We discussed it a bit after last night's panic attack in the restaurant and she says the therapy is covering the diet control point - but as she's never perceived it to be a significant problem I'm not sure whether I believe her. She also says that the therapy is overwhelmingly focused on her early relationships with her family ("We don't really talk about the actual current food issues.")

Apologies for the long and rambling post. As with most other boyfriend posts on the subreddit, I'm really just trying to find the best way to support her. I'm just worried that she'll spend 6 months in therapy and get nowhere because she hasn't been completely honest with herself or her therapist about what her problems are. I'm also not convinced that CAT is the right approach in the first place - the success statistics look poor to me - but there was a several month waiting list for CBT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Night Binging </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 12:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been having increasingly greater problems with my binge eating in the past few months and have been finding ways to control it. I can keep it under control until I come home from a long day (College student, athlete, working = long days) and mindlessly binge to the point that I have to purge directly after. This happens every day and every day I say the same thing to myself: "This won't happen tomorrow."

I need some advice/ tips on night time binging. I want to eat a normal amount for dinner and be able to be done for the night without eating everything else in sight.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: diagnosed with ED 2 years ago and I have no idea how to recover </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 12:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 years ago I was diagnosed by my counselor with an ED. I did not want to ask my mom to get treatment because I did not think that she would take me seriously, and I thought that I could fix it myself. I am now 20 years old. I did manage it for a while, but recently have been under a lot of stress, mostly because I have major depressive disorder and I guess I feel like if I can control my appearance it will make me happier. I realize that this isn't right. I want to get better I just don't know how, and I don't have insurance so I cannot get proper treatment. 

If anyone can please give me a treatment plan to retrain myself how to eat, be healthy, and love my self again I could never repay you. I'm making myself ill and I am so exhausted from being sick all the time. 

Thank you.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Book Suggestion for BED   Bulimia, Brain over Binge, there's a workbook, too! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 15:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This book got me recovered.

First of all, pardon my bad english! I've struggled with BED and Bulimia for 3-4 years, and can proudly say that I've recovered 90%. I don't think anyone can recover 100%, but I'm very happy with 90. I used to think about food all day long, always thinking I was fat, trying out new diets all the time and let food control my life. I isolated myself and was angry all the time.

The doctor put me on a lot of meds, made me talk about my childhood all the time to find out where it all started without any progress. One day I came over this book from one of the many youtube videos i watched about recovery; [brain over binge](http://brainoverbinge.com/).  I don't get anything for sharing this.

It really saved my life. I quit my meds almost right away (which I should not have done. Lower your dose gradually.) I feel like it's my duty to share it with others that need help and don't know how to recover from Binge eating, anorexia or bulimia. This book gave me a new perspective on life and on food. It's all in our heads! You've made it a habit. That's just it. It's all just a habit that you need to break out of, and this book teaches you how to do so! 

It's written by a woman who shares how she recovered, after struggling almost her whole life and she teach us through her book techniques to do when we are at our lowest!

Let me know if you read it. If you need help, comment. I wish to support you all! If I can do it, so can you!!

Edit: Please notify /u/sarahsdiary when you reply to this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I've been trying to recover but my flatmate has an ED, how do I cope? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 11:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been living with my boyfriend's family for nearly a decade and spent most of it obese (BED). I lost weight the typical way for a while, until last year when I went through a pretty severe 5 month restrict-purge cycle and lost a decent amount of weight, though I'm still on the higher end of healthy weight for my height.
When my boyfriend realized what was happening, he asked me to try for recovery. It's been about nine months since then. Nine painful months, honestly. One of my main struggles has been staying on a healthy path, knowing that his sister is bulimic, and that when she isn't purging, she's absolutely restricting and exercising to a degree.

I don't really know what to do. I can't exactly move out in the middle of us trying to get our lives together, and I can't confront their parents about it without admitting that I have the same disordered behaviour -- especially when I'm still trying to lose weight and their mom tells me I should stop being so militant about my diet (I'm not. I'm vegan). I also can't say much because they don't know for sure that she's still bulimic.

So how do you cope when you're trapped in a house with someone who is clearly suffering from the same ED you're trying to recover from? 

This is the first time I've really sat down and started looking into recovery communities and I'm excited about the links on the sidebar, but I'm really not sure where to start when a permanent part of my life is still connected to eating disorders.

Thanks for reading, any help would be immensely appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Male Anorexia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 05:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A friend of mine (male) has anorexia. A doctor informed him but didn't give him much direction other than "eat more". He doesn't consciously starve himself to my knowledge, so he doesn't really have any idea how to combat this if he never really feels hungry. 

Any advice I can pass along that's a little more specific/motivating than "eat more"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: A friend of mine told me she has Bulimia, how can I help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 02:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend admitted to having Bulimia today. 

I attempted to ask her about it and she told me she has not told anyone else, not even her parents.

Not sure how I should continue, all I know is that I should be careful about what I say.

Any help is greatly appreciated, thank you so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Social worker thinks I have an eating disorder, I'm afraid of not being taken seriously and of gaining weight in therapy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 23:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (English is not my native language, sorry for any mistakes)

A couple of weeks ago my social worker pointed out I might have an eating disorder. I was on a diet when some terrible events that caused me a lot of emotional stress happened and I discovered not eating as a weird source of comfort for me. While I wasn't able to control the circumstances I was in, I at least could control my eating. I lost a lot of weight in a scarily short amount of time.
Time passed, things got better at home and my eating habits changed a little bit. I still restricted and exercised but not nearly as bad as before.

Now, things have again gone downhill and so have my eating habits. I now obsess over my weight, it's all I can think about and not eating is currently my only source of comfort. The lesser I eat the better I feel. Again, people noticed and the social worker pointed out a possible clinical therapy should things not get better.

I was all for it but then someone pointed out that you usually get calorie dense foods and I freaked out.We are talking near hysterics. I'm deadly afraid of gaining weight and I'm trying to avoid certain foods at all costs. I also fear that people won't take me serious because I'm technically still in a normal weight range.

I'm not officially diagnosed with an eating disorder since my social worker is not qualified to do so.

How can I get help and find out if I have an eating disorder, since my social worker cannot diagnosis me?

How can I overcome my fear of foods and weight gain in order to seek treatment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to shift dark circles and gaunt face post recovery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 21:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Male, 24 years old here.

I will keep it short. Two years ago I hit my lowest ever weight and my face looked awful, like a skeleton with gaunt cheeks and dark circles that went from the corner of my eye right onto the top of my cheek. 

I am now back to my former, healthy weight and whilst my face has filled out a bit I still look gaunt and the dark circles remain.
I want my youthful face fat back. Is there anything I can do to help my face look fuller?

Isn't the face normally the first place to fill out? How can I deal with weightloss induced dark circles? Can anyone offer any insight?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
