<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3094</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-11 17:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feel free! I really like the lifting routine; I never feel overwhelmed by it or anything. I just really hate cardio, so that's my main struggle with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [QUESTION] Cheat meals: do they completely destroy your motivation, or is it just me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-11 16:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am currently working with macros and I plan out my meals for the week to make sure I meet them. I am allowed one cheat meal a week, which I know is pretty common. Here's my problem: once I have that cheat meal, I feel this overwhelming sense of failure and my brain just sort of gives up. I never fails, for the next couple of days I will actually under eat, not on purpose, but just because I lose the motivation to figure out what I need to be eating and where my macros are. I find it nearly impossible to get myself to the gym. It always takes me at least a couple of days to get back on track after the cheat meal, and I feel like it ruins all the hard work and progress I've made during the entire week. Am I alone in this? If you guys are dealing with similar things, how do you combat it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-05 17:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to exercise A LOT - I played competitive softball for both my school and for a traveling tournament team. I was the catcher so I was definitely in good shape, plus high school athletics included a lot of weightlifting and running. I played volleyball as well. However I've been pretty much entirely sedentary since 2009 besides chasing around a 2 year old. The time I spent struggling with ED weakened me considerably, so I've set myself back pretty far. I just really had the urge to dive headfirst into this. I hope I don't burn out :/  
  
This plan is part of the book I read, and he just proposes one leg day. These workout are typically taking about 45 minutes to 1 hour, and that's really all the time I have to spend at the gym. I work full time and have a 2 year old, so I'm pretty busy. Would having two leg days lengthen the workouts, or is there another way to situate it?  
  
I totally agree about the diet part - this is the aspect that's the hardest for me and the most confusing. I've really been having trouble getting 180 g of protein! I actually have felt like I'm eating a TON of food, but that could be because of my past habits. More than anything I'm just suck of chicken breasts, haha. I'll definitely look into tweaking my numbers because you're not the first person to say this.  
  
What I've been doing if I miss a workout is to shift all workouts by a day and using my Sunday (cardio only) as a lifting day to get myself back on track.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-05 17:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Diet is definitely the part of this that's giving me the most issues. I've never really focused on anything about food besides calorie count, so I've been trying to learn as much as I can. Multiple of people have suggested that I should lower protein, and I'm honestly glad because I was finding it nearly impossible to reach 180g. I am trying to cut, but I guess I should up my fat some too. I'm honestly finding it really hard to cram in 1550 calories, so upping that number seems daunting. I suppose that could be old demons more than anything, though. Thank you for your suggestions! It helps A TON. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-05 17:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're SO RIGHT. I tried to do cardio this morning after yesterday's legs and I damn near died. Someone else said that 4x a week cardio was too much, so I'm thinking of maybe just dropping Tuesday's cardio completely. Does that seem like a good idea to you?  
  
I like the idea of focusing more on my legs. They're definitely the part of my body that I'd most like to see improve - the women in my family seem to be cursed with extensive cellulite if you let your legs go AT ALL. I was a catcher in softball for 14 years so I took for granted having ridiculously toned legs and booty :( I'll look into this for sure! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-05 17:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow! Thank you so much for all of your input!  
  
I'm glad you suggested subbing the barbell lunges with the barbell hip thrusts. The lunges are the only exercise that I completely, 100% HATE with a burning passion. I've been looking for something I can sub but wasn't sure how to choose something else.  
  
As for the HIIT cardio, I've only been able to last 15 minutes so 25 was just sort of a goal, but I can see how it might be too much.   
  
The plan I'm following has a week 1-8 routine and then changes it up for weeks 9-16. I believe it subs in wide grip lat pulldown for the close grip, but I'm not 100% sure and I don't have it with me at the moment. Does that sound like a good idea to you?  
  
The reason I have Friday as my complete off day is because it's the one day that I absolutely have ZERO time for working out unless I want to wake up at 4am, which I'll never do on a Friday. I wish I could move it though :/  
  
Pretty much everyone who has commented on this has told me it's too much protein, and I'm SO GLAD. I was finding it nearly impossible to cram it all in!  
  
I'm not new to fitness, just starting over completely pretty much. I've been entirely inactive since 2009 plus a pregnancy in 2011. I didn't gain a whole lot of weight and I worked on my feet 40 hours up until the very last week of pregnancy, but I could definitely tell it set me back a bit. I do feel a bit overwhelmed by all the changes at once, but I'm excited about it.  
  
Thank you so much for all your input! You've helped tremendously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
