<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3259</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 16:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Autocorrect oh man.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 16:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chilling the dough helps it to spread less! Baking is all about experimenting with what works for you:)

And to broil simply means cook the tops to brown:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 06:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. You can lose weight but the "fat" mentality will still stay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 05:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard it's amazing on celery! Ahhhh you're making me so nostalgic! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 05:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah same! I always used to eat the good ol' Kraft PB, but when I realized it was all hydrogenated oils and sugar, I switched to natural. The peanut flavour is more intense imho and I agree, the processed does taste really odd once you've had real for so long. Although I do love the honey flavoured PBs which are the processed ones:/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chocolate chip cookie cheesecake! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 05:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 05:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used my mom's cheesecake recipe and or the crust I used a whole box of chocolate chip cookie dough pop tarts, blended that with butter and then added pieces of pillsbury cookie dough to the batter. It's topped with mini chocolate chip cookies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chocolate Chip Cookie cheesecake! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 05:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 04:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't get me wrong, one of my neighbours is super kind and nice but she always gets those professional people to do most of her outside work. That means at 7 am on a ducking Saturday morning I have to hear the weedwhacker/lawnmower/leafblower. And in the winter it's the snow removal company. Ffs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's one thing a woman can do to help her look and feel way better? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 04:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 04:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smooth! And I love it smeared on apples or just straight from the spoon...TBH I ate 1/4 of a jar tonight and I regret nothing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 04:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peanut butter

Ofc it has to be so high in calories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What food did you try that changed your life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 04:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 06:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem! I think the crust is the best part as I just discovered the magic of Tenderflake haha... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 06:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks yummy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 00:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recipe is my own!

I made the crust following the Tenderflake box's instructions. 

Filling is around 8 small apples, peeled and chopped. Throw it into a pot with around a cup of sugar, 1/4-1/2 cup of brandy and 1-2cups water. Add cinnamon and stir. Cook mixture until boiling and reduce heat. Once mixture is a bit thick add in 1/4 cup of flour and stir. Remove from heat and allow to cool. 

Heat oven to 400degrees F. Roll out crust until a very large circle on floured surface. Transfer to greased baking sheet and fill with Apple mixture. Make sure to leave enough crust so you can fold it over. Fold your crust and brush with egg wash and sugar. Bake for about 20-25 minutes or until crust is golden brown. 

Remove from heat and drizzle with a mixture of honey and butter. Serve immediately. 

Hope you enjoy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 06:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem! Let me know how they come out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 04:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure!

1 cup coconut oil
1 tbsp vanilla
1 cup white sugar
1/2 cup brown sugar
1 egg
Pinch of salt
1 tsp baking soda
2 cups flour
Any kind of additions you want (chocolate chips, dried fruit etc etc)

Preheat oven to 375 degrees F. Cream coconut oil and sugar for 2 minutes. Add vanilla and egg. Beat until smooth. Add in salt and baking soda. Slowly add in flour and once incorporated mix in your additions. Don't overwork the dough. You can chill the dough for however long you want which will help develop the flavour(I didn't in this case). Shape into balls and place on parchment lined or headed cookie sheet. Bake 10 minutes and then broil the tops for two minutes. Let cool and enjoy!

**** this recipe also makes really good snickerdoodles. Don't add any of the additions and mix together some sugar and cinnamon. Roll the dough balls in the mixture and bake!**** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 02:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really love your eyebrows </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A question about eyebrows... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 02:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys,

So I've been doing my own brows at home for a while and lately they've become a hot mess. They have no shape to them at all and don't help my appearance at all. 

I'm think about getting them either waxed or threaded and want to know which is better. Last time I got them waxed was a long time ago. 

Would threading make them look better? They're pretty sparse as it is. 

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 01:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, there's an egg in them. But it can be subbed for flax and it works well! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 01:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are so cute! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chocolate chip cookies made with coconut oil </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 01:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A tip for the flakiest pie crust ever! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 00:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright so I've been making pies for about 10 years and it's really been a learning experience. 

I've used shortening, butter, coconut oil, regular oil, margarine and lard. 

This weekend I made six Pie crusts using Tenderflake lard and the recipe on their box. 

Let me tell you that it is the BEST pastry ever. It tastes so good and is so. damn. flakey. 

Yes, lard is animal fat and is really bad for you, but pie isn't exactly seen as a health food. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best purchase you have made for yourself? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 22:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 22:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually for baking anything I use unsalted butter. This allows you to control how much salt you want in a recipe and won't risk a too salty recipe. 

Graham cracker crust I use unsalted. You don't add salt to a GC crust.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 22:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a fairly simple recipe(don't be off put by the time):

allrecipes.com/recipe/19165/creme-brulee/

 You can use the torch for anything that would normally need broiling. Baked Alaska, lemon meringue pie, getting the cheese bubbly on your casserole etc etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Warm apple galette with honey butter glaze </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 22:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 18:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used this recipe: allrecipes.com/recipe/152915/most-amazing-challah/

It was very sweet as there is quite a lot of honey in it. To be honest I didn't really like it as it turned out very dense and too sweet (still tasted good though). Also it calls for a lot of olive oil which I wasn't too happy about. 

If you want a really good challah, use the Betty Crocker Rich egg bread recipe. It's in the Betty Crocker cookbook (the red one) which I swear by as everything I've made has turned out great. Not sure if it's online but if not then just PM me and I'll send you the recipe! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 18:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's more of a sweet egg bread! I recommend making it and using it for French toast or bread pudding </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 18:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can tell these are really chewy...they look so good!! Chocolate chip cookies are my favourite things to bake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 03:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can tell you from a personal perspective that it has a lot to do with how the person is wired. Drugs obviously aren't used by just one specific demographic. Sure, some drugs like crack-cocaine are used by those who are "lowely" and cocaine is used by "rich party animals;" however, there is not set demographic. 

It can start with morbid curiosity. What does it feel like to be high on heroin? Just once wouldn't hurt would it? Thus ending in addiction to the drug (but not always). 

Of course you have to have the resources. And using other drugs can open up doors like that. People say marijuana is a gateway drug not because it will make you want to try harder things- but because it allows you to step foot into the world which is drugs. You meet people who know people who can score you some coke. Of course not everyone who does drugs like marijuana or cocaine etc etc(anything less harsh than heroin) ends up using harder drugs. They just become more easily accessible is all. 

And then there is the whole mental factor. Those who are mentally ill are more likely to turn to drugs to cope with their pain. A temporary fix may become a necessity to stay alive. 

Friends, family, parents who use drugs can have an impact on a person and they may begin to use. 

There are tons of factors as to why people begin to use heroin. Each person's reason is different. People obviously know it's bad and it's like every other addiction: once it's started its hard to stop.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why does wearing sunglasses seem to make people more attractive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 02:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 00:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super cute:) you should post this to r/zelda </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Homemade challah </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 23:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ladies, what is your hidden talent? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 19:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Not to toot my own horn but I'm a really good cook and baker. When people find out they're a bit taken aback but it's something I love to do!

What's your hidden talent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 01:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These look great but if I could give a tip it would to be to broil the tops so they're a rich brown colour. It really adds depth to the rolls! 

Pretzel rolls are so fun to make.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where are some good cities to backpack in? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 20:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking of taking a semester off and backpacking around the globe. I want to go to Europe and japan but I'm a single young woman traveling alone. Which cities are safest and cheapest?

Thanks!

*Any tips would be great too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 20:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My experience is that you will need to have proof of sufficient funds while you stay in the US. You might need permission from your parents (not sure though) and you obviously need to use your passport and licence. Your best bet is to go on the border website and look at their FAQ. You can also contact them by phone or email. 

You need to prove that you are just visiting the states and will be returning to Canada. This is why it's good to print out an itinerary and hotel bookings. Bring your debit or credit card. Don't say anything stupid while at the border. Because you're so young and traveling without a parent, you'll be more likely to be questioned and pulled over. 

That being said, just do your research and make sure you have all the documentation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's a dessert that's really fun to make? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 20:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will Sephora allow me to exchange my purchases? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 14:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys,

So I've never returned anything from Sephora before and what I want to return I bought in October and November. They are two foundations that I spent almost $80 on each and I hate the way they make my skin look. 

I don't have the boxes the bottles came in or my receipts, however they do show up on my purchases for my VIB card. 

Will Sephora allow me to exchange or receive store credit?

I live in Canada if that helps! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Made some "loaf"ely ciabatta bread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 00:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 23:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks so good! I would totally make this but I would probably eat it all in one sitting  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brandy- Caramel-apple pie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 23:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 21:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, sorry to hear about your  loss. It definitely does make depression and anxiety worse though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 21:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep...it's unfortunate how it affects the kids of those who fight constantly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Those who grew up with parents who always fought-but weren't divorced or separated-how did it affect you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 18:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My parents always fought and it really affected me and my sister.  I think my view on relationships is skewed and hurt by it as well as my mental health.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's one thing you shouldn't do while home alone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 02:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 07:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sashimi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If your period was a movie, what would the title be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 05:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 03:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Raw....?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 03:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frozen desserts are a bunch of sickly sweet lies... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 03:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha just like my mom.... She pulls out the butter every time a loaf of bread gets put on the table </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 03:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is one food you absolutely cannot resist? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 02:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Raw/cooked salmon is my weakness.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chocolate cupcakes with Nutella buttercream </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 01:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 04:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are so pretty! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 04:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coffee crisp is the best chocolate to receive EVER. You can head over to r/snackexchange if you want the legit thing but to make it at home I'm not too sure. 

It's mainly comprised of wafer and chocolate. What I would do is buy wafers (they sell them just plain in layers) and then make a coffee buttercream or coffee and chocolate ganache. Keep stacking them until it's the desired consistency and then dip into melted milk chocolate. 

Ive found a recipe for Kit Kats which are relatively similar to coffee crisps.  m.instructables.com/id/Homemade-Kit-Kat-Candy-Bar-Recipe/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The bar on Spotify for The complete Star Wars soundtrack is a lightsaber </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 03:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
