<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8986</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 07:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My rent is $700-- splitting a 1br that's $1395. If you go on the housing fb page, I've seen plenty of $500-600. And if you're looking at Oakland, you can go cheaper. The apartment I'm staying at is only a few blocks from campus, though, so it was worth it to me. With the meal plan (not in the $1000 budget), I should be able to eat almost every day in a cafeteria, where I plan to eat my protein. Carbs and fats are cheap.

The prices they list are on the higher side of things, I think. It should be pretty easy to do cheaper than that if you're interested. For instance, they put down $210/month for "personal"... I honestly can't imagine what they imagine would be in that $210.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 04:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm planning on spending less than the [cost of attendance](http://admissions.berkeley.edu/costofattendance) page on their website. I won't have a car, and the place I'm staying at is cheaper than what they put down, I can cook, and have lived on my own for 4 years. So I'm guessing $1000, plus the cost of the cheapest meal plan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 03:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find that conditioner doesn't help me personally with the grease, but an egg wash did. So try that if the conditioner doesn't help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-03 21:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work in a restaurant and am in the kitchen probably 1/4-1/2 of the time (not a cook). I think the sweat, for me, is a bigger deal than any oil that would come from it. I've been no-poo for 2 weeks at this point and it's fine. I would look up other people's suggestions of when they work out and stuff, but I haven't done anything special. I would just pin back any bangs if that works with your hairstyle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 21:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I figured. I just wanted to know why people say 6-8 weeks since I've never heard an explanation, especially with a source. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 03:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Water only.

Tried bs/acv and realized it's probably more harmful to my hair anyway, and even if it isn't, it's just a pain and I'd rather do this the easy way. So mostly out of laziness.

I have a BBB but not sure how much it matters with hair as short as mine. Works fine though. 

Used a dry shampoo (by LUSH, only because I had it) and it was helpful. Just did an egg wash and that was nice too. My hair is still wet from doing that so I don't really know the results.

I pin my bangs back when I feel like it'll feel dirty like when I work (restaurant job) or exercising. I did that anyways, though.

I mostly contribute the ease of all of my process because of how short my hair is. I do know I'd have a rougher time if my hair was more than shoulder length... but I guess that's one of the reasons I don't have it that long in the first place.

One thing I have noticed, though, is that my scalp feel less itchy/tight than before. Kind of how the Oil Cleansing Method feels on my face when I experimented with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does it take 6-8 weeks to get out of the transitional stage? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 03:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm experimenting with nopoo purely for my own entertainment, and a couple of weeks in. I'm fine with going back to shampoo if it doesn't work out, and I'm not really biased one way or the other. I never washed my hair too often anyway, and have relatively short hair (grown out pixie), so it isn't too big of a deal for me.

I'm just puzzled why the 6-8 week thing happens. If you have data to back it up, please source!

I keep making up different reasons that are totally not backed up by anything. For instance, let's say your hair grows 1" in 6-8 weeks. Maybe your oils from your scalp doesn't naturally doesn't reach over 1" and doesn't touch the old, shampoo'd hair.

Or maybe in 6 weeks, hair has been through enough wind that it has blown all the oil away. Honestly I'm just being silly and have no clue.

I've have heard that if you've gone through a stressful event (let's say it led to malnutrition) your hair will fall out 3 months after the event, and that's just how the hair cycle is. 

Anyone know? Any links? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 23:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. Didn't realize it wasn't in OP's possession. Could just be an outdoor cat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 22:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting! I think for me the fact that it doesn't hurt like a dislocation is just weirdness on my part. I fully dislocated my jaw (had to go to the ER to pop it back in) and it didn't hurt, either... It hasn't happened in a while so I haven't thought about it much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 09:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious, when you say your shoulder slides out of the socket, do you mean you dislocated it? I have hypermobility in my joints too, so I have a similar thing happen to me every once in a while, like with push ups once, but it has never caused pain exactly. It was more like an immediate intense fatigue in my shoulder. Just wondering if it was the same thing. I don't know if it's like a temporary dislocation (pops back into place immediately, probably due to the hypermobility). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 09:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> check it for a microchip if you haven't! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-20 09:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe /r/bodyweightfitness could help you out with the pullups. I think she did a bunch of gymnastics, and probably rock climbing too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 23:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here! She also likes putting things into boxes and bags, so backpacks and purses would have surprise toys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 22:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hiroki in shimokitazawa is pretty good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 03:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no reason not to apply. It's pretty unheard of, but my friend got in as a transfer with a 3.2 GPA. But he had good extra curriculars and a lot of help from professors. At the same time, I had a 3.8 and was rejected by UCLA (but got into Berkeley) with average amounts of extra curriculars.

I would add in your essays about your condition and why it was that you had lower grades, how you have overcome it, but don't be apologetic.  Show initiative and write about how it made you stronger. 

You can apply to other UCs too, it's just another button to click when you submit your application if you want to get out of your state school.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 00:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just used a referral from this thread, thanks! Passing it on, here's mine:

https://zm0ttl25i27.ting.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-08 18:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So could it be something like phantom foreskin? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-28 19:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite is Sprouts, and they're all over the place so it'll cut down on gas money. You can hit up Mexican and Asian markets, too. Japanese markets can be more expensive, though, so watch out. Korean (S-Mart in Torrance), Mexican (Northgate Markets, was called Top Valu), Chinese (99 Ranch), and Philippino (Seafood City in Carson for meat and weirder cuts) are all good. But for ease, I generally go to Sprouts. And depending on how big your household is, Costco. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-28 19:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine does Microsoft and Adobe CS for free (~30k students).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 18:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find audiobooks extra helpful when I'm doing something else, like cleaning or driving.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 08:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finger cots are helpful if you have cuts on your hand, or to help smooth out hangnails. Diseases can be transmitted via blood too! Percentages are very low, but you can never be too safe. It also feels nicer to not feel a nail snag. 

Another neat thing in a safe sex kit are some black gloves. Not sure if you can get black finger cots... They look better than the surgical kind IMO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 23:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A similar thing happened to me, and I told him pretty soon after what happened and how I felt. I honestly wouldn't have been able to hide my feelings since he was only gone for a few minutes out of the room.  My bf said that he had thought he deleted pictures, and that he missed the folder. Whether it's true or not, your bf might not even know how much it would affect you. My bf just deleted the photos and that was that. I felt weird for a while but it was all an accident and I can't change what happened. As long as your bf is willing to work with you on feeling wanted and all of that, it'll all work out. 

On the other hand, if he argues he wants to keep the photos despite how you feel or some other odd behavior like that, that's when it becomes a weird situation. But definitely tell him how you feel!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 19:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Santouka, at least where I am, is in a food court. Pretty good ramen, but they aren't a company that really needs to worry about presentation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 04:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will be transfering this fall for Psych (I think), and I was one class short of my IGETC and the counselor said it was fine. I even took a Finite Math (Math 21 at my CC), not even stats. As long as you have the credits, it's good. 

Specifically, she said this:

"If you have completed English 1, English 2, Math 21 and can show a high school transcript with 3 years of the same language other than English with a 'C' or better, then you don't need IGETC for admission."

And of course, you need a 3.0 or better this semester as per Conditions of Admission. I think that's the only way they would revoke the acceptance. Email your counselor just to be sure, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 03:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I think I'm not planning to do art. I did get a scholarship to a private art school, but it still ended up being more than Cal ($30k/yr with 12k/yr scholarship), and I would have had to start as a Sophomore, which I think most privates prefer.

I'm a little worried about the pre-recs... I definitely have enough credits, but am missing one IGETC course. I'll see what they have to say. Do you know anything about the Transfer Edge course? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 08:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Private art schools are $35k/yr. So UC is already a deal comparatively. Got into CSULB which would be convenient for me, but I would get a better degree at UCB. Plus, as a transfer, I only have to pay for 2 years worth of tuition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Art or Psychology (Transfer) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 05:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi!

I was admitted into the art program, as all of the colleges I've been applying to have been for art and that's what I've been studying.  The problem is that I haven't been hearing the best things about the art program, and I also love psychology. I know the Psych program is really good. Any news about the art program? And how hard is it for transfers to switch majors? 

I also am not sure about which prereqs I would need. I've checked Assist, but I'm not sure if the IGETC is enough. Also, have any transfers done the summer program before their first fall semester? 

And if anything... is there a number or email I can contact? I'm in Los Angeles, and have heard theres info I can get in the area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 18:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooh... Blythes :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 19:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Protein powder, ground up oatmeal, flour if you want... And whatever toppings I suppose! I can eat them plain though since the bananas have enough sweetness IMO. My recommendation is to make small pancakes, like palm sized, so they're easier to flip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-14 19:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some more unconventional foods. I always love to hide my eggs.

Soon dubu, a Korean tofu stew. I poach the eggs and it mixes in with tofu pretty well.

Same with ramen.

For deserts, custards and pumpkin pie. The last pumpkin pie I made had 6 eggs in it, and I could've probably done more. Go light on the sweeteners.

Chawanmushi, a savory type of Japanese custard.

Tamagoyaki. Again, Japanese, and very eggy but it's generally a different flavor, like adding soy sauce and sugar.

I made croquettes the other day (Japanese "korokke") and was able to chop up 4 hard boiled eggs to the mix without it tasting eggy. 

Banana and egg pancakes. Those are the only two ingredients. 2 eggs, 1 banana, pan fry.

I grew up with Japanese food, but consider looking up other country's foods that you're interested in. This gets me away from the general fried egg recipes that pop up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-03 23:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Just made this for lunch. I didn't know how easy it was, and I already had everything on hand since I made tamales a few weeks back. Stuffed with cheese and leftover cooked chicken, and topped with yogurt and salsa. Had some pickles on the side. I didn't have the traditional kind, but it worked. Really well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 00:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use a Tasin TS-108 to make my cat's food. So, it goes through pounds of bone every few months and it's been going well.  In terms of quieter/faster, I've read that the Weston #12 Meat Grinder is great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-04 17:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally understand. I think I realized it most when I'm reading that people with clean living spaces don't have a bunch of storage containers, they just have a lot less stuff to store in the first place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-04 09:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My latest way to do it is to ask myself if I've been doing just fine without it so far.  It worked for me in terms of not buying kitchen appliances, storage stuff, and clothes so far.  For instance, I want to buy a new litter box for my cat but realize I've been doing just fine with the one I have now.  I realize I don't need to upgrade/replace as much as I think I do. 

The other thing that I ask myself is if I imagine my perfect home, would it include this item? Usually it doesn't, since it all ends up being clutter and I imagine my perfect home to be quite minimal and simplistic, which I feel like I'm far from. I'll end up wanting to buy something dumb just because I have a small amount of cash to buy things, but realize in the big picture I don't need it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-29 08:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work as a cashier at a grocery store, but people pay with hundreds for small amounts all the time. It's an unpopular opinion, but I honestly love it. I get so many $20 bills, it makes it a lot easier to count my box at the end of the day to count eight $100s than forty $20s.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 09:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A good app for that on the iPhone that I used for anorexia is called Recovery Record. It's aesthetically pleasing and is not intrusive if you want it to be, using keywords and such. 

Another tip is to keep heavily caloric foods around like avocados and nuts and sunflower seeds.  It won't really make sense to remember to eat but it ending up to be less than 100 cal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-18 18:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's [this](http://imgur.com/a/TyI0X) tikka masala recipe posted recently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-09 19:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My worst was when I wanted to crack an egg in a bowl, but cracked it onto my counter next to the bowl. I didn't miss, my brain was just tired. It was like the walk of shame in cleaning form. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-02 19:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So hungry... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-02 19:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds delicious. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-02 18:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never done this, but why would you fold it in instead of mixing it with the dough before rolling it out? The closest I've done to this is a pie crust. Just curious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-02 18:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like threads like this are like psychoanalyzing a literary character, honestly. We only have a few paragraphs of their lives and make assumptions like this.  It's just an interesting thing to talk about, but I hope people don't take it too seriously to find an "answer" since we'll probably never know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-02 18:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who knows. 

I do know that someone very close to me had a weird sexual situation with their sibling when they were younger (no details) and it was because they were sexually abused by an older family member for a few years.  
It's obviously just speculation, but it would make sense if his sister had a sexual abusive history of some sort, because most people would not just choose their brother. And it could be that she never realized it was such, so she couldn't have brought it up. I definitely know victims who barely knew they were when it was much more subtle, like no penetration. The same goes for OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-02 17:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they meant that someone in her past that *isn't* her brother might have taken advantage of her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 01:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously. I get bulk even though my hair is less than a foot long, just because I bleach so often.  I get a huge tub of bleach for $15, easily will do a few feet of hair.  Mix a dark blue dye with cheap conditioner... where did 3 boxes per foot come from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there something that will protect my ends while bleaching my roots? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-17 20:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been bleaching my hair white for a while, and although it's short, the ends of my hair have been through more bleach than the rest of it. When I bleach my roots, the rest of it does get some bleach, no matter how much I try to avoid it. Is there something I can put in my hair that will protect the rest of my hair, at least partially stopping it from bleaching? Oils? I know people put vaseline to protect the skin... would that help? I don't mind washing my hair a few times afterwards to get it out. Cholesterol treatment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-17 19:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it's contemporary and it should break the boundaries and all of that, but I agree. It's more distracting than anything, especially using such delicate materials... It just looks like the ink (glaze? paint?) couldn't be controlled. I think it's supposed to juxtapose the whole delicate thing with such a rugged subject, but it loses that with such splotchiness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-06 22:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The other thing would be to make friends with burners! If you live in a large city, there's usually some type of burning man community. Also, BM decomp time is coming up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 07:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, as someone who is getting a major in art, it has confused me too. 

It depends on the school. Some schools have more of a focus on techniques, and others are more conceptually based.  It depends on the teacher on how they grade you.  With some teachers, you can be really shitty technically but if you can explain your choice, then it can go over well. People will probably point out that that's just learning how to bullshit, but if you're paying to learn how to bullshit then that's your choice.  
The confusion is why some teachers decide to do the attendance thing. 

Getting an art degree might not be as useful in the art world, like in the medical field, but you go (or, I go) to get the education.  In this world, what degree you get doesn't really matter as long as you get a degree. This isn't just for the arts, but you can say the same for a lot of majors.  But there's a lot of information that you can only get at a university.  It's the same with the opposite, that you can only get some information on the street, yet it's always better to have both in my opinion. 

It's not like one way to study art is better than the other, it just generally has different results.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 06:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's both, and it also depends on the class. For instance, in figure sculpture, attendance is crucial. Each class is about 5 hours long (once a week), so if you're one class behind on your sculpture (lets say it's a 3 session sculpture), your final piece is going to be a lot shittier. You also need to be in class because that's where the model is. Another example would be in printmaking, because you can't do a lot of the work without the machines. With most classes, though, you're there to take advice from the professor. It's stuff you can't get from a book. There generally aren't tests, but critiques, which happen more often than usual tests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-21 20:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This seems to happen to my bf, and he explains it similarly. If he builds up semen, and doesn't shoot then the liquids get absorbed and the proteins stay. If it happens enough, it'll get chunky. Can't back this up with any scientific evidence though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-24 20:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about melting ice? Unless you have to supply an art project or a huge camp or something, which should have had enough forethought about water in the first place.  I imagine price for ice should be ok, especially with the $20 charge for reentrance. If money is tight, when people start to leave on Sat and Sun, it felt like a lot of people were donating their leftover water, at least in my camp (~50 people). Obviously that would be the last thing to do on the list because no one likes a mooch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-24 20:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't watch Breaking Bad, but I imagine this could be a great way to meet people with similar interests too. It's different than bringing your tv/laptop or whatever and watching it in your tent. There's lots of movies that play, I think it's weird to judge when it's something someone really looks forward to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-23 10:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another point that might be uncommon to think about is allergies. Maybe OP can try switching toothpastes and see if that helps. Try one with minimal products that is SLS -free but still contains fluoride. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-23 07:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It can be really hard to track people down, and even moreso, it can be really hard to deal with people that don't want to change.  I have a few friends that have loved ones/parents whom are homeless (schizophrenia), but they can't hold them down even if they love them. They have seen doctors, but it's hard to remember to take medications, or not believe in them anymore. People get caught up in crime and whatnot too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 19:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Potatoes have more potassium than a banana! If we're going cost effective. Also, for me, I feel like the sweetness of coconut water helps with achyness for me. Apparently the body doesn't need sugar for that instant boost feeling, but just needs to taste it on the tongue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 20:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like lemon would be bad for the face, but hands can take a beating so I wouldn't worry that much. I always worry the pushing back stick could be pushed back too far if I didn't know what I was doing, so that's why using my own fingers would work better for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-18 03:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was just an unnecessary detail, at least in the title. "Some random brown haired guy..." would not be in the title normally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 20:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a girl who has sex with girls, her problems seem so strange to me.  Girls tend to be around the same size. I haven't heard any lesbians ever say that fingers/mouth seem too small. Have you tried focusing on her g-spot? It isn't too far away and adds to the girth feeling of it all. Aside from that, it doesn't seem like a physical problem but an emotional one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 20:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is the Braun worse? I use one, and it's terribly painful but I use it anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 20:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard this about shaving, but not waxing! There was a post a while ago about a strippers regimen to shaving. I believe it was to soften hair with oil for 10 minutes, use men's shaving cream, use rubbing alcohol after, and then use the deoderant. I've done this, which was amazing. But I wonder if it's true about waxing as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 20:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On topic of coconut oil: it's comedogenic, so it can make lots of people prone to breakouts. It's great for some (including me and SO), but just a warning! It would be especially horrible to try just a few days beforehand and break out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-11 01:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oops, I meant correcting to be able to check people out! I guess the "fuck what others think of me" thing is a big thing, I forgot, heh. It's just such an instinct not to look right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-11 01:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's how I feel. Same age too... I don't really check guys out I guess, but when I catch myself looking at a guy for a while I realize I could never do that to a girl! Do you try to correct it or anything? To "force" yourself to check them out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-11 01:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the weird thing... I have more gay/bi friends than straight. I've also had plenty of experience with both genders for my age (21). I'm more attracted to girls than not. I don't know what it is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I [F] still feel weird about checking girls out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 23:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm okay with looking at guys, but with girls I feel shy and maybe even feeling like its wrong. I think it stems from trying to hide it as a kid, but I know it's okay to do it now! Yet, I feel so embarrassed to still.

I was at a party yesterday with tons of half naked to naked who I'm certain would be okay with me checking them out, yet I couldn't. But it's with clothes girls too. Just checking out, not oogling. I feel like I need to avert my eyes. 

What do I need to accept? Can anyone relate?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 02:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most SSRIs seem to help me with my anxiety and depression, but I lose my appetite / don't feel hungry. I have weird side effects though, since Adderall helped my hunger which is the opposite of what it would usually do. I had to stop taking it because it made my heart beat too fast, though. Everyone's experience is different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 18:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, on the topic of soy sauce. Don't be afraid to use it as an ingredient. I see a lot of people just pouring it on rice, which as a Japanese lady, is weird! Teriyaki sauce is easy, for instance, and uses a bunch of it. Making stir fry too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 18:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The real stuff is sooo much better.  If you decide you can't handle the instant stuff, miso ( paste) is probably still as filled with sodium. The best instant stuff is by Miyasaka if you did go that route though. It's in little cubes but has a ra decent amount of extra stuff to make it good, like dried leek. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 08:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Japanese (or asian, i suppose) cuisine in general. The one downfall in Japanese cooking is the amount of sodium. So... A plus for op! Miso is great too. I use it as a dip for cucumbers, and there's miso soup too. The Japanese have different types of pickling, and kimchi should have a bunch of sodium too. Salted fish is popular. I'd say to look at foods near the sea... I'm just most familiar with Japanese. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-04 04:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard that putting in conditioner before you go swimming (and not washing it out) can protect your hair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-03 07:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Similarly, I used A D on my face and it went away within a few days.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-26 11:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious on how you would fix that. Don't premix, use a different noodle? 

On the other hand, it could work really well for a themed dinner too. I love that color. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-25 21:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our neighbors gave us a couch after all of us had left and got us a big red area on the MOOP map.

My boyfriend and I were actually running a tiny bit short, and a few campmates were leaving a few days early and actually asked if anyone wanted water. In that case, I think it's fine. We got in a last shower or something, and some water for the way home.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-24 19:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. My bf is a freckly burn-y type, and he applies it on me so that definitely helps get the hard to reach places. I had no idea about the time to kick in, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Her coal black eyes... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 23:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 23:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's no good for me but I don't have SD. I'm not sure how it works, but I was wondering if it relates to (what I've heard of) the antifungal properties of it. 

I feel like it's worth a shot, since it is so multipurpose that you wouldn't have to waste a whole product. But great info-- definitely patch! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 22:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds great. I'll pick that up.  I haven't done much research on the wipes, and what I did see was pretty expensive (Sephora stuff).

And thanks! I'll stick to the spray. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skincare for festivals / desert? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 21:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to Burning Man in a month for a week. I went last year but I felt like I could do better with cleansing.  I know at festivals I am extremely lazy at cleansing as I don't even have a sink to clean my face. I do have a solar shower bag but I only used it every few days.  Are there any recommendations for cleaning cloths? I bring baby wipes for my body but I'm not sure if that's best for my face. 

The environment will be strange, as it's in a desert. It wasn't as drying as I thought it would be.  The dust there is alkaline so even better than moisturizer was vinegar (maybe it's like the Aztec mask?). Any tips for that? Maybe toning with ACV?

On sunscreen-- I used Neutrogena spray sunscreen and didn't get burnt. I haven't read much besides "don't use it" on here, but I feel like it's much easier to reapply to my whole body and I would with the normal creamy sunscreens. I have a sample of Neutrogena's helioplex that I'll use for my face. Should I still perhaps apply a cream sunscreen to my shoulders?

And any other tips would be helpful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 21:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My boyfriend has it on his face and scalp, and he uses coconut oil! Of course, if it breaks you out, then stop using it. But it seems like he was cured of it. He's pretty low maintenance so he used it after he shaved, like once a week. He didn't wash it off or anything, so maybe before bedtime? It worked better than the prescription soaps and shampoos he's used. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 07:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know about tattoos, but scars heal horribly at BM. My bf got a few scratches a few years ago and they're still a bit keloid, and usually his skin heals great. I would wait, you wouldn't want a raised tattoo for life I imagine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 06:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The facial moisturizer is a little thick for my liking. I'm not used to how much facial moisturizers feel so I don't have much to compare it to. I've had a sample of a serum which was nice, but too expensive for me. It's much thicker than that, and the serum soaked in pretty quickly compared to the St Ives. I'd prefer a lotion a bit thinner, at least in the morning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 05:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes sense. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 05:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand that using the same line doesn't matter, but I was wondering more about if switching types of cleansers, for instance, could be less effective or more drying or whatever else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is mixing products ok? Also, St Ives Moisturizer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 05:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still have half my old Boscia facial cleanser, which works, but it seems CeraVe works for me as well and it's much cheaper. I'm wondering if theres any problem with mixing products, i.e. Boscia in the morning and CeraVe at night. I also like to keep a cleanser in the bath and one in the shower so I don't have to move stuff.

Also, does anyone use St Ives moisturizer? I know CeraVe is the popular option here, but I ordered a new St Ives moisturizer before I found SCA because there were many good reviews on Amazon. I'm curious about the CeraVe moisturizer but I have way too much St Ives to try it right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 00:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use it on everything. I think it's gentle enough to do that as I never felt it to be drying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-13 08:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I use the Aztec healing clay on my face, I don't see much of a difference but I definitely do with my chest and back. I also use witch hazel on them once or twice a day with a cotton ball, and it seems to help. There's so much dirt left on the cotton balls. It's also a lot easier than trying to use a cleanser on the parts when not showering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 19:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Californian, I feel the same way. In the last quake a few weeks ago, I told my SO that our neighbor must've shut the door loudly (we share a wall). He told me it was an earthquake. 

The only one I really noticed was visiting my grandparents a few years ago. They had a bunch of glass cabinets and things that shook loudly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-03 08:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can get one online for pretty cheap with free shipping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-23 11:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super weird one was some 5 year old dream that had as much crush-y feelings a 5 year old could have on Darla from the little rascals. 

The next was Amy lee from evanescence which I'm pretty embarrassed about but I was 11. Why are most of these answers totally cool? Not that she's still totally hot though. Them eyes... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-23 11:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My lesbian friend didnt even realize she was gay until she was 17! She never had a boyfriend either. Before she came out to me, I teased her about being gayer than me when she asked if I had heard the new Tegan and Sara album (and liking cats, and being a women's studies major...) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-21 00:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's half/half... Briefly looking it up, she was cut under her eye. I don't think lip injections were needed to fix that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-08 01:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Following the guide, I definitely think I have shallow breasts. The recommendations have been really helpful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-08 01:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you mean the Juna would potentially have that result, or the current bra is doing that? I hadn't ordered it (yet), so I'm just curious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 22:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I scoop/swooped completely, and didn't rearrange the material, my nipple kind of rests on top of the bra... but otherwise, I did. It's always a good reminder though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 22:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious, is there a name for our boob shape? I see that the overflow is common for those full on top, but my nipple is definitely about to pop at any moment in this one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
