<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1637</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 17:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The concepts of the Commonwealth vaults had a lot of potential, but the execution was god-awful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 15:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The environment of NV was less enjoyable than those of Fo3 and Fo4, but you have to admit it was well-executed. It really did feel like a wild wild western wasteland. It's just that you and I don't like the Old West genre.

Fo4 tried for a cross between the "film-noir" and "revolutionary America" themes, which are some of my favorite genres, and I think that for the most part they failed. Nick Valentine, for example, was great in theory but poorly implemented. He was too unambiguously good to fit the mold of the detective noir antihero, and any "investigation" quests turned out to be "go here, kill everything." The lighting was often inappropriate, though to be fair I was impressed by how often they managed to produce chiaroscuro considering how difficult lighting systems can be to get right.

Overall, I think Bethesda is better at gameplay and has a lot of really good ideas about story and setting. Obsidian's concepts are less interesting, but their execution and writing are incredible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 15:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a poor choice on Bethesda's part. It would have taken maybe 2 or 3 man-hours to write a conclusion for that story. Just add like 2 more terminals explaining how the residents arrived and got acclimated, and then how their society collapsed. 

Instead, they opted for the vault to be unfinished when the bombs fell. It was a lazy design choice and a complete waste of a potentially good vault idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 05:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm very happy with Bethesda's improvements on the combat mechanics and leveling system. The perk chart is miles ahead of number-juggling skills, the gunplay is decent, and unarmed combat finally feels like actually punching someone to death.

But the story in Fo4 is terribly implemented. Lack of ending cards is just one of Fo4's storytelling failures. Even more striking is the lack of interesting vaults. Vaults in New Vegas and Fo3 were really some of the best parts of those games, because they gave the player a sense of exploration, discovery, and often horror. 

The Commonweath has 5 vaults: 111, 114, 95, 75, and 81. 111 has a backstory, but it's very shallow and immediately apparent to the player. There is no exploration or discovery. 

114 had some exposition for its story, found on terminals, but never followed through with a conclusion of what happened to it. It set up an experiment of tricking pampered rich people into living in thrifty conditions, with a crazy super-libertarian overseer, but then neglected to give me any information about how that turned out or how Skinny Malone came to occupy it.

81 was... ok. The secret was a good idea in theory, but the entire experimental subsection of the vault felt extremely linear. You can't have an authentic sense of discovery with an on-rails experience.

95 and 75 were very well done. Especially in 95, both the dark secret and the pacing of the reveal were excellent. But even 95, which was the best Commonwealth vault imo, was not as well executed as the good vaults from 3 or NV.

In Fallout 3, we had 101, 112, 87, 92, 106 and 108. Each of them had interesting stories to tell, with a beginning, middle and end to be discovered mostly at the player's leisure. They all started by instilling a sense that "something is wrong here," and provoked curiosity and encouraged the discovery of each vault's secret agenda.

New Vegas had vaults 3, 19, 21, 22, 34 and, the most brilliantly told vault story, vault 11. With the exception of 21, each of these 6 provoked the player's curiosity, and even in vaults 3 and 34 where the reveals fell rather flat. And both of those exceptions contained valuable loot, so the player did not feel as if time was wasted in exploring them.

The lack of meaningful endings was an awful design choice on Bethesda's part, and their lack of consideration for player choice (in an open-world RPG no less) made their dungeons feel way to linear for the player to really explore.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I wanted a lot of a drug, what's to stop me from going to several different doctors and getting several different prescriptions for the same medication? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 00:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 00:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's such bullshit. Like, why would I be looking for a temporary solution? A problem is only temporary if the solution is permanent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 14:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The atmosphere of the Third Rail is so perfect. Dim lights and shady people, a singer with a golden voice and a rough cockney barkeep. It's so noir, I love it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 07:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  non-government

Well technically... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 02:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Several songs are the same, but there is much more variety. Have you been to The Third Rail in Goodneighbor? There's a singer, Magnolia, who performs in the bar. Pay her a visit and DCR will automatically add her songs to the lineup. She's got a gorgeous voice and sings a bunch of (original!) songs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Soundtrack Appreciation Thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 01:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, this soundtrack is amazing. Leagues ahead of Fo3 and NV. Magnolia has a heavenly voice, and her songs contribute hugely to the overall "noir" atmosphere. There are some misses (Crazy He Calls Me is still super annoying) but most of the tracks are really catchy. My personal favorite is The End of the World. So what did you like about the soundtrack? What did you dislike? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 21:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trademark, not copyright.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 21:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have such a pretty flag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 09:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ecuador. I never declared war, only conquered 1 state early on because Peru DoW'd me. To this day I cannot replicate the incredibly lucky success of events that somehow turned Ecuador into a WP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 04:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Limey protestant bastard! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 04:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> White cards: 

JOHN CENA

JAVERT

HERCULES MULLIGAN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 04:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ____! My kingdom for ____!

My Richard III cast played with this as a custom card and it works really well.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 03:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> White: "The Ol' Razzle-Dazzle"

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 00:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not if I was referring to the color! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 22:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big Bohemian Blob, Big Basque Blob *and* Big Burgundy Blob? Wow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SPOILER I was really disappointed in one part of the main plot... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 21:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kellog's memory sequence. When Nick told me we were going to the Memory Den I was ecstatic. I was going to get to explore the troubled memories of a ruthless murderer! Maybe even relive my own memories from before the war! I was so eager to continue the quest, to see what the devs came up with, to discover more about the characters and story. In my mind, I was going into part 2 of Tranquility Lane, my favorite part of Fallout 3. 

Instead, I got an on-rails sequence of boring cutscenes. Yes, Kellog's life was tragic. Yes, I was curious what happened to my son and the Institute. But it could have been done *so much better.* Tranquility Lane had me slowly figuring out the horror of a seemingly perfect world, discovering my father and the secrets in the minds of the subjects. It was engaging! And fun! But Kellog's mind made me sit through cutscenes without any interaction. That's not how you engage an audience in a video game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 19:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/NegativeWithGold  huh, interesting.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 03:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude the "nest of spicery" line made me gag every time I heard it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 12:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jack Nicholson called, he wants his eyebrows back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 23:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's like seeing a battlefield amputation and saying "cutting off someone's leg isn't medicine."

She was not a miracle worker. She couldn't magically heal the damage of the tech bubble. The fact that she managed to salvage as much of the company as she did is damn impressive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 15:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frankly at this point it is irresponsible of candidates to deny climate change for votes. Climate change deniers wouldn't exist if there was nobody feeding them false information. Paul handled it well politically but it was unethical of him to give credence to a provably wrong faction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 15:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm inclined to agree with guyinokc. In the end, this girl is going to feel like a victim and she'll blame Neil, but if he had treated her with more respect she might feel like *she* failed and blame her own performance.

The best evidence in support of your position is when two people of opposite views treat each other as respectable equals and the one with your views comes out on top. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 15:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the last thing we're trying to do here is create a "safe space" lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 15:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It had to be Mormons, didn't it? Couldn't even be proper protestants?

Like I love the guys, but their belief system is super wonky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 15:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes there's a way to do it, depending on the chair, but in general even when it's possible it isn't worth it. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 07:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill O'Reilly, who calls himself a "Five-star General in the War on Christmas" said that there was nothing offensive in Starbucks's cup design. I'd wager that most other conservative personalities feel the same. The "War on Christmas" is about the secularization of the holiday season and the supposed "suppression" of religious beliefs. It's about taking the "Christ" out of "Christmas." It's not about taking the snowflakes and Santa out of Christmas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 03:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah the moderators are very good so far, they've asked solid questions on the specifics of each candidate's economic plan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 03:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> high energy I like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 22:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Played **Seven Wonders** a few days ago, and I loved it! It's so simple but I can see how deep it is, guessing what your opponents go for, blocking them from playing good cards, keeping track of all the hands. It was a lot of fun, and I came in second! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I like myself best when I hang out with bad influences </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 07:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd really like some advice on how to handle this. See, I'm a Freshman in college, and I know this girl across the hall, lets call her T. T and I are both very introverted, and kind of dorky. Both Engineering majors, we share a lot of interests, etc. I really like her, and she likes me a lot, but our conversations always feel very forced because we each put so much value on the other's opinion. I really feel bad after hanging out with T, because I'm so painfully awkward around her that it makes me hate myself.

However, there's these other people in my hall, call them E, P, and D. These are party people. They're all Liberal Arts majors, they party every weekend and they are possessed by these petty interpersonal dramas. They're pretty much the definition of "the wrong crowd." 

But they make me feel good about myself. Confident. I know I'm smarter, more responsible, more mature, more kind, and all-around better than them. They make me happy to be me. I know I'm supposed to surround myself with people I like, who will help me improve myself. But much as I hate these people, and much as they are definitely not my crowd, they like me and they make me happy.  

I have no idea what to do. E and P are very happy people, whereas T is not totally satisfied. Should I hang out with E and P to learn from them how to be happy? I'm worried that I'll also pick up some things that I don't want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I please be evil? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 06:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "evil" might not be the right word for it, but... I'm in a state where I have 2 options of how to feel about the world: sad or angry. See, I can't seem to relate to other people at all. Most of the people I meet are completely unlike me, and when I do find like-minded people I realize that they make me uncomfortable. So there's a fundamental disconnect between "me" and "the rest of the world"; someone's doing something wrong here, because there's a problem. 

Now, if that problem is with me, I'm going to be sad. I'm going to hate myself for being a misanthropic sociopath who can't interact with others comfortably. I'm not going to hate anyone, in fact I make a point of trying to love everyone I see. So I'm going to get anxious about making other people feel uncomfortable, I'm going to avoid pushing my problems onto others, I'm going to try to take the rational, isolationist view of the world.

But if the problem is with the world, *then* I'm going to be really fucking mad. I have this incredible pent-up rage inside me, something that I've been keeping under control for a decade. If I say that the world is wrong and I am right, I will hate everyone and everything. I will hate people who are better than me out of envy, I will hate people who are worse out of disgust. I will wish the most cruel and painful torture on every goddamn person that isn't me. 

Nobody would know my thoughts, though. If I hate people, I don't care about making them feel comfortable. I'm going to talk to whoever the fuck I want because I want to, and if they feel uncomfortable then good because they all fucking deserve to. I'm going to use my acting skills to make myself appear charming and likeable without any attempt to be genuine, and if you're lucky I'll just use you as a tool and not psychologically and socially torture you for fun. If I'm angry, I'm going to hate the world and make no attempt to comply with it. It will still be controlled rage, but now I will indulge those furious desires.

I think it's wrong to be angry, to hate the world. But if I was angry I know I wouldn't care about right or wrong, logically or morally. I would just hate, and hate, universally, hate others for not conforming to my worldview, hate my worldview for not conforming to reality, hate myself for being such a sickeningly evil human being.

But *it would be so easy*. I could decide to go into "hate-mode" any moment. I'm so scared that at some point I'll snap out of this funk I'm in and look back and think "my god, I'm so ashamed of what I've done."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 06:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much for the feedback. Your suggestion for the flagship is a huge relief, I was worried that giving them too many Mech-Inf based abilities would make them unplayably inflexible. The -1 CC is also a great idea, since it will mean the players are better off with a small empire. 

What would you think about changing the racial ability from "2 Mech Infantry" to "4 Ground Forces?" It would make them much more vulnerable to have only ground forces, but would also allow them to improve their planets more. It could go along with the theme of a "Worker race" or a "terraforming race". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Custom Race: The Poncho Autocracy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 03:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Before the Twilight Wars, the Poncho were a very primitive tribal people. They lacked even the most basic of technologies. When a group of Hylar deserters landed on 2-Sco, they found themselves charmed by the simple Poncho, and resolved to "uplift" them from their barbaric past. 

 The Poncho were skeptical of the "witchcraft" the Hylar showed them, until one researcher introduced them to the concept of mechanical wheels. The Poncho were awed by the simple, elegant efficiency of the wheel. They eagerly learned all the Hylar had to offer, and within a few generations had gone from a backwards race of pseudo-sentients to a civilization that could rival the galaxy's great empires. They revere the Wheel above all things, almost religiously, as a symbol of the knowledge that showed them the light.

(Note: The backstory was kind of cobbled together, I'm mostly looking for mechanics and balance feedback.)

**Racial Ability:** Every 2 Mech Infantry on a planet increase its resource or influence value by 1



**Racial Tech 1:** (6) Your Mech Infantry may fire PDS shots

**Racial Tech 2:** (4) Each of your Destroyers may fire a pre-combat shot

**Representative 1:** (C) +1 vote for each refinery or colony you control

**Representative 2:** (S) Assassinate up to 2 representatives. You must abstain.

**Representative 3:** (C) +4 Gain 1 vote for each PDS or Mechanized Infantry unit you control

**Leaders:** Scientist, Agent, General

**Home System:** 2-Sco (3,3), 1-Sco (1,2)

**Starting Forces:** 1 SD, 3 Ground Forces, 1 Mechanized Infantry, 1 Carrier, 1 Destroyer, 1 PDS


**Flagship:** 6x3, gain 1 Trade Good for every hit by this ship

**Starting Techs:** Hylar V Assault Laser, Enviro Compensator

What do you think? They're supposed to be more of a "tall" race, who can succeed with a small number of systems if they are properly developed. I feel like the first Racial tech may be a bit overpowered, but I'm not sure how to nerf it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 22:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ACNL is a very idealistic game. It's nice, in a way, but the lack of conflict makes it less engaging IMO. I'd like to see villagers having direct confrontations with each other, and the mayor having to sort it out one way or another.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 22:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try Rune Factory! RF4 has you play the prince of a town, complete with a PWP system, and includes combat, farming and relationship-building. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 22:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snowball fights in winter, squirt gun fights in summer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 22:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New ordinances (unlockable?) that determine the weather. Like Rainy/Sunny would increase/decrease the chance of rain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 08:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tbh it's a very smart strategy. Trump operates like a force of nature, unstumpable, the only way to not get destroyed is to stay out of his way. Trump is focusing on attacking Hillary right now, but if he saw Sanders doing shit like this he would definitely respond in kind. Which would result in Sanders fighting Trump, the rest of the GOP probably following Trump's lead and fighting Sanders too, which makes Hillary look "above the fray" and more presidential.

If this is Hillary, then props to her for thinking of a way to get Trump to do her dirty work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 06:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Republicans lose because the party leadership is so afraid of a PR backlash that it refuses to fight. If the Republican establishment had any balls then they'd force a government shutdown to assert their authority. Sure, it'd be unpopular, but it would also show that they aren't weak. Instead they let themselves be cucked by the Democrats who do whatever they want and then say "whatcha gonna do about it?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 03:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm inclined to agree. I think Trump himself is a joke, but his campaign is extraordinarily well-run and his ground game is phenomenal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 23:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correction, isn't a scalar a one-dimensional, *one-entry* vector? Maybe that makes more sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 22:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't a scalar is a one-dimensional vector? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there any way to get Adventures without connecting to the servers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 06:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought Spore 7 years ago and I wanted to get back into it. Couldn't find the disk, so I torrented it. Is there any way to download Adventures without using the Spore servers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 16:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah driving in Europe is 21 for a lot of countries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 20:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't be so sure. FiveThirtyEight just published a piece saying that they might have originally been wrong about Cruz's chances.

EDIT: They didn't "just" release it, it was published on the 16th </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 13:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scientifically speaking, yes, your analysis is accurate.

But of the ~100 Billion humans that have ever lived, 7 Billion have not died. So *statistically* speaking I have a 7% chance of immortality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 22:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not right to criticize him for "not answering the question." He wasn't being evasive, he was making a point about the arrogance of the moderators. People complain about debaters not answering the questions because it's dishonest and shows an inability to think on one's feet, but Cruz's response didn't convey any of that. So don't go after him for "not answering the question" like it's the cardinal sin of debating etiquette.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 18:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  forgetting to answer the policy-related question he was asked!

Oh come on. He used his time to call out the moderators and then when he tried to answer the question they stopped him because he was "out of time." That wasn't his fault, it was the moderators being petty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 18:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Ben Carson isn't only dumb as a sack of rocks

The guy's a brain surgeon. He headed a department at Johns Hopkins. Saying he's wrong about politics is one thing, but it is inexcusable to call Ben Carson "dumb." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 07:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were softballs because those are the most prominent criticisms the candidates faced, and they were doubtless very well prepared to answer them. The questions gave them an opportunity to refute common points against them by reciting a rehearsed statement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 04:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he was making the point that the mainstream media is very left-biased. The Democrats got softball questions which they answered easily, and the GOP got... insults phrased as questions. A good moderator asks hard questions, but there were no hard questions asked tonight. There were only insults with question marks at the end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 17:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably because a) the church itself possibly hasn't done anything wrong, it may be all the employees, and b) because the church, as a corporate entity, does not make any yearly profit and as such is a non-profit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 00:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure how it would get back into the bloodstream, so I would guess not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 04:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Money is a fungible quantity, so which specific dollars are used is irrelevant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 18:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They received money in return for fetus body parts. Whether that was a reimbursement to cover the procedure's costs or a sale for profit is up for debate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 17:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the answers you're getting are ludicrously biased to the left. I'm going to try to give a non-partisan explanation. 

Planned Parenthood is an independent organization that provides women's health care. One of the services it provides is abortion. A large portion of the country is opposed to abortion on moral grounds (they believe it involves the killing of a human being). 

However, Planned Parenthood is given federal government funding every year. Many people believe that a practice as controversial as abortion should not be funded by the federal government, essentially arguing against their tax dollars being used for what they consider murder.

On top of that ever-present controversy, there have been some videos released that caught Planned Parenthood executives talking about selling the body parts of aborted fetuses. These videos have been heavily edited, so their accuracy is subject to suspicion, but the primary claims of the videos have not been discredited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 16:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The duty of the prosecutor isn't to convict people of crimes, it is to discover the truth and represent the state. That doesn't always mean conviction. One high-profile example is in Ferguson last summer, when the prosecutor chose to present everything to the Grand Jury when he could have sent it to court by selectively presenting the evidence. His decision cost him the publicity of a televised trial, but likely saved the state a great deal of money as well.

Defense attorneys are not bound by such high standards. Their job is to get the best deal for their clients. Whatever the defendant deserves, their attorney will try to make their situation better, with no regard to how much it might cost the state or endanger the people. 

Ultimately, prosecutors serve the state and are beholden to the people they serve. Defense attorneys are beholden only to their clients. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 15:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah like how the viking Rus named it Russia instead of Slavia, or how the Franks renamed Gaul after themselves, or how Alexander the Great founded a shitload of cities named Alexandria in other countries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 19:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The difference between Ivory Coast and Ireland's flags is that Ivory Coast's is orange-white-green, and Ireland's is green-white-orange.

Still not as bad as Chad stealing Romania's flag though. Fucking Chad. Even as a country he's "that guy." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 19:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Richard: Your reasons are too shallow and too quick

Elizabeth: No, my reasons are too deep and dead,

Two deep and dead poor infants in their graves

Richard: **Harp not on that string, madam, for it is past!**

In a very serious scene, Richard says "oh my god shut up about your dead children that was one time ok" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 08:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude chill. I'm not a fan of British standards on American flags but the Kingdom of Hawaii chose to keep the British standard as part of their flag because it was a convenient symbol. It doesn't represent British dominion over the islands.

And maybe instead of insulting me and giving me a "derp" flair you could try having an actual discussion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 07:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rebellion maybe, but rebellion against the United States? That's not something that a state should be endorsing. As for biases, the only bias I have here is for my county. Call me crazy but I think that The United States of America should have a bias towards The United States of America. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 07:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hawaii gets a pass because it was a truly sovereign nation before it was annexed. The Maryland argument is totally nonsensical.

EDIT: And Texas had a different flag when it was the Republic of Texas. In any case, there's no problem with the flag representing something not explicitly American. It's when it endorses a violent, treasonous, clearly anti-American movement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 06:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know I'm going to get downvoted for this, but it has to be said. See, normally I'm all for state's rights. The federal government should mind it's own damn business and let the states do their jobs. 

But the confederate flag (actually the battle flag of northern VA but whatever) is a symbol of a group of states that *actively rebelled against the Union*. It is a symbol of secession and hatred towards the United States and, ultimately, a treasonous failed rebellion. Free speech is all well and good, unless it is speech that encourages people to revolt against the US. That shit shouldn't fly.

Allowing citizens to fly flags is one thing, but states? Should we really allow states to *represent themselves with the symbol of violent anti-American rebellion?* The South lost the civil war; the CSA was never recognized and the territory it claimed was occupied by the USA. Losers don't get to fly their flags.

Edit: I want to respond to all of these comments, they make really good points, but I can't because I was banned for this comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 22:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow that's a really pretty blob color... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 01:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. I'm not sure how narrow the language is, but there is a law that forbids payment in vouchers rather than money. It was written to check the corrupt business practices of coal companies that owned entire towns, and effectively prevented their employees from saving money.

2. I do remember one recent case where Football players at a college tried to unionize. They argued that they were *practically* employees, just not *technically*. And that the technical definition of employee was not readily applicable to their situation. A lot of it comes down to whether or not the players consider themselves employees.

3. Your RA argument is interesting, and frankly novel. I've never heard it before and it does bring up some valid points. My RA gets a paycheck, so at least at some colleges there is money being paid. I'll have to look into it, but it's a very good point.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 23:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not legal (or fair) for a company to pay employees with vouchers that can only be redeemed at businesses operated by the company. This is the same sort of situation. People have a right to economic freedom. By compensating athletes with "free" housing, meals and education, they deprive those athletes of their right to financial self-determination.

Employees have to be paid, and they have to be paid in *money*. By definition, and by law, money is the *only* legal tender for wages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 18:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is this "rest of the world" you speak of? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 19:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit that's some impressive progress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 08:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't entirely agree with you. First, I think Trump or Fiorina would give Clinton a run for her money in the general. Fiorina because she's a strong candidate (barring the track-record vulnerability) and Trump because, much as I may distrust the man, he's pretty much gaffe-proof at this point.

Second, I don't think it's at all likely that one of the current top 3 will win the primary. Trump has plurality support, but more primary voters would vote for ANYONE ELSE over him than would currently vote for him. If it comes down to Trump vs [any real GOP candidate] then Trump loses. The other two don't have nearly enough money to win a long campaign. Once the issue candidates start to drop out, the primary base will coalesce around a single establishment candidate (my money's on Rubio), who will accept the anti-establishment sentiment as warranted while reminding the people that they ought to pick a somewhat experienced person as the nominee. 

What frightens me is how readily people accept the Democratic "free candy" strategy. I can respect someone whose views differ from mine, but I can't respect people blindly accepting proposals without some critical thinking. It seems to me that the people want free stuff, and some people want power enough to offer it to them, but eventually we're going to get the bill, and we won't be able to pay for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 07:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really thought O'Malley stuck out as a strong mainstream alternative to Clinton. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 03:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's a classic liberal populist. "Vote for me, I'll give you a bunch of free shit!" Nothing is free, things like healthcare and college cost money. Where is that money coming from? "Uh..." 

He has no plan regarding foreign policy, despite the fact that that is the majority of the President's job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 05:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh shit, wow. That's terrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 04:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright is this actual cancer or "subredditcancer" cancer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 22:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Individually, there are news stations with conservative biases and ones with liberal biases. However, as a whole, the "mainstream media" has a very significant liberal bias. 

First, consider the major TV news agencies in the US. NBC, CNN, MSNBC, Fox News, ABC, and CBS. Only one of those has a conservative bias. And Fox News is widely (and pretty universally) regarded as an unreliable source of news. The most neutral of these stations is probably CNN, which has a mid-left-wing bias. So a citizen who wants the most neutral reporting (i.e. most citizens) has to go to a station with a *liberal* bias.

The left wing has a diversity in news reporting that the right wing lacks. They have reporting from "slightly left of center" all the way to "far-left." The right wing only has "far-right." So any viewers that are left of center are going to get their news from a liberal source. Any that are right of center, but closer to "slightly left of center" than "far-right," are going to get their news from a liberal source. The only people experiencing the conservative bias are those whose views range from "solidly conservative" to "far right."

So a greater proportion of the country receives news with a liberal bias than that which receives news with a conservative bias. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 21:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well on the one hand, I don't listen to music. On the other hand, I'm a virgin. Probably music, just in case I ever get the chance to have sex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 18:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought O'Malley did extremely well. He was professional, charismatic and, most importantly, made no terrible gaffes. Nothing about the debate made me think that O'Malley would drop out any time soon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 18:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He did stick to his guns, much to O'Malley's disappointment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 17:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too. I remember in elementary and middle school I had hobbies, I had friends, I absolutely devoured new books, and I got straight A's. In High School, I pretty much stopped reading, still had some hobbies, a few friends, and got B's.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 15:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think that's fair. She might be a snake, but Hillary *does* have the respect and fear of a lot of world leaders. 

Also, much as I may despise Iran, I have to admit that the people seem to be pretty supportive of their government. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 15:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Webb's answer to the greatest enemy question actually made me say "holy shit" out loud. Would've brought down the house in a GOP debate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 15:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Say what you want about Hillary, but the woman is respected and *feared* by more world leaders than any president since Reagan. If she ends up as president, at least our state department wouldn't totally collapse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 05:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a matter of fact I do. He graduated from Harvard Law school, and had the political intelligence to become the most powerful man in the world. It would be foolish to say that Barack Obama is not smart and capable. He has made a poor president because of his misguided political views and lack of experience in foreign affairs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 01:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did read the article, thank you very much, and condemning as it tried to be there was just nothing to implicate Jeb or his senior staff in this. In fact, I would wager that a seasoned political campaigner like Jeb would have planted someone with no traceable connection to himself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 00:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it's fair for us to villainize our opponents like that. I have no doubt that Mr. Biden is a very smart and capable man. However, he holds flawed positions on many issues and unless he comes to recognize and amend those flaws I cannot in good conscience support his candidacy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 00:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough, I'll amend my statement. Trump is not a conservative, nor is he a liberal, he is a self-serving populist snake who has no ideals and will say whatever makes people give him more power and money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 23:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The argument isn't whether he's running as a Republican, it's whether he *is* a Republican. I can call myself a Democrat all I want, but if I'm pro-life, pro-gun, small-government, anti-amnesty, ect. then I'm not really a Democrat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 23:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously guys? Gee, I wonder if the person who attends political rallies is also the sort of person who would volunteer on a political campaign?

There's no reason to believe she was a plant. She was probably just a politically active woman who wanted to call out Trump. This sort of shit makes /r/conservative look like /r/conspiracy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 21:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Democratic Party has a tendency to talk down to minorities. They do a lot of race-baiting to drum up enthusiasm for their candidates. It's so fucking condescending. They treat black and Hispanic citizens like children. 

I don't think I've really read any conservative articles about Carson that treat his race like it's a big deal, whereas the left just couldn't wait to rave about how Obama was to be "the first black president!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 21:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Biden at least seems like a decent person. Sanders is a self-important, holier-than-thou radical, and Hilary is just slimy. I'd pick any of the Republicans over a Democrat any day, but among the Democratic candidates he's the least repulsive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 15:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Horses are for pussies #RhodokLife. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-11 20:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Money is a good indication of who will win the primary, but usually once the GOP has a candidate they will get most of the supporters and money that the other candidates had left over. So I'm judging purely by personality and appeal to all voters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-11 09:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please remember, guys, that we're electing a *nominee*, not a *president.* I like Cruz, but I think that candidates like Rubio are much more electable than him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 19:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> \ Tea party

\ Vote with Democrats

kek </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 18:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Desteapta-te Romane, the Romanian national anthem. I'm on mobile, I'll post a link later. The best way to describe it is that it sounds "deliciously fascist." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 18:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think capitalism is fundamentally perfect, except that it makes the assumption that people are perfectly rational actors. Truth is, we're humans, and we're flawed, but we're pretty damn close to perfect rationality. So the ideal system would be to take capitalism and tweak it a bit to account for human error. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 18:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Selfish: I wish to be fluent in all human languages

Malicious: Entire leadership of the Chinese Communist Party simultaneously drops dead.

Good: Everyone is straight and cis forever (nothing against gay or trans people, but by God this would make everything simpler for everyone.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 18:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they are equally likely possibilities, which is still very frightening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 06:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Much as you may feel that Boehner was a poor Speaker, this decision to stay is good for the party. If he was going to leave when he said he would, then the election for Speaker would be a complete mess. The GOP, fractured between Tea Party and Moderates, would fail to form a consensus around a candidate. Then a handful of RINOs would throw their support behind a "moderate" Democrat and suddenly we don't have a Republican Speaker, even though we have a majority. 

Like him or not, Boehner is better than a Democrat, and staying on until he has a sound successor is a good idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 01:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hamilton is great, not only because it's a phenomenal show but also because the Founding Fathers were portrayed as minorities. It gives future productions a reason to cast race-blind. If all white guys had played the Founders, then future productions would ALWAYS cast white men, due to the racism and slavery issues of the time. But now any actor of any race can be justifiably cast as figures who were historically white.

While I normally don't like race-exclusive casting, I think Hamilton is a good case because it sets a precedent for the roles to be open to non white actors, and it won't exclude white actors because, let's face it, there aren't enough black and Hispanic boys in musical theatre to put on a non-white high school show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 23:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Nixon would have respected him a lot if he had done it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's going on in Egypt right now? Is there a functioning government? Is it a secular democracy, or an Islamic military autocracy, or...? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 15:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It strikes me that I haven't heard anything about Egypt in years. What's happening there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 17:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweater vest, Navy formal pants and pilot shades. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 06:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you read it? Because it does have some dick jokes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 02:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Failer you and your group are amazing.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 20:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he fucked his maid? I don't recall exactly but references were made to Hamilton's Reynolds Pamphlet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 18:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Textbook strawman. The Anchor Baby amendment is supported by the Tea Party, who would never endorse Arnold's candidacy (too moderate). The strategist/intelligentsia Republicans would *think about* the candidacy amendment, but wouldn't even consider an Anchor Baby amendment. The real movers and shakers in the GOP are looking for a legislative and executive immigration solution, not a constitutional one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 18:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nobody should be killed for their faith. His statements towards Christians could just as easily have applied to Muslims (well Sunni Muslims at least). This act of violence was not only an attack on Christianity, but an attack on all people of faith. Thank you for your condolences.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 17:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was actually talk of a constitutional amendment to change this back when he was governor of California. He was nationally well-known, a popular governor of a normally Democratic state, and connected with the traditionally liberal Hollywood. Until that cheating scandal broke he was such a good GOP presidential candidate that the party floated the idea of *amending the constitution* to allow non-native citizens to run. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 17:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean yeah it's red, but speaking as someone who lives in the metro DC area I don't think there's any chance DC will vote Republican this election.

EDIT: My bad I misread the map </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 17:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know DC gets 3 electoral votes, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 17:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you conquer the Asiatic flatlands? One steppe at a time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 06:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahaha but seriously remove kebab. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 02:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Head of Church... 

I understand though, I'm just poking fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 01:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think most of us recognize the need for real, physical, military action against Islamic extremists in the Middle East. But it's good to poke fun at ourselves every once in a while, so we laugh and make DEUS VULT memes with the understanding that, when it's time to get serious, we really do need to take up arms to defend the faith. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 01:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well how do you feel about the Queen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any ships that focus on "suicide bomb" Zoltans? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 17:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since Zoltans deal 15 damage to everyone in a room upon death, a fun-yet-completely-impractical strategy would be to get 4 Zoltans, a clone bay, and a 4-man teleporter and board the enemy ship for the sole purpose of letting your Zoltans die and take the enemies with them. 

Are there any modded ships that focus on this sort of build? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 06:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to agree with you, so here's the argument that changed *my* view:

Rangers need to be able to communicate with local populations in order to be as versatile as they are. Adding a woman to the squad would improve its communicative abilities immensely, especially in traditionalist cultures where men and women have very different roles in society. In these cultures, a female Ranger would be able to gather more information from female locals than a male would. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 03:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If taxpayers didn't get to choose where their tax money went, we wouldn't be a democracy.

EDIT: Weird this is the third time this has happened. I post a comment to /r/conservative, it receives an initial positive response (~10 upvotes) then after a few hours it's been reduced to negative karma. Not saying this is brigading or anything, just pointing out a pattern I observed.

EDIT2: Back to +5, it probably just fluctuates slowly on this sub.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 02:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Compromise" is agreeing not to force taxpayers to fund procedures that fully HALF of them find morally repulsive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 21:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't buy a hat, but I did start wearing this grey newsboy cap I got in London a few years ago. I never wore hats because MFA insists that hats are a bad idea, but these past few days I've felt like "fuck it, it's raining out and I like this look." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 18:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I listen to the audiobooks. If it turns out to be one I particularly like, I will then go and read a physical copy. For Lolita, Heart of Darkness, The Man Who Was Thursday and a couple others I stopped listening to the audiobook when it became evident that this was a *really* good book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
