<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5711</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 01:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my eye balls they bleed that was fucking hard to see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 01:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh I'm sad for you 

hahahaha  what ever. go blow a  goat  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-30 06:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> after reading this i feel the need to go for a run  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-30 06:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why to go OP your promoting this guy.
hahahaha i actually  want to know how many contacts he gets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-30 06:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this needs a NSFW tag IMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Meta] if obesity really is genetic...... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-30 06:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i hear all the time that obesity is genetic ( its not btw).

so my thinking is if it really is genetic how come so many countries have VERY little to no obese or overweight people * cough ...cough japan.


and why is it a generally a "new thing" about 50 years but still. 


in the 1920's the worlds biggest person was like 400 pounds and that was a freak show. 

maybe its just me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-29 04:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but if she was switched at birth it wouldn't matter about ultra sounds and stuff.

i think she means what if she went home with the wrong parents  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't care if your sick. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-28 23:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have no sympathy or empathy for people who are sick and don't want to do anything about it. 

like for example: my mother has blisters all over her hands and feet open sores with puss its been 2 months. She complains all day about it but REFUSES to go to a doctor or an ER we live in canada its free 

so NO i don't care your hurting because you wont do anything about it. 

and that goes for anyone who is sick and complaining but won't help your self.


PS its not all sick people if your disabled and in pain i empathize I'm in a wheelchair i know pain . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-28 23:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if being fat is Genetic how come in 1912 the worlds fattest person was about 400 pounds.

also how come these genetics just kicked in lets say in the last 50 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-27 01:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 30LBs in one day thats just over a pound a hour your body would literally colaps onto its sent your bones and muscles couldn't handle the rapid change .

Also my grandmother has an auto immune disorder and a thyroid disorder. she is so thin she's practically see through and she eats more then my cousin who is a football player. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-27 00:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dildo: $25

The look on her face: Priceless  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-26 23:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wonder if the front looks the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-26 23:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> better question where did she find the fish and is it what brought her to the ER. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-26 02:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sorry I have a disability (physical) and I use a voice recognition software and it SUCKS at punctuation and grammar I'm really sorry I'm still new to it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your a mom not Albert Einstein </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-26 02:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> stop treating me like i don't know anything because your a parent and I'm not. 


Im in university and your living with our parents and your only 18 
and a grade 9 yes NINE drop out.

you are not smarter then me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-26 02:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have been laughing for like 00.5 seconds and that sir is a great feet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-25 22:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> waaa waaa waaa cry me a river. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-25 00:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fit Guy: i don't find fat girls attractive 


Fat girl: how dare you thin privilege thin privilege you are and ass whore you are discriminating agenst us 


Fat girl: i don't like fat guys 
Other fat girl: you shouldn't have to settle for less its just who you find sexy

fit guy:WTF </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-24 01:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did you both have fun? 
are you both ok with it?

if those are both Yes WOOT good for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-24 01:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to be complealty honest he sounds depressed. In my experience this really is only going to get worst. I really home that you sit down tonight and really weigh out your options time and life are short you need to find a way to be happy think about your self before him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I cant help you anymore </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-24 01:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My S.O has a lot of mental health problems she's always telling me that one one will help her.

The problem is we cant help her anymore she will not take ANY medication even if it helps and it does.
She REFUSES counselling or therapy and will not even consider going and so the doctors place her in the hospital she then stays for a few days then lies her way out.
then she gets really angry that no one will help her and gloating that she was right and they won't do anything for her.
she just doesn't realize that there are NO MORE options for her.
She won't take any help thats offered and does not see that they are giving every option they had and you won't exempt any of it. 

P.S i have a software that types for me do to a physical disability and its really messed up with punctuation so i apologize its all messed up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How long till TITP finds this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 05:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 00:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i don't know why your getting down voted 
its normal to have a favourite child and that is just the way it it 
as long as you don't neglect your other children its all good  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 23:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i would do the same every single time i got woken up i would report it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 04:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just because theres an age difference doesn't mean she a troll. My mom was 23 when she got married and my dad was like 35  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 04:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't appear to be worried or at a hospital. Are you ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 04:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i was frightened about what was happening there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 04:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww so cute </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: What is a feminist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 04:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i cant find a simple answer about EVERYTHING that a feminist believes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 04:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> are you being a one and done-r because i am thinking of only having one because i want them to have 100% of my attention  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 04:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Failed to open page 4X </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is my daughters "friend" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 04:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok so i am married to a woman have been for a year. 

My mother knows I'm a lesbian has for a long time and my mom is  very ok with gay people but is still introducing my wife as my friend. We just moved closer to her and are meeting her friends  the other day at the bar she introduced me and then said this is  her friend ***** like come on its been years why is she still doing this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> a third of all parents have a favourite child </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 03:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i saw a post earlier today about having a favourite child so i found this.

http://www.parenting.com/blogs/show-and-tell/deborah-skolnik/favorite-child

a third of parents admit to having a favourite child.

and your more likely to favour the child that most resembles you.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 02:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i agree with you i don't hate children at all i LOVE children. i think they are amazing and i spend most of my time with children ( family ). But for myself though I'm not 100% on being CF i know that being a parent changes your personality (not always for the best). Frankly I'm a very selfish person i always have been i just don't think that i would be able to get past my selfishness to take care of a child long term.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 01:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its not really a i find that person sexy its more 
i find that person cute  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 00:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats really ugly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 00:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> post this on r/childfree  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 00:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PLEASE post this on child free they will love it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 23:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my mother for sure has a fave it goes 
my brother (6) WHY: because she's married to his father and they tried for years to have him.
my sister (18) WHY: Most like her self actually almost the same person 
ME (20) WHY: nothing like her complete opposite  actually I'm a lot like her sister who she HATES i am her least favourite child  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 23:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and guess who is paying for all this 

TAX DOLLARS.!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 23:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i completely agree with you.
there are people who get up everyday and save lives  they get up and put milk in a container then walk back to the couch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 22:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> made my day  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am i Asexual </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 06:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have been with both men and woman i am a 20 year old female.


I have been sexually active since i was 14  but my problem is i don't know if i am asexual because i find woman attractive and i like to masturbate but i HATE sex.

 i get no feeling from it or enjoyment
so because i like to masturbate and find people attractive does that mean I'm not asexual I'm very confused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 05:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i would love to know when 13 year olds were taking care of themselves  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 05:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 13 is really young to be supporting yourself 
my cousin is 14 and even though she's really smart she could NEVER take care of her self  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
