<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6681</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 18:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After the success of the 3 day fast, I think I am going to attempt another fast (atleast 24 hours). Wish me luck! 

Breakfast: Banana, Orange, Soy milk (290 calories)

Lunch: Shepherds Pie and Tofu (340 calories)

Dinner: Skipped

Total: 630 calories

Scale: 128 lbs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 17:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Height: 5'9"

* CW: 128 lbs

* HW: 150lbs

* LW: 104 lbs

* GW: 0 lbs

* UGW: -1 lbs 

* WL this week: 5 lbs (mostly water weight) 

* BMI: 18.9

* Age: 18

* Gender expression: M?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 03:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best of luck to you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 19:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not exactly an expert at the topic, but I will give it a go:

For me, I both restrict and fast alot of the time. From a personal experience, I always find fasting easier. If I eat as little as 200-300 calories in a day, I find myself with alot of hunger and cravings. 

However, when I fast I find that the hunger cravings just stop after the 2nd day. Currently, i am three days into a fast and I feel fine (although I will probably end it soon). 

Fasting is also easier on me psychologically because i don't have to worry or even think about foods/calories. 

I guess this is all just personal opinion though. Both severe restriction and fasting will cause you to lose weight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 18:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I officially hit the 72 hour mark of my fast! That's three days! I decided today that I wanted to break the fast with 1,400 calories of healthy foods. 

Breakfast: Skipped

Lunch: Banana (105), Orange (65), almond milk (100). Mealplan lunch (rice,tofu,beans = 530)

Dinner: Mealplan (rice,tofu,beans= 600)

Total: 1,400 calories

Steps taken: 8000

Scale: 127 lbs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 19:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey! Just thought I would say that this is very common for people with eating disorders. I'm not a psychiatrist, but I believe this is BDD otherwise known as body dismorphic disorder. It's a common pairing with an ED diagnosis.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 19:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As of writing this, I am currently 48 hours into this fast! I'm going to try to make it through the rest of today, as I don't really have anything important to do.


Breakfast: Skipped

Lunch: Skipped

Dinner: Skipped

Total: 0 calories

Scale: 128 lbs
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 23:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Nope

Lunch: No way

Dinner: Nadda.

total: 0 calories

Still fasting away. I currently feel great. No ill effect - Infact I feel powerful and strong. Let's see how this goes~

Scale: 129 lbs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 23:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Male here!

 I definitely have insecure thoughts about it too, especially if my SO is aware of my ED. Also, as a general rule, the more underweight I am, the less libido I have. 

Thought I would provide a different perspective~~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 18:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever since I got away to university, I have completed two separate 24 hour fasts. I plan to go for a larger fast these next couple days, but I decided to eat a healthy 1200 meal first. It was really difficult for me but I was able to do it:

Breakfast: Skipped

Lunch: Res Lunch of Veggies and Beans with soy milk (1200 calories) 

Dinner: Skipped 

We will see how this fast goes. Wish me luck!! 

Scale: 130 lbs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
