<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3278</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 00:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you load the game into Dolphin VR it gives you game specific preferences... This newest version has the AR codes already loaded in and you can select them. One of them is the 60 fps hack and the other is the 60 fps jump fix. Those are the only two I'm using, plus I selected all the "Hide Box" options that clear up the UI. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 23:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I couldn't find any object removal codes for it. They weren't on /r/dolphinvrcullin. Do you know of another place to find them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ocarina of Time on Dolphin VR satisfying as hell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 22:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loaded up the Gamecube version of Ocarina of Time, my favorite game, to Dolphin VR, and I couldn't have been more delighted by the result. Some work definitely still needs to be done on the emulation (such as hiding the 16:9 widescreen black box), but with the 60 fps hack going it was the best I've ever seen it and I was completely immersed in the world. Seeing the artwork up close and being towered over by the Deku Tree was an experience that I never thought I'd have. I truly could not believe what I was looking at all through the opening sequence. Last night I played up through Gohma boss fight completely awestruck. Unfortunately, I was getting quite sick feeling by the end of it, though. 

So I'll probably take another stab at it today because it was just too much fun. This and Xenoblade Chronicles shocked the shit out of me at how well they run in VR.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Waited months, now I'm waiting on eye strain to go away. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 01:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yes, I feel like a fool. Played for several hours two days ago and felt like I was going cross eyed. I had my ipd set at 61 which looked the clearest, but after realizing something had to be wrong I found 66 to be the clearest. But the (temporary) damage was already done. I still feel like my eyes need more rest two days later, although I feel somewhat better. I measured my ipd using a ruler today and got 67. 

So, tl;dr: make sure to get your ipd right before diving in for the first time.

I'm going to sit out however many days it takes to feel completely normal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 22:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, BlazeRush, Lucky's Tale, and a ton of stuff on Virtual Desktop so far.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 21:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hm... I hadn't thought about eyes vs turning. IPD is what I was thinking was the problem but I'm sure 66 is the clearest for me. Maybe I had already stressed my eyes out before I found the right setting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eye fatigue surprised me on Day 1. What am I doing wrong? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 21:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi /r/Oculus. I got my Rift yesterday, played all day, and today I'm still feeling fatigued in my eyes/brain. After messing with the settings several times throughout the session, I am pretty sure I have it aligned for the clearest picture. Yet no matter what I do I feel like I'm going slightly cross-eyed right when I put on the headset.

This didn't stop me from having fun, although it is concerning. Now I'd love to jump back in, but I still feel some leftover eye strain from last night. I was taking turns with a friend who didn't feel anything like what I've described. 

Anyone else run into this issue? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 00:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I'm planning to do with the sensor bar is leave the one I already have plugged into my Wii and it should do the job for Dolphin as well. Being plugged in gives it power to send the infrared light so it doesn't matter what it is plugged in to. Otherwise people have said simple solutions like a lit candle will work, but I've never tried it.

And I'd imagine your HOTAS could be connected and configured like a gamepad within Dolphin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wii Sports on Dolphin VR? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 04:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really curious if this could work well. With the Wii remote it might feel like the Vive. Wii Sports Resort might even be the better candidate. I'm thinking these games and the rare few others with well done motion controls like Skyward Sword, Goldeneye, and Red Steel should be a priority for the emulation community.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 19:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 8:09 am, Southern California just got charged and got the processing email. My estimate had been April 25 - May 5. My order time seems to be an outlier based on the 8:06 numbers everyone keeps posting. I'm thinking it's because I live so close to Oculus HQ.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 09:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finishing up Stardew Valley with Dark Souls 3 waiting to go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Masters will be broadcast in virtual reality, only on GearVR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 04:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sad news that we can't try out our sweet CV1's with this weekend's Masters tournament. NextVR is the app GearVR users can download from Oculus Home to watch the telecast. I hope this doesn't set a precedent that excludes sports from their flagship HMD. Any chance it's possible to get NextVR running on the Rift?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How badass is EVE: Valkyrie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 21:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title. I want you to tell me this is a system seller.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EVE: Valkyrie impressions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 00:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After being completely blown away by it in 5 minutes at E3, EVE: Valkyrie is why I'm hyped. When I took off the headset, I was astonished to be back in the real world, and I haven't been satisfied with regular gaming since. 

So, those of you with a Rift on launch day, how is the overall gameplay? After reading Oculus Rift hardware reviews today, I feel like they'd be more stoked about the launch if they weren't slogging through Gear VR ports and focusing their time on potential aces like Eve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 21:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried Eve Valkyrie at E3 this year and was completely astonished. From then til now I have been dying to get back in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Most successful "streaks" in history? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 09:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For instance The Beatles incredible run of 12 #1 albums in 7 years. Or Tiger Woods going over a decade winning every major he led at the start of the final day. Or streaks to do with war, science, politics, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 08:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm alright I will keep an eye on Amazon. Thanks for the tip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 08:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for taking the time to comment. I'll go with a WD then. The reason I'm building a PC at all is because I preordered the Rift.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Build Help] 5820k, 980ti build - Which motherboard, cooler, power supply, storage? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 00:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got my heart set on the 5820k cpu, EVGA 980ti gpu, and the 500 gig 850 EVO SSD, but that's all I know for sure. I've heard the X99 class of motherboards are what I need, but which one is best? There's is some conflict on PCPartPicker - It says, " The motherboard M.2 slot #0 shares bandwidth with SATA 6.0 Gb/s ports. When the M.2 slot is populated, two SATA 6Gb/s ports are disabled."

As far as cooling, would love to get a clear answer on what is best for this setup which I will most likely overclock at some point in the future. Same goes for the power supply.

Finally, in addition to the SSD I was considering a 2 or 3 TB HDD.

Thank you for reading. 



[PCPartPicker part list](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/b8BDBm) / [Price breakdown by merchant](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/b8BDBm/by_merchant/)

Type|Item|Price
:----|:----|:----
**CPU** | [Intel Core i7-5820K 3.3GHz 6-Core Processor](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/intel-cpu-bx80648i75820k) | $374.99 @ Newegg 
**CPU Cooler** | [Corsair H110i GT 113.0 CFM Liquid CPU Cooler](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/corsair-cpu-cooler-cw9060019ww) | $95.10 @ Newegg 
**Motherboard** | [MSI X99A SLI PLUS ATX LGA2011-3 Motherboard](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/msi-motherboard-x99asliplus) | $211.06 @ Amazon 
**Memory** | [Corsair Vengeance LPX 16GB (2 x 8GB) DDR4-3000 Memory](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/corsair-memory-cmk16gx4m2b3000c15r) | $84.99 @ Newegg 
**Storage** | [Samsung 850 EVO 500GB M.2-2280 Solid State Drive](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/samsung-internal-hard-drive-mzn5e500bw) | $152.99 @ Micro Center 
**Video Card** | [EVGA GeForce GTX 980 Ti 6GB Superclocked+ ACX 2.0+ Video Card](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/evga-video-card-06gp44995kr) | $649.99 @ Amazon 
**Case** | [Phanteks Enthoo Pro ATX Full Tower Case](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/phanteks-case-phes614pbk) | $99.99 @ Amazon 
**Power Supply** | [EVGA 750W 80+ Gold Certified Fully-Modular ATX Power Supply](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/evga-power-supply-220g20750xr) | $99.99 @ Amazon 
**Operating System** | [Microsoft Windows 10 Home OEM (64-bit)](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/microsoft-os-kw900140) | $87.95 @ OutletPC 
 | *Prices include shipping, taxes, rebates, and discounts* |
 | Total (before mail-in rebates) | $1877.05
 | Mail-in rebates | -$20.00
 | **Total** | **$1857.05**
 | Generated by [PCPartPicker](http://pcpartpicker.com) 2016-02-09 18:41 EST-0500 |
**What is your intended use for this build? The more details the better.**
Oculus Rift and 1080p max overkill gaming.

**What is your budget (ballpark is okay)?**

$2000


**In what country are you purchasing your parts?**
USA

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 22:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I'll make that change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 22:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, this is exactly the kind of information I need to know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 22:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I probably will wait a couple of months. Doesn't seem like anything else is coming out between now and then though so I wanted to take some time to get a better understanding of what I need. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Build Help] Building Oculus capable PC now, upgrading to Pascal later. Is this the right machine? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 22:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ###Build Help/Ready: [PCPartPicker part list](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/CXKdLk) / [Price breakdown by merchant](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/CXKdLk/by_merchant/)

Type|Item|Price
:----|:----|:----
**CPU** | [Intel Core i5-6600K 3.5GHz Quad-Core Processor](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/intel-cpu-bx80662i56600k) | $254.88 @ OutletPC 
**CPU Cooler** | [Cooler Master Hyper 212 EVO 82.9 CFM Sleeve Bearing CPU Cooler](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/cooler-master-cpu-cooler-rr212e20pkr2) | $24.88 @ OutletPC 
**Motherboard** | [MSI Z170 Krait Gaming ATX LGA1151 Motherboard](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/msi-motherboard-z170kraitgaming) | $147.98 @ B H 
**Memory** | [Crucial Ballistix Sport 8GB (2 x 4GB) DDR4-2400 Memory](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/crucial-memory-bls2k4g4d240fsa) | $49.99 @ Adorama 
**Storage** | [Crucial BX100 500GB 2.5" Solid State Drive](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/crucial-internal-hard-drive-ct500bx100ssd1) | $178.99 @ Mac Mall 
**Storage** | [Seagate Barracuda 1TB 3.5" 7200RPM Internal Hard Drive](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/seagate-internal-hard-drive-st1000dm003) | $45.88 @ OutletPC 
**Video Card** | [Zotac GeForce GTX 980 Ti 6GB AMP! Video Card](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/zotac-video-card-zt9050310p) | $615.99 @ NCIX US 
**Case** | [Phanteks Enthoo Pro ATX Full Tower Case](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/phanteks-case-phes614pbk) | $107.99 @ NCIX US 
**Power Supply** | [EVGA SuperNOVA G2 550W 80+ Gold Certified Fully-Modular ATX Power Supply](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/evga-power-supply-220g20550y1) | $89.99 @ Amazon 
 | *Prices include shipping, taxes, rebates, and discounts* |
 | Total (before mail-in rebates) | $1526.57
 | Mail-in rebates | -$10.00
 | **Total** | **$1516.57**
 | Generated by [PCPartPicker](http://pcpartpicker.com) 2016-01-16 16:07 EST-0500 |
Hi everyone, I'm getting an Oculus Rift in March, and I've made up my mind to build a computer now prior to the Pascal cards coming out, and then upgrading later. I found this build on pcpartpicker.com that looks just right to me. Considering I will upgrade my gpu, are there any changes that would help me to better future proof it?

**If gaming, what kind of performance are you looking for? (Screen resolution, FPS, game settings)**

Max settings on Oculus CV1

**What is your budget (ballpark is okay)?**

$1500-$2000

**In what country are you purchasing your parts?**

USA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Build Help] Building Oculus capable PC now, then upgrading when Pascal comes out. Is this the right machine? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 21:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 05:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How will Oculus support VR mods for non-VR games? I haven't owned a quality gaming PC for several years, so there is a large backlog that I am hoping to play on my Rift once I build a new machine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 03:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How will Oculus support VR mods for non-VR games? I haven't owned a quality gaming PC for several years, so there is a large backlog that I am hoping to play on my Rift once I build a new machine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 21:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First new level in a long time. Went crazy with it.

More Money More Problems

46B6-0000-0104-2678

Please try it out and leave a comment and I will play yours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Muhammad Ali never publicly admitted losing to Joe Frazier, instead labelling the judges verdict a "White Man's Decision" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 10:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 07:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the hell, I made an auto level after taking a few days off from this game.

Do Not Move Auto Cannon

D0FC-0000-00A4-F911 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-10 02:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm late to this post, but here's my story:

A good friend of mine in Mississippi (we're both white) got brain cancer when we were in 10th grade and had to withdraw from school. By senior year she had recovered, and to celebrate her family bought her a new car. It was an exciting day for her to finally be driving since we'd all gotten our licenses and started driving during the couple of years she was sick. But unfortunately her motor skills had not fully returned.

So the night she'd gotten the car she came and picked me up and drove around town picking up another couple of friends and the plan was to get our older friend to buy us booze. He lived right by the highway. Once he was in the car we had to cross the eastbound lanes of the highway to get to the median to then go west, but instead of doing that she turns up the wrong way. We start yelling, "Mary, mary, no. Wrong way." She turns around and gets back to where we were before she started to cross. 

Then, she tries again, this time without looking left. There is a car coming fast, probably over 60 mph because its open highway. We slam into its back right door and it spins out and barrel rolls a 100 yards down the road and into the grass median. If she'd pulled out seconds earlier it would have been our left side they slammed in to. 

Anyway, we jumped out of the car and ran down to see if they are okay, while calling 911. The car is upside down but they are strapped in and appear alright, and they begin to crawl out themselves. The police and ambulance arrived very quickly. 

The men we hit were black and were from out of town, and the cops found weed in their car, so the police arrested them and blamed the whole thing on them. One of them had a broken arm. We were completely stunned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 12:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair. It doesn't get too crazy. I like having to pull stunts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 12:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Freaking God. Big Lebootski was carnage done the right way. I hadn't tried out the big heel yet. You should make a pro version.

Please try my newest level:5C70-0000-0091-3F50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 12:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1 is a nice blend of elements. Easy on the eyes, medium/easy difficulty. Medium length. I enjoyed it.

Please try mine:5C70-0000-0091-3F50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 11:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Avicii was rough. Had to learn the path by dying a few times before I could make it.

Please try mine:5C70-0000-0091-3F50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 11:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once I've reached the top, how in the hell do I make it over? I jumped in the editor to look and no matter what that's not a makeable jump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 11:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of a Zelda dungeon. You should take this concept even further with a much bigger level. I enjoyed it.

Please try mine:5C70-0000-0091-3F50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 11:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beat it and it was fairly tough. I was stuck on the 2nd area for a little while and then I managed to get through the rest on my first try but thats probably because I learned that I needed to act fast or Id lose. 

Please try mine:5C70-0000-0091-3F50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 10:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it. Somehow there are still new puzzles to be made in this game and you've done that here. I carried the spring to the end thinking it was for some purpose but I never had to use it. 

Please try mine:5C70-0000-0091-3F50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 10:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not bad. I thought it was on the easy side, which is a good thing in my book. 

Please try mine:5C70-0000-0091-3F50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 10:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First try. Used up almost the entire time. Did not pick up on the checkpoint. It's well made. I'm glad you gave plenty of power ups since this is more of a "figure it out" level than straight platforming. 

Please try mine:5C70-0000-0091-3F50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 10:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never thought I'd live to play as Bowser in the Kuribo's shoe, and now I have. Thank you for that. Enjoyed it.

Please try mine:5C70-0000-0091-3F50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 10:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, it was tough at spots. I haven't played one quite like this with vines and fire spitting plants. 

Please try mine:5C70-0000-0091-3F50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 10:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great one. It was clever all the way through. That is a concept they've used in other Mario games but it's the first time I've seen it done well in Maker. 

Please try mine:5C70-0000-0091-3F50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 09:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Took the high road. Only got tripped in the final hallway with those single block platforms. 

Please try mine:5C70-0000-0091-3F50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 09:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not bad. I was on the low road most of the time. Felt similar to a classic level.

Please try mine:5C70-0000-0091-3F50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 06:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Short and sweet. Had to pull a few stunts to get to the end. Not bad for a first level at all.

Please try mine:5C70-0000-0091-3F50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 06:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The aesthetic in the first section is well thought out, and the second RUN section was also fun. I first tried it but it is not easy easy. 

Please try mine:5C70-0000-0091-3F50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 06:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beat it. That was the right level of difficulty in my opinion. I managed to bounce up on the red bullets on the first try but I feel it was luck. Definitely challenging but not too much. 

Please try mine: 5C70-0000-0091-3F50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 06:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All Frills felt like a classic level to me with it's high, middle, and low roads. 

Please try mine:5C70-0000-0091-3F50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 23:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Starred so I could come back later. Got through the first area.

Please try mine: 5C70-0000-0091-3F50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 23:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beat it. It had a good flow. Not too hard. Enough power ups. 

Please try mine:5C70-0000-0091-3F50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 23:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Castle section was unexpected. I like how you incorporated the spike helm. 

Please try mine:5C70-0000-0091-3F50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 23:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beat it. I thought of the early jumps were a little awkwardly spaces, but I like the level overall. I didn't have much trouble once I got past the first obstacle.

Please try mine:5C70-0000-0091-3F50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 23:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bullet Stairs

5C70-0000-0091-3F50

I really love my newest level. It is challenging for sure but very forgiving, so you will not die much, if at all. Please try it. I'm about to start going down this thread playing levels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 10:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WOW I first tried it somehow. That is a great idea for a level, and I've never seen that before.

Please try mine: 5C70-0000-0091-3F50
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 10:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool level. It probably took a while to get the shell bouncing right. Good usage of the ground boos too.

Please try mine: 5C70-0000-0091-3F50
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 10:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh. Thanks for telling me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 10:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 10:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beat it. That was well designed. I opted for the low road and it all timed out nicely. I like that it was difficult but short. It didn't hurt much to die because I usually had learned something and was nearer to the end. 

Please try mine: 5C70-0000-0091-3F50
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 10:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bullet Stairs

5C70-0000-0091-3F50

I really love my newest level. It is challenging for sure but very forgiving, so you will not die much, if at all. Please try it. I'm about to start going down this thread playing levels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 03:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not bad, are there multiple exit paths? I like the wiggler area where he'll chase you down below. 

Please try mine:5C70-0000-0091-3F50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
