<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject375</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 05:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right I would've been fine with superdelegates flipping in favor of Bernie because he would've fought to get rid of Superdelegates, fixing the problem. Instead we get status-quo suits voting for the status-quo against the wishes of their constituents with no intent to change or improve the delegate system that they benefit from directly.

Also Howard Dean being a doctor is a weak argument of authority considering it's not really relevant to being a politician. By your logic, Ben Carson should pick the next President.

This whole notion that out-of-touch party elites who can't sympathize with the average American would know what's better for us than we do is just demoralizing. This election was decided by populists and Dean chose to deny his party's populist the vote. Maybe if Dean knew what was actually better for us, he would've nominated the candidate that stood a better chance of winning, instead of nominating the candidate that gives him money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, but I don't think Howard Dean knows better than his constituents. Maybe you're fine with superdelegates being authoritarians who dictate decisions that the majority votes against, but it still bothers me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I would have showed up, but the primary rules in my state forbade me from voting because I'm registered Independent. Someone like Bernie could've gotten me to join the party again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In some cases there were districts that voted in favor of Sanders during the primary, but the Representatives were Superdelegates and cast their votes for Clinton. Howard Dean did this and when they asked him why he voted against his constituents, his answer was basically "I think I know better than my constituents" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 07:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was on the local news here as well. The reason being that local news simply gets their national news from other sources. They read the AP report and just copied it verbatim. 

It's examples like these that should make you question media sources. Often the information you get is simply a piece of the story, having been passed through multiple channels with no independent verification along the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 04:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was some testing done by a Youtuber that found GTA V cops were not racist and actually used lethal force on Trevor more than anybody else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
