<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1271</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 22:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my main issue with Silicon Valley (apart from not addressing its diversity issues of course) is its repetitiveness. I've watched 3 seasons of the show and it kinda felt like I watched the same season 3 times but with new jokes (that I don't even find funny half of the time). So I'm still contemplating whether or not to start the new season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Silicon Valley's live ratings have taken quite a stumble. Is it because of the Game of Thrones delay or do people not know the show has returned? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 22:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always wondered why I never hear about Silicon Valley anywhere else apart from reddit (not on twitter or irl), but the show always does so well in ratings. It's a very subjective show so maybe many people just left it on after Game of Thrones but didn't get invested? or maybe the new season wasn't promoted well enough so many did not know it returned? I'd like to imagine Silicon Valley doesn't usually rely on much promotion since it airs right after Game of Thrones. 

Silicon Valley average ratings for a season usually lies somewhere between **1.5** - **1.8 million**. Season 3 finale live ratings was at **2.04 million**, but it took quite a huge stumble this season and the premiere live ratings was at **0.86 million**. 

Veep has taken quite a stumble as well tho not as much as Silicon Valley. For a show that usually gets a rating of **1 million+** season 6 premiered at **0.66 million**. 

It's not confirmed but by the looks of it **Insecure** will be airing right after Game of Thrones this year. It will be interesting to see how much that will help the show's ratings since its first season had an average ratings of **0.40 million**   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure what /u/ProspectDikadu deal is but you hit the nail right on the head here. The Leftovers is also one of my favorite shows of all time and just like The Sopranos it's subtle and have well written characters. I haven't seen The Wire yet, but I think I'm moving on to that next. I definitely appreciate The Sopranos but like you said the characters just aren't doing it for me I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 19:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> say what!? I hate police procedurals. what in god's earth could make you think I like them. Did you actually read the post before you commented on it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
