<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1323</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 10:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Submission statement**: In early 2017, a wave of prison riots in Brazil led to the murder and dismemberment of scores of prisoners. This violence put the spotlight on Brazils powerful and violent drug gangs. Despite running transnational operations, little is known about these gangs and the way that they operate. In this article, Lessing examines the historical origins of these gangs, their structures and their effects on Brazilian society; some of which have been surprisingly positive. A worthy read for anybody who has an interest in crime and the War on Drugs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brazils prison massacres are a frightening window into gang warfare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 10:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 08:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Small addition: One option is to approach the business dept head (she's the main boss) and ask to branch into the business stuff a bit more. However, I'm worried that if I do that my supervisor will take this badly. It might make her look irresponsible, because she did not utilize her intern. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help: I'm two months into a six month internship and my supervisor wont delegate. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 08:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This could be a bit long so please bear with me. I started an internship end of March working in the very small communications department of a decently large organization. Our organization works in about four countries and handles as many as 30 projects at a time. Our tiny comms dept. handles most of the work from these countries and projects. The comms. is bunched in with the business dept. We have two people in comms,.: my supervisor and me.


**More background info**: My supervisor is a friend from college and we get along well. We hang out regularly outside work and had been doing so long before I started here. She helped me get the post by putting in a good word for me, although my chances were already decent because I nailed the interview (I know because I befriended one of the people who interviewed me and she told me so). My supervisor does a good job and handles a lot of work. Even though her title is assistant there is no officer or dept head. The business dept head focuses on the business part and just leaves us to ourselves. 


**The Problem**: My supervisor almost never delegates or assigns me any work. I have moved from an intense work environment, where I was writing 7-10 pages a day (an average of 2000 words) to one where I handle as little as one article a week. This week she is away on a work trip and all I had to do was add three lines to an article I wrote last week and edit five templates. One of my coworkers gave me a small task to help her with yesterday and that was great. Unfortunately, without more training, I cant help with any of the business stuff. I have tried asking my supervisor to give me more tasks but all she ever says is no, you cant handle this, Ill just do it myself. During my interview, the main boss said that if I did well enough, they would likely hire me. Now Im worried that with nothing to do, they might not hire me simply because my position is redundant. To make it worse, my supervisor is always telling me (casually) that she has a lot of work to do. Sometimes she stays in the office four hours later than she needs to (although this has something to do with her taking a 2hr gym break at lunch). If the pay wasnt so good, I would have quit and gone back to my old job, even though I hated it. So I need help. Has anybody else dealt with this situation before? And how do I approach my supervisor and tell her to give me more work. 


PS: You might notice that the entire business and comms is a bit of a mess. Our boss is always late, rarely present and so there is very little accountability, especially in terms of punctuality.    
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking ridiculous. Next these "experts" will tell people to prevent shark attacks by not swimming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
