<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2577</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 23:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  In Australia you can't wear a balaclava or motorcycle helmet into a bank.

Same in the UK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 23:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He more suprised to see an unpixelated condom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 20:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't worse than I thought it would be because it's factoring in old people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 20:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait are you telling me that America is racist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 03:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His family have been super secretive about him, he's awake and we know he won't walk again but given how it's all been hush hush, he's most likely suffered brain damage and is in a terrible state. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 03:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to sprint home so that I could get changed and hang out with my friends everyday after school. We all lived nearby so it was a race to see who could get to our hangout first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 02:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to the celebs it doesn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 00:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All this thread title shows me is that people are suprised that Muslims are kind :S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why is there no centre of the universe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 03:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 02:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see he came as the future american leader. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 01:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering how common Mr Mimes are here, I'd happily trade them for level 1 Tauros, Kangaskhan or farfetch'd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 00:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surely a much better lpt would be to say drink more water and you'll never had chapped lips :s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 20:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came in here to shoot down the odd Spanish comment in the op.
We defnitely leave the house as soon as we can. I left when I finished school and haven't looked back and I don't have one friend that didn't do the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 20:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's not the Bare Naked Ladies, I don't know what's real anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 20:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'the corner' doesn't even make sense :S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 18:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people are idiots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 18:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only because of reddit that I realised that most people actually think in words. In my entire family my mother is the only one that does (had a big discussion last xmas) so I thought it was super rare until then.

I really struggle to understand why people add the extra layer of words. Why not just think it like the rest of us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 16:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy birthday! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 16:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I came in to write about a dog. Dammit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 14:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get super rich by being competitive, demand others cooperative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 13:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just punch him in the face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 13:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just be thankful you didn't grow up in Spain. You could smoke on buses and in schools! Put together with my dad smoking I honestly don't think I went a day without inhaling packets worth of cigarette fumes until I left home at 17.

I should also note that I was a moderate asthmatic growing up (hospitalised a few times with asthma attacks). I 'magically' got a lot better once I finished school, moved out and bought a car to travel in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 13:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not as weird as our drinking laws. Can't buy alcohol until 18 but can legally drink alcohol from age 5!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 13:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't have ID cards in the UK though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 13:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My last flight had a 12 hour delay so we we're stuck in the airport and I'm not exaggerating when at least 10 smokers had to be detained and told to chill the fuck out by the police because they had formed a mob and were starting to get very aggresive (borderline violent) to the staff because they weren't allowed to smoke (can't smoke in airports/can't go out and come back in). If that's not the behaviour of an addict I don't know what is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 03:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  you have to bypass martial arts when dealing with a horde of attackers

You will be the first to fall in the apocalypse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 01:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we stop sped up videos being on /all it's ruining the front page. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 15:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jogging. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 17:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Though Francisco Francos totalitarian Spanish regime was toppled nearly 40 years ago       

Toppled! Franco died, that's hardly a toppling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 00:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine sound the same too, I can only imagine it's people rushing and mumbling the letters quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 22:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What they should have done it released all generations of pokmon and have country specific pokmon, now that would have been cool.

There are 721 pokmon so you could easily give each country in the world 1 country specific pokmon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 22:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hadn't seen the cross over advertised anywhere (I watch all the shows and even I didn't know it was happening) so am impressed that it had record viewers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 21:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not even at all :S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 21:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know who Spez who until this controversy but it seems that I've given him 3 down votes for previous comments :D :D :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 19:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recycle my boxes and just keep my games stacked on a disc holder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 02:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone explain to me why the $10 pizza has to be signed for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 23:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mum didn't just have sex to have kids, she enjoys it and does it regularly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 23:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure most people accept that to be true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 23:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My school had classes based on intelligence, you also got a coloured tie to show which class you were in. It went purple, orange, red, yellow, green, and blue.

Yet despite having a clear system nobody in the blue class considered themselves to be 'thick'.

Not only that my school also had a number rating so you knew if you were ranked 184/184. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 23:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guy on the train tried to start a conversation today with me by saying 'do you ever have one of those days where you just want to punch someone'. He was harmless but I'm sure that would have scared a lot of people :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could a rangers fanboi write up bullet points to summarise the power rangers saga. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 22:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mordred  Modor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 18:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rest of the world? Doubt most people outside of North America get what's going on :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 18:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Double negative so it is a catfish? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 01:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All Brits would know it; not sure about Americans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL - The expression 'bloody Norah' comes from a maid who killed another servant...with a stick of celery! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 00:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 00:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THAT'S NOT JACK BLACK!!! He is just a tribute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 23:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're fun but agree they are super inconsistent. I probably get 1 out of every 100 messages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 23:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I wake up and it was all a dream. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 17:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why South Park is soo brillant, so many thinks that you think are nonsense turn out to be true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 17:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I put money into a drinks machine on Brighton pier (England) and for change out came a Spanish 5 peseta coin (with Franco on it) from the year my parents were born, who are Spanish and had to flee Franco.

No idea

1. How the money was accepted into the machine (nothing like English money)
2. Who was carrying it around as it's soo old and hasn't been valid currency in Spain for 14 years so it's not like it's in circulation.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 17:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the amount of users it is a little odd how slowly the site can seem to move. Then I go onto news website and they seem like they're frozen in time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 05:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We had this posted yesterday. Shameless karma whore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sex Pistols manager's son sets fire to 5 million punk collection, "punk was never meant to be nostalgic". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 01:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 00:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surely evolution takes million of years :s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 00:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make sure you have a condom on you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 00:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Latino my mum wanted to give me a name that you could say in both Spanish and English so 'Daniel' was a forerunner for a while.

I was actually given a completely unique name so the idea of me having a bog standard name is just alien to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 00:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks v like scaramanga.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 02:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What you need to do now is go to a mall and shout 'BEN!', the first person to come up to you, give them the cake and then walk off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In 2009 Red Bull took over   renamed 5th division football team 'SSV Markranstdt' to 'RasenBallsport Leipzig e.V'. After just being promoted to the first division, they are currently sitting top and are undefeated. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 00:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 20:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And they don't cost you a thing.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 18:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Ricky Gervais podcasts. Before he was a global star and made Karl Pilkington famous the two of them and Steven Merchant did podcasts in which they talk about nonsense but it's hilarious. The funniest podcasts you'll ever hear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 17:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually space is beige. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 17:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ladies and gentlemen is fine though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 17:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not easily digestible though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 00:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Signed, 15k signatures atm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL - 'Nice' originally used to mean foolish/stupid. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 23:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 23:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I literally got my citizenship this month but sadly Monty Python definitely did not come up.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 19:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never had this issue, must be lucky :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 18:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since the update quite a few sadly. Sadly because it makes the game too easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 18:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is this a life pro tip :s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 18:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spain's national football team has Manolo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 16:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're pussy whipped? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 16:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am the only one who this has never happened to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 10:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who used to work for the government, this was not a mistake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 10:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are they rare? I've got a fair few in London. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 10:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tried this a few days ago but my SO still couldn't understand the controls :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 21:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Despite being North of the UK you have to fly East to mainland Europe and then back North West to get there.

No UK flights go there :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 19:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't all uncircumcised men pull make the skin, couldn't imagine peeing otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 18:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ridiculous and quite frankly offensive statement to make without any sources whatsoever. Glad someone shot that down straight away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 18:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The economy is falling to pieces and they're wasting time on banning fisting. Get you priorities right, you bunch of non wankers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just caught a ditto - fyi it looked like a pidgey, was harder to catch than norm and then transformed into ditto after it was caught. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 02:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 02:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG I just logged in the first pokmon that I caught turned out to be a ditto.

I caught a pidgey, that was annoying me as it took 4 pokballs to catch, then a video played and it transformed into ditto and said 'ditto caught' :D

[My Ditto](https://i.imgur.com/xixZ9E9.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 02:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Legitimately thinking about going out at 1am to find one :D :D :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 22:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Superman lives here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 22:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Free standing mirror :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 20:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is this on the front page, it was only here less than a week ago! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 01:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I had unlimited money I genuinely wouldn't have any problems in my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 01:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can be anything you want to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 01:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's cheaters never prosper, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 01:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why say 'innocent people don't confess.' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 01:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No hitting my child rule. Why relatives think it's ok is beyond me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 01:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you post a comment with verified sources and a redditor just posts 'wrong/you're a liar etc.' without anything to back up their statement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 01:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plus not all murder is unacceptable, defending against the nazis is ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sarkozy concedes in centre-right primary </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 22:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 19:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Japanese government refuses to collect data on the ethnic identities of its citizens, claiming that there are no issues of race relations among Japanese citizens as they are all of the same race. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 14:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck trying to tell yourself girlfriend she's just hungry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 14:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Remix to Hammertime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 14:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once the paint can is in your house the volume of your house doesn't change just because the paint is now on the walls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 05:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grandpa what's the hair between her legs :s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 04:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't buy any condoms until I was 22 as we got them for free at my school and university. 

At uni they would keep them in boxes by reception and you would just help yourself. Reception was unmanned after 5 so you didn't have any awkward when picking them up. I just took a whole box for our house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 02:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hayao Miyazaki also recently came out of retirement to make one more film. I CANNOT WAIT!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 00:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's almost like she can't act. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 22:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you run out of money mid remastering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 18:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG I was literally just cleaning my webcam and thinking about Zuckerberg this and then came onto reddit to see this on the front page! Are you watching me :O :O :O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 02:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I look at myself over the last 8 years and I look at Obama, he looks like he's aged at double the rate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
