<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2423</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 04:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're doing Playstation figures now? 

I hope they make some Uncharted Figures and Aloy from Horizon Zero Dawn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 01:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I.. might of made him angry.

Might've or might have, not might of.

COME ON! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 01:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely hate the Nomad sections, I think it's cumbersome, and a real time suck. I also have no idea how to make money in this game. 

I don't think I'm anywhere close to finishing the game yet, but so far I agree with most of your points. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 00:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gimple's got AMC's hand up his ass, so of course he'd say that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 04:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched season 2 weekly and I loved it. Season 2 is just eons better than the tripe they've been churning out lately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like that Captain America figure, but I just don't like the head. Something about it is off putting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just kidding </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> best version of deadpool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is how good things come to an end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure the guy above you was just joking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 15:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, I wonder if those cloaks fit on Figuarts? I'll have to see if I can find my old Hasbro stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 03:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #**RHYMING INTENSIFIES** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 03:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did it so that you'd know he's on Avengers tower. If he was as small as he's supposed to be in relation to the A, you wouldn't even know he was on Avengers tower.

They're just reinforcing the fact that Spider-Man is in the MCU now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 02:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We blew it with the movie, let's try TV now!"

-Ubisoft </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 00:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FINALLY PETER PARKER! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got out of college with a BA in Film Theory a few months ago, and I still live with my parents. I do some online transcription work in the meantime and that get's me enough money to do what I want, but I wouldn't consider that being employed since I work from home.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those only work on the stuff they can't move though.

I know what you mean though. I'm technically unemployed, and I wanna hold off on the pre-order. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $220 at Sideshow. He just went up a few minutes ago. 

I'll probably get it since the Stark Spidey suit probably won't come with a Peter Parker head, based on the teaser for that Spider-Man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 07:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **THERE GOES MY HERO** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 07:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the clipping don't forget all the clipping. Especially with blood drinking guy's headdress.  And how Aloy's hair sometimes floats depending on the outfit she wears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 06:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This triggers reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You wearing some kind of $4,000 suit or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #**IT CREATES A DYNAMIC READING ENVIRONMENT!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Daily Show has been getting broadcast on BET lately, and now I can watch it along with the east coast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw those animations, most likely hidden loading screens, and I said to myself, "There's no way I'm gonna probe all these planets for some damn minerals."

Plus, I'm an adult now, and I don't have time for that kind of tedious gameplay. If people die in the final mission because I don't have enough potassium or whatever, that's fine with me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it normal to be offered Student Prime after my Student Prime account had expired? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 04:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted about my Student Prime account ending last Friday night (I'm the Mass Effect guy), and it ended as scheduled on the 22nd.

I saw that they were offering me Student Prime again that day, but I thought it was a mistake. Still, I was curious. So today I thought, "What the hell?" I clicked the button, and it appears I'm on track for another 4 years of Student Prime. 

So I was wondering if this was a mistake or something that happens on a regular basis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> -and their new long running show begins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate that they have an animation for probing planets that is probably a hidden loading screen,but they couldn't bother with doing animations for getting in and out of this rover. It's so lazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes sense, and it's pretty much what I had been suspecting. Thanks for answering! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did they leave for Andromeda after ME3 or during? 

Cuz I cured the genophage and they're acting like it's still a thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PARENTS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.livescience.com/41839-gamers-thrombosis.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 02:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still think it looks weird. I still see kid in the face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 22:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't wanna be a dick, but I just have to say, you probably shouldn't do that. You don't wanna get a blood clot in your ass that could lead to a heart attack. Gamers have died this way before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With a ton of balls.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So who's gonna post "My Shiny Teeth and Me" by Chip Skylark? Did r/music get to it already?/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 06:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guy, you don't understand. Louis CK has already covered it. Case closed.


 All hail the fat white dude in the black shirt for he is a mighty good fellow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great to finally see an episode where shit goes down *before* the final five minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> most likely he got lost cuz he's **BLIND**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Expect to see this music on r/music sometimes soon. Heck, maybe they'll even post My Shiny Teeth and Me again!/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 01:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They probably wouldn't have killed him if they'd known how big Mahershela Ali was gonna get a couple of months after the show launched. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me neither, but ever since they revealed the latest pictures of her I've been seeing that shitty label tossed around in this sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, and her U3 look is easily the most off putting. Her face looks like it shrunk, and that hair is huge. Her look in LL is miles better than that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's be real though: The teenagers that hang out in this sub aren't gonna get a stiffy from Nate's Belt Buckles, so they don't care that that was missing in U4, and that's why they're so upset about the "SJW-fication" of Chloe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was joke! Louis CK would have said the same thing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, yeah... nothing good comes from jumping the shark, and it sounds like the movie was garbage, hence the joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I was getting at.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About as long as a shark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> City of Webs, are you spinning just for me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a feeling his post was more motivated by him not wanting to play as a woman or the DLC focus on two women. This DLC seems to have brought the misogynists out of the woodwork. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 04:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it might just be the lighting and angle. She doesn't seem to have a huge nose in the multiplayer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't these fucking idiots wait until he pops out again?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

I also just finished the series last night, and I thought it captured the spirit of the novel very well, but it is very different from the novel.


Read the book in case you want to spend some more time with Jake and Sadie and the rest of the Jodie gang. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand why people are suddenly upset about how Chloe looks like in Lost Legacy. We've been able to see the character model since launch via the Multiplayer, and she looks just fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 22:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go back to your safe space at the_donald, kid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 22:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get Horizon. It's fantastic...

But I think it has some of the same wonky facial animation ME:A is getting shit on for... 

So if that's part of your beef with ME:A at the moment...

Get Horizon because it's still fucking fantastic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 19:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was happening in a thread here too. I saw it. With my own eyes.

It's why the gaming community is seen in a poor light.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 02:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That Luke Cage teaser was why I asked. Bummed to see there isn't. The, let's say, lukewarm reception to Iron Fist has turned me off of trying to binge it this weekend, and I was thinking if there was a teaser that might get my engine going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 01:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like someone is getting *pounded* tonight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 01:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a Defenders teaser at the end? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 01:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The songs will probably be up on iTunes Tuesday night.

SYNERGY! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 01:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #**YOU CAN'T LOCK UP THE SPEEDSTER VILLAINS** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Ha, looks like SH Figuarts isn't the only company to give Qui-Gon his Oh Face.](http://news.toyark.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2017/03/SH-Figuarts-Qui-Gon-Jinn-004.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! You old fuck!


[TFW Marc Webb Spider-Man is childhood to others.](http://i1.kym-cdn.com/entries/icons/original/000/013/292/tumblr_lz376laNSq1qaygy7o1_500.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are the only ones I want.

I just hate going into stores for something and coming out empty handed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> X-Men, and BTAS through a hazy filter, to demonstrate the necessity for waking up early on the weekend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know, it worked out pretty well for Obi-Wan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had no idea it was this close. Nothing much has happened this season to make me feel like we were closing in on a finale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, I just can't find the extra hundred in the budget this month to keep it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look, I don't need a lecture on this stuff. I know it already. I've studied it extensively in school.

The Walking Dead is just doing things very poorly right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so glad Qui-Gon's coming out, and that they included his O-face with the figure.

Dude's about to get permanently posed as dying! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I already surmized that based on how mind numbingly  slow this season has been moving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well they need to speed things up. These episodes have had maybe 30 minutes of necessary (character and  plot work)  content stretched out to an hour plus at times. 

This show isn't going to last however long the comics have, and they need to realize they're writing for television, not a monthly comic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 16:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The obdurate past is obdurate. It does not want be changed and will fight back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 16:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So basically he's confirming that Rick and the gang won't be fighting Negan's crew until the end of the season finale.


Gimple's gotta go. He is running the show into the ground now. This season has been terrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 07:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First thing I tried. I couldn't see the option. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 07:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, I can't seem to find it. Maybe it's cuz I'm still under the Student Prime membership? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 07:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hm, I think I might do that. I know it's more in the long run, but I can't drop an extra $100 on Prime right now. There are some other things I'm hoping to snag with Prime next month... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 06:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was no mystery to how it would end. The show needed a terrorist attack to happen, and this was the only viable option. Of course it was gonna end the way it did. I just wish it had happened sooner, because those minutes with Amira and the gang where a time suck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 06:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think 24 Legacy is bombing because the premiere left a bad taste in people's mouths considering it featured Muslim terrorists at a time when Trump and his cronies were then, still are now currently trying to invoke a Muslim ban for no good reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 05:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Winner! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, thank you. If that game isn't shipped by the time I go to sleep on Sunday, I'm gonna cancel it, since I'd wind up getting it earlier going to Target. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same.

u/slowmosloth explains why and I agree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think instead of characters, you should include different TV models. LEDs, OLEDs, CRTs, ancient TVs, Laptops, Desktops, gun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Replace a woman with  a man, for *more* diversity, lol.

Classic reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cancelling Prime subscription... Will my pre-order of Mass Effect Andromeda be eligible for Prime Savings? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Prime subscription is set to renew on the 20th of this month, the day before the game is released. 

I want to cancel it because I really don't want to fork over $99 this month.

Typically, games I've POed have shipped the day before they're released, and I'd get them release day. 

The Prime Savings is basically the only reason I'm not going to a brick and mortar store to by my games. So if Prime Savings won't be honored I'm just gonna cancel it and head to Best Buy or Target Tuesday morning.

So basically, I'm just wondering if my pre-order of Mass Effect Andromeda be eligible for Prime Savings after cancelling my Prime subscription? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People are acting as if Mass Effect never had weird, stilted animations. Honestly, this just looks par for the course to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IS there a Defenders teaser attached to the end of the season like there was for Luke Cage at DD 2's ending? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 21:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So is her penchant for gilding posts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 06:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just joshing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 05:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like it could be a decent plotline on 24 instead of more Muslim terrorists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I just use a little bit of this...](https://mobileimages.lowes.com/product/converted/023857/023857738117.jpg)

[A little bit of that...](http://zippooutdoor.com/wp-content/uploads/photo-gallery/ZippoLighter%20copy.jpg)

[And badda, bing badda boom, the fire rises in your room!](http://i2.kym-cdn.com/photos/images/facebook/000/000/130/disaster-girl.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You gotta remember that there are a lot of horny teenagers on this sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be more inclined to buy a second stormtrooper if they priced them at like $50 on their own.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> McDonald's is held to a higher standard than the POTUS these days. Sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love a tell all book or documentary about the goings on behind the scenes of the DCEU a hell of a lot more than I want another DCEU movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another issue with Horizon's faces was when they'd get out of sync with the audio. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least you're not REQUIRED to buy the DLC.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they're just excited for the possibility. 

I think It'd be a waste since Teersa already told you his story. Gimme more Aloy instead, please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember right before Horizon ZD came out and everyone was saying it was shit because of one bad cut scene?

"It looks like some basic bitch Ubisoft game!"

-r/PS4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 07:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you write *an* admission essay?

FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 06:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just thought they kept making different batches, after the initial pre-orders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 05:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #DON'T TELL HIM PHIL! 

It's not worth it! Luke's just gonna spend every episode at home next season anyway! Look at Haley and Alex for fucks sake, Phil! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 05:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're giving out toys at In-N-Out now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 04:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Need a writer/actor/guy willing to relocate to Atlanta if provided home with AC and all necessary and luxury amenities and 6 figure salary? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 03:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, maybe I should have said indirectly then, because even if they aren't allowed to sell in the US, collectors will wind up choosing which Qui-Gon they want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like they wanna compete directly with Hasbro's version. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Irritated as fuck to see he's a web exclusive. I knew they'd do that for the final member in the Duel of the Fates trio.

 Anyone know where to PO him, I ask begrudgingly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They had way more chemistry together than he did with "raised like brother and sister" Iris. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Barry literally just broke up with Iris cuz he wants to put some space between them while he tries to save her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Do you want to go bowling, cousin?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks like it'll be one of the great Pixar movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of the days of DSL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 03:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These would be great for recreating that scene in The Clone Wars movie where the walkers walk up the cliff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 03:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are Walgreens really well stocked with action figures these days? Back in the day the stuff they'd have was crap and overpriced. Any way to check online to see if they have these in stock? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 03:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because no one is paying redditors doesn't put them on a moral high ground for joke stealing, ~and~ making the jokes not funny.

Reddit constantly steals South Park jokes and runs them into the ground making them not funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 03:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit needs to get off it's fucking high horse with joke stealing, considering damn near every top/best comments feature memes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'll just do what they've been doing and put them in less episodes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 01:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck him up, Rachel!

EDIT: Come on, just two pages? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 01:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sean Spicer never had cool to begin with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
