<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2662</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A blonde and a lawyer are seated next to each other on a flight from LA to NY. The lawyer asks if she would like to play a fun game. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 03:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The blonde, tired, just wants to take a nap. Politely she declines and rolls over to the window to catch a few winks. The lawyer persists and explains that the game is easy and a lot of fun. 
He explains, "I ask you a question, and if you don't know the answer, you pay me $5.00, and vise versa." 
Again, she declines and tries to get some sleep. The lawyer, now agitated, says, "Okay, if you don't know the answer you pay me $5.00, and if I don't know the answer, I will pay you $500.00." This catches the blonde's attention and, figuring there will be no end to this torment unless she plays, agrees to the game. 
The lawyer asks the first question. "What's the distance from the earth to the moon?" The blonde doesn't say a word, reaches into her purse, pulls out a $5.00 bill and hands it to the lawyer. 
"Okay," says the lawyer," your turn." She asks the lawyer, "What goes up a hill with three legs and comes down with four legs?" The lawyer, puzzled, takes out his laptop computer and searches all his references. No answer. Frustrated, he sends e-mails to all his friends and coworkers, to no avail. After an hour, he wakes the blonde and hands her $500.00. 
The blonde says, "Thank you," puts her head on the pillow and goes back to sleep. 
The lawyer, who is more than a little miffed, wakes the blonde and asks, "Well, what's the answer?" Without a word, the blonde reaches into her purse, hands the lawyer $5.00, and goes back to sleep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today I learned that Stephen King's 'It' clown appears every 27 years. The original movie aired in 1990. The new remake airs in 2017. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 03:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump printed out made-up 300bn Nato invoice and handed it to Angela Merkel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Long] Charlie was visiting an old friend and his wife for dinner. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the time came to leave, his car wouldn't start, and it was too late to call the local service station.  
The husband urged Charlie to stay over. There was no spare bed in the house; there wasn't even a sofa. 
So Charlie would have to sleep with the husband and wife. 
No sooner had the husband fallen asleep when the wife taped Charlie on the shoulder and motioned for him to come over to her. 
"I couldn't do that," he whispered. 
"Your husband is my best friend!" 
"Listen, sugar," she whispered back, "there ain't nothing in the whole wide world could wake hime up now." 
"I can't believe that," 
Charlie said. 
"Certainly if I get on top of you and screw you, he'll wake up won't he? 
"Sugar, he certainly won't. If you don't believe me, 
pluck a hair out of his asshole and see if that wakes him." 
Charlie did just that. 
He was amazed when the husband remained asleep. 
So he climbed over to the wife's side of the bed and fucked her.
When he finished, he climbed back to his own side. 
It wasn't long before she tapped him on the shoulder and beckoned him over again. 
Again he pulled a hair to determine if his old friend was asleep. 
This went on eight times during the night. Each time Charlie screwed the woman, he first pulled out one of the husband's asshole hairs.
The ninth time he pulled a hair, the husband awoke 
and muttered: 
"Listen, Charlie, old pal, I don't mind you fucking my wife, 
but for Pete's sake, stop using my ass for a scoreboard!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Diamond steel plate worn smooth by shoes at amusement park. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The wife and I took a long, leisurely drive out to the country and pulled over to fill up our car's gas tank and tires... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was surprised to see that the station had a fee to fill the tires and asked me, "Why in the world do they charge for AIR?!"

I responded, "Inflation." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HMB while I skate off this roof </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you call a gay-porno starring Dwayne Johnson and Johnny Depp? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "*Rock Beats Scissors*" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The cracks in this sign's paint looks like a helicopter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
