<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3415</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure but it doesn't change my opinion that it looks a mess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, that'd be pleasant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That wouldn't fly in real life would it? All sorts of soot would probably get caught up in there... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it's not explicitly a creative mode I'm hoping it will be a core part of the game. Unlocking cosmetic blocks sounds like a fun and rewarding challenge for Terraria house designers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just thought of another one...what if the Creative Update is an attempt to make it so you can't just plop and NPC into a dungeon anymore and expect them to be happy? 

You'd still be able to give everyone a wooden House, but the Dryad would sell extra creative exclusive items and her normal items at a discount if you were to give her a nice living tree house for example. The mage would want a magical dwelling, the party girl a festive house, etc, etc. 

Each NPC could be made to sell unique creative only blocks and items that would enhance our already formidable buildings experience. 

I see potential here to add tons of new walls, backgrounds, furniture, and decorative objects for our abodes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not even past the Eye? The game must be quite the wonder for you then! 

I went bonkers killing things in the jungle once I learned they had added a Frikkin' Uzi to the game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here, I picked the game up again two weeks after not playing for the longest time. 

Last time I played Hallowed Armor was the best you could get and the hardest Boss was Skeletron Prime...I don't think Expert Mode was even a thing last time I played. 

Hella fun now though flying around with Nebula Armor and blasting zombies from my UFO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1.4 Creative Mode Predictions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shall we start guessing what the future holds?

"...developer Cenx mentioned that update 1.4 will have 'a form of creative mode'. This mode 'won't just give you everything. it will all need to be earned', unlike traditional creative modes in other games."

I personally am hoping for some kind of money sink similar to Starbounds replicator which allows you to make items at the cost of money instead of materials given that you've already found/made the item yourself. 

Obviously this would only apply to creative items and decorating items and none of them would have made through this method to prevent money exploits. 

What do you think fellow Terrarians?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have close to 500 hours now and I still need to refer to this ALL the time. 

http://terraria.gamepedia.com/Terraria_Wiki

It's my best friend when playing Terraria! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't say you didn't have fun or get your money's worth, we can argue all day long about those points because they are subjective. What I'm replying to is the objective points that make the game bad, i.e. slow patches, bugs, unbalanced classes and maps, poor in game functionality according to some.

I play a whole butt load of games that have these issues, shit my favorite game ever is POSTAL 2 what does that say about my taste? 

I'm still willing to admit that a game is bad in certain aspects though and if it is bad in enough I'm willing to call it a shitty game. 

As for my last comment it's merely opinion but I do believe most MP games these days are made with money in mind and little else. Games with heart like TF2 and LoL stay popular because they don't prescribe to the making a quick buck off a sub-par game method. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> developer these things would not exist in my games.

Yea but I made it clear I'd have control of my own games. There are a lot of really bad small things that persist in video games today that need to be fixed. 

The biggest issue in my opinion are the goofy ass and lengthy menus that a lot of games make you go through. Icons and stats that aren't explained and clunky menu controls make playing even the most "fun" game frustrating at points. Dragon's Dogma is a prime example of the kind of cuttle fuckery you can expect in a poorly thought out menu system. 

I got a million complaints and were I a developer I'd have a million solutions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Closer view of the houses: http://imgur.com/a/OyV4P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Still doing my best to be creative, here is the beginning of my Expert Mode NPC Village. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like it's working to me! A simple box but an effective one. I like the use of plaques to display items and you have a nice starting crafting area there!

Feel free to add me on Steam if you need someone to play Terraria with, "subject3415." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  What's the smallest an NPC house can be?

http://terraria.gamepedia.com/House

This is a pretty good read that will give you all the technical details.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 13:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the Trump administration taking away so much from public funding and now knowing this it's almost like our current government would love to take us back to the good ol' days where you didn't have to worry about people's rights and the bottom dollar was all that mattered.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 13:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But eating it though? C'mon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 13:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And gave the brave fighter $100. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 13:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem, good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 12:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been told the same. It means your not so long and thick as to hurt them but just long and thick enough to feel pleasure without feeling like she is going to be literally split open.

I don't know I don't think mine is anything to write home about but that is what I've garnered in my life experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 12:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea. The visual effect is an ok way to let the player know they are taking damage but I find it way to distracting compared to a traditional meter of health. 

I love CoD for the campaigns but the red smeared jelly effect bothers the piss out of me and so does the de-sync in Assassin's Creed. 

Were I a developer these things would not exist in my games.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 12:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://terraria.gamepedia.com/Spelunker_Potion

Your best friend. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 12:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd prefer developers stick to improving their games and coming up with some new and refreshing instead of relying on their legacy and the popularity of MOBAS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 12:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All that red filling the screen is retarded as shit. You can barely see what's happening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 12:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Digital Items are the new cancer of the gaming world. 

I love Paladins for example but you'll be fucked if you ever see me spending money on skins or customization items. 

I've bought ONE in my entire time and that was the 8-Bit Music Pack for CS:GO...which I miss.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 12:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Proof? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 12:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where and when did Valve sell hacks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 12:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be Captain Fact mister. 

He isn't sour he's telling the truth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 12:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came off more like a cringe teen trying to state a smug fact.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 12:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thankfully I only need Uplay to play Farcry 3 and Assassin's Creed. Then again I don't play them at all, so Uplay is useless to me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 12:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 12:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While some of those can be put on the publisher from the sound of it the game just fails in enough aspects to qualify as a fun but shitty game. If the player base is willing to leave in droves after only 20-30 hours of game play in today's world it's another here today gone tomorrow kind of experience, as it with most multiplayer games designed to get your buck. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 12:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP you're a condescending dick. This is the most polite I've ever seen a reblogging page ask someone and you go and be a total turd about it. 

Also, what do you mean disabled Facebook audience? 

Are you disparaging anyone who enjoys UNILAD as disabled or are you referring to disabled comments? Because I just checked their page and the latter isn't true. As a matter of fact it doesn't appear they stick their water mark on everything either. 

So you're also presumptuous. Stay classy OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 12:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Max out your buffs with all possible buff potions, make sure you reforge all your accessories to the best possible stats, make sure you also get the well fed buff, use the grindstone for the melee, crystal ball for magic, and summoning table for your summoner. 

While blocking the Moon Lord's lasers are good I find it easier to build a sky bridge out of asphalt and connect teleporters to each end for an infinite loop of running. 

In expert mode it's more vital you don't get hit at all as opposed attempting to take the brunt of an attack.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 10:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks great! And organization tip would be to use the plaques to put relevant item pictures above the chests indicating what kind of items they contain! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
