<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3859</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 01:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you! I appreciate that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The Walk" oil on wood </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 22:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IDAP of my cousin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 22:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Portfolio. Feedback and advice greatly appreciated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 22:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-30 03:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> omg, wow all these years and I didn't even know.. Thank you so much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "A Break" Oil on Canvas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-28 23:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IPAP of My Uncle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-28 23:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-27 21:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there too much work? Too many different types of galleries ? Is the organization too confusing?    Would it better to have fewer significant works under one gallery ? Thanks.in advance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 16:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ....ha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 19:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oil on wood and I started out in layers with a brush and finished it off with a knife.  I know nothing about the resin, will look into it. Thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 13:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha!!!! I thought it was deep at the moment. That commercial was shot a while ago. I feel video is also like a painting, it documents history,  captured what I was going through or the way I thought about things at the given moment.  Don't worry about it so much, I feel great hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 13:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks!! i usually do but I took the picture before signing!!! ahhh I will go back to those and sign them  ASAP thanks for the reminder. cheers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi guys, I want to share my latest painting with you </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 07:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 07:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, it's my mama. I took the picture and it felt so powerful, had to make that painting years later.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 06:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a year left in college but, yes, I am </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 06:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> here is the original photo http://i.imgur.com/OjTWOFg.jpg

and here is my website www.ramandipsingh.com (I'm still updating..I only have my most recent few paintings up) 

like my work on  facebook  "The art of raman singh"

thanks guys more to come </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi everyone, I want to share my latest painting with you guys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 04:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-06 04:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow awesome!!! Made my night.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 09:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool pic. Sucks we don't have many users in this sub.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 08:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sex.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 00:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome !! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 01:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, that makes me feel special </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 01:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one might a little hard to give away, it was a personal piece but if you are interested in having me create you one, shoot me a message </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 01:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please like my facebook page to keep up with my art!

www.facebook.com/singhscanvas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 01:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome comment!! I will be posting more as I finish them. 

Here is all of my paintings

www.noodos.jimdo.com/art-work

and you can also like my page to stay updated on facebook: 

https://www.facebook.com/SinghsCanvas
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi guys, I wanted to share my latest painting with you. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-30 22:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-30 20:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha thanks I actually used it as an experiment piece to learn a new technique and I know I should have paid more attention to the details. I don't consider it a 100% finished piece so I know there are probably more things to fix then what you mentioned. The curve is not actually a road it was sort of a cliff/hill so. Thanks for checking it out anyway. Next time I paint farmland I'll keep your comment in mind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-30 15:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> www.noodos.jimdo.com/art-work

here is the rest of my work(most of it) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-30 15:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This country embraces thought-provoking work, anything that can make you feel a new way or something you have never seen or thought of. 
They are more... modernistic, imagine weird combinations of sculpture and painting... and definitely the digital side of things are picking up.

 I am a major in Communication Arts, and most of classmates do a lot of digital work, 3-d, kinetic imaging, graphic design. I must be the only painter. Classical, traditional methods are still there but barely. 

It is very much about the message and not so much about traditional skill alone. There are some galleries that show amazing skill, but some just show a bunch of shit thrown together claiming a solid reason for it.   I have a couple friends making a living off painting, you just have to find the right people, the rich old people. 

here, this will give you an example: http://www.moma.org/collection/browse_results.php?criteria=O%3ADE%3AI%3A5|G%3AHI%3AE%3A1 page_number=1 template_id=6 sort_order=2

I plan on staying away from the weird and just mastering painting

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-30 14:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. It was a learning piece, I spent two months trying to experiment.  I used a technique called scumbling, it's basically laying down color using a thin medium and moving it around with a dry brush to layer it over existing colors, which creates depth. You can see in the clothes, purples, and blues, reds, I layed them over eachother after letting them dry. The painting it in oils but since I used liquin, it dries within a day.   

I am willing to sell but I am in the U.S right now
and this painting is 32" x 40"
It costs around a couple hundred($500-$1000) for  shipping alone which means I would have to sell it fairly expensive.


I could probably look into making prints for you guys though

and here is the rest of my work
www.noodos.jimdo.com/art-work

Thanks
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-30 14:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I will be sharing more soon and here is more of my paintings

www.noodos.jimdo.com/art-work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-30 14:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi and thank you. So last summer I visited my relatives in India and I took many pictures. This was on my uncles farm and it is one of the workers. I attend VCU here in the U.S and it is pretty great, ranked #1 public art school. I showed the pictures to my professor and he had a lot to say about the picture for this, said he felt a lot of energy from it so I decided to paint it.   
 I was trying new techniques in this painting called scumbling and using fast drying medium call liquin. I started by building a wooden panel and just primed it, no canvas involved. I draw it out in pencil first and started covering big sections in different colors. I just slowly go from big areas to details. When the details came I used scumbling, which is putting down paint, very small amount and pushing it around, with thin fast drying medium, it dries over the other colors instead of taking their place. You can see in the clothing how there are a lot of colors, purples reds etc. I just went in with each other and placed each other down with one brush and using a dry brush, moved the paint around. It' s a really cool effect. Sorry for the long explanation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-30 14:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here you go, it's the first painting

http://noodos.jimdo.com/art-work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-30 14:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a few paintings I did in India and will post them over time. Thanks so much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-30 14:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://noodos.jimdo.com/art-work/
 Thanks and 
Enjoy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-30 04:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! It's my life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi, r/India. I wanted to share with you my latest painting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-30 03:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I got this shot of the Super moon last night with Canon T4I </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-24 21:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-17 10:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beautifully spoken </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-03 10:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks !  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A painting I did for my teacher </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 20:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I painted a friend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 20:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-22 00:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are viewing this, please take a few seconds to VOTE for my design, I appreciate the support REDDIT!!!

 http://m.talenthouse.com/creativeinvites/preview/a8a6f25fa97ac173ab335b4f6529dcf2/978?fb_source=timeline ref=profile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-21 03:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you, I would appreciate your vote

http://www.talenthouse.com/creativeinvites/preview/a8a6f25fa97ac173ab335b4f6529dcf2/978 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IDA surreal self-portrait </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-21 01:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey guys, here is my submission for the Castle of Glass contest, let me know what you think! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-21 01:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-13 07:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm setting up prints at the moment, I will get back to you. Thank you :) 

Here is my work if you need to see more 


 http://rdeepmedia.wordpress.com/the-work-of-raman-singh/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-13 02:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I am using a bamboo tablet in photoshop. It's not the same without that because a mouse cannot be pressure sensitive. The pen and pad is amazing because it can pick up pressure so well and with the right settings in PhotoShop you can draw and paint  like you would traditionally.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 01:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hard to say an exact price. I have rarely had to mail them to someone but I do commissions around my area anywhere from 100-1000$ it depends on the size and content. Most portraits I've sold were around $300-$500. Murals go for more, I'm working on one for $1600. I am thinking of a way I can start selling prints, this is actually my first time working digitally so I am figuring things out printing wise and would love to sell this as a print , esp on this subreddit. Maybe even give out some free ones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 01:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's flattering and it happens to me all the time. But you can't compare someone's highlight reels to your behind the scenes. You must look up, get up and don't ever quit. Aim higher , try to out do whatever it is you think is impossible. Nothing is impossible. You got this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 00:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please, I built my knowledge of color and light from oil painting.  Here are some of my oil paintings,    http://rdeepmedia.wordpress.com/the-work-of-raman-singh/


Just because I am using digital doesn't mean that it is cheating. You still have to know how to PAINT. The process is very similar to oil painting  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-11 21:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-11 21:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I painted it digitally in PhotoShop using a tablet so that's why I was able to layer the colors so smoothly :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey guys, just wanted to share something I just finished painting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-11 19:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Reflection" Painted in photoshop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-11 19:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IDAP of Buddha </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-11 19:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-13 19:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I love India and I love my family and friends there. I come visit from the U.S every summer and over the years, I've noticed India slipping. I find it less and less comfortable each year and last year I told myself I wouldn't come back because of my terrible experience. I always visit Punjab and my family there. Over the years I've noticed my cousins, uncles and friends just kind of lose their selves to drugs and alcohol. I've also noticed kids selling drugs more and more on the streets and everyone basically losing touch of reality. It may just be a Punjab thing but it feels like there is really nothing else for them to do. They feel they are at a dead-end in life. I know I am in no position to judge them but really what else is there ? What is life for people like that? I mean how can they improve instead of just getting by . Another thing , the corruption, I feel disgusted everytime I have to fight off the stupid guards trying to steal my money at the exit of the Delhi airport, Wtf, its a serious problem. Every time they try to haggle the shit out of me. There are many similar instances when I come to India and that is one of the reasons I can appreciate the u.s, people here don't get away with shit like that. Sorry if this was irrelevant but I do love India, I am an art major and paint India all the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-07 01:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 5th grade I read " A Taste of Blackberries". Saddest thing ever. I will still tear up thinking about it. It's about a little boy who's best friend is allergic to bee stings. They are playing one summer and his friend gets stung by a couple bees and he dies. The main boy is in disbelief and sometimes even goes to his friends house after school like he used, only to find his mother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-20 22:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the truth man, hawks game was so painful to watch. He was stubborn and selfish for staying in, cousins would have done much better if they had given him a chance. Griffen said it at the end of the game, "I felt I was the best man on our team to get the job done so I stayed out there " (somethin like that).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IDAP of Night and day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 20:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Night and Day", Tablet in Photoshop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 20:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey guys, I just finished this motivational video.
Let me know what you think </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-31 17:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 07:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, this is actually my first digital piece! I started working on a tablet last week and I plan to turn this into a painting. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IDA study of my friends face </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 01:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IDA self-portrait in Photoshop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-17 19:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 16:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh woww now that's the stuff I was lookin for!!!!! I've actually seen some of these works in New York . Thanks!!! And let me know any more similar to him!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey guys, I had a question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-11 04:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to put together a list and study some new techniques. 

Does anyone have an idea who may be top oil painters of our time or know any websites that show the best contemporary realistic oil paintings?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-06 12:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was actually going to sleep but when I saw your picture I couldn't resist,[ A quick sketch](http://i.imgur.com/57vmE.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-01 04:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> VCU REPPIN!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-28 04:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, it was definitely a learning process.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I painted my friend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-27 17:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-24 09:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CONTENT REMOVED??!?!WHAT DID IT SAY? AHHH  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-23 06:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-22 19:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) thank you, I'm getting there also. Don't stop, do a lot of small paintings to understand light, color and composition.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend recently passed away in a car crash, I painted this for his family. "Iridescent" Oil on Canvas. 20"x30" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-22 14:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IDAP of my good friend who recently passed away </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-22 14:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-21 10:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's digital. Prob photoshop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-12 22:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know people are complaining about the punchline in the title, but atleast you didn't write "FINALLY FACEBOOK DELIVERED" DERRRRHURRR 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-30 04:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay , did not know that thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-29 21:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah oils and thanks, nothings really finished. the hands  still need more work, they are a little flat in the light areas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-27 21:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah I think I'll do that. The canvas has just been haunting me, i thought it had so much potential before I raninto a million problems. I had to do the face over completely at least 3 times. Right now Im working on 5 paintings at once, and will probably get back to it after. thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-27 20:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does anyone post their art?
I didn't finish this but I still spent a good amount of time on it and wanted to share it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-27 19:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes , thank you. I do know that the red is overpowering, I was in the process of toning it down before I abandoned it. I would like to finish, this was done from life sitting infront of a mirror so it's a little hard to set up everything again in my hallway. I've learning not all paintings are going to be successful. here are some other works

http://www.flickr.com/photos/noodosvision/sets/72157631248074926/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-27 19:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow thank you. Funny thing about bob ross, it was my birthday on October 29th and I went on google to see the custom logo for his birthday, it made my day to know we had the same birthday haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A self-portrait I gave up on </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-27 17:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IDA self-portrait </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-27 17:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My boy Simba </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-20 22:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My boy Simba  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-20 22:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-15 10:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. Very interesting you say that. This was just a small color study for the bigger painting. I do know it has a certain energy that the bigger piece did not have, makes me question my work    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-15 02:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's all good Haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-15 00:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha no its my mom, but its missing a lot of information like the hair an stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-14 23:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HOW DO YOU KNOW MY NAME </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-14 21:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scratch that, I just clicked on the link. That is my first attempt at a storyboard about a tree and his life . Deadline approached so I had to rush the end. Water colors. And yes really fun and interesting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-14 21:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your welcome. They were really fun because I've been switching back and forth between using brushes and palette knives. The palette knife ones are the more expressive pieces and basically don't have to worry about layers .I'm just laying paint down in knife strokes . Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-14 20:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finished paintings

http://www.flickr.com/photos/noodosvision/sets/72157631248074926/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Learning to paint using only primary and secondary colors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-14 19:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-10 01:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks
this was kind of just a sketch but heres some more work
http://www.flickr.com/photos/noodosvision/sets/72157631248074926/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-10 01:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well I don't have an official site I sell my work on just yet, but I'm working on it. I usually use paypal to sell online though. If you need some art, p.m me. I have been doing local commissions recently  , here's more work. 

http://www.flickr.com/photos/noodosvision/sets/72157631248074926/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-09 04:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you , it was done by a palette knife. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I painted my friend and her pet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-09 04:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-03 05:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shoot, got a lot of work to do still, its Been around 20 hours </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IDAP of my cousin, wip </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-31 06:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-28 21:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even though I have a 2011 I think the 03-04 bodies are the sickest, much meaner lookin and less bulky than the new gen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-11 18:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same, just bought mine too.fuck this article, I love my baby  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-11 18:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just bought this about two months ago, and fuckin love it. why is this telling me I'm an idiot?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-19 07:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mansa, Punjab, India </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-18 08:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol that's what I do all day actually. I step on it as soon as I get on the parkway and just laugh and scream all hysterical an sinister as I redline the gears. It'll make you do that  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-18 04:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a 2011 gt/cs but the boss still makes me want to cry, mad jealous. Congrats, treat her well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-17 05:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> your comment evoked a very painful mental image *cringe* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> oh lawdy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-11 11:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-03 01:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no I think your right, nice job checking out composition </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I painted my sister in oils </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-02 22:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I painted my sister </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-02 22:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just finished this painting of my sister, any feedback reddit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-02 22:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-29 07:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that I think about it, its insane. So back in the kazaa days, I was in 5th grade tryin to download dragonballz episodes and accidently downloaded an amv with "a place for my head". My life was never the same. I barely knew English an had never listened to music before but to this day LP has always been there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
