<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1577</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 06:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realized as soon as I posted this that I forgot the gloves, d'oh! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 06:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> original post
https://www.reddit.com/r/characterdrawing/comments/4z6yel/lfa_male_elven_spellsword/?st=is9oc60c sh=36cb5c38
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [RF] Male Elven Spellsword </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 06:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 20:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's a nervous tic, she can't help her self. she's tried to stop, but she can't just let it go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 20:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 05:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey I took a shot at your character, I hope you like it.

https://www.reddit.com/r/characterdrawing/comments/4zamjj/rf_female_dhampir_rogue/?st=is8d1b1f sh=fa9c1d69

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [RF] Female Dhampir Rogue. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 05:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 23:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually had to look up who she was, I didn't know who she was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 23:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh, jeez, yea. hah!  that would be unintentional. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 23:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Megan was the name of the woman he left at home, sorry I guess it wasn't clear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 01:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My name is, no.  Not that my name is no, its just that you shouldnt concern yourself with unimportant details like names.  I am beautiful, am I not? Shhh.  I know, I know, your ship is leaving, no, they are not coming back, they will sail away, because they do not love you like I do.  I didnt choose to love you, I didnt choose you.  The song did.  The song is more than me, and you.  The song is everything.  You heard the song when you were born, you heard the song when your parents told you they were proud of you, when you kissed your first girl, when you first decided that you loved the sea, and you will hear the song when you die.  It is the same for me.  I was brought into the world by the song.  Though for us it is crueler, I can sing my song, but each word, each breath that leaves my lips takes some of my song with it.  You see, I need you.  I love you.  Your song is so beautiful, I heard it when your ship drew close, and when our songs touched, well, it was magic.

I know, youre afraid, all you know is this world, I know that there is a part of you still fighting, still trying to return to your life before our songs became one.  That part of you has always been afraid, always told you that you couldnt succeed, that you shouldnt go, or shouldnt stay, or asked you maybe she isnt the one.  That part of you hates you, it would kill the song if it could.  It would create a world with no fear, no danger, it would kill all of the dragons and monsters, and turn off the stars.  It would flatten every mountain, and fill every sea, fill the sky with light so there would never be night.  It would kill me.

Dont look at me such, please dont hate me, I am not without compassion, I do not take just to take, this is my breath, this is my life, and when our songs are one, you will be part of my song, part of me.  I will forever more sing about the woman you loved before me, her name was Megan, and her hair was the color of honey, and her eyes like the sea.  Your father Curt, and his strong arms and fair voice, he would sing to your mother Alice on nights when you all gathered around the fire and tell you tales of the way the world should be.  Of your first ship, the Grey Cutter, and how afraid you were of its height and size, but how brave you were when those men attempted to take her by force.  Your life is beautiful, like a spring storm, you came on so fast, you overtook me with your waves and song like thunder rang out to me, it begged me to call you, and mine would take none other once it heard the beauty of yours.  

I fear I will not have many more like you, the world is growing so afraid, so fearful that no one chooses to live.  They instead stay on their islands called countries and wooden caves called homes, and warn their children against the sea.  They are all so afraid that even if I were to come across them, their song would be so fouled by fear I could not take them, even if I had no other.  I know others came on the boat with you, but their hearts knew only fear, you were afraid too, but more than fear was the excitement, the others warned you of me, said not to come this way.  They tried to take you when you heard our song, they were fools.  You are perfect, you are complete, you are alive, and I love you for it.  

Normally I would have let our songs swell and soar and become one by now, but your song is so sweet so full of life and living, we will take it slow, I will let you sing all that you can so that others, when they come to me, will know that you lived.  Sing to me of your birth, your childhood, your first skinned knee, your first fear, your first success, your first failure.  Sing to me of all the others that you have known.  Sing to me of your dreams, and desires.  Sing to me, sing to me!    

Shhhh, I know it is getting difficult to sing my love, the waters work against us, they move to swallow you, to take your perfectness from me and hide you in their depths, but please love, sing to me a little longer. Sing to me.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 18:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> awesome, I'm glad you like it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 08:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finished it up, I hope you like it!
https://www.reddit.com/r/characterdrawing/comments/4yharh/rf_leander_pavo_exjudge_turned_adventurer/?st=is1cu2ag sh=83f9eb9c
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 08:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Original post:
https://www.reddit.com/r/characterdrawing/comments/4ydwoh/lfa_leander_pavo_exjudge_turned_adventurer/?st=is0v7ncp sh=a6ceac7a </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [RF] Leander Pavo, ex-judge turned adventurer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 08:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 05:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to take a shot at this, I should be done tonight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 15:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!, I'm glad you like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 08:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got caught up, and finished it, I hope you like it!

https://www.reddit.com/r/characterdrawing/comments/4yaqb4/rf_elven_rogue_hailing_from_a_desert_tribe/?st=irzy3f2v sh=fa002f74

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [RF] Elven rogue hailing from a desert tribe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 08:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 08:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm taking a shot at your character, I really like the description.  I should be done by tomorrow.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 02:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fair, but the LFA said she was a wild sorceress, so control might be an issue.  I meant for the blade to be a little more "short broad blade" but I think it came out ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [RF] Elf who thinks she's a dwarf </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 00:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 19:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to give this a shot, I love the description! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 07:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is so awesome, so much jealousy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [RF] Would anyone be willing to draw my Starbound character? (Avian Male) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 21:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chromyx for /u/Druyii </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 05:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 05:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This may seem a bit harsh, but good LFA posts and bad sort themselves out.  Bad or boring posts don't get RFs, good and interesting one do.  More than that there are a slew of amazing and talented artists here, and each one of them has their own preferences.  I am notoriously fickle, choosing an LFA based on a line or sudden whim, other artists thrive on the structure and bounds of a posters request with references and color guides.
I think this subreddit is doing well, we're above 14,000 subscribers and we continuously improve on the quality of the art and LFAs.  right now things are working, and working well, there will always be LFAs that don't get filled, and those that post those LFAs may need to repost, if they don't get filled, or feel that the fill wasn't exactly what they had in mind, at the end of the day that just means more idea's brought to the page.  Long and short, thanks guys for all the work you do, and you're doing a great job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 16:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup,  the LFA mentioned the character was part of the bear tribe, and I like the Windhelm symbol, so it kind of fit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 16:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea,  from the LFA the person mentioned her as an inspiration,  so I went with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 04:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no worries I'm glad you like it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 03:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey I took a shot at your character, I hope you like it!

https://www.reddit.com/r/characterdrawing/comments/4rg0uc/rf_human_barbarian_sheildmaiden_ravenloft/?st=iqa6xwzt sh=840040b1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [RF] Human Barbarian Sheildmaiden (Ravenloft) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 03:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 18:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sorry, I did just read that right.  I've been a poser hold out for years, but last month I started using DAZ more and more.  This particular pic was done in DAZ3D, and then over to PS for more work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 18:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome!  I'm so glad you like it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 16:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, yea, usually I try to stay away from "fantasy female armor" where shock and awe is the main defensive point.  but as it was coming together it looked cool so I went with it.  
Thanks again!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 07:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that I've had time to think about it, and just to put the full "nerd on" I can see your point, where a strike to the upper outer torso would "slide" off and past the target, but any hits toward the middle of the chest would slide in until it struck home.  The rounded chest plate would help to have all blows strike away from home and slide off of the sides of target.  That being said, I think the "boob plate" looks cool, and isn't that what art is truly about?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 00:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> who doesn't mind a few crushed sternums? thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 00:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hah! Boobplate, that maybe my favorite phrase of the week, thanks for feedback. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 00:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yup, the base model is done there, then touch up and paint work in Photoshop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 22:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, took a shot at your character, I hope you like it.

https://www.reddit.com/r/characterdrawing/comments/4qytoa/rf_human_female_knight/?st=iq5lz5mt sh=1bfe30bf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [RF] Human Female Knight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 22:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 17:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries,  I'm glad you like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 20:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 03:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad you like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
