<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1563</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 03:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Now this is moonlight!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 13:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lost 50k doing thst </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 05:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> teach me senpi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 04:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right it should be Rape = Sex(Privilege)


That way it works in proportion, and if there's no privilege or sex, there is zero rape. As privilege increases and sex is constant, the rape becomes greater. As the amount of sex increases and privilege stays constant, rape becomes greater. You could also have a combination of someone who has almost no privilege at all lock someone else in a dungeon and molest them for years and it wouldn't be nearly the level of rape as if Donald Trump kissed a black disabled transgender muslim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 04:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Veganism isn't the only or even the best way to eat sustainably, but yeah it's true the way most of us eat isn't sustainable. We eat way too much red meat, and we don't eat a variety of foods. Especially us Americans. We're the worst. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 04:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Where_Is_Everybody%3F

I think this would be a good one, it could be done using VR.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 04:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've received a temporary one point penalty. After 24 hours your rating will return to normal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 04:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but if you blow your load you just have to wait another ten minutes or so to blow another one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 04:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the Entire History of you would be better for someone to get their feet wet. It's not overly dark or creepy or even philosophical like say White Christmas , but it's a much better episode than nosedive. I think it's more plausible as a scenario too. The episode portrays human tendencies to want to capture and relive every moment, coupled with a very plausible piece of technology that would allow them to do just that. There's even contact lenses that can record video being built/already built IIRC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it was really crucial and that was the only way yeah i supposed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely not. There are way too many sources to get an answer to a question. Either i'm unqualified for the job and i will likely run into more problems or it's something difficult and then I would work with my team and/or ask online. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 12:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I use r. I like using my left hand to parry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 12:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you that the controls as is are horrible for dark souls. I had to remap everything and it took time to get used to. After doing about 6 playthroughs with those controls I'm probably just as comfortable as you are with a controller. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 12:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally disagree. I started out using the PC controls and got used to the controls. I could switch to a controller if I wanted but I use a mouse and keyboard for every other game so I'd rather stick with what I'm comfortable with. I think whatever controls a person is best is superior. I also don't care how it was "meant" to be played. It really makes no difference to me at all. I like being able to dodge with the space bar, using mouse buttons to attack, using shift to hold up my shield and using r to parry. Most of all, I much prefer a mouse when looking around as opposed to a right joystick . I've played ds3 with a friend and used a controller. It's not a different experience at all really. It's just a matter of getting used to controls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After changing around the keys it's really not bad at all. Plus, I've seem someone beat the game with donkey kong bongos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use a mouse and keyboard, so I actually tap r to parry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 02:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is she getting half as long? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 02:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The skin is the worst part? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would police officers do for a living if they weren't police officers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 17:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some other job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 17:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm sorry, what I meant to say was you should be able to sell 5-year olds for heroin" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 17:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's pretty fucking racist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People having loud conversations in a relatively quiet place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "and from that day on, there was never violence between the police and the black community ." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 05:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh okay yeah I understand. I never really thought about that. I only worry about downvotes. That one person who brings you to 0 or -1 pretty much guarantees you'll be downvoted into oblivion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 04:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd suggest not using a shield. Really helps for a no shield run. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 04:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't kill her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 04:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's amazing. She needs to git gud though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 04:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would anyone know that you upvoted them? Isn't it anonymous? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 04:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely despise this. Even worse is when you need to go to a whole new page. Fuck that shit, I refuse to read your shitty article if you can't put it on one page. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 04:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We just got into using partial fractions during integration for my calc class and constantly need to do polynomial long division. It sucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 22:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I get it. She dug at her hard but it's a track, not just a series of tweets or something. If she was going to make a track and especially do after Ether, she should have seriously stepped her game up. She wasn't very clever with her lyrics and the flow was just weak. Really it was just shit talking over a beat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 22:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come, reek </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 22:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The track we're talking about is called shEther, after one of the greatest diss tracks of all time. I think it's fair for me to compare it with some of the greatest diss tracks ever given Remy deliberately made the connection with Ether. Don't name it that if you don't intend it to be one of the greats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol yes. I would love to see some more crazy science/engineering done by Eugene. The idea of using melted metal on the walkers is awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go listen to no vaseline and then tell me this was "vicious" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. Especially using Nas's ether. He absolutely shredded Jay Z, while also maintaining a good flow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ITT: pretending that this track was anything more than a steaming pile of garbage. What happened to good diss tracks?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A bloodbath? That shit was terrible. She should be ashamed for naming the track shether and using that beat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 04:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgot about that. Makes it even funnier that he's eating pickles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 04:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes it's not even when I'm miserable. I find it grounding and it makes me feel appreciation for the truly meaningful things in life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 02:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes all the time. I can never come up with a solid stance on abortion, but I'm perfectly happy to point out flawed arguments and to support arguments that i find compelling. Pretty much the same when it comes to the transgender debate. Can a biological man be a woman or vice versa? I personally don't think so. I understand the argument that gender is separate from biological sex, but in all reality the concept of gender derives from biological sex. Try and describe a persons gender, without speaking in terms of male and female. You can't. In my mind, no matter how feminine a man is, he is still biologically male. If he believes himself to be a woman, he has an incorrect belief. I have no problem with a dude wearing a dress or makeup or whatever. Do what you want, but you're not a woman no matter how much you believe you are. However I cannot stand how ignorant people hate on them, claim they are just perverts, and that it's morally wrong etc. Let people live. There's no reason why a person can't express themselves and be who they want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jokes aside there's room for interpretation. That's the point. Are they just really complex machines that uncannily mimic human behavior, or are they actual beings?

Edit: also Nick's memories and personality are not his own, they've been uploaded to him from someone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 01:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you think you don't have a hangover and then you sit up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 01:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what are you talking about? synths aren't people. They're just machines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 17:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is an identity though? It's a collection of what we do, who we interact with, our likes and dislikes, beliefs etc. In all reality none of those things are what we really are. We come up with a narrative and identity to describe this sort of "person" we are but in reality it's just an illusion. That's why I suppose we shouldn't care so much about identity and should seek to understand the world in the most objective way possible. Obviously there are limits to that as we are creatures that have limits to perception , biases etc. I believe gender is totally unnecessary and meaningless as an identity. Just like i think sexuality is pointless as an identity .

Edit: i don't mean to say that we should do away with identity completely. obviously we all need names and we need a way to understand and identity people. but I really believe that indulging in concepts like gender are nothing more than self obsession. It's not reality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 17:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't mean in a social way, I mean as in distinguishing between humans. As in the way I would distinguish a European person from an Asian person. Objective differences.  I am not concerned with how people view themselves subjectively.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 17:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do actually. I hate toast that is crunchy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 17:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i thought playtest was a bit overkill with "mindfuck" aspect. It went too far when the guy went home and everything and was still in the game. It was cool when you found out he wasn't really in that house, but it went way too far after that. Also one second in the game and he experienced all that? its just pushing it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's like they don't have any control over whether or not they get pregnant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 02:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't wanna spoil anything for people who don't watch the show or just started, but look at episodes like rick potion number 9 and tell me the show adheres to those tropes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At times it can be deep. Not deep as in "OMFG that shit was sooo deeep!!! My brain exploded!!!!" but it hits the nail on the head when it comes to the failings of human nature and some of the cold truths of the universe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 13:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think pretty much everyone understands the concept. It's just that not everyone buys into the idea that a person's subjective view of what they are makes them that thing and everyone else has to see it that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 13:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep. I don't think it's ever been men that don't want women in their restrooms . It's really for the safety and privacy of women. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 13:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> spot on. I can't stand the condescending attitude of lefties, and i for the better part of my life considered myself liberal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 13:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, because nothing could go wrong with a 200 pound man and a 120 pound woman in a bathroom alone. Literally no concern. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 04:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> check your virtual privelege </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 03:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He could use a big reusable water bottle and not generate any waste. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 18:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dragons don't have layers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 04:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he was in Ancient Greece he'd be in good company  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 04:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel the same way. I feel like a cunt criticizing something way beyond my ability, but I didn't really like that either. Otherwise absolutely stellar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For every complaint you can have about a game, there exists a game that doesn't have that issue.

Don't like a game that allows you to save too
much?

Try dark souls 


Don't like a game with tons of radiant quests?


Try dark souls 


Don't like a game that tells you where to go constantly?


try dark souls  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 16:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they fail and you're on the other side of the plane, you're good. If you're right next to them, you might get hurt/killed before they're stopped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 16:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm communicating right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hit  ler did  noth  ing wrong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nonconforming is just conforming to a different set of norms </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. As a dual major in CS and Communication, I have a major skill that the majority of CS majors don't have, the ability to communicate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually just step away from my computer and go do something for a while. It can take a bit depending on how much i'm downloading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 00:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Dwight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 00:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not if its just a quick intro. I hate long introductions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 18:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should really watch your sodium </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 13:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck Toby </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 13:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck off. You just posted this for shock value. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 12:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had plenty. Just tired of stale memes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 12:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't say? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 04:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The concept is, yeah. Integrals can be really hard sometimes but the ones in the picture aren't that hard. 

DAE math is hard??!! I hate that stupid circle jerk. Throw up a bunch of trig and calc stuff and everyone circlejerks to how "difficult" it is. That's the thing is i'm not trying to be smart at all. I guess its just cool to suck at math. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 04:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh hello there. I will stay behind to gaze at the sun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 04:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wtf are you even saying? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 03:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What purpose would going extinct achieve? What is the end goal? The entire reason we want to preserve the environment is so that we can live happily on a healthy planet. There's nothing to evaluate to say if the planet is better or not without our existence because we don't exist. It's like solving world hunger by killing everyone in the world. It solves the problem of starvation but not in a meaningful way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 03:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it comes off that way, but seriously this shit isn't that complicated if you've taken basic math.

Edit: didn't realize so many people would get salty about this. Maybe you should have paid attention in math class! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If an undead comes along after you and links the fire, the age of dark is delayed yet again. If this continues on and on forever, is the age of dark really inevitable? It only becomes inevitable if there is no undead to link the fire, or no undead chooses to link the fire. It seems then that linking the fire could be a really positive ending. Life can continue on if there is someone willing to make the ultimate sacrifice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After taking multiple calc classes I can't help but hate this meme. Shit is so basic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> exactly there's nothing inherent about this behavior that is tied to race. It's culture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 04:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hoes gonna be hoes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 04:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess i'm apathetic towards it. I want my friends to be happy, but as far as them meeting someone or whatever, that doesn't excite me. It's their business and if they end up really liking the person i'm more than happy to meet them and get to know them. I hate talking about relationships though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> more like reverse racism is racism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we're going to be technical, an sl1 caestus only run would have it even more difficult than that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seath the tailless </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just cut off Seaths tail after many frustrating attempts. Finally got that MLGS for my int character. I find it ironic that this tail cut is more difficult with and int based character than dex/strength/quality builds seeing as how the MLGS scales with int.

EDIT: int isn't the most difficult, just one of the more difficult to get the tail cut

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> for you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think i only died to him my very first play through. Capra sucks because of those damn dogs. Once theyre gone, it's ridiculously easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally just yesterday said Beyonce was overrated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Wall-E send the MOST ABSOLUTELY FUCKING CORRECT view of obesity" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then the msm refuses to acknowledge the crises, instead focusing on how racist everyone who doesnt want refugees are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit, better start leveling it then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even easier than Taurus Demon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone level resistance? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 03:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really see the purpose in it. I feel like those points would be netter spent on end, vit, or something to output damage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 21:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You also have to take soul level, weapons and armor etc. into account. At the point you dight gwyn, you are at the end of the game. You should have fully upgraded everything.  Also the area you fight gwyn in is pretty big, and theres stalagmites you can use as a barrier between you and him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 20:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this post gave me cancer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 20:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never parried Gwyn. I either dodge or use a greatshield to block. If i never heard that other people considered Gwyn hard, i'd say he's an easy boss. But, i've gotten absolutely destroyed by four kings and everyone says they are the easiest. Everyone has different experiences. I truly don't think its a meme. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 20:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> same. i've gotten rekt so many times by four kings but never have any trouble with gwyn at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 20:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i really don't think its a meme. i've never lost to gwyn more than once on any character. ive died to capra more than gwyn. some people have an easy time with certain bosses but struggle with others that seem to come easy to different players. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 17:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh okay that makes sense then. that's awesome haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 21:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whats the purpose of losing all your health before the fight? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 19:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i know im going to get flak for this, but if she doesnt say no or indicate that she wants to stop, then it cant be considered rape. If a cop shoots me because i didn't put my hands up, but he never said to put my hands up, whose fault is that? im not doubting that someone would freeze up but if someone starts kissing you and doing sexual stuff and you dont pull away or say stop, why would they have any reason to think you want to stop? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
