<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3727</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 15:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are so many things like world peace, hunger, population, diseases etc. In our country trees has become a rare thing, we do not have any very big jungle now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Serious What goal do you think humanity is not focused enough on achieving? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 15:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 15:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do not own a car. what about you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you hate most and love most about your car? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 15:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 14:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Munna Bhai MBBS" Its a Indian "Hindi" movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What movie can you watch over and over without ever getting tired of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 14:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Evidence of the Film 1913 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 13:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 13:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my country Pakistan one serial killer killed 100kids, can we call him pure evil? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 12:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Evil person does not care anybody and anything, he or she want to get his or her goal at any cost. the cost can be murder, robbing, raibing, torchering etc. I am not talking about common crimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did anybody drop mobile? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 12:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A man picks up answers a phone in the shopping center. "hello darling i recently saw a necklace in a catalog and i want it, so do you mind if i use your
credit card?" "how expensive is it?" the man says "just $1200" "that cheap? hell i'll get four of them for you so you'll wear a different one each season"
"your so generous honey, oh i also want a ring" "how expensive?"  "just $5000" "get two, one for each hand" "thank you! oh i also want a new car, it's
$40000" "sure why lot" "i love you dear! oh i gotta go, bye" after that the man quizzically looks around the mall and loudly asks "did anyone drop a phone?"
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 12:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you i will try to read it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What makes a person truly evil? Are they born that way or did their environment make them that way? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 11:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 08:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I impose direct democracy here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 08:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is not a rule </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You discover a beautiful island upon which you may build your own society. You make the rules. What is the first rule you put into place? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 08:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 08:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then why they are apes and we are human beings? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 07:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do not believe this theory. What about those who think this is right theory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If people evolved from apes, why are there still apes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 07:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you consider it more important to be liked or respected? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 07:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 07:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kangaroo and cricket teem[5 time world champion] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 07:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Life is infinitely stranger than anything which the mind of man could invent. We would not dare to conceive the things which are really mere commonplaces
of existence. If we could fly out of that window hand in hand, hover over this great city, gently remove the roofs, and peep in at the queer things which
are going on, the strange coincidences, the plannings, the cross-purposes, the wonderful chains of events, working through generations, and leading to
the most outre results, it would make all fiction with its conventionalities and foreseen conclusions most stale and unprofitable. [Sherlock Holms] 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 05:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> give that poster to some other person and observe it and it happend same than find the history of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 05:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no till now maybe in future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> have you ever listened a dieing person's last words and what were those? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 05:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> have you ever listened last words of a dieing person? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 05:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Concept of Politics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 03:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A small boy asks his Dad, "Daddy, what is politics?" Dad says, "Well son, let me try to explain it this way: I'm the breadwinner of the family, so let's
call me Capitalism. Your mom, she's the administrator of the money, so we'll call her the Government. We're here to take care of your needs, so we'll call
you the People. The nanny, we'll consider her the Working Class. And your baby brother, we'll call him the Future. Now, think about that and see if that
makes sense." So the little boy goes off to bed thinking about what Dad has said. Later that night, he hears his baby brother crying, so he gets up to
check on him. He finds that the baby has severely soiled his diaper. The little boy goes to his parents' room and finds his mother sound asleep. Not wanting
to wake her, he goes to the nanny's room. Finding the door locked, he peeks in the keyhole and sees his father having sex with the nanny. He gives up and
goes back to bed. The next morning, the little boy says to his father, "Dad, I think I understand the concept of politics now." The father says, "Good,
son, tell me in your own words what you think politics is all about." The little boy replies, "Well, while Capitalism is screwing the Working Class, the
Government is sound asleep, the People are being ignored and the Future is in Deep Shit. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 03:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prize Winner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 03:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A police officer stopped a car on the highway and went up to the driver. He saw the man, and said: "You've just won $1000 for wearing a seat belt! What
are you going to do with your prize money?" The man thought, and said back: "Maybe go to the driving school and get my licence!" His wife told the cop:
"Don't listen to him, he's a smartass when he's drunk".  All of this talking made a passenger in the back of the car wake up, and he blurted out: "I knew
we wouldn't get far in this stolen car. Why didn't you change the number plate?" A knock emerged from the trunk of the car, and the person in the trunk
said: "Are we at the border yet?" 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 03:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my life is to simple. I do not have any experience like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Describe something thats happened to you for which had no explanation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 03:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 03:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice shot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 02:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Less than 10years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
