<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2923</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 00:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do! I've only been playing with the pedals for an hour or so, so I still have a lot of experimenting to do, but so far it's super tweakable with a good variety of sounds, most of which are pretty great. The drive sounds surprisingly good too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 23:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definite Moogerfooger in there, but I don't know which one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NPD] x 2/Shaking with excitment/Apparently there's a blue Wizard of Pitch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 22:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 18:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I highly recommend the Diamond Compressor. It's super simple, sounds like a legit rackmount compressor (very high quality) and works well as a preamp too. Also, the tilt eq is faaaantastic for sculpting your tone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 08:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't help but notice that your board is made of carpet. Custom job? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 04:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best barometer for gear prices is sold items in eBay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 07:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is of you want a gooey dark analog delay (plus a bunch of other options in the case of meet maude). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 06:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not particularly. Meet Maude is exponentially better imo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 06:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had really high hopes for it and then some serious issues with the blend/delay level. Could never get it to sit right. I think I remember much more distortion than I was anticipating also. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 01:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ehx microsynth

boss ce-3

dod fx25b envelope filter

mxr phase 90

obne black fountain

ehx big muff pi (have had it for 10 + years and a friend finally modded it a month ago and made it usable)

boss oc-2 (a lot of people really love these... maybe I had a lemon)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 00:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds an awful lot like a repackaged synth wah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 23:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HERE HOW YOU DO THAT

https://youtu.be/NLI9NR07PW0

just for you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 00:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep! It's the mode that lets you tune the repeats when you are using the pedal as intended. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 05:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you plug it into itself in manual mode you get a tuneable oscillator. Pretttty, pretttty, pretttty good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 23:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So far I've mostly been messing with mode 1. I'll run a tone into it from the wurlitzer to the freeze, give it some stutters with the foxtrot, then use the ct5 to add 5ths and octaves by messing with the direction smooth all of that out a little with the fairfield. The length knob is great in this situation too, especially when you want to change the tempo by shortening or lengthening the fragments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 08:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it a lot so far. I'm pretty much just using it to add a little randomness/texture to the droney stuff that's coming out of the freeze. Haven't really gotten into the pitch aspect of it yet but I'm sure that will be fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 06:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude! That video just sent me down a 20 minute youtube whole of looking at Electro Lobotomy instruments. So cool...

As far as instruments go, guitar is my main one, but I've been using a good bit of this cool old Wurlitzer electric piano I got pretty recently --- http://i.imgur.com/lDsnKBV.jpg , a decent amount of autoharp (mostly backwards so far), bass, mangled drums, vocals... I'm probably going to get more into noise territory for dream sequences and stuff so I'm sure I'll be adding more weird/unconventional instruments and samples for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 01:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonderyak got it. Thanks so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 01:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct! And it's amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 01:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a lot! It's always refreshing to interact with cool, supportive people online. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 00:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah! I'm so excited. The director/producer/writer is someone I met in the first year or so that I moved to LA (been here for 5 and a half years doing various music things). I did some music for a short he made last year and he's seen me play shows and heard my music. He wrote a really good script and got it to the lead actress. She signed on and helped him wrangle more people. He then enlisted me as a kind of consultant to help with a song they perform in the movie and I told him I would love to write some original music for the movie if possible, and pretty quickly that turned into me being the composer. Soooo, time + work + luck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 00:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.imdb.com/title/tt5198796/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scoring a movie   these 4 have been an invaluable combo when pure dreaminess is called for. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 23:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 04:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one has ever looked cooler giving two thumbs up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tiny Terror </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 06:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tiny Terror/5 Pounds of Fury </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 05:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tiny Terror/5 Pounds of Fury </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 05:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 10:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aside from the fact that I posted it on here when I got it, I'd have to say my 1970s Bob Moog designed Maestro MP-1 phaser (it can be controlled easily with your foot and sounds amazing). Also, the alesis bitrman. I love that crazy thing. Oh, it's not exactly a pedal but I have this insane sounding spring reverb made by a company called Monacor. They were based in the US, but I have the German version for some reason.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 21:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah... that's exactly my point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can you think of anything more outdated than using a signature to verify your identity or agree to a contract? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 20:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 01:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peep Show </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 22:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jail time please </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 18:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually just got it so the only things I've done so far are move it and play it. Someone else put a different speaker and some new tubes in at some point but I think everything else is original. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1959 blonde Wurlitzer 700 electric piano [2640  1894] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 22:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1959 blonde Wurlitzer 700 electric piano [2640  1894] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 22:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 21:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [26401894] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1959 blonde Wurlitzer 700 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 21:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
