<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3364</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which idol's guest appearance in a show surprised you the most? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 09:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe because they were surprisingly funny or their personality was not what you expected. I thought CL's appearance in Running Man was cool because she was shy, which I really did not expect at all. Her on stage persona was really totally different to her appearance in the show which I found really found interesting.


I posted this on r/koreanvariety already which some of you may have seen. The input was good but there wasn't a lot of answers due to the smaller size so that's why I am reposting it here.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CODE KUNST - Parachute (Feat. Oh Hyuk   DOK2) [Korean R B] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 07:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA: West Brom's next 6 games are all green fixtures </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 14:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might want to bring in some WBA players to take advantage of this if you don't have any yet. I'd recommend Phillips or Brunt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Evgeny Emelyanov - Children Of Water [Pure Chill/Instrumental] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 14:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 13:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you whore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 13:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've taken Costa out for Defoe instead of Kane or Lukaku since both those two screwed me over last time I had them. Watch them get hat tricks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ZICO - Bermuda Triangle (Feat. Crush, DEAN) [Korean Rap] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 13:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 12:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I checked 'The Isle of Arran.' Really good stuff. Will definitely look at more from him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This guy's voice deserves much more attention </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 12:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RADWIMPS - Nandemonaiya [Chill] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 11:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 11:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus Christ. Daily Star really don't have any shame do they... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 08:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since Walcott is out and since he's impressed in his last few games I think its pretty likely for this game. Though I wouldn't be bringing him into an FPL team if that's what you're thinking since he isn't really nailed on yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 05:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those creatures on the left are pretty adorable as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which guest appearance in a show surprised you the most? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 04:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe because they were surprisingly funny or their personality was not what you expected. I thought CL's appearance in Running Man was cool because she was shy, which I really did not expect at all. Her on stage persona was really totally different to her appearance in the show which I found really found interesting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 04:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did u get him ip to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 12:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What were the french commentators saying? They sounded quite hyped lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 12:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are really good! Thanks for uploading it. I would love to see commentary for Zlatan's bicycle kick against England but it was a only a friendly so I don't think there will be much languages for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 10:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since you're in 17/18 maybe you could pick up Barzagli's regen if the original has retired. My regen was a beast with 83 pace + 90 strength. Only 6 foot but didn't matter. He was amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 10:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The teams good. Just keep in mind that Coutinho will be coming back into play for a very cheap price so maybe you'd want to fit him in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 11:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh thanks! So the only I can make a profit is by buying IF cards? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 11:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats true. Could you recommend me any cheap players that could receive upgrades then? I've literally got less than 2000 coins in the bank atm. It's alright if you don't know. Thanks for the answer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 11:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it a good idea to invest in more Lallana cards then? I think he will definitely be upgraded so maybe I could sell him for a profit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How can FIFA upgrades affect me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 11:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that the best performing players will get upgrades if their cards don't match their performances. If I already have their old card, will it be upgraded? Or will it stay the same? eg. I have Lallana's card so will he go up in ratings or remain the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> KSI Game recommendations? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 23:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd really like to see JJ try out Guild Wars 2. He didn't see my Twitter messages, he must be playing hard to get. Hopefully he'll see it here. Any other games you want KSI to play? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 13:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since I already have three Chelsea players (Hazard - Costa - Alonso) and now Ake, will one of them have to be traded out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HELP - Fifa Server Issue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 10:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where can I find contract expiry dates for players? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 09:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instead of searching player by player in game, is there a site that shows the dates? Also does anyone know any good players who have their contracts expire in 2018? I've just brought Eriksen in. Is there anyone else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 01:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Signing players when their contract expires? I know about it but I don't have the money to sign decent players. (I'm in a Bundesliga 2 team) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 08:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At what age will their physical stats stop growing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I get the most out of youth academy players? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 03:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should I be training them? I heard that it limits their physical growth if I do. Is it okay to loan them out? Can they fulfill their potential that way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way to check player career stats? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 14:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The squad report only shows season stats. Is there a way to see the career stats for my players? If there isn't, I really think there should be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To people who have gone to Japan, where did you and approximately how much did it cost? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 07:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 06:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As soon as I read 'dark shadowy figure' I was like wait... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 14:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have him but I really hope he doesn't do well since I left him on the bench. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 14:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted to put it on Benteke instead but didn't realise the GW was starting today. Oh well. Good luck to you too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 14:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit. I accidentally left the C on Phillips. Fingers crossed that its a blessing in disguise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 09:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of these commentators sound so bored. Don't they realise what they've witnessed?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 08:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not gonna lie. This is a sick team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bringing Benteke? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 03:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously Benteke has been pretty average recently. But his fixtures in the next couple of weeks are really good. He has Swansea next. Is it worth bringing him in for Anichebe or should I go for Defoe instead? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 17:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just shut up. Shut up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 17:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It should have a more flashy title to get noticed on r/all. Something like 'Giroud smites his non believers with a scorpion kick' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 15:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. But I kiss yours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 15:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus Christ. The week I take you out of my FPL team you go and do this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best and worst FPL move you've done this season? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 14:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best: Bringing in Gundogan before his 18 point week to get a total of 112 in week 10. Still pretty chuffed about that.

Worst: Keeping Gundogan in my starting eleven every week after hoping he could do the same thing again.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 07:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have any recent examples from this year, but 'Life of Pi' from 2012 was hyped up heaps and received rave reviews. Personally, I found it a bit boring. Visually, it was good, especially the whale scene but I was pretty disappointed with it overall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 07:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The action scenes were top notch. The movie could have been great if there was an actual decent plot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 07:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't seen About Time yet because I assumed it was just another romance movie. Was it worth the watch? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which movie made you cry the most? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 07:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *'Marley   Me'* wasn't as sad as everyone said it was.

*'The Pursuit of Happyness'* gave me feels, but not tears.

*'Up'* did result in tears, but just a few.

Now. *'Train to Busan.'* My god, I wept. Without spoiling the movie (if you haven't seen it yet do yourself a favor and go watch it), I'll just say this. The acting by the whole cast during the climax of the movie, the child actress especially, broke me. What movie has made you cry? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chelsea have won more games in a row (13) than they won all of last season (12) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 00:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best example you know of a supernatural event from our history? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 15:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 09:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah. These considerate comments are so much better than some of the crap that is in the YT comments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 00:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cloud Atlas. It was very complex but I still enjoyed, mainly because of that 'Sextet' OST. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 00:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cloud Atlas. It was very complex but I still enjoyed, mainly because of that 'Sextet' OST. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is an innocent action that could actually anger or terrify others? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 16:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is not actually an asshole but is seen as one? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 12:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If your favorite animal could speak, which celebrity's voice do you think would suit it the best? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 13:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 11:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Daesung x SNSD. Specifically Yoona. Check the Family Outing video if you haven't seen it yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 00:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/books/comments/5kkjwh/richard_adams_author_of_watership_down_and_other/?utm_content=title utm_medium=hot utm_source=reddit utm_name=frontpage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever wanted to know where pineapples come from? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 00:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 00:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too late for apologies. The pitchforks are out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever wanted to know where pineapples come from? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 00:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 22:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Took the C off Ibra for Sigurdsson. Well... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your top songs of 2016? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 10:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before 2017 begins and we farewell 2016, what are your favorite songs of 2016?

My top 6 are:

1. Jay Park: Me Like Yuh - Loved the tropical beat it had. Took me a long time to check out this song because to be honest, some of his other music wasn't really my type but after seeing this at 1 Million Dance Studio, I've been replaying this over and over again.

2. K.A.R.D: Oh Nana - Quickly became one of my favorite groups even though they only have one song.

3. EXO: Monster - The choreography in this alone was enough for me to love it. Was my favorite song for a long time before I heard Jay Park

4. Blackpink: Boombayah and Stay - As a person who is pretty new to Kpop, this group is the first girl group I really got into. Both these songs are really good, although Boombayah's bird calling is a bit offputting. I think 'Stay' is really underrated and deserves more views. Check it out if you haven't heard it yet. 

5. 4Minute: Hate - This song has been pretty divisive. I actually didn't like the song at all when I first heard it but it grew on me over time. The grey contacts in the MV look amazing as well.

6. BTS: Blood, Sweat and Tears - BTS is the first Kpop group I ever really followed. (I found about them with Dope if you cared). The MV for this tune was stunning, even though I had no idea what was going on. JHope killed it.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 07:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't mind. I don't think I'm going to see this movie anyway since I'm such a fucking pussy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 16:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that dance at 1:49 from Turbo? I think I recognise it from Running Man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 06:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe because the bowties were put on the mouth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 13:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks delicious af tho. How have I not seen any watermelon popsicles like this before? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 12:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank god I came across this group. They're brilliant. I can't wait yo see where they go next. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If people years ago thought their movies looked realistic, I wonder how they would react if they saw what we can create now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 12:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a skill you want to learn but haven't had the time to do so? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 01:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 01:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your family must be really into Christmas. They've even set up trees outside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 01:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'A real snowman? How is that pawssible?' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 01:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, if it gets wet in THAT area, its a girl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 15:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how even the dog is in a panic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 00:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I don't know what the average is but I got 47 so Im hoping that's enough. Fingers crossed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Butland? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 10:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any news on Butland's return? I thought he was supposed to return a few weeks ago but apparently not. I still have Jakupovic warming my bench. Should I trade him out now or wait for Butland? What are good GK options for under 5? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Racing Glaciers - First Light [Indie Rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 08:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A butterfly helps man get revenge on friend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 07:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 07:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fight me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 07:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that I think about it.. I think I've always used my left leg first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most pointless argument you've been involved in? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 07:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 06:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really know much about the group tbh, but still, people like this who feel the need to use needless hate to feel better about themselves really pisses me off. Hopefully this girl knows that the majority aren't so ignorant and actually care about her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>  Butterfly coincidentally causes a man to get slapped  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 03:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 00:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He better fucking not. I just brought him in for that wasteman Kane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 15:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully Stones will start. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 09:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking Clyne for Ake? But I don't know if Ake is guaranteed play time since he was getting no play time until 5 weeks ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 08:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't find it :( did he delete it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 08:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jakupovic//Heaton

Clyne//Walker//Alonso//Amat//Holebas

De Roon//Lallana//Sanchez//Sigurdsson//Hazard

Anichebe//Kane//Costa


Opinions on squad and any suggested transfers to make? My overall   league position is.. not ideal. Help would be much appreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 05:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't wait for JRE to react to this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 02:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is so awesome! Cheers for doing this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 01:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1223? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
