<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3191</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 07:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The dallas cowboys are Americas team. Alot of inbred rednecks say that. Must be the syphillis that gets past from family member to member. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beginne questions about some spells and temple </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 15:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. How does blnk work. When I se it, I go backwards. Does this dodge melee? Are there specific mobs this is really use fully against?

2. How does shrink work? Does this reduce my chance to be hit?if so how much?

Which temple blessings are most useful? I have been using the one to boost idle exp. they double in cost each use so I have avoided thr rest.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So e newbie questions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. How are the levels of mobs in dungeons chosen? I know it goes up if you invest in it. I think its based on the farthest you got in the wild. If that is correct the most efficient time to do dungeons is right after you enchant and recover power, then do a raid. 

2. Is there a way to keep charms and stockpile them? When i get them they seem to be active i mediately.

3. Does anyone know which spells have passives that increase spell exp? I found one. I think it may be more efficient to target those spells to rank 5 ( if i have them) first. 

4. Do you get more spell exp as you get farther into the wild? I think you you do, but I am not sure.

5. So far i have had the most success having a loadout of all the same spell type to take advantage of bonuses. For example, i use all ice right now. Any posts in here experimenting with different mixes?

6. What is HH? I see it referenced a few times. I have gotten to area 39 in the wild. 

7. It looks like a number of stats are missing  from the notebook that gives stats. Such as percent bonus for all of the sane type spells, etc... 2 of the same type, etc... Is that correct or am i missing stuff.

8. Anyway to run an ios cloud save on kongregate and vice/versa?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 05:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And why I didnt enlist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 05:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1000 years from now when the future archeologists unearth the American ruins, they will think this video is a religious ceremony where we are sacrifice children to the gods </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 05:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont speak or read scottish. Can someone translate?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 05:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont know what j street supporters are and I am jewish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 03:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Democrats could have fillibusteres this. Even if democrats voted no, since they didnt fillibuster they voted yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why didnt democrats fillibuster this? It takes 60 votes pass anything other than budget issues in the senate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you skip it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ho do you skip a research? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can choose to not pick a research. But then I am down to only two choices. I see in the faq it says that you can choose to not research certain things. Is there a way yo get another research to show up if you dont want the current ine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially after he got a roster bonus. Usually you nave to force a pay cut before thst </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For math I recommend khan academy. It has assignments and is very detailed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My cat used to be terrified of my remote control car when I was a kid. She could be on the couch and go bat shit if I used it. Would not go outside if I used it outside </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This reminds me of grand theft auto </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a Saddam Hussein election. Vote yes or we will know who you are. Ill bet this gets a saddam hussein vote of 90% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It should be combined with stupidity and compulsive masterbation to distill proper hate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The stadium STL built for the rams is a money loser. The rams left and they ate still on the hook for it. Second, if the state is going to build it, the state should own it. It should not be corporate welfare. Oakland and San Diego disagree. They refused to build it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tired of grammar nazis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isnt coal being replaced with natural gas primarily due to low prices </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you suck dick? If you do, you are gay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should not be couseling children.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your an asshole </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Easy way to get laid is bang her and promise her a 3 way with you twin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you lost weight and had smaller boobs than her, people might not ask </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best dolphins qb since Dan Marino. Not saying much. There are very few franchise qbs. These are guys you build a team around. Tannehill is a guy you keep because because there are virtually never you good qbs out there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all know Tom is a sub slut. He gets a pegging sack when he is a good boy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alot of people on here would be getting sued for harrassing cheerleaders </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hand geno a tray </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nassib was on a rookie contract so he was cheaper </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking millenial names. Just call please kick my sons ass #q1,#2,#3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its good that they have photos since CTE will cause neither to remember this in the future </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But he gets to do it for no pay and in the nfl offices. Dream job. He can then go to a bar and use this life experience to impress women </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Public funding for stadiums is bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her career is over and she will have trouble finding any employment in the future.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Showing off your mad gaming skills is thread about a graveyard is a bit fucked up. Typical gamer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did he see? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if men put a satellite in geosynchronous orbit above Valinorbandvsendvin unmanned drones with video. Would we whither from the site of the video? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Facebook with porn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 07:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Between 1981-1994, the giants had 7 different linebackers make the pro bowl. Now they dont care about linebackers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My down votes are from patriot fans. Atleast they hate trump too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The good news with my down votes is that their are alot of patriot fans who hate trump. This is why they are reading this forum.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 157 posts at the time I am posting this. Goddam we are addicted to football. We should all go watch March Madness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is unfair. He still has a ways to go to catch Ryan Leaf as the biggest failure in history.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With man in the high castle didnt they just release the the first episode publicly, but rest was on amazon prime at the same time?

When is the rest of Oasis coming out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a bitch fan. We kicked tom bradys bitch as twice. A real fan would called tom brady a cheater and a pussy bitch during the hearing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought amazon prime releases an entire season at once? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kids are walking disease factories. Who in their right minds wants to pick up these germ factories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This awful vague. Examples please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you elligible to join sfwa? You may want to join that and ask there. Also the fantasy sub is far more active and has alot of fantasy authors posting. Cons are typically SFF so asking there is good too. Worldcon is in Finland this yesr.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When he is standing next to it and roasting marshmellows with his grandchildren, its a family event. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He can just send the scientlogists to convert the Kremlin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ill bet right wing radio killed clinton for only being at 53%. Id use the real clear average and not go by one poll. The Average has him in the low 40s. We should go by one outlyer poll. His floor is probably 35% . He would likely not go below that if he burns a cross on the white house lawn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Need the cia for that. They have to steal it back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fbi really should have better things to do then to go after a football jersey.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you are a doctor? Is it realistic to think we might get a treatment that soon? Is there promising research? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stephen Hawking has had it for decades. He has a very rare type that doesnt progress to your lungs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no treatment. The doctors cant do anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Games Workshop claims they own the term Space Marine. They issue takedown orders to Amazon to have books removed that use that term. The term has been around since before Games Workshop existed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your mom may not be my favorite customer, but she is my best customer. Buying a new cadillac courtesy of all the masturbating I dispd on her face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok left side. JPP is on that side </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would you know? You are not a verfied cop? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giants lost a shitty tackle in FA and that is it A quick  Google search would help you avoid alternative facts. I expect Hankins to go, but he is replaceable. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rothlisberger is in the hof on the first ballot. Want to make a wager? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joe Namath. 2 good seasons injury plagued career. Threw 30% more interceptions than TDs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 22-25 with 2 drops in the first superbowl. Lawrence taylor disagrees with you. So does Parcells.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Browns will double their win total. Their fans will be all over this sub about how excited they are for the future </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dallas cowboys back to 4-12. Teams will chuck it all over the place against their non existent seconday and teams will blitz the hell out of the right side of the line. They lost two offensive linemen in the offseason. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could someone explain the rationald behind that rule? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joe Namath. 2 good seasons. Injury plagued career. He threw 30% more interceptions than TDs. He is in the hof for winning superbowl 3 even though he didnt throw a TD in the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He also had a all of fame receiver, hall of fame back, and the best offensive line of the decade </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sure he was out of shape and wasnt just old? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Germans were mass murdering jews at this time. Calling them dicks is an unerstatement </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So basically departments dont want to hire entry level candidates? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The man in black fled across the desert and the gunslinger followed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have never heard of a half priced book store. Is this a used bookstore? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have always had to sign a w4 and I have worked for several fortune 100 companies. They use ADP and they need a w4. They may be paying him under the table. This would work for though its illegal since he wont have to pay taxes. 

He should ask about the w4 and see what the owner says. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks way too small to be an orca. If its a newborn where is the mother? I think there are seals that look like Orca </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure it does. Germany should buy american weapons for its defense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wrote that wall of text and one of my 8 upvotes is one sentence on texting. Ill take it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DBA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You win. Giants besting the patriots in the superbowl in 2011 was same shit, different say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont think the giants have cap space at $7-8m/ year. They are near the cap. They will make moves to free up space, but Pugh and Beckham are going to need big contracts in the next two years.

Hankins is gone. You cant keep everyone.

If Hankins hasnt gotten his big contract yet, he probably wont.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a good idea. Fans love the backup qb. Unnecessary stress on Taylor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Replace the racist Columbus day with the far more Progressive Shit on the Cowboys Day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chris, this fan will suck your dick to make you feel better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 23:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Collin Kaepernick. He is definitely good enough to be a backup. He is an upgrade for some teams who have shit, but he is really only mediocre. His whole kneeling thing isnt that bad. I think the final straw were the socks with cops looking like pigs. That was ignorant. He isnt good enough to do this. If Dak Prescott, Russell Wilson, etc... Pull this teams would sign them and not give a shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 23:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is recovering from a knee injury. If he can play someone will sign him, but likely not until closer to the season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 23:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flipper Anderson. He had a 300 yard receiving game in the 1980s and 1100 yards on the season. Never had another 1000 yard season. Not terrible player, but no one would remember him, but for this game. 

Timmy Smith. 204 yards rushing in the superbowl in january 1988 as a rookie. Was a backup before that. Held out of training camp for a new contract. Show up fat. Had 470 yards rushing and wss benched. Cut after the season, was out of the league after that. Hope he git a big contract for 1988 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 23:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ryan Leaf. Its not even close </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 23:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marino never had a running game. Dolphins would try to establish the run, then late in alot of games Marino had to chuck it around alot to pull out games. Back when Marino played teams rarely ever gave up on the run early even if it was t working. Game planning wasnt as flexible.

The defense in miami was usually pretty bad too. Note it was bad for that era. Teams didnt score as much. He had better receivers than Elway early in his career. His two big time receivers didnt last too long and after that Elway tended to have better receivers . 

Id go elway because of 5 superbowls.

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 23:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an italian america, suck my dick. I didnt even know marino was italian. I have no idea who is an italian anything. You are an idiot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 23:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thonlinson average 3.8 yards a carry in 2008, 3.3 in 2009, ad was with the jets in 20. LT was old whn rivers was at his best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 23:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucker blindsided Oher </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 23:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The extra point is boring. Put the ball on the 1 yard line for a two piint conversion to get more people to go for 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 23:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell them to look into a reverse mortgage. You get cash. Bank gets the house when they die. Be careful with it. Make sure its in both of their names. You dont want the wrong one croaking and they get evicted. They can invest what they get out of it in low risk bonds. Id shop around and google this. Some reverse mortgages are probably better than others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 23:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $5m is self sustaining wealth. If you invest it moderately conservatively and shoot for say a 5% return( you would want more  if inflation is higher). That is $250,000 a year. You want to reinvest a portion of that so your networth stays slightly ahead of inflation.

I would probably spend $150,000 at most if I was retired? This is taxable. If its long term capital gains that is at 15%. If its from a 401k or a sep ira that is considered regular income so taxes are higher. You dont want to spend too much of it, in case you get sick( even if you have insurance co pays for major illnesses is alot) and emergencies.

I have a networth of over $1m( yes I have a house but I have over a million not including my house). I have made a six figure salary for over 10 years. I have this much money because I live modestly. I work in IT in the dc area. Lots of staff ups and stsff downs. The company I work for has had growing layoffs every year and this year there is a big merger I expect them to be huge. I have been laid off several times. Other times I have done temporary contracting. Lots of stress with job security.

For that reason I would rather save money so even though I am stressed and have been out if work for months at a time ( 2008 i was out for 3 months) , I atleast know I wont be homeless and I can eat.

Most people who make my income and many of them are married so they each make a six figure salary increase there spending and buy frivolous crap as their income goes up. Then they are desperate if something happens to their job. I have no credit card debt. I do buy new cars, but I buy the entry level models. I have a 2010 Chevy Malibu and it runs just fine. 

I dont balance my checkbook. I auto pay everything. If I want to order food, I dont worry about. I pay a maid service to clean my house once a month. I guess by reddit standards my big splurge is I have Fios TV with hbo. I also have netflix, amazon prime, and I just bought showtime amazon prime.

My big piece of furniture purchases in the last 10 years, I got a leather recliner and I bought a memory foam bed( got it from bed boss fir $800) . Bought an ipad 2 a few years ago. I built my current pc 4 years ago and the parts cost $1600. I have a droid phone, no text plan( texting is stupid) and I have limited minutes( dont like to talk on the phone)

I need to run out to target tomorrow and replace my 12 year old George Forman Grill. Wont sweat the cost.

I like to read alot, but I get most of the books outof the library that is $2 miles a way. I have a 10 speed bike I bought off of craigslist 10 years ago. 

About 4 years ago I had wood floors put into most of my house( my house is 1250 square feet). I have a heoa air filter built into my heater. I have bad allergies. 

I am single. I have no dependents. I like seeing my networth go up every year because it reduces stress and makes me feel more comfortable. 

In case you want to know how I invest, I use the vanguard total market fund and vanguard international fund. These have the lowest fees. I have a t rowe price tax free bond fund for virginia residents. I automatically about $1400/month into them . I max my 401k which is currently $16,000 and I got a $5000 match last year. I use a regular market index fund in that. I hve an mba. During the program, I took my first finance class, realized financial planners are scam artists, fired him, and just use low cost index funds. 

Asa rule, if you feel and act rich you will likely just spend all your money and have nothing. Id rather have less stress.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a telltale sign that someone is lying? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 22:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a way to pick which building you want? There are quests to build two of a certain large building. Right now i need 2 star towers. The only way i see to speed this up is a new city, with only large commercials and then raise building speed research. It seems random. Its a real grind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 06:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have am mba. It is pretty useless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 06:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of food beyond what normal theaters have? Is everything really expensive? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone got links to Lawrence Taylor full game tape? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 00:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There lots of clips and montages. Looking for all or most defensive plays in a game. A couple of years ago I found the first game Madden/Summerall did during LTs rookie year. It wss just defensive plays. About 8 minutes long. His name was called on almost every play. Madden was drooling over him. I have not been able to find it since so it may be done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 00:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He sucked his first two years at tackle. Pff ratings in the 70s are generally considered poor. The giants line is so bad we have very low standards. He moved to guard because by most teams standards, he cant cut it as a tackle. I have a post on their sub go ask them. 

You are delusional </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 22:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> John jerry is significantly better thab fluker at guard. Jerry is in the hall of mediocre. Other teams would sign, but nobody would really want him. Per that article fluker was terrible at guard and mediocre at RT. Bobby hart is absolute garbsge. So mediocre is a huge upgrade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 22:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chargers fans think fluker sucks. I made a post on their forum. Our standards of good are much lower due to shit line for so long </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 22:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You really are an idiot. That would kill vast numbers of south koreans. You military expertise is brilliant. All those video games. Nuking india in civilization isnt the same thing. And they have thousands of artillery pieces over the entire front, plus long range missiles and nukes. 

You are a true military genious. Id hate to run into you in an online game. Im dead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasnt in the article. Anyone have that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The foreign policy comes from trump. Tillerson is the voice. All military leaders would advise that preemptive action is not an option. Seoul is 30 miles from the border and NK has a massive amount of artillery. There are 10 million people in Seoul. They could level the city on a moments notice. You cant take out that much artillery that fast. They can also hit Japan with missiles. 

NK doesnt give a shit about its people. They have nukes. They just murdered the dictators brother at an airport in another country. They are so isolated the US cant even get good bios on the NK leadership. The current dipshit in charge is a total flake. Who the fuck knows what he would do? Nuking north korea is fucking stupid. First off its tiny and the radiation would go into China and South Korea. Second its a massacre , and third they can likely lob nukes at our allies and hit US bases with nukes in the region along with nuking Tokyo.  

There is no evidence that NK is collapsing. The government appears to have complete and oppressive control. china props them up because they dont want massive refugees or a US ally on their border. 

One option is getting China to come down harder on them. I doubt they want NK to be able to nuke the US. They know that if they did NK gets nuked and china has radiation out their ass. However, china is busy building islands to seize the south china sea and trump is a fucking dumbass. So unlikely that this will work.

Its anazing, Trump threatens everyone including allies, but he has butt love for Putin. Even if he isnt a traitor( i want to see an investigation), he is an idiot. Russia is the Austria Hungary of the 21st. Trump wants to shackle us to a corpse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you sure comcast has your name? How did you get notified of collections? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Per PFF , DJ Fluker was much better at RT than at Guard and much better than Bobby Hart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
If My memory is correct John Jerry graded at 77 and Bobby Hart was the worst tackle in the league at 47.

Per Link below at RT, Fluker graded at 71 and 77. Then moved to guard and graded in the 50s and 60s. I see the news articles saying that Fluker was brought in to play guard. He is absolute shit at Guard and Jerry is much better.  A 77 is bleh. Not worst, but prefer to upgrade. If fluker is the same mediocre RT he was 2 years ago its a huge improvement over Hart and he would be higher graded than Flowers ( but flowers goes against the better pass rusher ). He cant run block for shit, but neither can Hart.

The chargers moving a guy to guard who was better than both of the Giants tackles tells you how shit the line was.  I think the new plan is to have Hart/Fluker compete for the RT job in training camp since they signed Jerry. Unless of course they get a good tackle in the draft. 

All the press reports say Fluker is a very hard worker and coachable. Maybe a new coach will catch things his orevious coaches didnt and coach him up. I will take a 75 grade at RT as a big upgrade. Its still not reliable. If fluker is decent, the giants can focus on helping Flowers more in pass protection. Put a TE on his side to chip. Back can line up more on Flowers side to focus on support.

One knock on fluker is that he is easily fooled by stunts. 

Link below has Flukers PFF grades.

http://www.nj.com/giants/index.ssf/2017/03/giants_offensive_line_a_look_at_dj_fluker_could_an.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that was because they were done with nassib and johnson signed late so he didnt know the offense. IF the giants carry 3 this year we have to wonder if elis bad play was due to injuries no one talked about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im sure its not guatanteed. I doubt the giants will carry 3 qbs. Either johnson or Geno will grt cut in trainimg camp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt the giants will carry 3 qbs. Either Johnson or Geno will get cut in training camp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smetimes the 1990 nfc championship game is on youtube. Parcells said it was the bestvgame he ever coached. Madden and Summerall announced. Phil Simms got injured in week 12 and they won a superbowl with a backup qb.

Joe Montana had his career ended wirh 49ers. LT recovered a fumble when Roger Craig( on the 1980s all decade team) fumbled while trying to out the clock. Giants faked a punt on that drive and hiked it to,a linebacker who ran for a first down. 

Giants also lost their starting RB that year. Rodney Hampton was a rookie and went on to have several 1000 yard seasons got hurt. OJ Anderson who had been an all pro when he was young, but was ancient had a 1000 yard season and was superbowl mvp.

This is before free agency. So alot of guys on the team for a long time. Hostetler was a backup for 6 years. 3 of the 4 linebackers were together since 1984 and so was Leonard Marshall. Giants signed Everson Walls who had been an all pro safety with the cowboys.

Their best defensive player that year was Pepper Johnson. His has been the linebackers coach in New England for years. 

It was a better game than the superbowl. In my opinion a bigger upset Joe Montana, Jerry Rice Rice Ronnie Lott, Roger Craig and others were going for a 3 peat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the way the new regime jandles injuries. Keep the guys down. Coughlin repeatedly brought guys back too soon and they got hurt again. I blame Coughlin for ruining Hakeem Nicks in 2012. Foot injury in the offseason, kept bringing him back too soon. After that he couldnt play anymore.

I hope they go slow with Thompson. Does anyone have details on his injury? It was something with his foot right? If any issues at all put him on PUP for 6 weeks. No risks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the only lineman they lost was a guard Doug Free to retirement. They lost a starting DT who was solid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck dallas. Down their best safety too. They lost a starting DT. The guard they lost likely wont be a problem with the rest of their line.

Looks like dallas is going to rely on a rookie secondary. This might allow dallas to lead the league in run defense since it will be o easy to throw against them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The most economical solution to preventing the Social Security trust fund from running out is Soylent Green. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Franchise tag is based on position. There is no oline position in franchising. Guards make less money than tackles. You can google this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Id rather not get arrested if I stub my toe and curse :) I hope police can show restraint. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were gas lines in the 70s. Arab countries boycotted selling gas to the US. This lead to a collapse of the oil market since non OPEC countries drilled. I remember that gas was around .90 cents a gallon when I was in high school in 1991-1992, but was $1.30 a gallon 10 years earlier.

Opec fucked that one up. 

Like I said above Soylent Green. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soylent Green. Euthanize the fuckers before they bankrupt social security. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 60s generation were the rebels. They protested everything. Smoked weed. Now they are old and hated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get the law. I dont think it should be allowed. The police officers are still public servants right? You have the ability to order me to do what you say. I dont think its a good idea for private orgs to discriminate. If it is, we might as well get some satanists to form a police force and the cops can sacrifice chickens.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would you think of a job as a church cop. Sounds like a blowoff job or am I missing something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The same tiny percent of people who bought a house at 20 then buy one now. Part of the problem with housing prices is that most of the US is wide open spaces, but most the jobs stay clustered in a small area. So we pack in and prices go up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its illegal to curse in front of kids? People do that all the time at sports arenas. I honestly didnt know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 05:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my day we called that blowing someone off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pun. Nice catch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those of us in our 40s are gen xers. We are the children of the baby boomers. Cut off is basically growing up without internet and cell phones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are on reddit and watching porn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thst idnt new to your generations. There are lots of poor people in previous generations. There was a bubble with the baby boomers. People in general were much poorer before ww2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are delusional. Only people who bought houses at 20 are celebrities or people who used mommys money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im a gen Xer. Career job hopper for 18 years. This works </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All those things you stated is mindlessly being on your phone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flint michigan. You literally cant use the water </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw shaq say that once. Id like to see that guy be a ballerina or a gymnast.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Works for trump.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we will get either there is no investigation or no comment which means there is one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You cant learn to lead in a classroom. The management classes are a joke. The mba doesnt teach you how to usefully understand metrics. I work in IT and was not impressed with their technical classes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Religious people of reddit, how do you respond to the fact that there is no scientific evidence for anything you beleive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Religion. Its all bullshit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have a link of people believing it and not just shitposting? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a meme nit a conspiracy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an mba. Its not hard and has very little useful info </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What prey tell attracted you to him. I have never heard of someone too lazy to learn to drive. Driving is freedom. My grandparents (and I am 42 so ww2 generation), never drove. They lived in new york city and could never afford a car. I have never heard of someone too lazy to learn to drive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
