<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1397</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Law Professor Says Trump Has Already Committed Impeachable Offenses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 01:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Law Professor Says Trump Has Already Committed Impeachable Offenses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 01:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 16:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I were an art teacher, I would tell this artist to think about extending the hind legs back to the bubble blower, which would enhance the creation effect, while mitigating any fart effects </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 06:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know those stupid phone menus you get when calling customer service or something?

"Please listen closely as our menu has changed... Press1 for blah, press 2 for blegh, and so on. "


I hate them. 

What if, instead of having to listen, the companies' phone system sent some data to your phone, and the keypad would be the menu options instead of (or in addition to) the numbers. 

Tada! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 04:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not really a secret. The deplorables just don't care, that's partly why they are deplorable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 14:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, tiny, ingrown hands </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 13:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny enough I meant the episode, not the song. I guess I got mixed up, but he figured it out. Whoops </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 05:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder why light of the seven wasnt nominated for anything? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 16:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a fantastic middle Eastern shop in back of jewelry store on Wabash </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 15:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I became fast friends with a somewhat outcast classmate in 3rd grade. 

All because he was playing battleship with someone, and impressed me with the "I1" home.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 15:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always wondered what they thought of Kansas city, such a weird airport. 

Also screw berlin. That airport is the worst </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 15:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ((secret liberal)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 15:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have Hitler in orange and Hillary Clinton? Uh, Hillary has a cough and emails, I guess I'll just have to go with that other guy... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 14:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it's a fruit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 14:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read that in Jim gaffigan's voices.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 00:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Diplomats, even SoS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 16:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps just missed the cut, but the famous statue The Thinker, by Rodin. 1904. I always thought it's like ancient Greece or something. Nope. Just a while ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 01:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except for that one time you were asked if he was an Israeli citizen.
Point being is that it's racist against both
.
http://www.politico.com/blogs/media/2015/06/nprs-diane-rehm-asks-bernie-sanders-about-israeli-citizenship-rumors-208583 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 01:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except for that one time you were asked if you were an Israeli citizen.
Point being is that it's racist against both of you.
http://www.politico.com/blogs/media/2015/06/nprs-diane-rehm-asks-bernie-sanders-about-israeli-citizenship-rumors-208583 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 01:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except for that one time you were asked if you were an Israeli citizen. 

Point being is that it's racist against both of you. 

http://www.politico.com/blogs/media/2015/06/nprs-diane-rehm-asks-bernie-sanders-about-israeli-citizenship-rumors-208583 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 00:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He just wanted to get drunk and enjoy a game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 00:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Greetings from Chicago. On a scale from 1 to OMFG, are wet going to finally being it this year? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 06:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God of the old testament </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 03:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in a niceish part of Chicago, 2000sf condo with beautiful park views. Mortgage is 550 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 14:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bedbugs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 15:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A whole basket of 'em </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 05:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of them evolved from quickly writing the majiscule. http://imgur.com/njWurIj </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 05:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/George_H._W._Bush_vomiting_incident </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 01:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would be fine if he was mentally healthy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 00:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If your friend lives in a permit zone, the city gives them temporary passes for visitors  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 00:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tour the Baha'i temple in Wilmette or the Hindu complex in naperville. Historic Pickwick theater in Niles. Frank Lloyd wright home and studio and other homes in oak park, ravinia festivals in highland park,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 00:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> paywall </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 00:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean "especially the ones who I disagree with"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 23:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, trump and the right have been forcing her to act superhuman.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 22:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so happy nostalgia is the trend du jure.  How I missed thee, o French toast crunch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Essentially bread is food handles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 22:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 15:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her insults are very Arkansas. So eloquent and cutting. I'm just waiting for her to break out the "bless his heart" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 05:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I allowed to be a little negative? Cause the graphic design leaves me wanting. It looks like a generic  brochure in a medical office for incontinence or something. 

(Also by having Kaine higher and less cut off the edge, makes it seem like it's his ticket) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 05:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually food is in CMYK, no? Or rgby? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 05:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think your cake printer is low on ink. Probably the cyan cartridge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 05:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Text message screens. Everyone has an iPhone or Android, everyone knows what the user interface looks like, so just use that. Not some shitty stand in screen that they all use </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we all agree how great the turn of phrase is. "basket of deplorables." It's Churchill level insult, imho </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 04:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 04:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The tax structure in Saudi Arabia gauges Palestinians and recently Syrians over other nationalities </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 14:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me and a friend were walking once (we are Orthodox Jews) and an agitated young man asks us if we are jewish. We says yes, and he proceeds to pull out of his bag a Yiddish Bible (Ben chomesh lmikra, only available in some rare jewish stores for super Orthodox, so it's weird for him to.have yhis)  and opens it to the story of Noah and the flood, where he has scribbled som calculations and diagrams in the margins. 

He asks us if his dimensions are correct.

we just kind of say yeah, they look OK (didn't look that closely).


He then exclaims "I knew it!"

Slams the book shut, puts it back in his bag and walks off muttering loudly, "I knew it, it's a spaceship! It's a spaceship! I knew it!"


Still not sure what that was.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 21:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mexico city actually has a very large and active jewish community. Fun fact, Louie CK is Mexican Jewish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 21:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about underwater? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 20:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Porque no los dos? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 18:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 18:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So sad. A couple of years ago, he came, in character, to a community event. He spent a lot of time with my autistic brother, ensuring he felt included, and was not offput when my brother started to trail around him for the entirety of the event. 

Not only that, he followed up with a beautiful letter to the event organizer (who then passed it on to my parents) about how much he enjoyed spending time with my brother etc.

My parents have that letter framed in their house.

Benny is a real mentsch. he will be missed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 01:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who are all these negative nancies calling this awkward? This was such a refreshing candid and genuine laid back chitchat with people on a personal level. The whole time I was watching this, I was thinking that more people need see this side of her. Just a nice, normal human.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 01:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When in a conversation about multiple members of the same family unit, we typically refer to the individuals by they're first name. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 01:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone transcribe, in one place, what he says? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "You're fired!" Trump's most famous line is for being a job destroyer, not creator. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 21:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 01:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'll cost you at least 250 to see her in Chicago. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 22:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it's small fries compared to what trump says and stands for. Seriously, trump is so evil that ailes is princely the most upstanding part of his campaign.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 16:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's exactly the commenters point. Injustice comics are for a modern audience. Whereas the context of supermans character at its inception was to literally be a goodie two shoes as a counter to the nazi ubermensch and the evil that that mindset created. 

Injustice comics would just be nazi ubermensch, and not it's counterpoint, and we then wouldn't need a comic book character when it's right there in our faces as real life. 

Today, many forget that context, and therefore the Injustice comics are interesting/seem necessary. But at supermans core, Injustice comics are antithesis of his purpose as comic character.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 14:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. Twitter is the worst, so many redirects and loading crap, for whats essentially an SMS text. Twitter should be the fastest site anywhere, yet it's among the slowest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 14:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.washingtonpost.com/entertainment/museums/why-two-american-museums-are-fighting-to-keep-art-stolen-by-the-nazis/2015/06/30/16aef5ae-1bad-11e5-bd7f-4611a60dd8e5_story.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 03:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But he took a bus to Montreal, and be got a handy at the fair from a miner... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dont get complacent: Fox national poll: Clinton and Trump in virtual tie in 4-way race </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 12:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 18:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you can simulate this, and other conditions, here: 

http://www.traffic-simulation.de/

its a great tool and visualization (and game).

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 14:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stolen,but perhaps not by illegal immigrants? Just run of the mill identity theft </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 13:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually owned by south Korean cult.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 05:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makes sense. Already insurance companies hate Uber and other ride share. It would be beneficial to get in to take advantage of this to set the groundgame for future co-owneship business models </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 04:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh you mean that bran stark shouldn't be perfectly coiffed after all that time in a cave? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 04:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would you like to know? I'll tell you right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 17:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This article is in part based on this one: http://globegazette.com/news/iowa/grassley-says-surprising-trump-victory-can-happen/article_e054e643-d8f3-55e7-9528-12ee0f90fbec.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grassley hints of Supreme Court confirmation in lame-duck </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 17:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 17:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make it a whole legion, and you ahve got Rome Sweet Rome sequel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 15:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, as someone who uses desktop page on mobile, there is no submit button, and return doesn't work. For me to submit I have to use the Reddit.com/submit any way to fix that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 04:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I were to guess, I would assume that within the first year, they would cost cost to retail price, perhaps with the tax credit built in to the price. But not much less than that. Plenty of people want it at full Pryce but not willing to wait in line.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 04:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No no no, you misunderstand. The UK Brexited Europe, so they don't appear on the maid anymore. They voted to be erased from the map.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 04:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how"Europe" doesn't have the UK. Might be too confusing for him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 04:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The highways need major loving. I know many of this sub's demographic are anti-car (or live close to public transportation and/or close enough to bike), but the highways are seriously clogged. 

The 90-94 from the loop to the junction need two more lanes in each direction. There needs to be a off-surface-street connection from South on 94 to north on 90 (and the reverse),

Also, while the 290-4 help, there needs to be a better way to route cross-country truck traffic around and away from the city so that they don't further clog the system.

Also, parking needs major help everywhere. 

A rail line that does an outer ring around the city without going to the loop would also be great and help cross-urban traffic. 

No more traffic cameras.   Bad. 


Lastly, all the connections across the river to the north suburbs need widening, but that is actually done purposefully to prevent city people from going to the suburbs. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 03:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. Definitely above my price point, but something to hold on to.

Tks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 02:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fitted? Or comply? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 02:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't seen the film. Whats going on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 01:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope he brings it again for Sully. I can't wait </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 00:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Live each day like it's your last </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 00:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have been measured, and you absolutely came up short.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 00:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm anything but moderation when it comes to Andy coops </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 22:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dammit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 21:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel bad for news pundits. It's really hard to encapsulate detailed policy proposals in 140 characters. It's Hillary's own fault her candidacy isn't tweet friendly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 19:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lebensborn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 19:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything Tom Cruise and Les Goodman  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 18:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can tell your Jewish coworker to brush up on his knowledge. 

Middle of the night:


http://m.chabad.org/holidays/JewishNewYear/template_cdo/aid/989585/jewish/Kaparot.htm

"Timing...predawn hours"

Whipping: 

http://www.latimes.com/world/middleeast/la-me-yomkippur-pg10_wire5_k8fevync-photo.html


And 
http://www.nbcnews.com/news/religion/ultra-orthodox-jews-israel-atone-yom-kippur-n218041

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 16:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use etymotics and shures for ie noise reduction. But no custom. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 15:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Orthodox Jewish, we have so many it's ridiculous. One is, the night before Yom Kippur, we get up in middle of the night to swing live chickens over our heads a few times, then it's slaughtered while you watch. (it's donated to poor families), then you back to sleep. 

Later in the day, you get on your hands and knees facing south while someone whips you 30 times with a leather belt while you both recite some verses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thank goodness Amerigo Vespucci named the continent for his first name and not last name. Could you imagine *The United States of Vespucci*? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 14:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 05:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was 4 nearing my birthday, my dad told me that because I behaved do well the past year, I was going to skip 5 and be 6 years old. I was so excited, and I told all my friends and rubbed it in there faces... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 05:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But unless you mod, that sibilance is painful after 20 minutes. Besides, you have a 10' thick as crap cord and you better be carrying some amp, as it's impedance is too high, and a crappy fiio won't do jack - besides, 1500$ equipment is silly to compare to a Bose product. 

If anything, m-50s, maybe Shure or Sennheiser momentum and the like (mdr-1r). At the hd800 end, you're talking ultrasone editions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 00:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After they caught him, they threw Christie back under the bus, and Carson in the back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 19:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> America's step dad literally becoming a America's step dad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 18:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. He stuck a sticker on 12.5, while dunking on 10

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Slam_Dunk_Contest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 18:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No they can't. World record is 12' by a Harlem globetrotter

Edit: spelling, and wow, that's a a lot of down votes for something not very controversial: https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Michael_Wilson_(basketball) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 17:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the perfectly cast thread: Josh Gad as dog </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 16:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bruce almighty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wonderwoman Reportedly a Mess: Ex-Warner Bros. Employee writes scathing letter to studio head: 'What are you even doing?' , </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 21:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arianna Huffington is leaving The Huffington Post </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 14:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't think Fox News or Oliver North know the meaning of irony. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 06:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recently there have been some articles questioning the efficacy of flossing. Is there evidence that flossing is useful? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 04:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HP CEO Meg Whitman backs Clinton, denounces 'demagogue' Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 06:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HP CEO Meg Whitman backs Clinton, denounces 'demagogue' Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 06:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Last Week Tonight with John Oliver: Democratic National Convention (HBO) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 03:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] Do the seven kingdoms' thrones have names? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 17:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The State argued in court that "counties with Sunday voting in 2014 were disproportionately black" and "disproportionately Democratic," and said it did away with Sunday voting as a result. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 06:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is anyone as excited about Hillary's surrogates as much as me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 21:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aside from Hillary herself, we are kind of living in an era of the dream team of dem campaigners.

Can you just imagine, Bill Clinton, Barrack (and Michelle) Obama, Elizabeth Warren, Joe Biden, and yes - even Sanders, all stumping for Hillary. 

These are some of the best orators and campaigners in American history at the same time, on the same team. 

It's going to be glorious. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [everything] what are your thoughts on who fits the role of the three heads of the dragon? If A+J=T is not true. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 04:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I imagine Jon Snow is one. There of course there is the popular, but controversial,  theory that tyrion is really the son of Aerys. 

Assuming that's not true, who is the third head?

I'm guessing Brans flying lessons could be a dragon. Otherwise, maybe young Griff (in the books)

And if young Griff is the third, and also is a blackfure, that could present realistic obstacle to dany. 

If not them,then who? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FiveThirtyEight election forecast shows Trump ahead </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 21:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Clinton selects Tim Kaine as running mate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 02:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vanilla nice: Signs point to Kaine as Clintons VP choice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 16:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tesla just changed its mission </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 00:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LABOUR LEADERSHIP BETTING: Owen Smith is now the firm favourite to take over from Jeremy Corbyn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 12:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Consumer Reports] Tesla's Autopilot: Too Much Autonomy Too Soon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 15:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tesla Autopilot was engaged in Model X rollover. Driver to be cited </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 19:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tesla Airbags Didn't Deploy, Says Accident Report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 01:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bernie Blew It: How Bernie Sanders overplayed his hand lost his leverage over Hillary and the party </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 20:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [everything] Lady Mormont for... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 03:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [everything] are we just going to take it for granted she is next... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 20:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [everything] so apparently zootopia DMV sloth analog is in the citadel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 08:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lucas Museum Gives Up On Chicago Location, Moving To California </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 19:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lucas Museum Gives Up On Chicago Location, Moving To California </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 19:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Theory: The real way Jared saves... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 04:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...The company.

Warning: GoT levels of tinfoil incoming:

At the end of the episode, we see the long shot of thousands of workers using the site in a large room.

**What**:The way the company is saved is that these people will actually end up liking the platform and begin using it in their day to day life, and it will spread like crazy there. 

**Why**: in 3rd world countries data is very expensive, having a 0KB data system would be extremely beneficial to them. 

**How**: the neural net gets better through the proximity and density of these constant users

**Bonus**: Glocal: helping the world in a local place. 

Why i think so: too much time used on a shot that is simply a punchline.

But it first will get worse, before better, per SV formula. 

Also , a non- centralized data platform like this could be good in protest movement like firechat did : http://www.wired.com/2014/10/firechat-hong-kong-usage/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Everything] I don't think its just the characters who are being shipped... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 19:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [no spoilers] what is your battle of the bastards NBA vs GoT gameplan? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 00:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does global rising temperatures have any predicted effect on long term a structure viability of supertalls? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 05:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ie, as thermal expansion cycles get longer, will there be unplanned for stresses on expansion joints?  especially on  supertalls where the overall effect of expansion is very large. 

Or is the predicted effect so tiny that on each component, it's well within the designed tolerance, and other factors will come in long before thermal expansion?

Thanks

Unplanned: not designed for. Or do modern buildings require taking this eventuality into account (100 year event, 500 year event, etc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [S6] annoying possibility for battle of the bastards no one is mentioning. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 23:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All season long, or so it seems, thedirectors/show runners have been splitting major stories/payoffs over two episodes that should have been 1. 

Jon's resurrection 

Cleganbowl/clegancancel

Waif-Arya fight

Dany capture/Dany Burn

Seige of Mereen (still not resolved)

Etc


I think we are going to have the major portion the battle, then will be cliffhung until episode 10. 

It's going to suck. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [S6E8] Does anyone else not buy the negotiation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 19:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this will be a bit harsh, but I don't buy Edmure's surrender. 

He mentioned that he never met his kid. As much as it's your own kid, can you really love someone you never met? Does he love his wife, whom he was forced into a political marriage he didn't want, and only met once, and is Frey (at the end of the day). 

Would he really risk everything for them? Especially with no guarantees (why would he believe a Lannister who orchestrated a breaking of guest rite). 

It seems too much to give for so little.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New York's governor ordered a boycott of Israel's boycotters  and other states are following suit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 01:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [main spoilers] why are the events in the play shown as connected? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 17:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have some trouble understanding why the play arya watches will show all the events that they show as part of a single narrative. (We, the audience, know, because of dramatic irony, that all events are connected, but would the people of westeros and wasps know?



For example, it seems that the play is the story of the war of 5 kings. Which makes sense, that's a good story, if difficult to tell in play format. 

However, the killing of joff and tywin are only tangential to the story. As is the original death of Robert. 

As far as people would be concerned, the war of 5 kings begins with the beheading of Ned, and ends with the red wedding/blackwater. 

And it's not just "a story about intrigue across westeros" because those events happened across a long period of time (relatively) and are not, in the scheme of things in that world, that important or unusual, to be interesting. 

And varys wouldn't be an important character at this point in understanding the story to the people in the show, for another example. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [main spoilers] stupid question: why do the starks have maetsers if they believe in the old gods? ie, Luwin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 04:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> or is it just that the septs send smart people to all the houses, so its a net benefit to the starks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [everything] The director of Sunday's 'Game of Thrones' episode compared Daenerys to Hitler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 00:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teslas newest hire may be proof Elon Musk is ready to hear some hard truths about batteries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 16:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mysterious website slams Elon Musk as 'American Swindler' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 22:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mysterious website slams Elon Musk as 'American Swindler' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 22:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [everything] Game of Thrones Season 6: Episode #5  Kristian Nairn (Hodor) and Isaac Hempstead-White talk "the door" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 20:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ayahuasca Shaman Dreading Another Week Of Guiding Tech CEOs To Spiritual Oneness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 00:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Palestinians are passive. Have they given up? - Opinion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 02:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [everything] 'Game of Thrones' Has a Ramsay Bolton Problem and Here's Why </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 20:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who wore it better? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 04:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5:How do some actors also direct in their own movies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 01:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> or perhaps, some directors act in their own movies...

How can an actor in a scene be able to really have a command of an entire set, including the take, when they are also trying to act? Do they yell their own "Action!"s and "Cut!"s.

Are they not too busy to do both?


Examples: Most Woody Allens; Ben Affleck (Argo); Clint Eastwood (Million Dollar Baby);  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elon Musk just made a totally mind-blowing change to Tesla's strategy: "Musk now wants to hit 500,000 by 2018, a full two years ahead of schedule." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 01:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From a call to the center: Chicago has X for test drive at Highland Park and Oakbrook. Old Orchard within 2 weeks. Grand soon,as well </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 23:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OMA seems to produce so many interesting architects, more than other firms. Is there a comprehensive list of Rem's influence? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 08:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For starters:

Zaha

FOA

Neuteling-Riedijk

Studio Gang

MVRDV

BIG

Buro Ole Sheeren

REX

^  ^Some ^smaller ^firms:

^NLE

^UrbanLabs

^Point ^Supreme

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My fridge buttons decided to randomize themselves </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 05:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The buttons on my fridge controls have been scrambled. Help. (Bosch linea 800) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 02:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> #FEELTHEBERN </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 07:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Polish rabbi not from Israel, not a rabbi, not very informed on Judaism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 21:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 9th Model S ever built up for auction. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 02:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elderly Lady Tries Tesla Autopilot for the First Time [X-Post r/teslamotors] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 15:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pixar Shows First 27 Minutes of 'Finding Dory' to Much Laughter and Tears </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 15:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Tesla forks the Model III right now into sedan option and Compact SUV option, how many of you would switch to SUV? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 04:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assuming same production schedule, you keep your current place in line (ie no change in delivery schedule/rebate), and the SUV will be around a 10% premium over the sedan version.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WSJ Dan Neil Review: Tesla Model X "takes a sustainably harvested baseball bat to Panzer wagons like Porsche Cayenne Turbo and Range Rover Sport SVR." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 16:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did you ever realize that Montrose is Rosemont? [Showerthought] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 18:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is up with the little angled end of Model 3 Doorhandles? (photo, with X+S comparison) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 00:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tesla truck. More confirmation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 21:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Total Leaf sales 2011-2015: 200k Model 3: 115k in 1 day. Think about that. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 08:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leaf is the best selling EV in the world. But cannot touch model 3's numbers. And that was sight unseen. 

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nissan_Leaf (source) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Motor Trend Facebook page, now with ridealong video of model 3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 06:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The queue order seemed very confusing and elaborate, so I made a chart. Of course, it's wrong - what is the order? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 22:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TV] From the "S6. Teaser Hall of Faces" Are there implications (see below) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 03:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the teaser: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OmrA8nOZF2Q

Is the narration implying that the house of black and white, and their ability to work with death somehow related to the white walkers and their zombies? are they perhaps allied?

Bonus: would it be possible that for cleganebowl the hound fights the mountain by being temporarily resurrected through the body of a faceless-man, or through zombie-whitewalker?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best 45 second interview ever (x-post r/siliconvalleyHBO) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 03:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> American Teen Survives Attack in Brussels, His Third Brush With Terrorism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 02:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Update on Tesla that burst into flames in Norway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 23:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that 20% of Israelis get married abroad to circumvent the religious restrictions at home. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 20:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Opinion] [Zogby] Rest In Peace To The Republican Party </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 16:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Drumpf, and VP Corpus Christie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 23:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girthers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 22:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just resolved my 9 month moto x replacement! Let me tell you how, and perhaps save some of you. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 18:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  *  6 months oops.

I sent in a moto x 2014 for repair in September of 2015. It only just got replaced last week.

I know all of the horror stories, and have experienced them myself. Let me give you some specific numbers and contacts that perhaps save you some of the hassle that has badgered many of us. 

The way to do this is one of two ways. You can tweet at @Moto_Support. This usually works. The associated email for twitter support is vqcb43@motorola.com

Otherwise, you need to speak to a manager at repair escalation. Motorola customer service pretends that there is no direct number. This is not true. The direct number for repair escalations is **1-888-355-8422** (M-F 8-8 EST), no wait or hold, it is direct.

Now, repair escalation team will not *necessarily* help. As they did not help me. 

You want to ask for a manager there. They will hem and haw and ask you for more information and try to (pretend) to resolve it themselves, or in one instance with me, deny that they have a manager above them.

**Absolutely do not give in**, insist, politely on being transferred to one of their managers. The managers of the repair escalation team can help.

If any of you need a specific manager's name, PM me, and I will give that to you so you can ask to be transferred to that specific manager.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Gates thinks Apple should help unlock an iPhone for the FBI </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 14:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chicago students turn tables on BDS with new tactic - Diaspora </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 19:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT When logging out of your online bank, don't just x the tab, logout all the way </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 18:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a security hole, at least on Chase.com, that if you close the tab while logged in, and then try to go the address again, you will need to log back in.

However, if you ctrl+shift+T, it will load the page back, completely signed in and active. So, just be aware
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Serious question that I've been struggling with in regards to getting his legislation through Congress, even if he gets super-majorities in both houses. (Not a question about being too left) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 04:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all remember the difficulty that obama had getting legislation through, even with both majorities - and he had full backing from the party.

Would the DNC/dem establishment hold it against Bernie the fact that he always was an independent. Granted he caucased with them, but (Hillary aside) would the Washington Establishment not feel obligated to be loyal to him, and do his difficult work if he did not participate in the party for so long (donating to national committee, campaigning for fellow dems, and generally involved in their platforms and programs?

Thanks for your gentle responses  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know the story behind this photo? Found on Facebook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 02:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Model 3 Unveiling Date Confirmed: March 31st </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 23:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [stocks] Tesla is Falling Out of Favor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 02:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Majority of ultra-Orthodox men now working </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 04:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A customer was so annoying that Tesla decided not to sell him a car </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 05:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are the words for "cousin" so grammatically wierd in Hebrew? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 16:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> -; -;  ; -

Why do you conjugate the second half?

It causes this wierd meaning that male cousins are children of uncles, whereas female cousins are daughters of aunts. 

As well as the pluralization, that if you have multiple cousins, meaning is also multiple aunts/uncles.


Is there a grammatical reason that these words are set up like that?


Bonus question: AFAIK Hebrew does not typically verbify nouns. Is  an exception or simply slang/idiomatic with bad grammar?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ASK] near max TH9 (working on walls and heroes), defended from silver to master's since update. Now stuck. What is a good defensive base, and what is a good 2 star pushing strategy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 23:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've used this base for about 9 months: http://imgur.com/7oH4eRw essentially A modified Mankey base. Was good until last week, now have one only one defense in last week. Usually get taken for 2 stars. 

What is the in pushing base?


Also, I used to be able to two star with gibarch consistently, or even superqueen. But  recently have been failing every attack (also loonian).

What is the in pushing strategy?

My goal is to get to champions. That's it. 

Thanks for your time and help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chicago cop to sue family of black teen he killed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 23:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tesla is Getting Clobbered (stocks) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 21:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recently totalled my car. At the same time, received a substantial monetary gift: Should I lay off my car loan myself, and take insurance money in cash? Or should I let insurance pay the loan? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 15:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

Typo in headline: i pay off not lay off. 

I have a loan on a car. Totalled it last week. Insurance will pay the lender, and then give me the remainder. 


Would it be beneficial for me to let that process happen, or use the newfound money to pay off the lender immediately, and let the insurance company pay me directly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You don't even come close </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 04:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 10/11k coming from insurance for totalled honda insight, what should I look for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 03:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a 2010 honda insight, before cruise control and VSA and ESC etc. Flew off the road in an icy patch and goodbye. (its was 43,000 miles)

Now, what should I get?

Ideally, I would like to stick around the total that insurance will give me. And chase auto will only give financing on a car less than 5 years old. And would like a low mileage car.

I really liked the insight, I liked having a hybrid, and I liked having a long hatchback (great for luggage).

I looked into a 2011 Honda Insight, which had all the features that i needed to keep car on road (vsa esc and cruise control) for 11k, but looked at prius because of better features, gas and resale value. (also has push-to-start which I learned about, and is useful).

I felt the prius c had too small of trunk. and the regular prius, because of holding its value, seems to expensive.

Is it worth the jump in price? should I be considering another vehicle? I am way too indecisive now.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Freed Iranians Never Boarded Flight Out of US </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 15:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Freed Iranians Never Boarded Flight Out of US </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 15:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A while back there were some allegationsagainst Louis ck of sexual misconduct? Anything come of it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 03:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically, any updates on this post:


https://m.reddit.com/r/OutOfTheLoop/comments/381fb1/whats_up_with_the_recent_louis_ck_sexual/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5 what are the north African refugees? I thought all the refugees were Syrian. What are the north African (such as morrocon) fleeing from </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 21:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the US surgeon generals are also given the rank of rear-admiral as the leader of the United States Public Health Commissioned Corps - a military service branch of health and wellness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 05:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the US surgeon generals are also given the rank of rear-admiral as the leader of the United States Public Health Commissioned Corps - a military service branch of health and wellness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 05:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stupid question I was curious about: what is the tallest building ever demolished/dismantled? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 04:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have any modern skyscrapers ever been taken down? I know some towers, like pruit igoe, and many Japanese and Singaporean have been taken down. What was the tallest? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the West Bank refugee camps refuse to join the Third Intifada </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 04:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I know this is kind of passe, but should I upgrade or not? Story inside </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 15:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tl;Dr should I sell the replacement 2nd gen and get pure, or just stick with 2nd gen?


Basically, I upgraded from 1st gen 6 months ago. A week after buying it, it broke. Motorola, with their customer service as it were, only replaced it this week. (Have been on busted 1st gen since), so, after they're finally sending replacement, the pure has been released, and the 2nd gen is extra old. Should I just stick with it, or sell it on eBay or something to fund an upgrade to pure?

Many thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oregon standoff: Feds forcibly removed black occupiers from wildlife refuge in 1979 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 05:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Clintons Lead Slipping Faster in 2016 Election Polls Than in 2008 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 05:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MISC] this guy's "highest trophy" of less than his current </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 04:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there way to find out if there are any new Honda Insights left unsold in the US? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 03:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just totalled my 2010 insight, and really want another one. It was so much fun. 

I know that it's been discontinued, but as of April, there were still many around. How would I find out if there is any inventory left? I figured I'd probably get a good deal on one?

Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
