<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject322</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 23:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's fucked up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 23:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I woke up one evening after I had the most vivid dream, that I just knew wasn't a dream. First off, I was young. Maybe 11-14. And in this "Dream" I was walking down a street, like just on the road. But it was super late at night. Maybe 2 AM and I was in a suburban area. Just like, little houses all along the street with bigish yards.

Anyway, I'm holding a briefcase and I'm in a suit. Though I never saw the suit, I just knew I was in one. I'm looking away from the street, and when I look back up there's a car rushing straight at me.

I woke up once the headlights filled my entire view. 

I remember I was a black door to door salesman with a shaven head.

That's all I remember, but I remember it more clearly than any dream I've ever had.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People who believe they've lived a past life, why do you believe and if you know, what was yours? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 23:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a roleplay forum. Any kind of content super hero would be fun. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 07:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 06:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm up for helping with this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 17:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 15:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a poem, it's a lullaby. Hush little baby. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 15:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a poem though. It's the lullaby, hush little baby.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 10:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vanilla. Sugar. Cinnamon. Honey. My grandmother used to tell me stories about the old days, a time of peace when the Avatar kept balance between the Vanilla Tribes, Sugar Kingdom, Cinnamon Nation, and Honey Nomads. But that all changed when the Cinnamon Nation attacked. Only the Avatar mastered all four flavours. Only he could stop the ruthless Cinnamonbenders. But when the world needed him most, he vanished. A hundred years have passed and the Cinnamon Nation is nearing victory in the War. Two years ago, my father and the men of my tribe journeyed to the Sugar Kingdom to help fight against the Cinnamon Nation, leaving me and my brother to look after our tribe. Some people believe that the Avatar was never reborn into the Honey Nomads, and that the cycle is broken. But I haven't lost hope. I still believe that somehow, the Avatar will return to save the world
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 10:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vanilla. Sugar. Cinnamon. Honey. My grandmother used to tell me stories about the old days, a time of peace when the Avatar kept balance between the Vanilla Tribes, Sugar Kingdom, Cinnamon Nation, and Honey Nomads. But that all changed when the Cinnamon Nation attacked. Only the Avatar mastered all four flavours. Only he could stop the ruthless Cinnamonbenders. But when the world needed him most, he vanished. A hundred years have passed and the Cinnamon Nation is nearing victory in the War. Two years ago, my father and the men of my tribe journeyed to the Sugar Kingdom to help fight against the Cinnamon Nation, leaving me and my brother to look after our tribe. Some people believe that the Avatar was never reborn into the Honey Nomads, and that the cycle is broken. But I haven't lost hope. I still believe that somehow, the Avatar will return to save the world </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hush little rager </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 09:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hush little rager
don't say a word


Before you're polyed into a bird


and if your shit you, should flip


Down to bronze your MMR will dip


And if thine MMR thou doth tank


we'll hear the salt about your rank


And if your rank you should bemoan


play a hero with whom you can own


First pick Nova if you're a Tool


Neither should you lock Illidan you Fool


Just calm down and count to ten


When you want to win use Vikings with Play Again


Your micro is shit, and so are you


When you get salty all the team hears is Boo hoo hoo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 07:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is wrong with the kit though? You're just expressing a negative and not adding to the conversation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 04:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This video really helps explain the "Glasses Mafia" in an entertaining way. 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CAeHuDcy_bY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 04:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also have a referal link, which will give me 10$ towards my next purchase and 10$ off your first if you use it.

https://ca.eyebuydirect.com/976851

I didn't include it in the main body of the post, because me saving money is not the point of this post. though if you want to use this link that'd be dandy. I also encourage other users who are already members to post their links here as replies to this one. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: Always buy glasses online, you'll be able to get similar frames as in store, with 100s of dollars in the difference. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 04:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 03:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fixed. Thanks for the heads up. I'm going to listen to that podcast now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favourite gaming song/playlist? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 03:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's mine at the moment. I want to build it up. Rock, rap, and electronic music are my favourites.

https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL2aW6WBanyIXw_4eWLuaiHRtTgMX1NkAn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 22:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to see what people come up with, but two thoughts I had were seeing the main character being driven insane by the foolishness of everyone else (Like we as viewers often are.)

Or the main character using these awesome new powers, becomes the talk of the town. (Think "The invention of lying" but with common human decency. ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [wp]You have a regular amount of common sense and interpersonal skills, you have been transported too the world of a Dramatic T.V show making you the most sensible person on earth. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 22:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 05:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That last one was just a Team-wipe via awesome combo. Not much of a WTF moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 01:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd be out of Q range easy, if he's out of your laser range. And by the time he hunts you, your cooldown on laser will be back up and it start all over, only now Illidan doesn't have his Ult. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 09:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Illidan ran in the opposite direction of me, that's exactly what I'll do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 05:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then he backs off in the opposite direction until his cooldown is fixed. Or he chases you depending on the Terrain you've fought in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 23:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Laser build Azmodan would like a word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 23:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then you're playing in a different league than OP and the vikingnplayer will be able to respond in the way I described, it is very easy to lightly harass two lanes, and keep Olaf alive if your allies are keeping pressure on.

In OPs league, with a viking of that level, his plan works just fine. But there's a reason vikings are viable, and its because as simple as this counter play seems, its never that simple
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 18:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's only got two lanes to cover because of his split. Baelog and Olaf are bottom vs Eric.

This guy is obviously a new vikings player, even if the skin wasn't a give away. That's nothing against him, but that's why vikings are such a high skill cap, you need to be able to control all three.

But you can tell he doesn't even check on Eric more than once or twice after he sits him in the gate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 04:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who plays Vikings, that won't work for someone like Dehaka.

That Eric can kite him all day, and should have been peppering him with attacks.

If it was a tanged hero, or he was against Olaf, yes that is an okay strategy. But even then, with Micro, Olaf can soak, run, heal. Since he has the muradin trait.

Baelog can do the harass thing like Eric, just not as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 19:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup! And they gave me a lot of sass and attitude when I was asking what it was too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 19:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excatly! Just treat me with kindness and even if your product is slightly worse (Not thecase here. Love these glasses) I will be preaching your virtues to everyone I can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 01:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No idea, sorry to say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 01:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah man. You can get several styles actually to go with different outfits! I've spent about 125 dollars with them, and I have three pairs of sunglasses and three pairs of regular ones. (They often have BOGO events.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 23:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to think I'm that kinda guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 23:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup! If my glasses aren't on, I cannot even read the laptop I'm sitting at. And they're amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 23:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No idea. I just use those fellas, but I'm pretty sure they're worldwide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 23:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their sunglasses are amazing and it's only 5 bucks more to tint them.  (You can even pick the colour) though they do have transition options (Too expensive for me) and mirrored (Which look rad as hell) and I use my glasses for driving and reading, so I'd say you're probably good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 21:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do it. If I can even put one more customer onto them I'd be glad. I do kinda owe them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 21:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm super poor. So I know what it's like to need glasses on the cheap. 

Also this company is amazing. I lost my only pair once, and when I ordered new ones they rushed them out for me. (I was supposed to wait three weeks, I waited three days.)

That kinda thing makes me super loyal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 21:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, anyone who thought this was crazy and want to be able to buy glasses for like, 15 dollars (even perscription sunglasses!) 

https://ca.eyebuydirect.com/ 976851

Sites like that are amazing. I put a little space between the number and the link, because if you add that number to the link and buy something, I get 5 bucks towards my next glasses, but I don't want to trick folks into doing it. (If you want to though, that'd be super.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 19:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is this "chain" thing I keep hearing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey guys, based off that fantastic "skit" that some random users made in the current r/all Rick and Morty post, I made a sub reddit where creative fans can get together and write dialogue for made up episodes while we wait for the next season. Also. I really need mod help with it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 07:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 07:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rick! Rick man! Aww jeez. I've been having weird dreams Rick. Real weird. Weirder than normal man. They're.... ya'know... big boy dreams. But they're messed up man. Ya gotta help me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [prompt] Scary Terry's high school aged daughter, Scary Terri, runs away from home and begins hanging out in Morty's subconscious. Rick and Morty need to help Reconcile their father daughter relationship. Morty is equally aroused and terrified by Scary Terri. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 07:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [meta] I'm a shitty mod and need more mods who're less shitty than me to help make this place presentable. Any nominations? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 07:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [meta] Acknowledging the guys who gave me the idea. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 07:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u/Rammite, u/gh0sti, u/thekingoflightbeer, u/braintrustinc, u/NusringPositivism, u/Adorno_a_window, u/End_Of_Century, u/euphoneus

All came together and made a hilarious "mini" episode in an r/funny post. 

https://www.reddit.com/r/funny/comments/5doxsx/morty_you_got_you_gotta_play_the_drums_morty_you/

This made me want to make a subreddit dedicated too that to see what we could do! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 07:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/RedditWritesRM/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 07:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/RedditWritesRM/

There's a subreddit for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 07:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dunno yet. That was the last page hook </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is this thing that tells me I did good, since when do we have them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 22:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/8Bt7SrU
http://i.imgur.com/8Bt7SrU.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 08:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Report and move on. It's all you can do, and if you can ruin smurf by getting it banned, all the better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 18:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol what? Must have wanted retirees.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 09:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is certainly not the same, he's better balanced now. Making his spiders a skill shot was a good move, but otherwise he's got the same... Flavour? Like. If you played him before, it was easy to get back into him. But it's the difference between Jaina and Kael. If you can play one, you can play the other, but you may not be able to play them at the same level without practice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 06:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The worst is that "You have been dropped" thing that happens. Lagging out and immediately start the reconnect? I can live with that. But being dropped because of Blizzard for one reason or another? That pains me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 05:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a TLV player, I would love APM as a score statistic. Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 05:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/acontextmash </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 05:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who LOVES specialist heroes Naz is just.... An unwieldy assassin. 

He does great damage, but no burst. He has great wave clear, but his sustain isn't strong. His crowd control is cool in concept, but easily countered. (Unless you're on his team, then it's the best CC in the game. _)

A great Nazeboo will be amazing. 

A good Nazeboo will be okay.

An okay Nazeboo will be bad.

And a bad Nazeboo will literally kill his teammates.

And if you're Amazing with Nazeboo, you're probably pretty great with some better heroes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Main Reason I bought Tyranny, aside from eveything else I love about this style of game, is the 49.99(CDN) price tag. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 05:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't bought a new game in ages. I think... Fire Emblem Fates was the last one I purchased brand new?

And all because every couple of years, the price of games goes up by 10 dollars. EVEN DIGITAL COPIES! And there's no reason for it other than corporate greed. And I'm super poor. Crazy broke all the time, I'm sure many of you can relate.

But I looked at Tyranny's price tag. And what it was offering me as a consumer. And I decided I HAD to support that. I had to show the corporate world, that a fair price on a new game IS worth something. I know my single purchase wont do much. But I hope enough of us support this pricing model that those with the big game licenses at least take notice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 20:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like that you're making content, that's great. But walls give vision which will get your allies ganked, and give your enemies advantage on rotation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the best answer yet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 03:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has been happening regularly for me ever since the Zarya patch.

And it's the most rage inducing thing, because not only does it force you to restart the client, not only does it rub it in your face when you click "leave" that you'll be marked as a leaver, but there's no warning at all. No lag. No FPS drop. No stuttering of any kind. Just. "You have been dropped"

And no recourse but to reboot the entire client, and then go through the awful reconnect system. I LOVE this game, and I've been planning through this for awhile now. It's been killing me. T_T </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] You do not want to be here. You keep doing everything you can to prove that, but everything you do just seems to confirm to everyone else you belong. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 22:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is your super try hard hero? And why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 21:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I'm about to start a quick match game with four randos I picked out of three different chat channels. (Teamleague, ARAM, and General) and the premise of this team up, was we'd each, regardless of comp, pick a super try hard hero to try and carry the game individually. Showing off, being flashy and stupid, just having fun.

I picked Illidan, because I love chasing and killing people, and hunting into solo laners. 

But I got to wondering, who is YOUR super tryhard hero?

Our team is "Illidan. Silver 1(I swear I belong in High gold low plat) Diablo. Gold 3. Li-Ming. Diamond 5. Kael. Bronze 3. Slyvanas. I'm not actually sure." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 01:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you meant to say my new phone backround.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 01:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. You visit in the future. It's one of the sites that open up with the Pendants power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 16:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never used anything but ZSNES so I wouldn't know haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 02:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol

Features:

**o Currently runs Space Invaders (+ derivatives).**
  

o Very fast Intel 8080 emulation (100% assembler).

o Freeware.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 02:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OH! I had that problem in FFV as well! The pirate ship yeah? My brother and I just removed the layer that was in our way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 00:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow! For real?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 00:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno why you got downvoted. That's exactly what I meant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 00:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beautiful. Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 21:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Down grading 3DS? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 20:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always thought this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PsBattle: This "just holding his shit together" looking officer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 19:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 19:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right? Currently it's at 50 for me. But back in the days before I had a job it was closer to 90% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your fondest memories of Emulation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 18:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Family didn't have a lot of money, so getting most games was out of the question. Especially rare RPGs on the SNES. So my brother would always pirate them. And I'd try to play, but never be able to make it very far, but I always wanted to play them like my brother. 

As I went through school, I began to learn to read, and using those games to motivate me, I became the best reader in my grade straight through highschool.

My early start, learning to read from those games, really helped set me up for a lifetime with a love for literature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 25 [M4F] Toronto, Ontario, CANADA - Hey there ladies south of the border, you're desperate to leave your country, I'm desperate not to die a lone. Let's help each other out. (Or just a Canadian girl who's looking for something long term.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 19:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So a few rules before you pop up here and are wowed by my exotic Canadian Charms.

Ya gotta dig, or at least be able to put up with nerd culture. I know I know. A lot of it is in your face these days, some people even go over board. Don't worry about that with me. No sirree. I'm just looking for someone to watch the latest marvel movies with me, play some Co-Op video games, and maybe join me on DnD adventures once in awhile.

You've gotta like to eat. By that I mean, be open to every kinda food there is! I love to cook, I love to try new things when I cook. I need folks with an open mind. Bonus if you like spicy stuff.

Being able to enjoy the out doors is a must. As you sneak across the boarder I'm sure you're going to be doing plenty of camping anyway, but I want to do it in our leisure time as well! 

As for what you look like. Well. Whatever. Honestly. If I find you attractive, great! But I don't really have a "type" all shapes and sizes. I guess one weakness I have is very short girls. Like 5'3 and shorter. But there are plenty of beautiful tall women. Height is not a breaking point for me. Besides, I'm 6'3 so most men and women I've dated have been shorter than me.

https://i.imgur.com/vuTbdtN.jpg

There I am. My head is looking pleasantly squared in that photo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 19:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did not see that ending coming. Literally laughed out loud </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Powerman and Ironfist seen the return of Alex Wilder! Power Man And Ironfist #10 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 18:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 15:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was that about, and when? Canadian here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the things I love about this sub is the positivity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 17:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the posts on the front page are usually hype, fan content, or praising the game. Inside of those you'll always get salt factories complaining how they hate posts that talk up the game we love, but those voices are drowned out by the upvotes from our community that lifts our collective positivity to the front page proving that the majority loves being joyful, and all of the negativity can stay here in the newest first salt farms where it belongs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 22:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fucking National Treasure movies, so much fun. Great stupid concept, and then you throw goddamn Nicholas Cage into it. He's such a bad actor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 22:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. The "hangover" of going to a movie by yourself really sucks. It's the trip home that's the worst. That's the time you always spend talking about the movie! That's basically the point of going with someone, because you're hardly going to be chatting during the entire thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 22:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're ever in Toronto, we can catch a flick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 21:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone who said they'd go with me cancelled on me, as usual. So I went to see Ant Man by myself. I loved it. I honestly had a great time, and now I enjoy going to see movies by myself. 

The only bad part is right afterwards, which would normally be spent talking to people about the movie, I was alone again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 16:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. I didn't realize it was limited back in the day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are all the top comments in the later sleep times front page post being removed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 02:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 02:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm Canadian, and I spell Favourite like that. Speaking of, so did you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 19:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you ping an AI, it will follow you. If you ping it again, it will stop and do its own thing.

If you ping a Merc camp it will start moving towards it, asses if it can capture it on it's own, or with the help of nearby heroes, and it will start the camp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 20:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the movie didn't come out until Thursday night? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 18:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've beaten both Lost Vikings games, and I'm a level 16 in game. So I might be biased though. lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 14:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd rather this than the current garden terror splash art </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 04:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It happens so much and is ruining the game for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 15:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That kills me. It has been happening to me since the Zarya patch and there is no way to reconnect unless you reboot hots </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 06:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is some. I came here to mention him as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 17:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about those of us who have been having fun with it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 03:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not if you make the map really tiny, and give it a timer of like 5 minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 21:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Nightshade

thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Brawl Idea] Leap Frog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 21:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inspired by the Sonya leaping onto Murky illustration on the front page, this idea would have one team of all murkys and one team of all Muradins.

The Murkys would have no auto attacks and able to use their bubble once per life.

The muradins would have no auto attacks, and only be able to kill a murky by landing a dwarf toss onto him.

There would be vents and bushes everywhere, each murky puffer fish would drop a slowing slime, and the murkys would have sprint.

The next round, the roles swap. The winnign team is which ever one killed the most murkys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 08:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who the hell was Tilda? She kept talking about fighting the avengers and stuff. Who was she before Nighthawk? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 20:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dunks are awesome when enemies are clumped, or running, but laser is a better team fight tool.

Also, demonic invasion is your ult on Laser build.

Your demons get body blocks, give you better pushing potential and Black Pool is not worth it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 18:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Laser isnt' as strong as it used to be, with bound minion being on the same tier as march, turning you into a one trick pony. (Where it used to be zoning/teamfights and pushing. It's now just zoning.)

But any map where you need to hold a location, Skytemple for instance, or blackharts. 

OR any map that's narrow and hard for people to run from you, tomb, or the between lane areas of Dragon shire for example.

It's super powerful vs the like of Illidan or Thrall. Very few heroes can out duel you, and high level players know this, so once you drop a laser, they run away giving you an Escape.

Or if they don't you get a kill.

If they have plenty of stuns, even micro stuns, don't risk it. Just buff your demon warriors and push to win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 00:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rexxar is half ogre </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 00:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What part if Canada? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 00:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love to run the TLV and battle myself as each viking serves a different warlord. Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 19:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine is from my youth. My uncle was berating some of the workers he knocked a bunch of roofing supplies, including a bucket of tar to the ground. 

"What did I do to get paired with a couple of *fagnificant fucks* like yourself?

Source: I'm Bi, and I like to write. I think this was the moment in my life I learned to love alliteration.

Edit: I'm paraphrasing the rest of his sentance. I only really remember the insult. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is an insult, that may not be directed at, but is otherwise offensive too, your minority group, that you find amusing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 19:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 19:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 01:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is perfect! Thanks.

In fact, I always thought standing was a full move action. So I've just learned something! haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm starting a campagin of 5e with two young boys. One 5 one 8. What are some easy quick reference "cheat sheets" I can print off? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 23:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially for combat rules and what not. But really I'd love to have a "Player screen" much like the DM screen. Where the boys can quickly reference it during the game.

But any neat little cheat sheets would be great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OC]So my nephew is running his very first DnD game. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 23:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So my nephew is running his very first DnD game. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 23:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 22:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He leans so heavily on his Foggy argument, but it disregards the context. Foggy is a private attorney. He's not trying deny castle this right, he just does not want him as a client.

Its why he went into private practice with Matt. So they can decide their clientel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 20:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The appendage one might be a bit too punishing, though I could make it "You loose use of 1 appendage for 1d4 days".

The Square one sounds fund though. I like that. Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 18:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 15:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We could use a bunch of these for sure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 15:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah thats an Aasimir effect if I recall. It makes it more difficult to escape being swallowed whole.

In pathfinder I believe. Thats a good idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 15:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh each suit will have negative effects for sure.

Like maybe you are compelled to aid the next person who requests it regardless of reward, or you loose gold etc.

So no one suit will be all positive and no one suit will be all negative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 07:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's pretty neat. I could see building a class around this. Class skill, start each round drawing a card.

As you level up you can add multiple draws, make it so you're able to draw from a specific suite at will by specializing in it. 

Another ability to draw an extra card as a move action etc.

Actually. I might make a custom class like that using this deck of yours.

It becomes less random the higher level you are, whereas at low levels you are either mighty, or middling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 07:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah. I like the idea that any mage can make one card a day via a ritual and once all 52 are assembled you're good to go. So like, it wont be super common  because not everyone has 52 days a year to spend making one, but there'll be a few floating around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The deck of minor things" Help make suggestions for this magical item! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 07:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, the idea here is a custom, non game breaking version of the Deck of Many things. I'm sure there must be other versions of this idea, and feel free to submit links. But I want to make one with all of you!
  
So. Some rules.
Diamond = Lawful
Heart = Good
Spade = Evil
Club = Chaotic
  
The higher the card value, the more impressive the effect.
  
So. Maybe the lawful 2 of diamonds will allow a character to gain 2x their charisma modifer in minor healing potions.
Where as the Chaotic 2 of clubs will give the player 2x 2d20s in gold coins.
  
So, the diamonds will have controlled effects, the clubs will have random effects.
The hearts will have generous effects like, you gain an aura that gives anyone in range a +1 to a saving throw once a day.
The Spades will have a selfish effect. You have +1 to a saving throw twice a day.
  
This helps give a kind of theme to the deck of Minor things.
    
What do you all think? Any suggestions?
    
**Hearts:**

* Ace:
* 2:
* 3:
* 4:
* 5: Anyone you consider a friend, within range, gains a +1 to a saving throw once a day. That range is 10feet.
* 6:
* 7:
* 8:
* 9:
* 10:
* Jack:
* Queen:
* King: Gain a Level 2 Squire of any class. The squire cannot level up and has one of the three good natures.


**Diamonds:**

* Ace:
* 2: Gain 2x your Cha modifier worth of minor healing potions. (For negative charaisma multiply by -2)
* 3:
* 4:
* 5:
* 6:
* 7:
* 8:
* 9:
* 10:
* Jack:
* Queen:
* King: Gain a Level 2 Squire of any class. The squire cannot level up and has one of the three lawful natures. 


**Spades:**

* Ace:
* 2:
* 3:
* 4:
* 5: You gain +1 to any saving throw twice a day.
* 6:
* 7:
* 8:
* 9:
* 10:
* Jack:
* Queen:
* King: Gain a Level 2 Squire of any class. The squire cannot level up and has one of the three evil natures.


**Clubs:**

* Ace:
* 2:Gain 2x 2d20 in gold coins
* 3:
* 4:
* 5:
* 6:
* 7:
* 8:
* 9:
* 10:
* Jack:
* Queen:
* King: Gain a Level 2 Squire of any class. The squire cannot level up and has one of the three Chaotic natures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 23:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And look at how small the amount of coins you got from it is. They really need to make duplicates worth atleast half, if not more. But I doubt they will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 09:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in lobby, all was good. I dropped.

It was a demotion game. I didn't even get to try and defend my rank.

And it does this all the time in game. Just drops me. No lag. No warning. And it's not the normal lag out drop. It's "You have been dropped" and I cannot rejoin without restarting the client. What is with that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't follow Esports very much, who should I, and others, choose as our Champion? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 20:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 20:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My main problem is, barely any lore was released. If each time the ARG was solved, a chunk of info about things in the game world was shown, that'd be wonderful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 06:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. I just got the roadhog skin. Again. And got 200 gold for the duplicate when it costs 3k to buy. Like. That's nonsense right there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 06:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too much gold in my opinion. Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 05:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I totally think it's good we made a stink, so it doesn't happen again. But the effort put in is beautiful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 05:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To the Devs - As frustrating as this whole Sombra thing has been, thank you for doing it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 05:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The amount of effort you put into this really speaks to how much you love what you're doing, and dispite all the complaints, and how it's even bugging me, I want to let you know that I, and I'm sure others, really love the effort you're putting in. And don't let this discourage you from doing something like this in the future! 

Heck, having a year long one, with other hero releases like Ana's in between, could be fun. But you're more clever than I, so you'd know better than me if your audience would love or hate that.

Just. Thanks for the enthusiasm. Don't let negativity sour it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 23:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. looks amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 23:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never. It's a mashup of Spiderman and Eternity by this guy
https://www.artstation.com/artwork/wv95V </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 20:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah, orange for sure. That's why I mentioned disruptors first.

But a golden Azmo with blue, and a black one with red would be great to cover other protoss tribes. (Or black and green.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 19:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No no. The disruptors from LOTV have the perfect bomb. Or tempests.

Also, his black pool should have an energizer I'm the middle in its deployed state. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 19:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right? So upsetting we didn't get more.

Alarak is cool, but his trait feels lacking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 19:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love it!

As for his soldier, zealots work, his lieutenant a high templar looking guy. Think Tass from broodward. Very short range.

And his drop is obviously probes. 

I think you were the guy I talked to about Dark Archon Azmodan, and I love what you did too my favourite hero with this purifier skin. He looks great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 00:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The point is to make you think. A guy like me? I will go 3-5. Maybe.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 21:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats the point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA: If you cannot win 12-2 in ranked play at level 5 and higher, you're probably not going to win very much in the new arena </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 21:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 00:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm down. Friday evenings every two weeks? Weekly is a bit of a commitment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 14:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Much like flat earth, what are some outlandish theories that people actually believe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 14:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 03:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I was picturing a Taldarim style thing. So for his basic units, the new Alarak minion from Starcraft II Co-Op.  A taldarim Zealot. 
http://vignette3.wikia.nocookie.net/starcraft/images/2/23/Taldarim_Zealot_SC2_Rend.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20151028025721

Then an Ascendet for his Lieutant
http://vignette1.wikia.nocookie.net/starcraft/images/d/dd/Taldarim_High_Templar_SC2_Rend.jpg/revision/latest/scale-to-width-down/200?cb=20151028023307

And supplicants for his Demonic Invasion
http://vignette1.wikia.nocookie.net/starcraft/images/c/c3/Supplicant_SC2-LotV_Rend1.png/revision/latest/scale-to-width-down/150?cb=20160911090225

And as for his legs, make them lighting that's arcing off his main Archon body. Like with each step, another one appears and fades, less like legs and more like static.

I've thought a lot about it. Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 02:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, I have had a skin idea I'd love to see in your style!

Dark Archon Azmodan! I think you'd kill it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 09:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just pimp it out so it looks fly as shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Calling an ask reddit thread a repost, is like going to a theme party and telling all the people who weren't at the last one not to enjoy themselves </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 03:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 03:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Canadian I didn't get it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 23:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happened with Starcraft 2? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
