<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2947</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 10:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow someone actually did get falsely banned, Wait that happens all the time. However its the people who cry wolf on here that ruins it for the actual people who were falsely banned smh, Its great that they rectify their mistakes quickly though. and i hope the legit sincere people actually are able to get the support they need from jagex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 09:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, Nessy done took my elysian Lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 09:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can go on as many accounts as your pc can handle (not against the rules) although breaking multiple rules on many accounts, rwt mass botting etc. Will get your accounts chain banned (They ban all accounts associated with your I.P) but thats rare unless you're a serious rule breaker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just got Lured for elysian :( </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 08:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got the elysian from 99 slayer + many months of merching.
Anyways i was at the grand exchange when someone came up to me and traded, He put up a 400m cashstack (which he probably got from luring)   said do you want. I'm like sure. He said add me. the scammer then messaged me saying he's tired of playing this game and is leaving for college, so he's giving away all his items but first i need to play a trust game.

He then traded and gave me a ring of dueling, which i accepted   he told me to follow. 

I went over to the duel arena and followed him, when suddenly (scammer #2) comes out of nowhere. He then says, watch out this guy has been scamming people all day, I was lucky enough to anti-lure him though. scammer #2 then goes on explaining how theres 2 rounds, and you take the money and run on the first round. But the more items you bring the bigger the prize will be. So me thinking i can anti-scam i decide to play along and bring my elysian. 

Anyways we arrive at the mage training arena. He then goes onto explain that when you drop items, they appear for everyone in 60 seconds exactly I then agree, He then says to go in the creatures graveyard and try dropping anything going out, then going back in   picking it up. I do it (still playing along) I'm able too obviously. He then says first round of trust game, i want you to drop your ely inside the creatures graveyard, Then come out and trade him for my prize. Still thinking i can pick it up whenever. I go and drop it then quickly come back up and trade him. He then confirms by trading me then he stalls time about 35 seconds in trade. He then says Bury the bones and you win the game, But pick up your elysian first before it goes away. He then puts up 27 bones and an arma helmet in trade   i accept fast. thinking i got a free arma helm i decide to run and pick up my elysian, Still have about 20 seconds. But i cant enter the graveyard, because you cant bring in bones. I then panic and begin dropping my bones as quickly as possible. He enters the graveyard   says thanks. im panic dropping bones as fast as possible. But its too late, he then comes up with the elysian, im pleading with him to give it back, He says he'll give it back on one condition, I say whats the condition, He then says He needs about tree fiddy, Well it was about this time I noticed that this scammer was about 8 stories tall and was a crustacean from the protozoic era. I said, "Dammit monster, I ain't giving you no tree-fitty! After that i went on my way   started to rebuild from slayer   merching. long story short never trust a scammer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 04:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> leader says doesnt seem experienced enough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone help me find the name of this song? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 04:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
