<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2797</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 08:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> try not even being invited. poor you... not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 08:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> saaaaaaaaame </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> spent another Halloween completely alone while everyone else is dressed up at a bar having fun... yay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 08:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> getting really fucking sick of this shit. maybe if I kill myself it will finally send a fucking message  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 04:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cant relate actually. strangely I have high self esteem and depression. Im just a highly frustrated and disappointed person I guess is how to explain it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 04:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 23:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like this might only be true for metrizable topological spaces? not sure though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> does anyone know where to find how Euler calculated taxicab number(4,2,2)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 22:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just learned that the taxicab number problem is actually a very deep problem in number theory. just wondering how he went about getting this number. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 06:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 05:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 05:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> prove the product of two odd numbers is odd. 

prove there are 2,598,960 different 5 card hands from a standard 52 card deck. 

prove that if A divides B and B divides C, then A divides C.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> why do they say the most important work you do in math happens by age 30-40? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 05:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont understand this even remotely im lost </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 18:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks thats actually what I was thinking  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 02:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> depends on the problem  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 00:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in calculus anything over 0 is infinity  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 00:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 22:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the question doesnt say differentiable. it just says prove that a continuous 1:1 function on [a,b] is either increasing or decreasing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 22:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> proving that a 1:1 function on a closed interval is either increasing or decreasing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 21:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im not completely sure how to set up the proof for this. Im not asking for the proof and actually please do not post it. Im just wondering if it is necessary to use some sort of example function or not, since one was not given. OR should I use proof by contradiction to show that if we have a value for which f'(c)=0 , then there is a y value corresponding to more than one x value? thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 04:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh you have to subtract the repeats? I got 1400  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [introductory] combinatorics. how many of the first 10000 natural numbers are divisible by 10 or 25? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 21:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whats the method of attack for this problem, for some reason Im a little unsure. Im more so looking for method than just the answer, thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 00:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im still looking for something different.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1+2+3+4....+n = {n(n+1)}/2. alternative proofs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 00:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> are there any proofs for this other than the common Gauss proof where you rewrite the sum backwards, and them add them? I find this proof kinda boring for some reason  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> most people who love math love games in my experience. anyone here who loves math but has almost no interest in games? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 03:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fucking hate games. I never feel like investing that much mental energy in something that will never make a difference nor pay off long term. I always lose and never have fun. Id rather just be doing math.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> the go board and graph theory? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 20:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> are there any strategies for this game developed using math? Im assuming if so it would use graph theory. any links would be appreciated. just started playing go not too long ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 01:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> alright sweet thanks for your 2 cents  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 01:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks for that. thats interesting  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 06:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> to those who work on algorithms and are very familiar with them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 23:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just started studying algorithms for my discrete math class, and read that Euler and Jacobi did work on algorithms. does anyone know how to explain how algorithms were used and or useful well before computers?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 02:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> taking an intro class that uses Alice, only the 2nd project and already im struggling a LOT </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 03:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we have to make a tortoise grab and wave around a cookie from a stool. this seems fucking impossible. I already hate programming and want to go nowhere with it at all. I cant at all get the tortoise to move its arm in any fashion to grab the cookie (yeah yeah vehicle property bla bla bla). also I have no fucking idea how to place the tortoise and the stool relative to each other.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> best linear algebra books suggestions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 00:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> have calc experience, just now starting linear algebra. whats a good book that not only explains the math well but also the intuition behind it? thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 00:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Im really fucking sick of edibles not working </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 05:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whats the deal? I have done so much research and so many wasted fucking experiments. an entire fucking 8th wasted on a batch of brownies that affect everyone but me. I feel NOTHING from them EVER no matter how much I eat. the fuck IS this shit? this keeps happening. every fucking time I try edibles that either I or someone else made.... NOTHING HAPPENS  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 16:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a LOT of acid  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 22:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> appreciate the suggestions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 22:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> any suggestions for introductory analysis books? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 05:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is the Dover textbook any good? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 04:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> men dont want me boo hoo oh he treated me like shit boo hoo lets assign arbitrary imaginary labels. yeah this is why there has never been a female genius  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 00:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> become a research scientist  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On handling your tarantula... the big taboo it seems </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 05:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have read many times that it is not necessary and if nothing else a high risk. however recently an owner of several reptiles and spiders/tarantulas told me that it is actually a good thing to handle your tarantula often. not sure what to believe. I handle mine about once a week. also Im sure it depends on species to an extent. I have and avic avic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
