<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3240</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 02:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> White 20 year old girl who works as a peppy waitress at an Olive Garden, is going to school for art, and I FUCKING LOVE pumpkin spice stuff. I also wear a lot of mauve colored lipstick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 02:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally me. I was such a die hard my senior year of high school. Didn't shave and yelled at anyone who questioned it (I'm a girl), angrily hated on America on my Tumblr, thought republicans were all horroble people, etc etc. The sort of feeling you get when you step off the super lib train is so refreshing because it's hard to be angry all the time. Plus my armpits feel so much better now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 02:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to think that annoying, over-bearing and judgmental vegans were a minority. Until my sister watched some super biased documentary that obviously twisted information and statistics into their favor and decided to become one. I sent her one joke about it (Being a vegan is a big missed steak) and she literally just flipped her shit on me. All of her friends are just as bad and I can't stand it. Now that I know a bunch, they're all just so pretentious about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 00:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My younger sister is an annoying brat. Stuck up, self righteous, know it all, and vain. But I would give my life for hers without blinking. There's this sort of secondary maternal feeling you get for younger siblings when you're the oldest. When my parents were busy, I took care of her. I'm sure if you were to go back in time to that moment and tell your brother right before it happened, he would do it all over again in a heartbeat. He loved you and I'm sure he would be thrilled to know you met the man of your dreams. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 00:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha its a pretty simple story. And greasy nerd guy was alright, I talked to him about video games for a bit, but he looked and smelled like he hadn't showered in over a week :/ Downside of some nerds, unfortunately. I only saw him around at school maybe once or twice, but he was playing his 3DS so didn't bother him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 09:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stupid high school me believed some lady trying to return random stuff to a Wal Mart without a receipt or ID, believed that she needed money for her daughters birthday. 2 seconds after agreeing to help her, I realized she was trying to return shit she stole, but I was already getting in line with her with my ID. Good thing I pretty much only shop at Target now. Bitch walked out of there with like $150 and didn't even hand me a $5. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 09:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> US Olympic swimmer who lied about being mugged in Rio just to get attention/press. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
