<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3318</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 03:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like a Japanese Tea Ceremony for drunks

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BBn7mdV7-tQ
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 03:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep I'm "that guy"- Totally out of my league.  With all possible meekness and respect....   You stated "Unfortunately, not a single scrap of the list survives"  So how do we know there is a list?
Edit - was a list
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 01:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Help Hillary Clinton win </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 22:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shut your Cum Dumpster! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today my wife and I marked our twenty year wedding anniversary. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 03:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I would have killed her I would be out of jail by now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 00:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (name of college police) SURVEILLANCE VAN or SURVEILLANCE DRONE

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 02:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some may think it is a bit lame, but hay its a good way to harness creativity. This is what nightmares are made of.
- I'm gonna bale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 03:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ice.  Get it real cold and see if it flick off. - Not based on experience just an idea.  Maybe the other extreme - get it warm with a blow dryer and dab with absorbent cloth. Blow straight down so it does not spread.

 Sounds like a tough one, maybe leave good enough alone.  Keep it on the sunny side, your wife has smooth legs! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 02:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just saying how it worked in the old school.  T-Shirts were soaked and sweat ran down into our pants, but we looked good!   This is a big thing at boot camp when you are a drill instructor- recruits are sweating in the hot sun and you look you just stepped out of air-conditioning, actually you were soaked and miserable.   Perception! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 02:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking the same thing.  Tax money paying for the death of Indians just sucks.  I do not think that the times that these atrocities happened is an excuse.  These were human beings.  
Your right, it should be acknowledged.
The only issue I would have with acknowledging what happened is the cost of all the claims people will put against the government for something that happened 100 years ago.  Suddenly everyone would have some American Indian in them,,,,Elizabeth Warren syndrome.
Back to your point.  Those were some mean bastards that invaded their land.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ishi the last Yahi (1992) - Ishi, "the last wild Indian in North America," For more than 40 years, Ishi had lived in hiding with a tiny band of survivors. When he walked into the white man's world, he was the last Yahi Indian alive. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 01:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 00:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this was real interesting to me - I found a documentary...

http://www.snagfilms.com/films/title/ishi_the_last_yahi

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 04:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a little bit odd in the beginning - remember there is no reason to wear them stretched real tight.   Clip them to the front of your shirt, I always lined it up with the pleats or the center of the breast pocket  - then the other end to the side of you sock.   If you put the front clips to the front of your socks they will slide off your knee caps when you walk.
Really becomes second nature after a few days and just part of getting dressed.  
Another thing we did in the military is line up the front of the shirt opening with the edge of the belt buckle with the zipper.  Its called a "gig line"   Here is a reference: http://gallogrotte.tumblr.com/post/22463691050/gentlemen-check-your-gig-line-what-is-it-where

Good luck!



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 01:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here you go....http://www.militaryuniformsupply.com/military-uniform-shirt-stays

I am retired military and I swear by these things.    When you see military folks with their shirts tight and straight this is what they  are using.  Keeps your socks up too! 
Clip one end to the shirt tail and the other to your socks.  They also have a version that you put under your heel in your shoe.

Another hack for Drill instructors and those who care is to scotch guard the inside of your shirts so nobody can see you sweat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 13:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reference:
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Grind_%28skateboarding%29 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 23:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop skateboarders from "grinding" along the wall.  Grinds are tricks that involve the skateboarder sliding along an object using the trucks of a skateboard rather than the wheels.
Marks up the item they are grinding on.  These pieces of metal discourage skateboard use in the area and are cheaper then cleaning/repairing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 17:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> grandma had all her furniture covered with plastic because she was a squirter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 02:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it quieter than a regular snare or just higher pitched?  By the way, what diameter is that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
