<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2469</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 21:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you :) ... there are more, you can find them in my channel :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inktober day 6: hidden woman, ink, 1280x720p </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 21:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> InkTober day 5: about sadness, Ink, 1280x720p </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 19:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inktober da 4: Hungry for pastries?, ink, 1280x720p </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 06:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 06:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks, and thank you for your suggestion, I'll do something about it :) ... everyone has their own thing, if drawing is not for you then you'll surely find something you're better at :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 21:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as far as I know, these things are most of the time scammers...think about it carefully, what do you need a network for? As I understood from reading other people's experience, unless you are already a big youtuber, they won't provide anything more than what you already do for yourself, and they are most of the time only interested in cutting further your earnings to fill their pocket.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> InkTober day 3: Childhood collection, Ink, 1280x720p </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 21:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 12:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm participating to InkTober so I'll have 1 drawing video everyday for the month of October. To make it a bit more challenging, I'm also voicing them over to improve my narration skills...here is my first video https://youtu.be/Hr-kEw-dfaA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 08:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> get yourself a basic tripod and mount your camera on it, it's really easy to use and not so expensive. Otherwise if you really don't wanna spend a cent, then do some DIY, for example fix some pieces of woods together and tap your camera to it. as long as your camera is fixed above your head, you should be able to film.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> InkTober day 2: Noisy drawing, Ink, 200mb </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 21:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> InkTober day 1: Fast Cycling, Ink, 300mb </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 20:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dreaming about Peony, Watercolor, 1280x720px </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 21:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Winter Witch, Amani Aura, Watercolor, 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 23:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's chat a bit while blending with the spirit of Autumn [17 views] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 14:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 09:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're welcome :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Merging with Autumn, Watercolor, 500mb </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 07:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Love Autumn Forests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 07:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 07:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is not my art, you can find the artist on dA but I'm glad you like it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 07:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you can follow the link and find the artist on dA :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 21:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no problem :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 21:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> certainly :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 21:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well this is not my art and the artist published this with the watermark :/ ... but glad you like it anyways :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sunset wind, GeneRazART, Digital art, 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 17:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The little blue bird, watercolor, 500mb </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 08:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Green eyed girl with horns, TundraColours, Watercolor, 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 20:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Autumn is Here, SurrenderComics, digital, 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 22:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 09:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'm doing some research on it...I'll probably make a new series of videos that is more suitable for inserting lots of keywords. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 20:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks for sharing your experience. I'll think about it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 13:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes, but I'm as well doing some study about how to choose video keywords and SEOs to better rank on search right now. That's why I take my time to only make one video per week, I can only make videos at home after work, but I can comment on other people video during work breaks so it all add up well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 12:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> surely, but that's my worth at this moment. I'm running in and out of ideas and always trying something new but I still haven't found the right tune :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 21:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sadly there is nothing faster if you don't want to spend money on advertisement or end up with ghost subscribers. Even people you find that way may might not really be interested in your content...do some research on keywords as well though, if your video rank well on google/youtube search and they are awesome, you'll surely gain more subs... or try talking about trending topics while playing your games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 19:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been doing a little experiment for my channel recently...I go to the youtube search tab and I type a keyword I am interested in...for example "Watercolor painting" ... I then change the video filter to today or last hour ... then I look at all the videos (max 10 min) that seem good from all channels that have less or equal subscribers than me... I watch their video and then leave nice comments ABOUT THEIR VIDEO (I never ask them to check me back) ... I have calculated that after every 20-30 comments, I get one of them to subscribe .... I don't know exactly if this is going to keep up but I got 5 subscribers that way...making sure to do this at least 2 hours a day for the past week (not necessarily 2 hour straight but whenever I have a little time to spare) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brush Pen Panels (by Laith) (no pencil sketch) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 17:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Serafina Blackwater, Rali-95, Digital Painting, 2016w </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 15:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blue Rose, Daily Painting, Watercolor, 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 08:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's Dray Jojo...with drawing tips </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 07:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A random Shoujo Manga girl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 20:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cut it all under the sunset </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 20:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 18:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have copyright issues on some videos, you have solve those on each video one by one, I suspect bellow each of the videos, there should be some link to "copyright dispute" or "counter ID claim" but I'm not sure...Please go to youtube copyright center and learn what you should do, watch the video and there are other options too https://www.youtube.com/yt/copyright/
If you are still lost, don't do anything, it will expire in 3 month and in the meantime, do not include anyone else's footage on your video...make your video from scratch 100% without any thing else from the internet....In the mean time you can do some research about what to do, maybe ask the same question you have here on youtube help forum and get advices from experts https://productforums.google.com/forum/#!forum/youtube </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beautiful sea turtle with a nebula background watercolor painting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 12:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 10:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are confident your videos are really good, I'd advice to try making them go viral by using paid promotion via google Adwords...if you hook up enough people they might share your stuff on their social media to get your first push.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elf, Anastasja A. Art, watercolour, 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 07:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 20:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it says that you have to resolve your copyright or community guidelines issues...check your in your channel if you have those by going to CHANNEL/Status and feature, there should be some angry faces there. If you have videos  copyright claim, resolve according to this https://support.google.com/youtube/answer/2814000#resolve
Don't delete the videos. If it's community guideline here is how to appeal https://support.google.com/youtube/answer/185111 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 10:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well, if you don't even appreciate your looks, I hardly believe anyone else would...which means you gonna get highly depressed for any kind of negative comments/feedbacks (which will inevitably happen)...you are overly self-conscious about yourself, even though you don't even know if you are gonna get views...which means you'll put yourself even lower if  you don't get views thinking no one wants to watch your video...I'd advice to forget about being a youtuber...come back when you have figured out how to love yourself.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 18:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did you get an email from google Adsense?normally they should send you the reason why they disabled it and then you can follow their links for things that you can do...they told me once that I received a 30 days disable because they detected invalid clicks and then I asked people at the Adsense forum and they told me it was a one time only warning, if they detect invalid clicks again my adsense account will be permanently disabled. So the safest idea I got is to disable monetisation all together and wait that my video get at least 1K views on average before re-enabling it. You can ask question at the adsense forum if this doesn't help you https://productforums.google.com/forum/#!forum/adsense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Relaxing Autumn Scenery, Jayshree Sharma, Watercolour, 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 13:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 10:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  maybe you needed to wait a bit before it happens...or maybe you are not popular enough to appear on the first search page result. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 10:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's the r/Art sub...well the rule is not there but I suspect it is, I've been posting too much of my stuff there...and I saw somewhere that there are some subreddit that are very strict to that, some sub would state it clearly and some will not...but that doesn't mean the rule is not there...I also tried to post my stuff on the r/Videos, it was rejected right away even though I have already accumulated enough link karma...when I asked the moderators, they said it was because more than 10% of my links comes from the same source and that is why I couldn't get passed the SPAM filter. In fact I didn't like this because I give feedbacks to the community regularly, it is just that my contributions are more comments than post links :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 10:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahaha! please don't...I'll cry...lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 07:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you can just type Kaguya naruto on google and you can find her pictures :)...and this is not my drawing by the way :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smiling Fionna (by Ari Draws)[1 views] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 01:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 01:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a bit but she reminded me more of kaguya character from naruto </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pink hair with horns, TundraColours, watercolor, 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 01:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Never a bride (by TheRichAntArt) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 20:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beautiful Fall forest (by Bianca Janell)[7 views] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 20:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Landscape, David, watercolour, 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 20:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> random art, Danielle Mack, Mixed media, 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 20:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 16:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From all testimonies I've heard so far and personal point of view, it's all bullshit. Plus I read somewhere it was against youtube policy.
Question #1 If you absolutely want sub4sub, I wouldn't advice any use of third party platforms for sub4sub ... youtube is very skilled at detecting those stuff so you might get your account banned if you are caught. (read some online reviews about subpal)
Question #2 If the subscribers who voluntarily decided to subscribe to you are not watching your videos, why would random people who don't know you but sub4sub, do so? they will be absolutely ghost...but if that's what you want, then it's for you to judge.
PS: are you aware that you'd be deceiving the companying you want promotion from by showing them your fake fame? well, that's not for me the judge but if I were them and I found out, I'd be really pissed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 11:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Entertaining others is really hard to do and you can't rely your existence on that because people's liking is relative, there is nothing universal, people may be entertained when watching Pewdiepie's gameplay videos but they may be not when it's you playing the same game even if you basically say the same thing...The first person you need to entertain is yourself, and hope to find other people who are as entertained as yourself just the way Pewdiepie's fans are entertained by him...If you want to please people, first please yourself, because if you are not happy in the first place, you cannot share any happiness to anyone. So be happy in order to make people happy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 10:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend, you need to heal your soul, take a really long break and enjoy the sun and the beautiful flowers, it's still not too late because autumn has just started. There are some nice colours waiting for you out there. I have been on youtube for 1 year and I already know how you feel, you've tried so many things but nothing is working. However, you need to be content and focus on the bright part of everything. You need to do things that satisfies YOU and only YOU because you'd get hurt every time if you are waiting for something in exchange of your hard work (views, attention, ...). As for the money spent, trust me, I've spent much much much more into my equipments, art materials and advertisement. I'd wished my channel popularity would explode once I reach 1K subscribers so I paid for adword video advertisements and DeviantArt ads and worked hard on my videos until I reached 1K. But you know what, nothing happened. Not only that, but the subscribers I got seem all fake since they are hardly actively watching my videos.  I'm also about to get banned from some subreddit because of the only "10% self-promotion is allowed" rule, my self posts are getting automatically downvoted. For one moment I was lost and felt despair because of all the money I spent...but then I remembered "Why I was doing it", it's for ME. It's my passion and I'll keep posting my videos for myself and for the very few REAL followers I've got...I became really happy when I see the likes on my video, for example when I get 25 views and get 5 likes...I suddenly feel like there is more energy coming so that I can keep going just for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drawing A Beautiful Hummingbird, by Braff Zacklin [6 views] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 21:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beautiful spring blossoms, Cassandra Hanley, colour pencil, 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 20:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's Draw Jibril (No Game No Life) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 19:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 18:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there is no effective way to remedy to inactive subscriber...all we can do is post as often as possible and expect them to check their subscriptions. You should just persevere in making quality content and make cards, playlists without relying too much on your subscribers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 11:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an artwork entitled: "Crush to red rose".
https://youtu.be/8CeviTuHGfI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House, Hadley Queen, ink, 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 19:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Play Doh Ice Cream Popsicle (Disney Galaxy) [64 views] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 18:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The endless fight against gravity (Keshri Abhishek)[60 views] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 08:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 21:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :/ perhaps you need to re-evaluate your content and your keywords...you can't get views for search if your video do not appear in search result in the first place...or perhaps it do appear in search result but the title and/or thumbnail may not be enticing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blacksummer colouring improved a lot, give her some cheers :) [151] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 19:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 13:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Outstanding thumbnails are more effective...it doesn't matter whether your title is all caps or not, search engines do not differentiate between minuscules and majuscules.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 13:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> please don't go and start a youtube channel when you've got so much on you plate...you should do what you want to do, for yourself unless you are already successful, in which case you would ask your fan base. If you haven't got any idea, I suggest you just watch what other people makes, and learn from them, maybe you'll get inspired to do something YOU like.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crush the rose, watercolor, ...Mb </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 23:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unicorn Girl by Pearberrie [24 views] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 20:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 20:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's marketing competition, there is nothing much that one can do about it...try to PM the video to your friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 11:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you tried to PM the owner of that video and ask them? I think that would be more efficient rather than asking random people here :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kingyo Yukata, Jeremiah ketner, Watercolor, 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 11:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cooking for a Cause, NGO Chicago coalition for the homeless (by Eicoff)[1 view] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 09:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lemonade mint, Digital Painting, 500MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 00:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 21:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's a really crazy issue, but if you haven't came across that then you should just take a look FYI 
https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/16737?hl=en
Google is doing this to protect advertisers from fraud
https://support.google.com/adwords/answer/2549113
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 15:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't use copyrighted materials unless given permission, monetised or not monetised.
It is advised by other sources and I understood from my personal experience that early monetisation is not beneficial for a channel. It's better to first reach 1k views per video before starting to monetise. The reason is "invalid clicks", if you get even one out of the few clicks you get due to your few number of views, no matter where it comes from, you may get your adsense account banned. However if you get one out of several clicks from 1K views, you're safer. I understood from reading about invalid clicks that they constitute 10% of the clicks that Google Adsense analyses, so if you, by any hazard got more than 10% invalid clicks then you could get your adsense account banned. Better be safe than trying to repair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 09:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure since I'm not a lawyer but maybe write up some general formal agreement between all the members of the channel you are working on...have everybody sign the agreement and give one copy to each members...well do as much as you can to make sure it's authentic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
