<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2840</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This right here. I had an anime phase a while ago where I would obsess over it and everyone would be put off by me. It's not like I stopped showering or something, or even stopped other activities that I enjoyed. It's just super annoying how the stigma around it paints it in a bad light. They seem to forget that some of their greatest childhood shows were actually anime. Pokemon? Video game turned anime.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My brother quit smoking for a while because he could vape. The smell of mangos or berries is so much nicer than the smell of a cremation. He would vape those huge clouds alone or with his family/friends. It's a much better alternative to smoking for every party involved. The stigma around it just depresses me tbh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My sister was telling me of this guy in her gym class who was such a rude shit after he became atheist. He was apparently a pretty nice guy, but now goes out of his way to make sure people feel like shit. "What's wrong with you and that hijab? You're oppressed and have to ask your dad for everything." "You didn't do anything today in class, the only thing that ran was your mouth." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've resisted playing actual video games because of this. A good number of my friends are gamers and they're like "you're a shitty gamer if the only game you play is little big planet" IMO I offhandedly mentioned I played it, I never said I was a hardcore gamer. Some of my favorite games are really immersive and fun, but are really hated on because it's not about a soldier in a building shooting at other soldiers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Japan has such a rich history, but the only thing people remember is the anime and hentai. Their society and social structure is so alien to the rest of the world. They're like the only country ever who actually fought to keep their emperor in power. They actually like their rulers, unlike most countries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only reason we were able to decode the eygytion hieroglyphics is because of the rosseta stone. There were 3 lines of text, each of a different language. They knew two of the languages, and they both translated into the same thing. They figured out the last line(which was the eygytian hieroglyphics) also has the same translation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a Viking or someone of Nordic descent who battled the invading Saxon/British army for an hour. Alone. He literally fought for an hour against a fully fledged army before he was taken down. Just blows my brains how insane this feat is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conservative Jewish schoolgirl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reek. My poor poor reek :( how can they deface a greyjoy like that? Fucking Ramsey should eat shit and die being pulverized in the penis area.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you got a good thing going, you want to milk it out for as long as possible. They'll probably make a side story of a charecter, or perhaps they'll take a random event and make a series out of it. Perhaps tywins conquest and how he consolidated the power of house Lannister.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tywin is loyal as shit to his family. He would never harm a Lannister. I think that he would've held up his bargain, simply because he got what he wanted. Jamie as heir. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hydrogen started having opinions after sometime.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The world's longest wall is in Australia(suck it trump) to separate Australia into two sides, the human side, and the side that has animals that want to rip your throat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think so. When we learn history, we're talking about thousands of years. It'll take a hell of a long time for the volume of lessons to increase, unless there's a major war, like WWIII. Unlike before, right now the advancements are spread out over long periods of time, instead of it happening quickly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess we'll be talking about how to updated jail broken iPhones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha yea I'm a bit of a retard when it comes to reddit. Fairly new here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the majority  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not what happens in my country IMO. Happens in Afghanistan and Saudi, not gonna deny, but the majority of Arabs aren't like that. Sister studied for 4 years at NYU and my other two sisters are both studying at RSCI Bahrain, and both are taking/took an exchange program in Ireland. Use your brain not what trump says.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Replied to the wrong comment oops  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: UN ambassador isn't synonymous with ambassador to the UN </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also makes you much less stressed. When I didn't do my homework or something small like that I always straight up say I didn't do it. No excuses, no nothing. Teacher are still annoyed but I'm not feeling stressed af.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do realize that they teach us this stuff in math and chemistry right? Horrible system to punish your kids for drugs if they're just paying attention in class.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not Japanese, but Arab. When to America and was talking with the local kids. Turns out the bullying they show on TV is as intense as real life. This kid was telling me how they made fun of his dad of not driving properly and died when a truck smashed into him. What the actual fuck? Another was telling me how the guys in her class would slap her ass all the time 

This just seemed super weird to me, that for them nothing is off the table when it comes to bullying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
