<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1772</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 13:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whether a girl is just trying to be nice or actually likes me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 13:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lindsey Stirling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 13:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A prayer book I received as a gift 19 years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 12:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> End it in a haste BBC Merlin style where they jammed content worthy of its own season into an episode or two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 12:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They all fail eventually... But here's some honorable mentions if you're looking for some newer stuff to burn through: [Flower Dance](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AULG4MoYxQk), Lindsey Stirling's [Radioactive](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aE2GCa-_nyU) cover, Kotoko's [Sociometry](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=X9bEHn7yaqM), Suzanne Vega - [Tom's Diner](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YjCsnI-3i6A),  
[Clokx](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WmZjhsoEFLI) (remix of coldplay's Clocks), and perhaps my all-time favorite: Linkin Park's [Numb](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kXYiU_JCYtU) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 11:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd probably love this: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yI1m28AO7no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 11:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He married a gorgeous natural beauty, makes an impressive salary, and does lots of speaking at social events and stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 11:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://vine.co/v/OHYHiIJgxvh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 11:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, and what if that person becomes your boyfriend and you encounter another "soulmate" more soulmate than that soulmate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 11:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fiverr. Lots of cool services on there for 5 bucks. Imagine what you could do with 6 such services. I found a resume critique service on there. My resume's never looked better after I implemented some of their suggestions. Need a new logo for your site? Suck at grammar and need something proofread by a professional? 5 bucks.  Need a stranger to give you advice therapy style? 5 bucks. Need something photoshopped? Need to design a flyer or poster? Want to create a customize card to mail out? Need career advice? Need help finding a job? Need something translated? 5 bucks. Too lazy to read something and need a summary on something? Procrastinating and need some help on whatever? Need help advertising? Endless possibilities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 11:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well played. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 10:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Up up and oy-vey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 10:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Final Fantasy 8 [Balamb Garden](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pSt-fNv5d68) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 14:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reaching Keter and seeing it are two entirely different things. Being successful with meditations and erring in any of your learnings will result in an erroneous understanding of the experience. Keter is sublime, you don't reach it. But it sounds like you did merit a lofty level of understanding in some aspect; unfortunately, it's an incomplete understanding. Creation had to begin with something, that something is God. If God surrounds all and fills all, how is there any room for nothingness to exist without somethingness? You see, nothingness was there all along as was somethingness and they are in a complete unity beyond man's comprehension with God. There are 10 sefirot; it's the ultimate expression of the unity of somethingness (1) with nothingness (0). One without the other is like painting the whole world in either white or black. Thus the sefirot do not remain stagnant as somethingness or nothingness. This unity can be taken a step further as 1+0 = 1. "Hashem Echad". The nothingness is there even if the somethingness is completely filling it. The placement you saw, using the physical description of "inside" is also erroneous as-is "garden" as these terms do not mean what you think they mean in the upper worlds where everything is in one "confusing" unity with each other where everything co-exists in the same "place" as various degrees of potential. It takes many years to train the mind how to process such meditations like a newborn baby trying to process the colors it's seeing for the first time. Keep on learning until those colors start coming into focus more. Even still, there's many lens to view truth with. Each lens might reveal a different reality -- each one true -- according to the part of reality it's in tune with. But if there's dirt on the lens, and you don't realize it's dirt, then you'd have an erroneous view of reality. But once you understand it's dirt, you can come to a true understanding by distinguishing between reality and dirt on the lens. Perhaps you were seeing something like this: http://www.workofthechariot.com/TextFiles/Graphics/upper_light.gif
But unfortunately, it's a difficult diagram to understand within the context of the upper worlds as the somethingness and nothingness are in a complete unity with God. The question becomes what are we? something? nothing? Rather God surrounds and fills all worlds. The diagram is a lens to reality but isn't the only diagram to see that reality with. Understanding it properly, however, where the intended meaning of the diagram is blurred, is best accompanied by understanding other kinds of diagrams until one understands how this kind of stuff works and doesn't work. Then when you pick up various Kabbalistic books, read them and understand them, then you can improve as a kabbalist. But if you'd like to synchronize with an established meditation out there so you understand what you're seeing, to get the hang of meditation, I'd suggest you look at page 119 of Meditation and Kabbalah: https://books.google.com/books?id=nW_GAAAAQBAJ lpg=PA119 ots=hF3pzMWYH4 dq=bahir%20nogah pg=PA119 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 09:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Variation_Selectors_Supplement </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 06:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In no particular order, I'd recommend: [The Early Kabbalah](https://www.amazon.com/Early-Kabbalah-Classics-Western-Spirituality/dp/0809127695), [The Kabbalistic Mirror of Genesis](https://www.amazon.com/Kabbalistic-Mirror-Genesis-Commentary-Chapters/dp/1620554631), [Meditation and Kabbalah](https://www.amazon.com/Meditation-Kabbalah-Aryeh-Kaplan/dp/0877286167), [Lessons in Tanya](https://www.amazon.com/Lessons-Tanya-vols-Yosef-Wineberg/dp/0826605400), [138 Openings of Wisdom](https://www.amazon.com/Openings-Wisdom-Moshe-chaim-Luzzatto/dp/B0017S8JZM), [Anatomy of the Soul](https://www.amazon.com/Anatomy-Soul-Chaim-Kramer/dp/1502912570), [Sefer Yetzirah](https://www.amazon.com/Sefer-Yetzirah-Creation-Aryeh-Kaplan/dp/0877288550), and [A Tapestry for the Soul](https://www.amazon.com/Tapestry-Soul-Introduction-Zohar/dp/9657222044). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 06:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry for the delayed response. The tree of life model has its roots in Genesis itself and Moses knew of the keys of the oral Torah to make use of practical kabbalah and succeeded in ascending very high as he knew divine names the angels did not. Kabbalah, again, if you haven't seen my [older post](https://www.reddit.com/r/kabbalah/comments/31ygex/i_have_a_question_about_the_kabbalic_conception/), is an oral tradition passed down originating with the prophets and slowly written down over time in such a manner so the next generation has access to the knowledge of the previous generation, but in such a way so as that only the worthy could make use of it, due to its immense power, so it's preserved properly and not corrupted along the way. Most attribute Sefer Yetzeriah to Avraham Avinu. The book of Adam spoke of souls of the future including Messiah, which fell into the hands of King Solomon, where he wrote about what he read in the book of Adam, which made its way into the Zohar. Reading where the diagram comes from, there's various Kabbalistic schools of thought. For example Lurianic Kabbalah via the Ari z"l came after the Zohar. The Zohar, which appeared in the 13th century via Moses de Leon, ascribed the work to Rabbi Shimon bar Yochai of the 2nd century. Rabbi Shimon bar Yochai in turn was one of the most eminent disciples of Rabbi Akiva of the 1st century. Rabbi Akiva was one of the last in possession of the prophetic keys as per the four which entered Pardes story. So where it comes from and who do you credit is a matter of how well teachings were preserved and who you recognize as the originator despite them crediting their teachings to their teacher. The question is then if they developed their own system or taught what their teacher taught them. Ultimately when you track back tradition so far, the oral Torah was much stronger back then, so it's almost certain that the diagram of the sefirot has its origins with the school of the early prophets, going back as far as you want to credit whoever discovered or was taught the initial system. If Avraham Avinu was indeed the author of Sefer Yetzeriah, as he is traditionally attributed, "Ten are the numbers of the ineffable Sephiroth, ten and not nine, ten and not eleven." (a sign he knew of two systems of the sefirot, one with keter and one with da'at) then this would be the prime candidate for the oldest surviving source for the system of the Sefirot as Avraham Avinu predated even Moses if Genesis could be credited provided there was an oral tradition surrounding it. Is Avraham Avinu the originator of the sefirot? Probably not. As the sapphire staff of Moses has a symbolic lineage passing from teacher to student as mentioned in Sefer HaYashar with an amazing history. Adam, after he was expelled from the Garden of Eden, took this staff when he began to till the soil. Then it reached Noach, then Sheim, then Avraham - Yitzhak - Yaakov who gave it to Yoseif when he came to Egypt. After his death, the Pharaoh had it brought to his palace where Yisro stole it for himself and anchored it in the ground of his garden. Where Moses claimed it (King Arthur style, wonder who copied who) and was given Tzipporah. (wish finding my soulmate was that easy) The word for sapphire in Hebrew is  which is related to the word  (to count) and thus  (enumeration) and  (sefirot / enumerations). Thus you can see the system of the sefirot was probably handed down with the staff teacher to student as whoever had the staff in a particular generation was the sole leader of the generation and also had prophecy. Thus how did they gain prophecy? (what is that staff in your hand?) Avraham discovered God's existence by himself without help by anyone, as Moshiach will do in the future, I read somewhere. So if the system of the sefirot is related to the sapphire staff, it seems Adam, the first man, who was a prophet, was the first in possession of it. Did he invent it himself? Did he take it from Gan Eden? Or was he created a prophet with the teachings built into him? Did an angel teach him? Whatever the case, the system of the sefirot must've originated in the upper worlds and entered the hands of man through someone with access to the upper worlds.

With all that out of the way, the Bahir is pretty old, 1st century attributed to Nehunya ben HaKanah. But Sefer Yetzirah is apparently the earliest extant book on Jewish esotericism, and as it mentions the sefirot, then it would be the earliest verifiable source as Avraham predated the 1st century by almost 2 millennia: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sefer_Yetzirah

Edit:
You might also find this answer up your alley as per the diagrams:
https://www.reddit.com/r/kabbalah/comments/4xngal/which_is_the_correct_tree_of_life/d6ixhww/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 13:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's start by trying to understand what is actually being stated: Yud () is spelled Yud-vav-dalet () and by taking the Vav and Dalet from it, you can form the letter Hei(). Note that Yud(chochmah) and Hei(Bina) are referencing the Tetragrammaton just as the four worlds correspond its letters. What's being said here is whether Atzilut, the Yud, is the root of Briyah, the Hei, as when Yod is spelled out (Yud-Vav-Dalet) then it's able to create the letter Hei. The answer to this, quite simply, is yes, as the Zohar states. The question then is how can a Kabbalistic book come later and contradict it? Rather, we need to re-read it to really understand what's being stated.

Kabbalah, in my opinion, can be summarized in one word: Tzimtzum (constriction). Each of the worlds have their own set of Sefirot, ad infinitum. Rather step back to Ein Sof and the creation of light on the first day: Ohr Ein Sof. Now we have light. Understand this light, the light of the first day, is not a physical light. Kabbalah speaks in terms of "the language of the branches" (as we're down here in the physical where the branch points at its root somewhere within the spiritual). Light, then, points at something in the upper worlds. Not sun light, rather the light which emanates from Ein Sof. This isn't to say there's something separate from Ein Sof, so as to create a separation from Him, God forbid. God's unity with creation is beyond creation's ability to understand as no thought can encompass Him as the part cannot comprehend the whole. We can, however, understand in a manner of reaching without reaching, though. Now, metaphorically speaking, a prism can be used to turn white light into a rainbow. Just like that, Ohr Ein Sof can be filtered (constricted) into an array of colors (the sefirot). But does blue emanate from red or does it emanate from the original light itself? Understand that the 10 sefirot are taken from the 10 sayings in Genesis. Thus, then, let there be light and there was light corresponds the first of the 10 sefirot: Keter(Gen 1:3). The division of light from darkness also happened on the first day. There was evening and there was morning: day one. Note that the sun wasn't created yet until the 4th day. The days in Genesis are purely spiritual days in reference to the spiritual light which the physical light down here points at as per the language of the branches which awaits the righteous in the world to come. These weren't normal earthly days despite that popular error in understanding. It doesn't matter how big the rabbi, each rabbi has their territory of Torah study which they're good at; and to trying to understand Genesis without Kabbalistic understanding of the structure of creation, is to err greatly and to mislead as you can't fully explain what's going on as one needs to first hear the explanation before they can give it, and that explanation is found nowhere better than Kabbalah. In the Talmud we often encounter disagreements between various rabbis such as Hillel and Shammai. Then we have people like the Posek HaDor to act as a decision maker between the two rabbis. Yet this style of decision making doesn't prevent the tendency of "two Jews three opinions" as anyone can voice their opinion on the matter, and if they're respected enough, boom, you have another opinion to argue over. We don't see any sort of "you're right and you're wrong" kind of decision making in Judaism as the disagreements are usually all in gray areas which aren't necessarily mutually exclusive. But there are also areas which are mutually exclusive which we must pick and choose who is right and who is wrong. The case of Genesis is one of them. Either they were normal earthly days as we're used to, or something purely spiritual we have no comprehension of, except the worthiest of the Kabbalists. As someone enlightened that knows his way around the upper worlds: I'll tell you, the correct answer is the latter. But believe what you want or need to believe to keep at your own healthy pace. Moving on: The division between the upper and lower "waters": Chochmah(Gen 1:6) [etc....](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sephirot#Rabbinic_significance) As we know, the four letters of the divine name correspond the four elements (not the periodic table elements as water is hydrogen and oxygen while fire isn't even an element. Think photosynthesis instead). As "waters" is referred to in the plural here, we know that as the divine name has two Heis, that Hei is water. So, that means Yud(Chochmah) is fire, which makes sense as it's closer to Keter(Ohr). Let's rephrase the question: where did the lower world come from? Did it come directly from Ohr? Or did it emanate from the world above it? The verse answers that for us: "Let there be a firmament in the midst of the Waters, and let it divide the Waters from the Waters." So, what is this firmament? How do we step from the upper hei to the lower hei? Ah, with the 6(Vav) sefirot of Zeir Anpin. I've read that those that understand this topic, between the separation between the upper and lower waters, aren't supposed to go into detail explaining it, so I'll stop here short before I make too many connections so you don't err in your understanding as there's a lot of prerequisites in theology you should be savvy with, and have a deep Yiras Hashem before discussing such topics. I probably already went too deep here, so I'll provide a link to one of my previous posts in the hope that you'll become familiar with some of the preliminary topics to cover what I already said. There's a lot in Kabbalah to understand so as not to err, and this older post of mine should bring you up to speed as per pace differences: 
https://www.reddit.com/r/kabbalah/comments/31ygex/i_have_a_question_about_the_kabbalic_conception/

So, with all this said, whatever you understood keep; and discard everything you didn't. As nothing can be said about Ein Sof at all. In regard to a direct answer to the question, the topic of tzimtzum as explained in Kabbalah answers it head one, but the topic is rather lengthy. The following image, if you understand it carefully, explains it very well: http://www.newkabbalah.com/images/ein.jpg (don't worry, despite the domain name newkabbalah, this image was laid out with military precision and as authentic as it gets) So once you've located the Kav(line) in the picture, you'll see it's the link between the Sefirot. But you shouldn't think this Kav creates a direct link between Malchut(this world) and Ohr Ein Sof in such a way as to completely fill this world with Ohr as it would cause the nothingness to get filled back with somethingness which was constricted (As per the Baal Shem Tov, to where did God constrict Himself? To the divine letters.) We already know that God is the only Absolute and all else depends upon Him, and thus, if God so pleased, heaven forbid, He could un-constrict Himself and cause all of creation to collapse back to whence it came. Rather, the Kav(line), in the manner of tzimtzum, diminishes in radiance (like [degree of truth](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fuzzy_logic) the further away from Ohr Ein Sof it goes. Thus, you see, when the Kav goes through Keter, the beam of "light" gets filtered by Keter and we have Chochmah. Then the beam of light gets filtered by Chochmah and we have Bina etc. The question, then, is what is the material of the sefirot that it can filter the light. The sefirot have no power in somethingness nor in nothingness rather only in the constant changing or moving from one to the other like a battery draining in power until it's recharged. Note this is not like a resistor which keeps a constant voltage, rather the sefirot need the quality to be able to fluctuate lest they get sucked into one or the other because there is no middle, it's either one or the other - meaning it's either constricted or not at that particular time. Just as a branch when it is cut from its source, the plant keeps most of its green features like before it was cut. Only a day later you'll notice the plant showing signs of dying. So too the sefirot. Going back on the material aspect, I recall reading in The Guide for the Perplexed "Whence was the earth created? He took snow under the throne of glory and threw it." whatever this means metaphorically. No hints on this one, if you followed my post you'll figure it out on your own.

So once you understand all this fluctuation, you'll see the two don't contradict one another as per the relationship of Gen 1:6 and Gen 1:9 and the relationship of the Sefirot coming into being via "sayings" and the nature of such sayings to Ein Sof as per His mysterious (from our perspective) unity. Short answer: Yes. One is simply stating God's unity, that you can't learn out from here that one came out from the other as per the detail with the letters mentioned. Rather, this is indeed the case, as per the Zohar, just for a different reasoning.

Hope that makes sense. If anyone disagrees on any of this, toss in a reply, don't be shy, that way I can answer you, or you can teach me. Otherwise I'm a pretty savvy Kabbalist that meditates on his learnings, you can trust my system for the most-part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 22:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surprised this got a downvote. I'm a deep-thinker, programmer, and future author if it helps anyone relate to it. A variant of the pen is mightier than the sword. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 22:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The two most powerful warriors are patience and time." - Leo Tolstoy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 22:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kevin Sorbo as Hercules </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 20:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Final Fantasy 7, it just came out when I was finishing off middle school and my mom was still around-and-about. When Final Fantasy 8 came out, I was in my freshman year in high school year when she was battling an advanced stage of breast cancer. She had a serious diet coke/pepsi drinking problem back then that she couldn't control and would hide it in the trunk of her car. She was under a lot of stress at the time. My grandma was at a very old age when (breast?) cancer eventually took her life too, but my mom went first. And believe it or not, my bro went even before her, seeing his mom suffering, getting dumped by his girlfriend, battling depression and schizophrenia at the same time wasn't easy for him. Yeah, so Final Fantasy 7 was the last decent game I was playing before my life went into a nosedive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 11:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A change of priorities </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 09:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With unpopular products like Windows Phone, and crappy operating systems like Windows 10, even I have been trying to migrate away from Windows after 2 decades of loyalty due to the all bullshit they're tossing into their operating system these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 09:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Work on [boosting](https://zenhabits.net/25-killer-actions-to-boost-your-self-confidence/) your self-confidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 09:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cake icing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 12:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> K.I.T.T. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 12:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The stairs to the basement </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 12:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that dyslexiaic is taking over the web </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 12:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 11:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uber/Lyft </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 11:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dump her and find something better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 11:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> people like people who like people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 11:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taxes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 11:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coming to terms with your poor health that you're eventually going to die, probably alone, and broke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 11:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> monty python and the holy grail </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 11:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get an injection from the future making me immortal dr who style.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 11:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zippo, if I wind up going it's because I got dragged into it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 11:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is the song that doesn't end... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 11:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :error, could not list movie because it does not exist: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 11:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Healthy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 10:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honesty more than anything, healthy, weighs her words, and firm about her beliefs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 10:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a million reasons why I should give you up
But the heart wants what it wants </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 10:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Create a custom program to implement the public/private key encrypting algorithm used by HTTPS, then encrypt files you'd like to protect using the program with the public key, and decrypt it using the program with the private key. Then store the encrypting program, the decrypting program, and your encrypted file in different places. Finally strengthen the security on the accounts you store the files under, such as by enabling 2-step login, using a strong password, and changing your password frequently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 09:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Life sucks, then you die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 08:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Daniel Tosh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you get when you cross Johnny Depp with Nicolas Cage? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 16:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Johnny Cage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 11:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What entry-level programming job pays 110k a year?  Is this assuming a bachelor's degree? I've been a full stack LAMP web developer for over a decade now and lucky to find work for 80-90k. But entry-level, seriously? Programming what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The US currency looks like Monopoly money </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 09:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 06:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why couldn't they choose an icon for Edge that doesn't look like another Internet Explorer version...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 06:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm dying lmfao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 05:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna vote for the Cleveland Browns.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which NFL team do you consider to be the worst? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 04:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 11:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A nerf gun. They'll shoot everybody with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 08:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasting hours of time on the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 07:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Microsoft "works" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 07:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Answering my ex's text messages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 07:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My manner of moving around the house. Like if I get up from a chair, I push the chair backwards and turn it to the side while I proceed to spin with the chair until I'm facing 180 degree from where I was originally pointed. Then I proceed to spin the chair 270 degrees while I push it back in under the table. Another example is if I'm going to get something out of the fridge, I face my back to the fridge, while I proceed to pull it open with my left hand on the inside of the handle, and my right hand on the outside of the handle. I pull it in a sudden motion as I spin 90 degrees and once the door reaches the exact angle I wanted it to, I stop the door with my right hand that was already on the outside of the handle and continue turning another 90 degrees until I'm facing the fridge and my right hand is behind me keeping the door open. Once I find the desired item, I do the spin move in reverse to close the fridge and use my left hand to stop the door from slamming. Another example is how I walk the dog. If I'm holding the leash with my right hand, I wrap the leash around my arm for more grip in my hand, and if the dog tries to go behind me and around me, essentially wrapping my arm around my back, so I spin my body with the dog until my arm isn't hyperextending around my back, then once I've freed my arm, I'd be directly behind the dog so I pull 45 degrees backwards to the right, so the dog winds up to my right, so I can continue holding the leash in my right hand. I believe many years of practicing katas has crept its way into my daily life due to my desire for efficient movements. On the other hand, this manner of movement probably isn't as rare as I think to other martial artists like we see in karate kid "paint the fence. wax on wax off." and the "karate kid" the more recent knock off which was closer to kung fu with the "jacket on, jacket off" scene. It's completely different movements than "wax on, wax off" but the idea is it's a similar mindset to approaching daily life. But I believe each person develops their own unique way of moving around to some degree based on the body type, health, mentality, training, wisdom, efficiency, and goals etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 06:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My ex... wish she'd move on already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 06:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Made me laugh, take my upvote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 03:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [King Arthur and the Knights of Justice](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=USUucZVnno0). It was what I looked forward to watching when I got back home from school as a kid. I got fooled into watching it multiple times in the hopes of catching the ending. It never came as the show got cancelled mid-plot and continued to air.
  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 03:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like what happens when a Chuck Norris joke meets its polar opposite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 14:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're so useless, I'm not going to waste my time insulting you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 11:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [cookieclicker](http://orteil.dashnet.org/cookieclicker/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 10:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many subreddits that keep up with every kind of topic out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 10:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Terrorism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 10:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pervy Sage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 10:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> intoxicate yourself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 10:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Electricity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 10:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Common Core Homework </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 10:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> white fish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 10:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably 20 or so [unless one of them was a 2nd degree black belt](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d_8ao3o5ohU). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 10:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many guys did you screw? How often do you screw?  
Have you ever experimented? What are your fetishes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 09:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 08:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call up some friends to help claim some of it. Create an operation to launder it. Then form a company with the mission of revolutionizing web development. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 08:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fire ant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 00:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Self-identity otherwise a large portion of the straight population would be gay or bi for having experimented.  No matter what label you choose, there's a degree of truth to each label. This is where the [Kinsey scale](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kinsey_scale) comes into play. Perhaps experimenting might make a person gayer but not necessarily gay or bi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 11:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 11:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haters gonna hate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 11:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An activewear T-shirt I found on land's end that was marked down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 10:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Play in the NBA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 10:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time and patience will get you to the top. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 10:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rice and liquid aminos(soy sauce) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 10:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neapolitan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 10:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The amount I get paid per hour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 10:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hang around someone prettier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 10:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dental issues </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 10:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have all your teeth and nails pulled. Then be hung upsidedown with your hands tied behind your back and have spiders crawl all over you in an unbearably hot room. Then get pepper sprayed in your eyes, and have an annoying buzzing noise at a subtle pitch mess with your head where it's coming from. Then have diarrhea forced down your throat and all the hair on your body ripped off simultaneously. Then be scratched all over your body and have all types of impurities enter the wounds, and starved for a day. Then force-fed and starved again, for a week, and be exposed to the sun until every inch of your flesh is sunburned. Then be forced to stare into the sun until you went blind. Then be exposed to very loud sounds until you go deaf. Have your tongue cut off, and your cheeks pierced. Then have your arms and legs ripped off. And finally get waterboarded to death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 09:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being around your crush. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 09:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The front-end when I'm developing the back-end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 23:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The day of my 2008 meditation. Would be nice to re-experience it so I can document it better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 23:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some sort of Jesus figure and go around healing people. Wake up the next day super rich after having collected loads of cash from all the people I healed. Then get whacked so hard by the IRS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 22:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ass to the future </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 21:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's less qualified than even Trump :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 21:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About as feasible as Deez Nuts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 09:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> kim kardashian </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 09:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strive to do one thing meaningful per day that makes the whole day worth living. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 09:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> anxiety so you can get a prescription in the form of green happiness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 09:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Browse the net in 4G </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 09:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The smell of used retainers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 09:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> looking up scissoring without feeling guilty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 09:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First 25 seconds or so of evanescence's [imaginary](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=odatDWByonw). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 09:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Party tricks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
