<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1239</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 08:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did not expect this much hate for trying to avoid looking like a liar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 06:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, that's useful to know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 06:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like fun. Thanks for the reply! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 05:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant after the fact. Like, between getting in and before I actually pass the SF course. Am I considered infantry in the interim?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 04:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, so what happens if I'm told to do some PT task ("drop and give me 50" for example) and I am unable to fully finish due to muscle fatigue or some other factor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 10:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Close. It's the second greatest. The first greatest was Patrick Stewart as Jean-Luc Picard. If you don't know him you should check him out he's a great actor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 09:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm an 18x SF recruit. I ship on Tuesday for Basic, and I'm wondering what I should have as my flair. I don't want to press the Special Forces flair and look like an ass. Should I choose that or infantry? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 23:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because people give you free stuff and cater to your every whim. I cannot be expected to treat this power with any responsibility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 18:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have already accepted that modern pop hits will one day be listened to like oldies from the 40's are today. 

That's right kiddies. Justin Bieber and Kanye West will one day be listened to by old folks like old folks nowadays listen to Dean Martin and Frank Sinatra. 

Honestly do you even care about avoiding the apocalypse at this point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 04:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn. You Canadians are scary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 04:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm. Worked deli in high school. I would much rather sweat my ass off in Afghanistan than relive that experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 04:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I almost always get thanks from these people. I get more thanks from people asking for change than I do from patients and their families when I'm working as a medic(in fact I rarely ever get a sincere thank you no matter how bad the call is), and perhaps more surprisingly, probably the same is true when I'm in my military uniform (which is stereotypically a beacon for people to go throw gratitude at). I figure most of the time I'm helping someone screwed over by some circumstance I'm not aware of.

I'm more pissed off by entitled assholes that not only refuse to partake in charity(you're not legally or otherwise required to give anything of course), but take it further by operating under the prosperity gospel and act like anyone asking for any help at all is some evil, freeloading con man and less than human, whilst they, despite all their flaws, are just a perfect human being who doesn't owe anybody anything ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 07:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do this every time I'm in this situation. 

I'll also say out load "Great chat" if I try to talk to someone and they just blow me off/walk past me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 11:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes sense. Maybe it would have been more constructive to ask how often the antics seen in said reels are intentional, or if they're a rare occurrence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious]How much do directors/the crew get pissed off by the antics shown in "blooper reels"? Does it get out of hand? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 10:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 21:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd never make it as an EMT. We have to put up with it all the time. 

Except there's usually also some form of poop involved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 01:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look to his 3rd End of Faith podcast, it's very much like what you are asking for. He details the inquisition, witch trials, persecution of other religions (namely the Jews) and other topics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 19:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I can tell its part of the numerous bits of Trek lore that's been pulled off terribly thus far and hasn't really been fixed yet. Thanks everyone for your replies . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 18:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been in medic uniform grabbing lunch between calls and had a woman storm up to me:

Lady: "excuse me, where's the peanut butter?"

Me, with a Jim face, display my full uniform, complete with big patches that say "EMT" "AMBULANCE" and medical equipment poking out of my pockets. 

After she seemed totally oblivious nonetheless:"Ma'am I don't work here"

She gave a loud "UGH!" And stormed off in a fury(past the actual uniformed employees stocking the aisle), allowing me to continue my Jim impression. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 18:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CPR requires sudden, intense pressure applied rapidly. Holding a wound does not require that. Think of it like an egg. Try squeezing one, you won't damage it no matter how hard you squeeze. Tap it on something ever so lightly and it will crack open. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 20:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might be the most passive-aggressive LPT to date. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 18:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an EMT, the only thing you can do is check for bleeding and apply pressure if you see it and holding/supporting the head in place so that it is immobilized. Don't roll them over except if they are in danger of not being able to breathe. Let EMTs do the moving when they arrive. They could have spinal injury, which means the last thing you want is to shift their back or neck. Without a license to practice, there's not much you can, or should, do. Don't try to be the hero if you aren't qualified, you'll just make things worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was Star Trek history (the Eugenics Wars) retconned during ENT? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 00:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now we all know that TOS had laid out a very different late 20th/early 21st century than we actually wound up with, which makes sense given that it was far off at the time. The events described as having taken place were quite incompatible with our real world history, most specifically things like the Eugenics Wars. However, I can't help but recall that there was an arc during ENT that involved shapeshifters going back in time to help the Nazis win WWII or something absurd like that. In the culmination of this arc, we are shown visions of Earth circa the 20th into the 21st century, complete with Bill Clinton, GWB, and 9/11. Now, clearly, this is a departure from the original established timeline of events Star Trek was abiding by in favor of a more real-world depiction of history. I'm curious, was this a deliberate retcon, or was the time line messed up during the arc? It's hard to take the canonizing of our real world modern history and combine that with the original series', incredibly deadly Eugenics conflicts supposedly happening at about the same time.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 17:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only way to take on the toughest enemies in dark souls is to do it while playing "Danger Zone" by Kenny Loggins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 00:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're going to make a joke about tragedies, at least make them funny. It's the line between edgy and hilarious. You're on the lame side of that line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
