<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1565</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 10:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the owner of Weed Man....I mean the whole goddamn thing, and he is the nicest, most honest person you will ever meet. If you have feedback on one of the franchises, email the company. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 23:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having been through multiple lawnmowers, including using gas stabilizer, the ONLY thing that I have found to work, and have also had suggested to me by the people who I have had work on previous lawnmower engines, is to use the high grade gas. Here in Canada they suggest the highest grade from Shell. Haven't had a problem since. Including today when it started on the 3rd pull with last year's gas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are speaking specifically of SL, I too own it and love owning it. I agree that it's time will come. But they are different with their B2B model and that is exactly what I mean by being different from their competition.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed to an extent. Risk does not guarantee return. It guarantees risk. OP said he wants to eventually get back into the big three. So if OP puts his investable assets into smaller, much riskier companies and they drop, then he won't have that capital to eventually put back into the bigger names. Risk management is still very important in this sector.

As for index investing.....I believe that is the next major problem brewing in the markets. You cannot have such a large proportion of market participants (both retail and institutional) owning the exact same thing in the exact same percentage forever. That is not what makes the market work. What happens when everyone owns the same thing and runs for the exit at the same time? Proper active management should and will always have a place in the market and will regain favour again after the next major crash. My humble opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, but do you do it at the expense of owning them or in addition to it? ACB alone will be selling 100M grams a year at full capacity, and if they average $6 a gram, that's $600M in revenue. Focusing on oil could drive that higher given the higher revenue that oil generates. To me this should warrant a market cap many times higher than where it is currently. Maybe not though? Maybe 1.5 times sales is a sufficient market cap? If so, that's fully priced in now thus requiring something else to make the company more valuable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting approach, and certainly could work out to be right. BUT, when buying the smaller companies you take on much more risk that they cannot compete and therefore possibly end up failing, or at least not really being much of a player. Not saying that WILL happen, but it COULD. Keep in mind the massive amounts of money the big three are spending on their own expansion and production. The more they produce and handle themselves, the less likely they will be to want to acquire additional production through other companies. Keep in mind that acquisitions come at a cost premium, and as the industry unfolds and gets going, low cost will be very important, as with any commodity. So acquiring other expensive production may not be of interest. The small companies you focus on should have a very specific niche or something that really differentiates them from the rest that would warrant the investment of precious capital from the larger players and that would offer the bigger company a distinct and unique competitive advantage against the others. I think owning a core of the big guys and adding a few smaller players around the edges is what I would do.

But what the fuck do I know. This is all just my opinion and I have lost money at times and missed great opportunities like everyone else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who's scruffy looking? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
