<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2482</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 18:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely, you can.  You can be present for the cremation if you request it.

You can't actually SEE anything.  They put the body in a cardbox box and slide it into the cremation oven, and that's it.  There aren't windows to see into it or anything.  

You wouldn't be allowed to stay for the "clean-up" after the process is done, however.  (typically) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, that's a lot of pressure.  

"Make the shot, or your buddies die" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 14:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right!  Nice catch, thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 05:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just surprised that Trump is doing something without telegraphing it first via Twitter.

If he learns how to use a door handle, we're all fucked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 22:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohhhh, watch out everybody!  We got someone that has more than one friend here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 22:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whatever life/animal/whatever they find first, they really should name it Clarke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 22:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guarantee you that quite a few people/organizations are "saving" President Trump's tweets the instant they are posted.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 22:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's...uh..."death knell".  

Which is redundant, as a knell is the sound of a bell wrung specifically for a funeral or a death.

A death nail is a tragic trip to the Emergency Room. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 22:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You assume you have a clear path in front or behind you.  You may be boxed in.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 21:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a pretty great tip, actually.  
I sit in on interviews daily (HR rep), and the best interviews are the ones where the applicant seems genuinely excited to be there.  They leave a lasting impression even after they depart the room.

The BEST best applicants are the ones that are so motivated and excited to begin, that they infect the panel members with that motivation also.  
Remember, the panel themselves are probably bored out of their minds...after listening to people for lengthy amounts of time, that they know shouldn't even be there in the first place.  The applicant that can perk the panel members up, can motivate and convince the members how great they'd be in the position....those are the people that get selected 99 times out of 100.
...and I don't mean, just by selling yourself by talking about your great accomplishments.  Anyone can do that.  True, genuine, enthusiasm.  It's hard to fake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 21:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you need lessons on the use of a spoiler tag?  Yeesh! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 21:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just read it...was sort of underwhelming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 19:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't you heard?  It's now the DM~~V~~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those letters also make up 'Enlist' and 'Tinsel'.  Doesn't mean I'm going to volunteer to go to the North Pole and make toys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhh, the wonderful fluidity and relativism of the English language.

Yes, a law enforcement officer (LEO) is considered a civilian, compared to a member of the armed forces.

Also yes, a non-LEO citizen is considered a civilian, compared to a member of the LEO community.

So, that being said...
Is an LEO a civilian, when compared to a soldier?  Yes.
Is a citizen a civilian, when compared to an LEO?  Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No they aren't.

civilian
svilyn/
noun
noun: civilian; plural noun: civilians

    1.
    a person not in the armed services or the police force. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 14:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right.  This.

When I heard about him not accepting a salary, the very first think I thought of was "Well, of course he doesn't want a salary...because then people might be able to force him to show his tax records."  

Mark my words...in about a year, there will be SOME kind of story about how President Trump says that his taxes aren't important or a matter of record, "because I didn't even accept a salary for doing this important job." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 05:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, absolutely.  My comment wasn't even a joke.  

President Trump using ~~his~~ our military might to take all eyes off his inept Presidency is my largest fear in life at the moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 01:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dear Mr. President,

Please don't nuke someone because you're a petulant child and need to feel powerful after being shown to be such a loser.  

Thank you.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just keep in mind, every pony grows up to be a horse.  

LPT: Horses are expensive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I figured all dogs just had a ruff time understanding each other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're lion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a Blackvue 650, dual channel (both front and rear cameras). it cost an arm and a leg, but whatever.

I used to use a Mobius action cam mounted forward facing, but I had issues where I noticed that it sometimes failed to turn on when i started the engine, depending on ambient temperature, etc.  I switched to the Blackvue so that I would have confidence it would work when I needed it (dash cam is something I want to not think about unless I need it later), so far so good.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100% sure you mean Disney World, not Disney Land. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really makes me wonder why some reposts get upvotes (like this one), and others get nothing.

Chaos theory! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I caught a minor fender bender right in front of me, about a year ago.  Nothing else too interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 19:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have a downvote for being so honest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 19:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great story Donald...now, back on topic... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 19:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PM me.  Totally not CPS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 19:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In some districts/areas, sure.  Not every disctrict/area has the same workload, however, and case workers can give more...personalized...attention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 19:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL: Vikings spoke and wrote modern day English </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 19:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's 95% the reason I got a dash cam for my car...to be able to catch things like that.  The other 5% is to protect myself from a He-said/She-said accident situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The point is...if someone was stealing your credit card, they probably were just going to charge something on it.  

BUT, if they see the PIN, they may be tempted to just go get cash from an ATM instead...and get the card locked up from your deliberate honey-pot PIN.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this point...PIN and ATM have basically become words in and of themselves.  Just like how IHOP used to stand for International House of Pancakes....now, it's just IHOP.  Like, that's literally the name of the restaurant chain.  IHOP.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 21:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty shrewd of Intel.

Worldwide free advertisement, for just doing something they were going to do anyways.

Expand manufacturing operation that already exists...millions.

Opportunity to make the business in the Oval Office, ensuring maximum exposure and support?  Priceless </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 20:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why complicate things by adding a generation between it?

Not everyone will have a son or daughter, but everyone is a son or daughter.

*shrug* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mildly Interesting Fact:  Many law enforcement departments in the U.S. have an un-written (or even a written in some cases) policy to keep their vehicles always above half a tank of fuel, just in case they have to participate in a vehicle chase. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 20:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least Pence isn't (hopefully) being pinched by Putin because of Trump's indiscretions in a hotel room. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 20:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that Trump doesn't fundamentally understand just HOW MUCH the majority of the U.S., and the world for that matter, are against him and think he's a buffoon.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 16:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This interview says otherwise.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Dn1ZK2kcfQ8)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 15:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 15:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found the Russian account </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 15:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're simplifying a very complicated subject.   

You have no right to kill a man passing you on the street by saying you felt afraid for your life, because he looked intimidating.

You also have to have a jury of your peers agree that any reasonable person would have been afraid for their lives in the same situation.  
That typically requires motive, acts, and a weapon.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 15:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really nice when the facts come out after the incident, over the next few days, and your prejudice was confirmed, eh?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 23:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, they'll be safe behind their wall to the south. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 23:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being scared and afraid does not legally justify deadly force. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 23:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow.  News flash, not everyone that's a French citizen is a guy, or white, or a non-muslim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 17:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 7yo said "It's doing the the Dabb!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 15:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Third column from the left, third person back...plaid shirt. Dude? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 15:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, they are really going for the Plausible Deniability route when the ball is deflated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 15:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plot twist: GIF is in reverse, and "Mommy, I found a puppy!" is heard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 23:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, I hope Putin washes his hands after having his hands in so many puppets... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the U.S., we put the month first.  That's dated May 8th, 2013.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 21:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Into their website's nutrition calculator...put...

6oz Victoria Filet Mignon

Side Blue Cheese Chopped Salad

Side Grilled Asparagus


You're welcome. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 21:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't that awfully biased of you to assume that the person is an immigrant, without further information?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that's a completely different type of wrong headline...as it would be inferring information that is not known.  This guy could possibly (unlikely) just be a mentally unstable person, with no ties to terrorism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sad day when in my quiet moments...instead of hoping for no war or conflict, I instead hope that the war stays conventional, and doesn't go nuclear.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then you need to find a more accurate timepiece with more significant digits. =)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Concealed Carry......you're not doing it right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL: 100% of Dental Hygienists polled recommend Mentadent as the toothpaste you should use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great breakdown! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have no way to tell or control whether another human will die before the execution is carried out.  Even if you made the decision to perform the execution, and then immediately pull the trigger half a second later...someone, somewhere, may have died during that half second. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
