<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1863</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL there are at least 61 "First Church of Christ, Scientist" notable enough to have a wikipedia page </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 03:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 03:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, I didn't leave a link. But I thought it was clear enough from the context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 13:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you read the post? Did you do the (I realize offensive) act of clicking on a story? They are gone.  And as I mentioned above, I did a quick Google and didn't see an announcement. You're welcome to do some research of your own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 19:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it used to be pretty prominently featured on the homepage, but over the years it got more and more neglected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 19:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're exceptional. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 14:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The $200,000+ pricetag will be well worth the envy of your neighbors at the country club. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 13:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a good chart in the article showing by time of day by week, but here's the explanation:
The most likely time for a baby to be born is Tuesday afternoon, closely followed by Wednesday and Thursday afternoons. The least likely time for a baby to be born, shaded in green, is very early Sunday or Monday morning.
 There are primarily three ways to give birth: vaginal delivery, induced delivery and Cesarean section. Looking at the time of day when births occur using each method shows very different patterns (see graph here).

Vaginal births happen more or less evenly spaced out during the day, with a slight bump in the early morning hours. C-section births typically happen either around 8:00 am or noon. Induced deliveries typically happen around 3:00 pm.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the most babies are born in the afternoons on Tuesdays, Wednesdays, and Thursdays in the US, to make it more convenient for everyone amid rising c-section rates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 13:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 13:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.boston.com/community/forums </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 20:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, because there has been no connection between boston.com and NYT since John Henry bought the Globe three years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 20:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AFAIK there has been no announcement. A quick Googling didn't turn up anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 19:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it may have been gone for a while without me noticing. I did notice as well on my first visit in months that they had also killed off BDCwire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boston.com has killed comments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 17:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure we'll all miss the deep, intelligent commentary on issues of the day (the lingering forums have a message that they will be closed on May 31 and not archived) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New solar panel technology using common materials instead of rare earths could make solar panels far cheaper </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 17:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 21:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jokes like that will help you get ahead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 17:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  After the blade did its work, Raleighs body was buried but his head was given to his wife Elizabeth, who was just a teensy bit quirky about it. According to Shepherd of the Ocean, a Raleigh bio by J.H. Adamson and H.F. Holland, She had [the head] embalmed and kept it by her side, frequently inquiring of visitors if they would like to see Sir Walter. Many sources say that Bess lugged the head around with her at all times until her own death 29 years later </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL after Sir Walter Raleigh was beheaded, his widow kept the embalmed head by her side for 22 years, and would ask guests if they would like to meet him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 17:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 13:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An interesting explainer, and it clarifies two key phenomena that drive me crazy: people braking that cause 'shockwave' backups, and people merging too early. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Traffic Forms, And How Changing Driver Habits Could Help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 13:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
