<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3288</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most games are decided because of a lack off balancing and the fact that 70 % av players are fricking leavers and cowards. People even leave games when we are winning! 

They REALLY need to fix this in steel division. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 11:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are usually one or two servers up. The skyttergrav.se servers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 11:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once every few months I play. But most of the time Wargame: red dragons fullfills my cold war/ modern day rts needs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 17:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6d/German-Turkish_Treaty_of_Friendship_and_Non-Aggression.jpg
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 13:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eZFOWdM-Noo
Rhodesian weapons and vehicles. Enough here to make a coalition deck of SA and Rhodesia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> South africa and Rhodesian vehicles and weapons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 13:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 12:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the attention to detail, better graphics, bounty hunter targets that move, getting the mood of the west right and such. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 12:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that game is gold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 15:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love Archs videos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah me too, got "The world of ice and fire" lore book last year, and since then I have been buying all the lore books I could find. Kong is ba far one of the best out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 10:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finally smart infatry. I hated the fact that inf in wargame would just stand in the open and get killed when I wasn`t looking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 10:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice to see the bomber! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 09:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either Renaissance or Victoria total war would be my gess. China could work but It would be kinda similar to shogun 2, and that game is still relatively new. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 08:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lolwut? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 08:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, things are moving really fast. I love it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 08:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice, never thought about that, I thought u could ony use in game screenshots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 08:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, me too! I had all but given up on ever getting the book untill i found it cheap on amazon and got it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 13:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RDR already has a huge lobby (the entire map), and just use hardcore to remove auto-aim and such. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 13:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of people still online last time I checker (a few months ago) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 13:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I`d radther we play a new character, and that Dutch`s gang will somehow be involved in the game, as quest givers and important figures, but that we, the players, are not directly part of their gang and crew. Maybe we could play a lawman hunting for them, while also being involved in other things and such? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The world of Kong - A natural history of skull island (one of the best fictional books ever) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 13:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 12:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool to see the surrendering soldiers, and it seems like infantry indeed will be able to use cover. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 12:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 12:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just hope they don`t go to familiar with the game, I was, and still am, kinda hoping for a bran new setting, and that the old gang members might play a role, but not be all about John martson and co again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It had to do with copyrights I think, apparently somone own the right to some of the ww2 vehicles still. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but can origin and steam players play togheter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 08:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sudden strikes looks badass, but they don`t sell it on steam. Maybe they sell it on gog though....? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 08:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too bad I can`t buy it anymore, they removed it from steam and other sites. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems kinda dated and wierd witht eh top-down view, but could be fun I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hm, too bad. The vietnam war is such and underused setting for games. There are rumors, however, that the next cod game will go back in time, maybe to Vietnam. And I hope DICE decided to make another Vietnam game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mot so much on the ps3, sadly. I only ever find games with 2 or 3 players, even on weekends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any other Vietnam war games that you would recomend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I`m one of the ufortunate souls who hasn`t recieved a beta code. and thought it would be a good idea to start a threat about other Vietnam war games that are out there. I already know a few, like Bf vietnam and BC2 Vietnam, and of course black ops 1. Are there any other Vietnam war games out there that you would recomend? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WW2 and other strategy games to play while we wait! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello all. I am sure you are just as hyped for Steel Division - Normandy 44 as I am, and the purpose of this thread is to make a list of other ww2 rts games that are worth playing and than can help us get through the long wait before Steel division releases.

Some games I would recomend:
The company of heroes series.
The blitzkrieg series (Haven`t played the third yet)
Men of war franchise.
Gates of hell (similar to men of war?
Soldiers: Arena (Remake of Soliders: heroes of ww2, which was the progenitor of the men of war series)
Sudden strike 4

i know there are other badass rts games out there, but At first i Think a list of ww2 games would do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could be used for ressuply duties, carry weapons across the map and a few soldiers. And the kilobri could be used as a recon/scout. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 12:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There isn`t very much informaation about them, but some of the helicopters entered service in 1941/42, so thye might very well have been used in the west front in 1944. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 12:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love to see the helicopters. They never get anny love in ww2 rts games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 12:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They wre actually build and used during ww2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 12:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AH, too bad. I would love some helicopters and unique units- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 12:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should be very limited in suply and have to be used at the correct time, but I would love it. No ww2 games ever include these unique weapons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
