<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject398</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you think it is possible that Donald Trump may have been ask to run for president and make outlandish headlines to take attention away from Bernie Sanders out of fear that he is gaining traction? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 03:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 03:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At 63 yrs old I have came to the times of one last chance and/or one last time and I have no way of knowing while it is happening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 03:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I would do first in this situation is go to the hotel management and explain the what is going on and see if you could volunteer work in exchange for a place to stay. Since you are an artist they may exchange a room for a mural or something but be willing to clean shit up if it keeps a roof over your head for a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BTW, How does it happen? If you think an opportunity is happening, just go with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently retired straight, very average looking M/63 hairstylist of 32 years. I have so many I don't even tell the stories because I wouldn't believe someone telling me so many. From the lesbian at a party on the coat bed with people coming in setting and talking to us, to the demure hot as hell clerk in the center of an open woman's clothing store, to local gym's head aerobic instructor. How about dropping something off a client's house she had left behind at my salon and ending up going at it in the open doorway with my car running in the driveway and her son in the next room? Or the time with the hot 20 year younger 110 lb blond twin on my lap in a Geo Storm at 55 mph at night on winding road. I mention she was a twin because... yep TWINS! Stripper? Been there more than once. In the tanning room in my busy salon, couple times, one time was with the other twin. Waking up in the middle of the night wondering who the woman was undressing in my dark bedroom... several times with different women. I could go on but like I said, I would stop believing you if you told me so many. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 19:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was sort of short circuited by Lightning once during an oldies concert while standing on the pitchers mound in Three Rivers Stadium. I don't know how close it hit but everything went black for me for a short while. Was still standing when I re-booted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious]What seemingly rare occurrence actually happens all the time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 18:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 01:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wedding soup </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] You are a character in a book who, on you own, comes to realize that when the story ends so does your existence... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 21:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 15:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 15:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your family has to be real scum cum lickers to stay with you after you steal a ball from a Grandma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 22:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alfred E. Newman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 17:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 63 yr old male here, just got back from the first extended travel of my life 5 weeks ago, 3 months in Santa Ana, El Salvador. When asked how my vacation was I answer "It was just another place where "I" lived." Discovered that if "I" don't have the energy to change what I don't like where "I" live, "I" won't change where "I" don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 16:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a problem with Katy. On a scale of 10 I would rate her a 9.5 for good looks. BUT, I find nothing sexy about her. She just does not exude any sexuality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 16:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My oldest son (43 years old now) made up "conflunked" around 6 years old. Whole family adopted it. All went well until he got in trouble for arguing with his teacher over it not being a real word that he used in an assignment in the 5th grade. We had never thought to tell him it wasn't a "real" word... because it was in our world. The meaning??? I think it is quite obvious. You tell me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who Pooped out side??? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 21:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 00:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, yes it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 05:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, thank you, I'm here every night through the rest of the week. And folks remember to tip your bartenders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 05:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry hugefish I thought you were dicking around. I'm not on vacation I'm living for three months in another country. I live like the locals who get by on lesson 750 a month. type travel into the search bar up there. You'll find subreddits with people budgeting $20 or less a day and traveling the world. Then there are sites like workaway .info where people will give you three meals and a bed to come and help them out so it can be free other than getting there.. If you're interested go check out a few other subreddits come on back and ask questions. As far as how do I live at home? I got a cheap place 525 a month I take in a roommate. I got a piece of shit car that I bought for $1000 on Craigslist and I have shit insurance on it 38 dollars a month. Keep the lights down low the electricity bill cheap buy most of my stuff at Goodwill. Took a part time job I don't need. Don't cash paychecks until the company start bitching that I'm holding too many. Use that money to travel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 04:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't buy no bling shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 04:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I usually over use them, I'm doing this on a phone, but fuck you very much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What I did to not go over budget while I'm here. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 01:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I set my daily budget at $25 usd for shelter and food while I'm out here. But just before I left for my trip I got a little nervous about being my age (62m) and just stepping off a plane with nowhere to stay and no one I know. So I made a reservation through AirB B at a very nice here in Santa Ana. While talking to my host Rosy, I explained that I was staying at least a month maybe more and I would go stir crazy just setting around doing tourist stuff and is there any things I could do to help out around the place while I am here. Turns out she is over whelmed and would love me to be her assistant during my stay but she is booked for the first 18 days and would I mind staying at her friends B B which he is just trying to start up. The cost still came out to $16.50 a day for room and breakfast so that really cut into my budget leaving $7.50 for both of my other meals per day. That can easily be done here but hey... I'm a fat guy. After a few days at Rosy's friend's b b I realized this fellow and his two sons were struggling some so I suggested we go to the super market and I would buy some groceries and if his house keeper would fix them we could all share. This was deemed a good idea by all. So, I filled up a cart with mostly native foods (had to buy so Oreos) and it came to $81. It works out to over 10 days within my budget but I have been told that it may be a few more that that and remember I am feeding four people. I now eat my meals in their humble home and am treated like family, no more eating alone on the veranda. And if it comes out to a little bit more than that, I don't care... I'm family. I'll make it up somewhere else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 19:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are correct it is in Central America just south of Guatemala on the west coast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 18:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay , yes I have three grown children who within the last five years have become comfortable and happy with their lives so I don't worry about them too much. I rent my home off of my older son who lives next door and even though its small I have moved into one room and take in roommates to reduce the cost. I took a low level low responsibility position in my son store that I helped him start and with Social Security starting last April it covered almost all my expenses and I was able to save almost all of my $10 an hour paychecks . Since the position was low level it was easy for me to take a three month sabbatical with the promise of my job when I come back. As for as my dog and cat there was a man in his forties at work who is trying to get back on his feet after a couple DUI's so I asked him to live in my place and take care of my animals until I return. I even asked him as a favor to me since he has just gotten his license back to drive my car for me while I'm gone . But the biggest thing that helped me prepare for this was becoming homeless in 05 and 06 and learning exactly how little I need in my life. I set travel as a priority in my life and everything else became secondary. I drive junk for cars I shop at Goodwill and I take in roommates to reduce my cost of living. I do not live  to impress others with the things I have.
I hope that answers some of your questions
 And as for the "what ifs"... I have to trust in others. Stuff is going to happen at home if I am there or not. I'll deal with it when and how I can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
