<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject350</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm on to my last 2 months left to live in the UK what are some things to do or see you'd recommend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-02 12:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys, Wife and I have been in the UK for the last year and and a half and we've thoroughly enjoyed it. We've seen all the major tourist sites, local sites, and would like to think have given the city life a good go! (Not to mention multiple European trips) We recently moved out of London to Sussex and have seen much of the South too.

We've driven around to pretty much all of Southern England and some parts of Wales. We've also been to York (for the Tour de France - great city!) Some places on my list next are Liverpool, Manchester and Edinburgh. At the same time I'm very interested in exploring more of London that maybe I haven't seen yet or upcoming events I should look into? 

The time has come for us to return home so wanted to get some ideas on some of the stuff we should do before we head home end of September. Not planning on leaving England so anything in the UK and preferably drive-able, doesnt matter how long or far.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-02 12:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bath is spectacular and we loved the Christmas markets there. Been on 2 separate occassions now. Pump rooms were lavish. Thanks for your reco on Notting Hill Carnival.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-02 12:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK - have decided its probably better to ask in another sub-reddit. Using r/askUK now, apparently its good advice for tourists - which I am :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-21 00:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vulnerability by Berne Brown is one of my favourites.. I found it opened up my mind to a new way of living.. https://www.ted.com/talks/brene_brown_on_vulnerability </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-12 00:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Salt and pepper shakers from each new country I travel to. Been collecting since 2010 and so far have Singapore, New Zealand, UAE, UK, France, Czech Republic, Norway, Sweden, Denmark, Spain, India, Finland, Belgium and Malaysia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Disturbing video shows Australian sheep bashed with hammers, kicked by shearers | SBS News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 12:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 20:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No idea how to resubmit from my mobile. The link doesn't work  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It wouldn't be the same if the last name wasn't quite so apt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 20:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm at the Viking ship museum in Oslo, and saw this behind the ticket counter.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 14:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cupcakes and newspapers. Suddenly a dog appears. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-06 13:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Train guards and ticket checkers of Reddit, what are some of the best and worst moments of your career? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-27 09:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-27 09:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quite possible but I'll have you know that my dog will share all her treats with her stuffed toy moose first and then eat them later.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-08 09:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the absolute worst but, money removed from your bank account instantly post an online purchase but a refund takes "upto 3 business days".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 19:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That the globe has a North and a South is not exactly how the Earth would look when it is in orbit. It would depend upon where in relation to this planet you are at when looked at from Space. 

North is not always at the top.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
