<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1811</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 15:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best link that I've found so far.  
http://fox8.com/on-air/live-streaming-sc/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 15:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Donatas Motiejunas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What about Anderson Varejao </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 10:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 11:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm the same as you. I never take photos of myself and very rarely get photos taken of me. But I just stopped caring what people think about me, oh you're this or that, whatever, if you don't like me or say something bad about me, that's your problem. I must not care what other people may think about me. Btw [here's](http://i.imgur.com/DFg88S6.jpg) me. Only acceptable picture that I have lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 19:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Uruguay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 18:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bob Marley   The Wailers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 18:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never understood why people like coins more with gasoline poured on them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 20:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the way you die boy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 19:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 20M. I experience terrible loneliness too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 10:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No way GS is gonna lose game 7 on their home floor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 10:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably next 7 decades until next Lebron is born. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 10:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not english speaker, what does high road mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 17:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you ask him yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 16:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made the post. Thank you for telling people the importance of the gym. Apparently you are a better motivator than me :)  

Go to the gym people, it is very tough in the beginning, but very rewarding in the end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 17:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Joe, thank you for doing AMA, can you ask Lebron why he doesn't like [Guillermo](https://youtu.be/zYR7dCBYpUg?t=4m57s) ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: What would it feel like to inhale in a vacuum chamber? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 17:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 08:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GS Warriors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 20:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bye bye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 11:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for sharing your feelings with us. We all feel your pain together. Keep your head up! Life will get better sooner or later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 12:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi,  
To be honest, for me it is comforting that there are people in this world like me. I really thought that I was the one who failed so much in life. I didn't go to college, I never had a girlfriend, I lost all my friends due to my anxiety, I work from home so I rarely go outside and don't meet people. It hurts so much seeing happy couples in public and thinking to myself that I problably will never be able to achieve that due to my inexperience and anxiety.   

But remember that you are not alone. There are probably milions of people like you in the world.  

I know this sucks so much and I'm so tired of loneliness, but you have to have high hopes and pray for the best. Don't be pesimistic all the time. I'm here with you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 11:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this a macro lens? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 11:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get into fitness. Start going to the gym. Getting in shape will make you feel a lot better.  

I'm in the same situation as you. I have no opportunities, nowhere to go, my job is from home, no friends, no girlfriend, nothing. So the gym is my only hope of going out somewhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 16:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here](https://youtu.be/229ZhY9DRKo) is his dog </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How do doctors deliberately put patients in to coma? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 16:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 20:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, the first step is accepting it and knowing that you have to work with it, that it is a process. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 08:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I know it sucks, I'm a guy and I get very nervous and anxious when a cute girl walks by me in the gym, heart gets racing, mouth gets dry, but, it is really important to tell your mind that nobody really cares what you do there and nobody judges you, you have to re-program your mind, your brain is the greatest computer in the world and you can control it. You must not care what others think about you, you must be in your own way, if somebody does not like you, that's their problem, I know it's easier said than done, but this is what you have to do. Whenever I feel down or experience failure I remember this quote:  

 Success is not the absence of failure, but the persistance through it.  

Everyone experience failure, everyone! that's a fact, but different people react to it different ways. You have to put bad experiences behind you and try to come out better the next time, you must think positively everytime.  

Keep your head up and remember that there are millions of people struggling like you everyday.  

Other than that I just wished that there would be some sort of way for people with SA to connect with each other in real life, that would make the situation of socializing or dating so much easier.  


*If you want to talk about anything or get something off your chest, please pm me, I'm a good listener :)* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 22:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why you must break me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 19:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, we don't really like him here, he didn't participate in any of our national teams and now he renounced his Lithuanian nationality to become a U.S. citizen...  

We Lithuanians just wished he could have done something for our country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 17:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm from [here](http://www.ucl.ac.uk/atlas/lithuanian/images/lithuania_map.gif), I've been LeBron fan since the beginning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In my opinion one of the best piano dueling scene </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 14:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to be happy regardless of the Game 1 outcome </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 14:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bet a lot of money on GSW.   


Sorry for the shitpost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 10:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, no problem. If you want to talk about fitness or just something in general, just pm me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 10:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's even less, we are talking about maybe just couple of water molecules, but this "tea spoon" example is just to help you visualise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 18:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I first started going to the gym couple months ago I was very nervous around people there and I wasn't really sure what I was doing, of course I was self conscious of every move I made, that's an everyday with SA. I experienced failure and anxiety, but I tried to stay persistant through it.  

The basics of fitness is first deciding what are you going to go for: endurance? strength? muscle growth? If you want to go for strength the repetition range for each set of excercise is 3-6 reps and about 3 sets for each excercise. So a good knee excersices would be leg extensions, barbell lunges, dumbell step ups and squats. As for the heart, I'm sorry I can't give you a good advice on how to get a good cardio workout, because I don't do it myself and have little knowledge of it, but in general before your workout run on treadmill for 5 mins and after the workout do a 15-25 mins walk on a moderate pace.  

More information for knee excercises: http://www.bodybuilding.com/fun/5-leg-exercises-bypass-knee-injury.htm  
Information for strength excercises: http://www.bodybuilding.com/fun/wotw57.htm  
Cardio information: http://www.bodybuilding.com/fun/wotw79.htm  
What I was doing the first 4 weeks: http://www.muscleandfitness.com/workouts/workout-routines/complete-mf-beginners-training-guide-0  

Also may not be for you, but me personally I watched [these guys](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mKKSOXwO1vQ list=PL9ECDeQxnERv42odn9ZtNH29IPrLfC2qH) a lot and learned so much from them not to mention they are funny and had SA issues when they were young. They do fitness advice and a lot of other stuff, just add hodgetwins in youtube search to your topic that you want to do research on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 16:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently thought about this, bet a lot of money on GSW, if Cavs were to win the finals you just paid a lot of money for the championship, if not, you made some money. This was just interesting thought for me lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 11:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly, the gym is a great tool to boost your mood and energy. Not only I make progress physically in the gym, but my mind also assumes that I'm making progress with my SA at the same time, so it's just a great way to start making change with yourself. I wish all the people here in this subreddit would want to makes changes with themselves and just not sit at the computer all day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 06:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm here to help you. Is there anything you don't know about or want to ask something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 20:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the beautiful girls in the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 19:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are sore because you do not train a particular muscle group frequent enough, or you just started and the soreness is completely normal. Once I started working out I was sore for like 7-10 days, before I seriously started working out and feel good physically and mentally. Of course you trained your body for short period of time, you shocked your body and you didn't like the result, but if you were to continue, be persistant, that's when the results start to show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arnold Schwarzenegger encounters elephant in South Africa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 15:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 14:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that the "tea spoon" is meant to be what have we sampled of the universe so far and not the earth itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please go to the gym! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 14:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boys and girls, please put some respect on yourselves and your bodies, go to the gym, it will be very tough initially, you will experience failure, but if you stay persistant through it, eventually you will feel much better about yourselves, trust me, I'm experiencing this change right now.  

Please make a decision if you want to get better or not.  
I'm rooting for you all!  

Edit: by the downvotes I see you guys don't like to be motivated at all and just like the way you are right now. Nothing comes easy in life, you have to work really hard at it and the gym was a really good example of how to start making changes with yourselves not only physically, but also mentally, getting in shape can do wonders to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saying there's no other life in the universe is the same thing as taking a tea spoon of water from the ocean and saying there's no whales in the ocean. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 13:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neil deGrasse Tyson </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 13:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comic con </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 14:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> U ain't Chris Smoove babyyy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 15:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I too have a laptop and saving for a PC. What are you planning to put in your build? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 15:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, no problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 13:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are the preferable dimensions for the banner? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 13:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted to skip my graduation, but I had no other choice but to go, It was in church with like a thousand people and the school principal was announcing people's names who then had to go up the stage, shake hand and turn the other way for the camera. It was frickin' intense fear, but I did it lol... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is what helps me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 11:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it's probably not for everyone, but this is what helps me when I feel down or depressed.  

1. [ASMR Videos](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-8YZ7PVZgMo). For me personally it really does relieve stress and gets you relaxed. There is really a big variety of videos to choose from. Headphones is a must.  

2. Again not for everyone, but these guys [Hodgetwins](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yyO3gVwpa6Y), they're so funny and inspirational guys, they were really shy when they were young and had many social and financial issues like most of us do here, but they decided to do something about their lives so they hit the gym. I, for 2 years watched them and wanted to go to the gym and use their advices to build muscle and get in shape, but I just couldn't do it, because I was so scared to go out of the house, let alone sign up to the gym, but my desire to be better overcame my fears and somehow I did it. [Their motivation video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GEzgVs1YG-s)  

3. Not for everyone again, ignore if you don't like this.   
God and hope. You really have to pray and hope for the best, don't be pesimistic all the time, keep your head up, look at the glass as half full, not half empty and just pray everyday.  

4. And last, but not least, this quote:  
Success is not the absence of failure, but the persistance through it.  

Meaning that if you want to succeed, you must be persistant through failure. You have to understand that you will experience failure, but the most important thing is to not give up and understand that you have to put that experience in the past and be better the next time. This quote is really improtant to build in your mind.  

I hope I helped someone. Best of luck to everyone. Never give up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Old Lada engine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 08:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 17:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the info! One more question, If I were to pick a cheap motherboard for overclocking as oppose to picking really expensive one, I know that one would have more features than the other, but would there be any performance differences?  
Like this: https://pcpartpicker.com/part/gigabyte-motherboard-gaz170hd3p  
Or this: https://pcpartpicker.com/part/msi-motherboard-z170apro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 16:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I won't be doing SLI. Also is the overclocking really worth it? Maybe I should get the i5 6500 and stock cooler? I only want to do oc, because of the future proofing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 07:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, I thought 6600k only supports: DDR4-1866/2133, DDR3L-1333/1600 @ 1.35V ram  
Is my ram a bad choice or what?  
sadly, I don't have that case and psu available where I live </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> $1000-$1200 R9 390   i5 6600k OC build, help needed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 18:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi everybody,  
This is going to be my first ever build, I've never built a pc before, but I did read a lot about it and done some research and it turns out there are so many options available that I just don't know what choice would be better and I'm asking you guys to help me out weigh the options.  

These are the parts I know I want in my build:  
**GPU:** MSI R9 390  
**CPU:** i5 6600K  
**HDD:** WD Blue 1TB 7200rpm  
**SSD:** Samsung 750 evo 128gb  
**RAM:** DDR4 Kingston HyperX Fury 2133MHz CL14 1.2V  
**Case:** Cooler MasterCase5 (maybe, don't know yet)  
**Cooler:** Hyper 212 evo

And I really don't know how to choose the right **motherboard** and **power supply**. For power supply I'm thinking Corsair, but not so sure about the wattage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Send help [0:26] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 12:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 07:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol this is like 15 years old stuff.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man thinks he's a cat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 07:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 07:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine if they lose the series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 20:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two words: Michel Thomas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 20:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look on the bright side of things, we will celebrate at home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 20:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will they lie there all day if no one touches them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 16:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it's some kind of new language that I'm unaware of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just found this video with David Blatt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 21:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 16:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nesikelk nakti, ryte neziurek jokiu naujienu ir atsisiusk is linkomanijos, taip darau jau 3 metus, o siaip aisku jeigu rungtynes anksciau kada parodo visada pasinaudoju galimybe ziureti tiesiogiai, eik i /r/nbastreams </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 07:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also: https://vine.co/v/i0tuJnmlmDt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mo Williams crashes the post game interview </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 07:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 14:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, I may try that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gabe The Dog - 20 Min. MegaMix </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 14:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 11:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rent it? What does that mean? Is it like a new way to torrent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 07:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is up with the Hodgetwins lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 08:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know your feeling, because I was exactly the same as you, I really wanted to go to the gym, I too walked passed it and seen people there and thinking how could I go there and not act like a weirdo, but I had to do it, because I knew I had to work with myself, nobody would have done things for me, I had to do it myself and I really was scared to go there knowing that there are many experienced people there and I'm like a poor noob going there, but I did it, because my desire to start changes with myself overcame the fear of failure. Before doing something, first of all you have to make a decision if you want to change your life now and train your SA, that should be the first step. If you sign up to the gym, first couple of weeks are going to be tough for you, because you are going to experience some bad situations, maybe not knowing how to use a machine properly or someone giving you the weird look, this happened to me.  

But...  

What drove me through my failure was this quote:  
The success is not the absence of failure, but the persistance through it. 

This is what drives me everyday. Whenever I experience any failure, I remember this quote. I can not give up this time, I have to be persistent! Because that's how you achieve success! That quote is really important to build in your mind.  

Please make a decision brother, I'm rooting for ya! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 15:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  What I advice you to do is to muster all your courage and sign up to the gym. I was exactly like you couple months ago, sitting weeks at home doing nothing and then I said fuck it, I have to do something about this madness, so I mustered all the courage I got and signed up, my heart was pounding as I was going there and when I did it, I felt slightly better about myself, because I managed to achieve something. I started to read a lot about fitness, how to build muscle faster, how to achieve more in the gym, what supplements to use and when. There's a channel on youtube called "Hodgetwins" they gave me tons of motivation, they are such a funny and inspirational guys. Go watch them!  

 Other than that, it still hurts my heart a lot when I see people being happy in relationships and just simply seeing a cute girl in public thinking to myself that it would be impossible for me to approach a girl in any situation, but being in the gym making some progress, seeing results in the mirror, makes me feel better about myself. It is interesting for me because when I'm making progress in the gym my mind kind of assumes that I'm making some progress with my SA, getting in shape can definitely make you feel more confident.  

 If you want some help on how to get started with lifting weights, please ask me anything, I would be glad to help you! You have to do something about yourself, you have to make a decision now, because if you don't, you will fall in to deeper depression. I feel your pain brother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Group of french guys secretly drilling deep in to the sealed Paris catacombs and then transforming the place </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 13:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 14:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man I can so relate to you, I feel exactly the same as you, seeing other people having relationships it's just depressing for me, I have so much love to give just like you...it's so frustrating... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 19:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm from Lithuania, where you from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 15:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but remember less games played, less of a chance to get injured. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 15:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yess!! I want to see Wade vs Lebron too!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If a prostitute gets pregnant, it's considered a work related accident </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 11:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 19:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder was there any films recorded prior to this, but never found, or this is the very first? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 18:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah they're very cool personalities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 18:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love to Lakers confirmed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 18:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iman Shumpert would be interesting addition too in my opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 14:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know all of his songs, all of them are great, right now I'm learning Magnetic Rag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 12:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you like Scott Joplin? His music brings smile on my face whenever I play his songs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 08:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hitrolic pres </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 17:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Social anxiety is a bitch, I have it too, and sometimes can't do things that I'd want to..
Also I love TWD too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 17:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live right next to you. I'm from Lithuania :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 16:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hitrolic pres </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 12:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man! They're so cool. haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 07:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This turns gay people in to straight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 17:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone's really rich. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crazy guy playing guitar in train </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 21:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Charles Barkley's eastern conference predictions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 20:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 19:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not even from your continent and I'm die hard Cavs fan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian airport worker destroys an airplane after getting fired </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 20:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All kinds of tingle action in my body </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 11:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 11:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 11:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AAaand it's blocked in Lithuania.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 11:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 20:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/theworldisflat  lolololololol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any cheats in real life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 11:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 16:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would be even cooler if he managed to make 3D models of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 19:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got it. Also did a bit of googling. Hahaha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 18:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can somebody explain me the "Pipe" part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> J.R. Smith Warns Marcus Morris Not To Mess With Him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 17:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you're at the store and realize you forgot your wallet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 16:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: What are anti-static bags made of? How they work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 16:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 19:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do I still click the video link and then go to see the comments, I can go straight to the comments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 18:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, looks great to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woman disappointed by absence of McLobsters fell to the ground </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 18:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How was school? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 08:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What should've been fixed a long time ago? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 20:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What seems wrong, but is the correct way of doing it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 15:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 19:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What year is this from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 18:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't dead. Open inside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 13:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rick is the face of the show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 13:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know anything about comics. Will anybody ever kill Negan? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Jackie Chan is almost deaf in his right ear because of the injury he suffered while filming Armour of God. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 19:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 17:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The walking dead. So fun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 13:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Home alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 16:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's pronounced Coral </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 18:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's just a natural reflex with him. It's automatic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 15:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dat was gr8 content m8. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some incredible facts that seem very wrong? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 07:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 06:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, thanks for the answers. I don't really care about value that much. Is there a coin here that is worth putting in a 2x2? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 17:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google maps require internet connection.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 17:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this possible with android? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 16:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know right. Her death reminded me of Gus from breaking bad. God damn... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
