<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3065</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 02:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aka Edward 40 hands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 02:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No internet would be awesome.  Kids would have to actually find ways to entertain themselves...maybe go outside and play or something weird like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 02:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not older than dirt but I remember when they invented mud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 02:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a question posted earlier... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 02:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't be a piece of shit alcoholic and force your kids to live off the grid in a trailer out in the woods because you spent all the money on beer and now you're too fucked up to get a good paying job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 02:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Luke...I am your father, come to the dark side with me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 02:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> World of tanks...I have probably about a 20-30% chance of surviving but an overall 51% chance of winning the battle if that matters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 08:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smear the queer was a fun one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 07:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would have to be a gay bar to pick up hot lesbian babes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 07:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd turn that shit back off before my kids found out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 07:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No more Internet for you EVER! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 07:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Odyssey II in 1983...Commodore 64 in 1986 with a tape drive...some 133mhz desktop in 1997 with a dial up modem...more newer ones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 07:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bears CAN kill you but if they know you are coming they will GTFO.  I used to go mountain biking quite a lot when I lived in Alaska and would see big ass grizzley bear tracks and piles of bear crap but never saw a bear while on my bike because I would yell out "hey bear" every once in a while to let them know I'm coming through.  However this one time me and a friend were riding our bikes into Denali NP and were stopped at a visitor center after they had closed for the day.  We were eating some food and taking our time and just when we were getting ready to leave we saw a grizzley bear walking our direction about 1/4 mile away so we got on our bikes and hauled ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 07:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I'm talking about right here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 06:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Already on that!  Gonna retire from the railroad and get another pension woo hoo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 04:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a successful military career and am now retired from that and getting paid $24k a year for the rest of my life! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 04:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Liquor before beer you are in the clear...beer before liquor never been sicker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 04:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do...they put it on my military ID and dog tags. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 04:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The helicopter" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 02:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excel wasn't even envented yet when I was in high school so that wasn't an option for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 22:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here...drink coffee first thing in the morning then take a big ol dump.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 02:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have to compare this to wearing the spandex biking shorts in public, which I only do while actually riding my bike.  Same with mens leggings...sould only be worn while running, preparing to run or directly after running.  If you feel the need to stop by a store and grab a quick after run snack please do everyone around you a favor and slip a pair of shorts on...unless you live in California. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 20:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy fukin shit that was hilarious!  I was taking a shit when I saw this...I was laughing so hard tears were coming out of my eyes as the toilet seat bounced!  Funniest damn thing I've seen on here in a loooong time!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 05:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a part of a trailer hitch setup.  The ball mounts in the bottom hole...looks like ACME has been making trailer hitches since 1938 and are still in business according to their website. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 02:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen plenty of poor people with no kids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 02:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had kids for the past 15 years now...still don't regret it.  I'm pretty sure at this point I never will regret having them UNLESS they all become heroin junkies mooching off from society. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 01:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 07:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you took two weeks off and it still hurts?  Go see a doctor if you can before it gets worse.  I ignored pain in my foot and it just got worse and had to stop running for almost 2 years before it got better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 07:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 05:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd wipe it down with WD40 and call it good, I like the rustic look. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 04:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While editing you should occasionally look away from your monitor for a few seconds because your eyes basically get saturated and need a break. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 06:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should check out the Minolta X-700.  I had one years ago and liked it, there are tons of lenses you can use on it for cheap.  If you want to use the shutter priority you have to use the MD lenses and not the older MC lenses.  I currently have a Minolta SRT 101, it is full manual and doesn't have shutter priority and I had to do some work to it so that's probably not what you are looking for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 05:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I lived in Alaska and did winter riding I had a nice Columbia coat that you can zip the liner out, Goretex pants over thermal underwear, winter gloves, thick socks and a gator face mask.  Personally I didn't like going out on my bike if it was colder than 20F because the shifter and brake cables didn't act right...and that one time I started getting hypothermic lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 06:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good thing you included the leaf for scale, otherwise it would look a little off...everything looks in focus and the horizon is straight, I don't see anything "wrong" with it...I would print this and hang it on my wall! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 01:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a really nice scene with potential, good choice!  I would have gotten a little closer to the waterfall/rapids part to get the tree branches out of the top of the pic and emphasize the water more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 00:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's almost like being invisible!  Nobody bothers you during lunch break or stops you from getting work done.  You don't have to engage in "being nice" conversations which serves no purpose other than making the other person feel better about whatever they wanted to talk about.  Only have to worry about yourself which gives you freedom to do whatever you want whenever you feel like doing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 00:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really the only place/thing I would like to see is an active volcano so Hawaii would be the place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 23:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't eat the cookie fat ass, you should go vomit instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 22:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They do a good enough job of sticking it to themselves so I don't have to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 22:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know, it has been great ever since I've been here.  I have a good job, nice house, my children have a chance to go to college if they want to.  I grew up poor, like trailer in the woods poor with no electricity and drinking powdered milk.  I made a decision early in life that I wanted better so I went and got it.  Maybe the people waiting for someone to save them should take a look in the mirror because really they are the only ones that can do something about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 19:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Raced" my car on the Nurburgring in Germany.  I made the mistake of watching crash videos before I went out there for the last time and reading about how many people are killed on that track every year.  Needless to say I still drove like a madman and even passed a few cars but when I was done I had to take a break and let the adrenaline dissipate.  It is so much damn fun though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 02:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The clearest sky I have ever seen was outside Fairbanks Alaska in the middle of winter, awesome aurora up there...should add that to the list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 01:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It makes you not care about your problems, they are still there but you don't care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 01:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fellow WOT player? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 00:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the same page "Are aliens draining our solar energy?".  I find it hard to take news like this seriously when they have links to alien stories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 05:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty lit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 22:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only had one dog chase me on the trail and it was medium sized so I would have easily been able to beat its ass but lucky for the dog the owner called it back.  Out on the road I have been chased several times and once had 3 dogs try to circle me...don't let them do that.  One time a little dog got close enough I kicked it in the face so that was fun.  If you are worried enough just carry bear spray and you should be fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 22:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically the chain stretches which causes the links to be a little farther apart, they use a chain gage to measure the amount of stretch.  The cassette teeth wear down as the chain stretches so you will have to replace both at some point.  I ran mine for 6 years before I replaced mine and it wasn't slipping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 18:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would rather have these nice ants rather than these damn fire ants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 17:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrong article lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 17:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all I'm glad the little girl is ok but who cares about an ebook? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 19:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is an awesome website www.bocn.co.uk where collectors of inert ordinance share their collections and help members identify items, you should check it out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 02:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, I don't want random teachers running experiments on my kids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 02:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha stupid customers...thank god I don't have to deal with that shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 02:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an old Nikon D40 I still use, it has the same 6.1mp sensor as your D70.  It really depends on what you are taking pics of and what you plan on doing with them.  I like to do landscape photography so I like the ability to put a polarizer on the lens and also like the ability to get a RAW file to run through photoshop.  But if you plan on taking pics of people to put on your Twitter or whatever then the phone would be best because of Internet connection.  Bottom line, there are things my D40 can do that my iPhone camera can't do.  I just took these pics the other day with my D40:  https://i.imgur.com/QDDmAUL.jpg
https://i.imgur.com/jdnyCET.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 19:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 18 and 19 are legal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 19:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My opinion of people that drive big diesel trucks just to be driving one because they think it is cool versus owning one to tow horse trailers or other work related uses is that they are ignorant.  I see it all the time here in Texas, these guys will leave their diesel truck running while they go in the store just to make sure everyone sees that they are driving a big diesel truck.  It is the redneck version of people that drive Mercedes and Audi cars, like look at me I can afford to spend most of the money I earn on my vehicle versus saving for retirement or moving out of my trailer or perhaps saving for my child's college education...ignorance.  But hey it's a free country do what you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 06:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Internet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 06:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lazy eye but smoking hot otherwise </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 06:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rape Kevin Bacon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 06:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nobody would see your invisible turd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 06:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where I work (railroad) Thursday and Friday are paid holidays, basically you get paid to stay home.  In the past they still needed some people to work so they would pay us time and a half ($45 per hr) and I was scheduled to work 8 hrs Thursday and 12 hrs Friday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 05:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was no internet.  Kids had to go outside to play with the neighbor kids.  Now they all just lay around the house and don't do shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 05:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or wear cowboy hats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 05:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At first I wasn't going to because my work was gonna pay me an extra $900 to work this Thursday and Friday but then they canceled the overtime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 05:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I regret nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 05:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going because I'll be the scariest thing in the forest.  Nothing worse than a white guy running through the woods at night with a murder weapon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 05:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The correct answer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 05:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Netherlands were nice, wouldn't mind living there for a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 05:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 05:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally selling your ass? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 05:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a job, work overtime, start a webcam stripper show, help old people in your area, babysitting, raking leaves, picking apples...the list goes on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 05:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remind me to never go there, it sounds terrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 04:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should have titled it "the other voyager". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 04:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definately needs some vanilla ice cream in that empty space! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 04:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At first I thought she had just participated in one of those Spartan races but she doesn't look tired and her shoulders are still clean.  So did she just rub dirt on her face for the pic?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 04:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, thanks for the explanation and nice shot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 04:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bootleg canyon in Boulder City, NV has the sharpest rocks I have seen along any MTB trail and I have ridden in a lot of places since I started back '97. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 04:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I forgot about those!  So when using one of those do you have to focus one side then move the other subject until it is also in focus? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 01:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Top secret spy plane sent to observe tsunami. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 00:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow that was fast!  Just saw an article 5 minutes ago that said it was 15 hrs and 45 minutes away in light speed time.  Must have teleported or broke the laws of physics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 05:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 05:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before YouTube you had to buy a vhs tape to watch this kind of riding...some things are better left in the past </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 00:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would be awesome to go back a few hundred years before Europeans showed up to the Americas and brought their diseases.  I grew up in Michigan and there used to be native villages everywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 19:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have used Cokin filters a loooong time ago, seems like they were a big brand back in the day not sure if they are still around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 17:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since you plan on backpacking and hauling your gear around you might want to ask the folks at r/campingandhiking what they use during their excursions to get some ideas on good lightweight cameras and equipment.  I'm not up to speed on the latest cameras to make a recommendation one way or another but I have been seeing a lot of mirrorless cameras lately from Sony that take great pics and 4k video as well with the ability to use "older" manual focus lenses so you don't need to spend a bunch of money on a new lens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 17:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like that it looks like you might get blown off the cliff, cool shot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 22:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope you got better pics of the place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 06:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've sucked on stripper titties before, it was fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 06:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like a Dave Chapelle skit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 05:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am fairly certain the Army does not operate this plane...I'm leaning more towards Air Force. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 08:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good weenie, stay off the smack </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 06:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends which sub, this one new, gone wild top. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 06:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've just been doing it for a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 05:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> VW rabbit...ram 1500 quad cab with the Hemi but I have owned 6 other trucks, 10 other cars, 2 SUV's and a jeep.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 05:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So do you believe everything you see on TV or read on the Internet?  The media likes to push stories that get people to watch them.  So far I haven't seen the sky fall where I am but I have seen the same crap you see on TV.  But it's like you said, it isn't effecting me personally so everything is good.  Until Trump sets policies in place that negatively effect my way of life and how I want to pursue it then we can talk.  For now it is all speculation and crying Hillary supporters still trying to win the election that has already been decided.  But hey, if you don't want to come over and see for yourself then just stay where you are and continue reading about what the media wants you to believe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 05:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I have traveled and lived in Germany for 4 years and visited several other countries.  I was born and raised in the good old USA and am glad to be back because after all it is home.  Everything here is so damn convenient and I took it for granted because it was all I knew.  After seeing what other countries have to offer it is still my opinion that USA is still #1.  Yea Germany has nice infrastructure such as the autobahn but their culture is so weird compared to what I am used to.  Also take into consideration that most of what you think you know about the U.S. has been filtered through the media.  Nobody likes to hear about good news or boring stories so what gets played the most are the bad things that do happen here.  I will admit, we are not perfect but if I want feel like going to the store and getting groceries at 11pm on a Sunday Walmart is there for me.  Try doing that in Germany because everything is closed on Sunday.  I will raise my children here because they have the freedom to choose what they want to be when they grow up.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 04:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wore Napalm Death shirts and ignored everyone...listened to death metal before anyone knew what it was.  I was quite literally the only person in my entire school that did.  My older brother listened to the cure and dressed like Robert Smith.  I was more pissed off than depressed I guess lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 03:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best insults come from having insight into the other person.  Such as "people that listen to background noise podcasts are fucking retards".  See what I mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 03:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey man, it was an unfortunate industrial accident! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 03:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First tape was Metallica and justice for all because of that one song. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
