<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3183</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Chinese  English] It's writing in a painting, I believe, of plum blossoms. It might be an artist's signature. I'm curious though overall what says. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 04:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 02:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow, thanks for the education. I was not aware of that. Glad to know.   
  
Blossoming in the winter sounds pretty cool.   
  
Thanks again. I'll try a repost with Chinese in the title. I had, actually, originally posted this with CN/KR/JP in the title but didn't get any responses so then took a more focused approach. 
   
Really, thanks again for your time, the brief cultural education, and your contribution to this sub! Really awesome thing to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 21:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> obsession of the removal of materialistic things. 
   
lol don't be coy with me. there's a difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 20:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get it, green energy would be a new sector. You could have plants to make solar panels, and farms to run them. Same with wind turbines.     
 
I don't see a problem with that really. There are jobs, people just aren't traind for them. Technology sector is where it's at. Looking back to jobs that are eitehr costing companies $1/hr wage outsourced or could be done by a robot isn't fixing the problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 20:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The thing we're not talking about is unemployment is at 5%. And we have jobs available we just need to train people for those jobs. Not being willing to learn the new trades of the 21st century is what's holding America back. Plus most factories are automated by robots nowadays. Looking toward manufacturing as your savior is naive at best and completely foolhardy at worst. But technology and software development? Plenty of room there for jobs.
   
Besides, Trump's picking at talking points without knowing the whole situation. Many of these companies do have factories in the U.S. BMW oncluded.  
  
The reality is, for the average job, you won't be a 50 cent/hour wage no matter how much you tariff it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 06:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey thanks a lot. i might try to report as Chinese. I apologize for assuming the cherry blossoms indicated a Japanese painting. Are cherry blossoms prominent in Chinese culture as well? I wasn't aware of that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Japanese  English] Artwork with cherry blossoms. It looks sorta old. Small chance it's Chinese or Korean but doubtful. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 07:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 06:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's  just the cutest lillest dik i ever saw.  
   
but don't lie to yourself when you're watching porn you don't like a flaccid dick do you? you seeing a... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 02:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol you're unreal. i wasn't being anything. you made a really poor judgment when you choose to compare this to depression. i called you out on it. you're acting like a child.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 23:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as someone who has depression and feels uncomfortable looking at images like that you picked an incredibly stupid thing for comparison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 22:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not the same thing at all lol.  
  
especially cause it's not even a real phobia. it's not a fear but more like a disgust or  being offput by it.   
   
get a grip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 20:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah i get what you're saying I guess I just saw it more as her seeing herself as she was for the first time. The way everyone has always seen her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 20:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> actually, it won't be. for like getting shit done meter or a president, he's actually done quite a bit.  
 
they say an incoming president hope to get 50% of the things they want done actually done and obama was pushing 70%. i dont remember the %'s exactly but it was pretty impressive and surprising. 
  
the racial tension thing i just don't understand. also the president doesnt make 'jobs' in the sense you think they can. a generation of bartenders and waiters is because we'll never beat a 50 cent wage in the phillipines or bangladesh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 20:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, no that's not how logic works. Because it actually happened to Obama.   
  
It's been accepted that the republican strategy was to have a nonworking government rather than one that did anything. And it's exactly how they won over the last 2 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 19:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eh to be fair if he didn't think it was in our nation's best interest of security to end certain programs he shouldn't. I'm not sure why you'd think that's a bad thing.
 
He did end those wars though. A new one sprouted up that he stayed out of. That's not really on him.   
  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 19:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drain the swamp...have you seen trump's nominees? I actually had a lot of hope for him once he won but I got fooled once with change, Trump's going to be going at it the same way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 19:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol def not man. the uhh thing can certainly be prominent at times but you've clearly   never spoken publicly. silence is really hard to deal with. i'd rather a couple uhh's followed by saying something that makes sense than George W.'s off-script. Who I said the same thing about, as far as it being a difficult part of their job. But to call Obama a bumbling idiot is just off. I mean you can think it but most people with experience dealing with him find him the exact opposite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 19:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> actually that's not entirely true. most reporters who spend extensive                                                  time with him all say he keeps that calm cool demeanor almost all the time. that he is as thoughtful and as much of a thinker as he appears. 
  
short video clips where he is 'off-script' probably aren't really good sources because you're seeing what's probably a  public event and answering to a chaotic sort of situation. If you've never spoken publicly you have no idea how difficult speaking or Q A can be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 19:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> glad to see this up here! 
 
how does one become a speech writer outside of jsut being a writer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 08:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah i thought they might by. poke around though, you might come across something similar. idef appreciate your tastes! i enjoy a lot of the same stuff. atm i've diverged a bit, tastes obviously change and go through different cycles/changes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 08:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry for the more  plain language...welp nvm that shit was brilliant. My first go through was only seeing 3/4 or maybe 1/2 of what was going on with white's pressure. 
   
Now from a stylistic or maybe strategic perspective, does this stem from Black's reluctance to meet White head-on trading pieces early?  
  
 Or was that queen move just that damn good? #rekted #pwned </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 02:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the only proper answer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 02:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but gram positive sound, well, positive! pfffffft nasty of the nasties! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 02:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Le Carre you  philistine!     
  
lol :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 01:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> purity ring. it's a lil electro poppy but maybe you'll like it. 
   
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IIPMzeNWAtk  
   
odesza can have a bit much going on. but this track comes to mind.  
   
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wPqTCrm61-I </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 23:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol fa real? i'd like to know what really happened then. it's not something to be made up that's just not something he'd do but def makes it a bit odd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 22:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Solid ideas to make her unique to her kit. I always thought of it like War Paint baseline, CC reduction baseline, Add the short stun from spear to apply after she reaches the target, CD reduction on spear/mystic baseline and that's all I can remember at the moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 22:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> funny story, i forgot what ship he was on but my dad was a an NYPD ESU cop. As a part of their uniforms they have an E-#, he was in 9 Truck so it was E-9.
   
He was being given a tour with other guys from the truck and all day they walked around the ship they were being saluted. Often the sailors made a point of saluting them when they saw the E-9.    
  
They all got a kick out of it, especially the couple guys giving them the tour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 21:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i only had to read those first 2 lines of i was the...it's clearly bullshit people don't confess, or talk like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 21:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so i read the first line of your comment, checked the story, then went to say that's too literary to be true. then read the second line. no one actually confesses to shit like that. 
  
i know it exists too, it just seemed so dramatic. dirty looks in the grocery store? um, okay? real or imagined looks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 21:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i dont know if he had the right words there. and to be fair, unless you regularly do live broadcasting/public speaking not getting every word right comes with the territory. it's hard. 
  
that said, it was a prepped or should have been a prepped question and it was ambitious to claim that at best. rising in popularity as an alternative? would have been a better phrase maybe. But that's also not really applying to the average game, it's applying to eSports which is a big chunk of gaming but not all games. It was weird.   
   
Not sure how much experience he has. Sometimes people see a bigger guy like Elon Musk or something and feel the need to make a claim like that I guess? I dont know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 20:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> was she out of character? or is this her character coming to fruition and finally being realized as the weak one who was strung along and is still being strung along by him? Like Nina said she was, being used. 
  
I'm not saying you're wrong, just there might be a bit more behind her motivations. This show needs to be read like a book. He's a literary figure, or at least his story certainly was through the affair. Now it's kind of turned into this tragic downfall. Helen, who always loved him, is trying to help him, again.  
   
It's not so much she just didn't leave his life, you have to consider why. And she's always held this small sliver of hope for way too long that it could be forgotten. Now take into account an immense guilt she feels. I mean, she owes him. No way around it. How do you pay that back? Someone doing a bid for you like that?
   
So to make it so clear cut that, come on Helen, wtf?! Isn't really fair to the past. Sure it's been years but he only got out of prison, she only got her chance to start making it right now when he was released.  
  
I don't know if it's she's entirely oblivious. She want's to help but doesn't know where to start. To some extent it's an unfair expectation for her to know how to help someone who is an addict out of prison. She'd never have the slightest clue what is going on with someone like that. 
 
What she needs to do is start telling the truth. Or enough of a truth. That he wasn't driving that night and he was protecting someone else from going to prison. Let people speculate whether it was her or Allison.   
  
As for the lying, it seems just like that secret, helping him and the why needs to be a secret because of its origin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 13:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah you shoot till the threats neutralized, cops get a bad rap, no one is shooting at a guy laying on the ground.  
  
but there's one of you, with a capped mag #. there's 2+ cops with at least 9+ round magazines.  
  
me and a partner do 18 rounds a clip each. that's 36 if we use two.  
   
cops really aren't any different than most people in that situation. scared, making a million decisions a minute, and have at least a few trips to the range a  year usually, minimum of a couple. 
  
 like i said, this situation i'm cool with it. but it's not a justification to shoot anyone committing a crime anytime.
  
it sounds silly but what if this is a supermarket, and next door is a day care. bear with me, i know it's fucking ridiculous, but at that range you want to risk the 45 not over penetrating?    
  
i'm just saying that whole, oh fuck yeah we all need guns response to these videos isnt healthy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 13:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> precisely  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 13:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm 100% on the same page here. and that close range shooting was on point too. range time doesn't =tactical under fire time. his first shots  were dead on. the later ones, on a moving target that might have been returning fire, obviously were not.   
  
saying this is hoo rah! yeah this is why we all need CCL is cavalier at best and as much a made believe world as any "liberal fucktard" is living in.
  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 13:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no but i also don't want it to be the one where it turns into a standoff and be the hostage because someone thought they'd be a cowboy or be the murder victim from a through n through or missed shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 13:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "or clip the dude just getting into his car?" what about that scenario? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 13:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's a interesting two sentences isn't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 13:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's a good point. that stats on gun ownership in the home and death by firearm in the same home and accident by firearm are a helluva lot higher than you supermaning this situation. and that's not some liberal bullshit stat. it was cdc stats until congress told them to stop keeping them because of the gun lobby. 
   
but they started to again. you're a helluva lot more at risk for suicide or accident with a gun in the house.more guns=more people shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 13:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> naturally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 13:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> umm colloquially? i think in that context...and what i said nothing really misses the mark.   
   
it's a weak point anyway. nothing guarentees you'll be taken hostage or shot either. except most armed robberies don't turn into murders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 13:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're absolutely right, you don't know what's in the direction except probably a door and a parking lot. so he very well could have put anyone's life at risk who was outside his store too. 
   
i got no problem with this really. it's saying this incident justifies the use in defense of property, especially insured commercial goods or $, all the time that bothers me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 13:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm a gun owner dude. i bet most of these guns don't get sold or make  it that far at all. it becomes pretty easy to track down the bad guys with a new load of guns.  
  
regardless, here there's no problem with what happened. saying that justifies it universally is a make believe world too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 12:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except there probably is. At least statistically. Otherwise there would be a lot more armed robberies turned into murder 

Actually, why not just shoot them first if that's the case? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 12:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, you'd probably see alot more people shot, period good or bad. He very well, looking at the end of the clip, could have caught the coworker dude too looking at the direction he was firing. 
  
I'm not saying bad guys should have free reign or some shit, and robbing a gun store is exactly how this should have gone down. But he had a good draw on that dude and they weren't very smart to begin with. It always could turn out worst. Especially if there's other people standing around. 
  
Best  case? No one is killed, the owner collects his insurance money for products stolen and that's that.        </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 03:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well you have an awesome sense of humor.  
  
i feel like my optician is never that helpful and just tied to sell me on what gives them the most commission. if they're even actually trained opticians and not jsut hired sales in lab coats.  
  
anyway, pretty funny. and glasses that don't fit will kill you from the regular headaches and constant pushing up your nose you need to do :P. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah they marketed the shit out of their network n phones too. 
  
 once they had that can you hear me now guy doing the ads lol they were bound to kill it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the 'i don't have high blood pressure anymore!'  
  'what medicine do you take?'   
  'metopropol' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i dont know how an open mandible fracture wasn't bothering her though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my girl tolerates my book store habit and tips to barnes and noble are like...events where's she's like alright ill spend 2 hours in there with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is actually pretty true. they're all rockstars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol...glad this is somewhere
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 22:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to some extent though, don't you want that guy to know his shit and to know he knows his shit?  
  
like not having a full on confidence/bordering on arrogance will get people killed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 22:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> here i am thinking of a margin account, margin securities and calls.  
  
or buy more money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 22:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> things like graphite though? or a fusion engine? i mean...we're really on the cusp of some shit.  
  
genetic splicing? i'm not even sure how to rank those. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 22:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> username checks out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 22:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> derivatives  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 22:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> coupled with, how often do you wash your hat or jacket or gloves or scarf? 
  
I mean think about that. A lot of hospitals don't have doctors wear ties  for this very reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 22:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why don't you wear hats though? i feel like i can tell the heat is just escaping out of the top of my head and jacket without a hat on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 22:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's actually fascinating. if she did take to and understood the advice to google it. like googling it is its own magical explainer of things.   
  
also, are you an ob/gyn? and why do you guys always have the oddest sense of humor? not that there's anything wrong with doing that but making a joke of it...whyyyy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 22:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> crabs swim too.. . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 22:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah religion often coincides with   political upheaval or need. so historically you may have started out meaning to help people who needed it but eventually it turned into a power structure institution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 22:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i was thinking about this after a few nights sleeping in a non traditional position. you need to lay down for a few hours each night or gravity takes its effect on fluid in your body. obviously less so for younger in shape people. 
   
so it's not just sleep but the physical act of laying down as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 22:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i think a more fitting question would be do we feel some pain? a short pike in heartbeat that then goes down, maybe the person felt the initial pain or maybe a constant discomfort of poking and prodding, like the dentist?  
 
really this is all made moot because the drugs used while you were knocked out are the same drugs your on as you wake up. and often you're not in pain when you wake up and before you're given oral or more IV painkillers without the knockout effect.
   
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 22:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> doesn't meant they used them on lobster claws though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 21:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ai too. also medicine. and depending on how we continue to develop construction materials possibly those too. and there's the fusion experiments, https://www.iter.org/. 
 
i think yall are downplaying some major major contributions to how a society could or arguably needs to advance.  
  
then there's things like antibiotic resistant bacteria. like the invention of penicillin and within 100 years or so the resistance to it? and then there's CRISPR, aka super affordable gene splicing. which they're using to potentially eradicate lime disease changing a whole species ability to carry it, http://www.nytimes.com/2016/06/08/science/ticks-lyme-disease-mice-nantucket.html.  
   
and in 30 years or 40, maybe 50, you might even be able to make diseases at home gene editing and building will be so affordable. then what?  
  
i mean, i honestly think we're more likely to be remembered for finally inventing something that fucking ended it all rather than anything else. or some major fuck up that led to major innovation. 
  
and i'm really not sure how any of us are having this conversation without mentioning global warming. the inventions that come out of trying to give people places to live and ways and means will probably be heralded as critical.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 06:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> true that. to me though there felt like a big difference between manipulating data and stats and flat out like not accepting them. and on the heels of climate change/global warming it just feels like... 
  
culturally the media's changed in this country and there's a strong anti-intellectualism going on. i hate to sound like that but it's true. people don't read papers, or read much at all, and to be able to flat out refute facts, which is different than manipulate or downplay them, is a bit more alarming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 06:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my bad man, i was joking. and really just jealous i can't look at a bird and recognize it's difference from a similar one by beak color. 
   
it's really rather impressive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 06:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i think the teamfight thing is kinda eh...if you keep putting creep down u have constant regen n speed in fights. maw really shouldnt be understated and those minions do have a place in team fights.     
  
zag had a place in the game for a while, then sort of fell back the game back after that crazy rework again. meta's change though and it's not that she's bad there's just better options. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 09:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Though, it is fascinating to see these buttons on the specific utility shirt he's wearing

lol classic history sub family comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 09:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fa real? 
  
also awesome username btw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 09:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> beef isn't really sustainable though. it takes a lot to raise cattle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 09:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not much of a good bird watcher are ypu eh? i mean that was a close up too!  
   
/u/Swolebrah is slackin' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 09:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but I feel like feeling like crime is up or unemployment isn't low are...they got him elected you know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 05:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i just counted the list from the poll that didn't have chogall could have swore he had 15 not including chogall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 04:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> less than half the heroes introduced in 2016     were wc. it was something like 15 and 7 were wc. i get where people are coming from but they're trying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 04:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they actually address the naz and arthas thing right on the page that they describe this on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 06:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah but that doesnt explain the chain bomb continuously going off and staying on the character. the effect shouldn't persist because they didn't die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 06:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if usertext_body '=='  
  print 'this guy codes'
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 06:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> make it rain on dem bitches 
  
you know, because the elves were gangsters with rap ambitions. 
   
u might even say, 
   
ambitionz as a ridah 
    
edit: fyi folks that's the symbol/artwork for KT's flamestrike. Was present in WC3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 06:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> or the timing works out just enough for shield to regen a sliver. 
   
i actually got one of those uther redemption kills on the core. it was like a week after i saw it on here too and then i had my chance. 
   
best part was team was like back off or bad core calll we lose. and i'm like just focus the core not them , core core core. we get it to 1% and are killed and they're all sorta salty. then ban uther comes back alive and thwump! geegee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [JAPANESE English] It's a painting or drawing or a cherry blossom so I suspect it's Japanese. Just curious, I want to hang it up but not without knowing what it says. Possibly CN or KR instead. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 22:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 22:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who casts and has a bit of appreciation for how difficult it is, don't even address the haters.  
   
i do give you a lot of credit for trying to address the haters. Most people will never understand the idea of not speaking on something they haven't experienced.   
  
Ultimately it's vastly more important to entertain the veiwers than it is to pick up on every single thing that's happenening. Especially when casting  you're looking for the next 2, 3, 4 things taht are going to happen because of that artanis switch so trying to highlight it all or in a sense 'go back' isn't going to work. The game just moves too fast. Again, something you wouldn't get unless you've casted.  
  
And I recommend you go and try to cast. Take a replay and cast. I did when learning how to. I"m sure Khaldor spent time casting replays to no one in particular. I personally spent time practicing just the play by plays and time spent just talking about the match and transitioning to the play by plays and fights.  As  a whole though entertainment is the goal. Not every single ability called out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 22:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's late game but i think kara's 3 person radiant dash cleanse might have some value here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 10:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do you gorge in your offtime? with  friends just for fun? 
   
are you tired of the gorgeous ;) jokes yet?  
  
is this your ama  like your stitches? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 10:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Step 3: Roll face across keyboard firmly
 

That's the step i missed, personally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 10:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hell yeah before the start of a big tournament like that? def want to get everyone in the same room and be like we agree on all this for rules? this with streaming? etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 08:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> great play and great sticking with him for the continued heal as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 08:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is this confirmed on anything but SA twitter account? might be a miscommunication or misunderstanding. seems odd there would be no ptr or  no patch notes release at all                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 08:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> boomshakalaka </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 08:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i wouldn't say that. I'd say it's hard to get up on the level he needs to be in the time periods he needs to be. Over the course of another year he very well could put himself in that much better of a position with a new team.  
  
he's professional through and through and that combined with his solid word hard attitude is half the battle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 08:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> real classy guy. best of luck in 2017. Never know where  another year of practice and  play will take you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 08:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i watched some of this it was pretty fun/awesome. 
   
this particularly was some bdp's though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 08:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> even with healing ward the 2% heal a second gets a ton of value in duo tank/bruiser/beefy comps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 06:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol right. like the match made in heaven, and he's waited all his life, all his evolutions, and all his hats for this moment. the moment it didn't just feel right. the moment it *was* right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 01:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah i also got a bit tunneled vision too. because if there wasn't multi-targets you'd have 0 incentive to use it and that kills flexibility/utility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 01:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well multiple targets is incentive too. in a lot of ways has been a big part of it. especially when it was etc/kt and u could trip stun lock. but the point was to ensure the stun landed on the target u wanted it to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 21:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'd be remiss if i didn't mention you could prolly make a decent dollar selling these as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 21:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> who knows anymore man? and really does it matter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 19:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> waitu started this woodworking project by drilling a hole? my god! it's revolutionary!  
  
jp jp :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 17:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would consider internal temps/overheating as a potential concern.   edit: lol it was early for me. despite seeing the glass i kept thinking it was an all wood  box.
 
really awesome though. it's beautiful really </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 07:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have a laser that freezes. i'm looking for investments actually! 
   
it's the gaz-o-tronic 10000! I'm making it with exclusively imported goblin parts and genius  gnome engineering! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 07:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm also curious if this was tongue in cheek or serious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 07:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well that's the biggest thing that a lot of people are missing in this thread. he casts laser and i cast blizzard or charge/q in with sonya and he has to cancel what he was lasering </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 07:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the other thing is the rate he stacks at is insane. when he does get his stacks, and arguably the talents for the other abilities, they become pretty damn strong for his role. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 21:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> any cfhance you know what this means too? Or what language it is?  
  
http://imgur.com/a/vyDt8  
  
Thanks! At least if I know it's Japanese for sure I can specifically request that in the post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 21:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks a lot. fitting with KR new years coming up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 21:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks man! much appreciated. i've had it for a lil bit now but since its  that time of year pretty fitting. although being that my dog did mess it up a bit i'm not sure that's a good omen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 19:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> for the record you guys are absolutely ridiculous here.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 19:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i absolutely love the look of these weapons! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 14:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dog damaged it a little bit but the part on the left was just a shorter line that was straight/parallel to the the longer one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [KR/CN/JPN/Unknown  ENGLISH Single Character] Woven charm like piece. Single 'character' unsure of the language though, willing to teach or practice English w/ you!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 14:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 13:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bhaha oh shit. that describes the situation to a T. although the owner said in general he's a dick. the way he had held my hand with the claws though was wild. it was so interesting that he had my hands held but pulling away would annihilate my hand.                                                                                                                                                                                                                   his mouth is open and closing in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 03:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> are those blank receivers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 21:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i met this cat yesterday that was so cute. and he'd lay there let you rub his head then as you move to his tummy grab your hands with his claw and open his mouth to bite too. And you're stuck there cause pulling away with his claws holding your hand precariously will lead to them digging and scratching the shit out of your hand.  
  
When I looked into his eyes though, they were soft, until it glanced up at me and I saw this darkness in them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 21:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that one baby is like, i got no say in this! this is some bullshit, put some more booze in my bottle if I'm laying out here for another 3 hours! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 00:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I hear that. But to some extent those have been in the game and only now are getting some love. While EQ is certainly much easier to use BL does have a timing element to it.  
  
Generally though I don't think it's so much a trend. A lot of valid points though. To some extent, they're kind of the crux of each of the issues that he addresses anytime someone brings it up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 21:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's some interesting stuff. yeah that kind of boat might be a bit different than a pure dragger/troller.  
  
Have you ever considered writing a book? Or having a ghostwriter do the heavy lifting through interviewing you? I'm sure there's a ton of stories there but as a whole it sounds super interesting. 
 
 I'm not some agent or anything. Just a guy who loves the water, boats, ships, fishing, and writing. And the stories that come along with it, having been raised on the water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 20:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woot! Newsday is #1!  
  
lol... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 20:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey man i'm a writer at heart. A pen and paper, many notebook kind of guy. Love day/week/month planners. 
  
That said, you very well may be able to sell it, to people like me, with an accompanied day/week/month planner or something and/or a  booklet that explain the phases. I wouldn't be surprised if the people who like this calendar would also like a personal planner or something. 
  
I get it was out of the scope and maybe without mechanical elements to keep alongside an app or something it may not be the way to go. Then again digital err'thing nowadays so... 
  
So I'm no help. Lol.   
  
And my bad, just saw like 7 or 8 posts on it when I searched for the post I saw about that cool calendar. Super cool stuff though man. Great job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 20:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Palestinian State has never been closer to being recognized and on the same hand Israel continues to colonize it.  
  
It's messy, and at the moment relatively peaceful. I'm not sure what will happen under trump though. There are calls, within Israel, for annexation rather than continuing on a two state solution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
