<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2472</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boko Haram Kills 7 New Army Recruits, Abducts Female Soldier </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Grey's Anatomy,' 'Scandal,' 'How to Get Away With Murder' Renewed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chad Stahelski on Directing John Wick: Chapter 2 and Future Installments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SS-GB's dystopian parallel universe  The BBC TV adaptation of Len Deightons novel about a Nazi-occupied Britain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 19:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canadian Muslim grilled about her faith and view on Trump at US border stop: The case raises concerns that border patrol agents are targeting minorities more broadly in the wake of Donald Trumps travel ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 19:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 19:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And take Trump with him as well.

Edit: The FBI should be investigated as well. They leaked to the media that the [FBI has not found any evidence of wrongdoing or illicit ties to the Russian government](https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/national-security/fbi-reviewed-flynns-calls-with-russian-ambassador-but-found-nothing-illicit/2017/01/23/aa83879a-e1ae-11e6-a547-5fb9411d332c_story.html?utm_term=.0735f569b4a5), and yet here we are, a few weeks later, and it appeared that, like Flynn, they lied to the American people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 18:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Omarosa - ['Every critic, every detractor will have to bow down to President Trump'](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zzSvzTTBALg)

Looks like Mr. Abrams refused to bow down to the Snowflake-in-Chief.

Edit: Not that Abrams was a great choice to begin with, he is a neocon and was involved in Iran-contra.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Putin floats summit with Trump in Slovenia, first lady's birthplace </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  With a Slovene-born first lady in the U.S. and close relations with both Moscow and Berlin, the leader of the small Alpine nation is maneuvering his country to play a bigger role on the world stage.[...] In his telephone call with Trump, Pahor proposed Slovenia as the venue for the American leaders first summit with Putin, an offer he plans to make to Russian president as well.[...] Pahor declined to discuss the details of his discussion with Trump, except to say they had a very nice debate. The highlight, however, appears to have come when Trump put Melania on the phone. He invited the first lady to come on the phone and speak to me in the beautiful Slovene language, Pahor said. It was very touching. It was a lovely gesture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald, meet Vladimir: Slovenia acts as matchmaker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 03:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have a mole at the White House.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump: I Lost :( </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 00:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not likely.

 The White House could take the issue to the Supreme Court, but the prospects for such an appeal are uncertain due in part to the high court being short a justice and split evenly between Democratic and Republican appointed justices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 00:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A three-judge panel of the 9th Circuit Court of Appeals unanimously rejected the Justice Departments request to lift a Seattle-based judges restraining order that blocked authorities from carrying out the limits Trump sought to impose on travel to the U.S. by refugees and by citizens of seven majority-Muslim countries. The White House could take the issue to the Supreme Court, but the prospects for such an appeal are uncertain due in part to the high court being short a justice and split evenly between Democratic and Republican appointed justices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Appeals court rules unanimously against Trump travel ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 00:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 00:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ruled unanimously, I love it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 23:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is he trying to get himself fired?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Forgotten Roddenberry: Planet Earth - A completely retooled and recast version of the adventures of 20th Century scientist, Dylan Hunt, in a post-apocalyptic future. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 23:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. From the real article:

 [Ortega voted in the November 2012 election and May 2014 GOP primary runoff in Dallas County.](http://www.dallasnews.com/news/tarrant-county/2017/02/08/grand-prairie-woman-found-guilty-illegal-voting)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny how this article omitted the fact that she voted in [GOP primary runoff in Dallas County.](http://www.dallasnews.com/news/tarrant-county/2017/02/08/grand-prairie-woman-found-guilty-illegal-voting) 

Edit: This Mexican woman is a [legal U.S. resident, but is not a citizen](http://www.nbcdfw.com/news/local/Trial-Begins-in-Alleged-Illegal-Voting-in-Tarrant-County-413091043.html), she has no right to vote but she is not an illegal immigrant. And it is ironic that she voted  in the GOP primaries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ira Steven Behrs New Deep Space Nine Doc 'What We Leave Behind' Launches Teaser and Crowdfunding Campaign </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "Kellyanne has been counseled and that's all we are going to go with," Spicer told reporters during his daily briefing. "She's been counseled on the subject and that's it."

Crooked White House.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ira-Steven Behrs 'Deep Space Nine' Documentary: 'What We Left Behind' Indiegogo Pitch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> '24': Taking a Look Back at Every '24' Mole, Ranked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First he voted for Sessions and now this?#Mole  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Senator on senator combat has happened before on the floor of the congress, but it's been more than a hundred years.

Might be a good time to bring that back! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China vice premier says falsifying economic data will be punished: Any officials found responsible for bogus statistics would face demerits, denying them promotion, Zhang said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  In light of Gorsuchs comments, some Republicans are pointing to that as evidence that hell be independent from Trump. But Schiff rejected that premise in a Thursday interview, suggesting that the criticism could have been intentional with the hopes that it would be leaked to reporters. It maybe have been quite calculated in terms of what Judge Gorsuch said, Schiff said during a Thursday interview on CNN. It may have been very well choreographed, very specific intention to use those terms knowing that theyd essentially be leaked to the press.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dem rep: Gorsuch comments may have been 'choreographed' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interview with 'Star Trek: Deep Space Nine' Showrunner: Ira Steven Behr assembled his old writer's room to break the first new episode in almost 20 years  and filmed what happened for a new documentary. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Republicans Rand Paul of Kentucky and Mike Lee of Utah have joined Democrats Chris Murphy of Connecticut and Al Franken of Minnesota to request a classified briefing from the Trump administration on our actions and objectives in Yemen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bipartisan group of senators demand Yemen briefing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The Trump administration is considering a bold and controversial vision for the U.S. space program that calls for a "rapid and affordable" return to the moon by 2020, the construction of privately operated space stations and the redirection of NASA's mission to "the large-scale economic development of space," according to internal documents obtained by POLITICO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump advisers' space plan: To moon, Mars and beyond </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Trump, Pirate-in-Chief.](https://i2.wp.com/www.danielholdings.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/Trump-pirate-1.jpeg)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And? The Republican crooks running the White House and Congress don't care about the law anymore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 04:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to see him finishes 'The Night Chronicles' trilogy. Shyamalan produced the first movie in that trilogy called 'Devil' in 2010   there were plans to produce two more movies with similar supernatural theme but nothing happened since then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With Split a Hit, M. Night Shyamalans Master Plan Is in Motion: The surprise box-office hit is just the juice the director needed to launch a cinematic universe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shailene Woodley is Officially Passing on the Divergent TV Movie: No, Im not going to be on the television show. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Season 5 was the best of the entire series, I re-watch that season every year when I feel like watching 24. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 17:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the [source article](http://www.politico.com/story/2017/02/trump-foreign-leaders-phone-calls-234770): 

 At one point, Trump declared that the French can continue protecting NATO, but that the U.S. wants our money back, the official said, adding that Trump seemed to be **obsessing over money.**" It was a difficult conversation, because he talks like hes speaking publicly, the official said. It's not the usual way heads of state speak to each other. **He speaks with slogans and the conversation was not completely organized.**

Trump is a national embarrassment.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US military to rent space in Trump Tower </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 02:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 00:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  and he was a perfect fit for Tom Zarek.

Absolutely. Loved his take on the character of a rebel-turned politician and then back to his roots by the end.  

Rest in peace, Richard Hatch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Richard Hatch, Battlestar Galactica star, dead at 71 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 00:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Oklahoma City' Explores Anti-Government Sentiments That Contributed to Bombing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 22:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 22:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Senate Minority Leader Chuck Schumer (D-N.Y.) on Tuesday accused President Trumps Supreme Court nominee of wriggling out of answering questions at a closed-door meeting. "The judge today avoided answers like the plague," Schumer said of Neil Gorsuch. "This president is testing fundamental underpinnings of our democracy and its institutions. These times deserve answers and Judge Gorsuch did not provide them." 

Edit: And here is what Sen. McCain said in October.

 [Sen. McCain](http://www.npr.org/2016/10/17/498328520/sen-mccain-says-republicans-will-block-all-court-nominations-if-clinton-wins) Says Republicans Will Block All Court Nominations If Clinton Wins: "I promise you that we will be united against any Supreme Court nominee that Hillary Clinton, if she were president, would put up," he declared. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Schumer: Trump's Supreme Court pick 'avoided answers like the plague' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 22:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 21:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't watch the WH daily circus, did Jim Acosta, CNN's White House correspondent, corrected Baghdad Sean or he wasn't given a chance to ask any questions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 20:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you like to know more? 

[Civil Forfeiture: Last Week Tonight with John Oliver](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3kEpZWGgJks) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Theresa May jokes about Donald Trumps hands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 20:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of this has happened before and will happen again.

Making a TV show based on a movie is not something new; the trend comes and goes every decade or so. Sometime it works beautifully as in the case of Buffy, Stargate SG-1, Hannibal, Terminator: The Sarah Connor Chronicles, Bates Motel and most recently Westworld but most of the time they dont find an audience and get axed after a season or two like what happened with Minority Report, Dominion, The Firm and Limitless.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TV Ratings: '24: Legacy' Soft Again in Time Slot Bow, 'Timeless' Goes Low </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im currently watching The Flash and The Expanse. Back in the days I used to watch more shows regularly; from Lost, Boston Legal and 24 to Battlestar Galactica and The Wire, nowadays I just dont feel the same about any of the current shows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump's logic! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  President Donald Trump, asked this morning why he thinks the press is not reporting on terror attacks  a stunning claim he made yesterday in a speech to military personnel  told a pool reporter, I dont have to think, I have to know. Because I am reported on, possibly more than anybody in the world, he said. I happen to know how dishonest the media is. I happen to know stories about me that should be good  or bad, you know I dont mind a bad story if its true. But I dont like storiesthat should be a positive story when they make them totally negative. I understand the total dishonesty of the media. Better than anybody. I let people know it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump Knows Press Not Covering Terror Attacks Because He Is Most Reported-On Person In World </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israel targeted under law passed to help 9/11 families sue Saudis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 17:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 17:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Rosie ODonnell on Monday tweeted that she would be up for portraying Chief White House Strategist Steve Bannon on SNL if asked to do so, after a report about the president's anger at SNL's portrayal of his team led to a social media push for her to get involved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rosie O'Donnell: I'll play Bannon on 'SNL' if asked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 17:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 03:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And right on time, Trump is attacking them on Twitter just now

 [Trump](https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/828793887275761665): The failing @nytimes was forced to apologize to its subscribers for the poor reporting it did on my election win. Now they are worse! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 03:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a FULL 15 MINUTES! Everyone was smiling, everyone was happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 03:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you watch his very [first briefing](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K9Chqb5uoUA)? It was hysterical, Period.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House rattled by McCarthy's spoof of Spicer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 02:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 02:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama did NOT approve it.

 [NBC News](http://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/yemen-raid-had-secret-target-al-qaeda-leader-qassim-al-n717616): After the election, the Pentagon presented President Barack Obama's team with a broad plan to accelerate U.S. counterterrorism operations in Yemen, and **the Obama administration referred the proposal to the incoming Trump team**.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 02:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The list covers from September 2014 to December 2016 and lists 78 ISIS-led attacks it say occurred worldwide. The list includes such notable attacks as the **November 2015 massacre in Paris and a mass shooting in San Bernardino, Calif., that same year**. There are 78 attacks listed on this list, Jim Acosta, CNNs senior White House correspondent, said on-air. "**Its a head-scratcher as several of these, we here at CNN and other international news outlets, covered these extensively.**" All of these, youll recall, we covered extensively. Its puzzling as to why the White House would include these attacks on this list when they were covered for days on end." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kevin Feige Hints Marvel's Movie Future Lies In Space: "A lot of our upcoming movies will be as much up here as they are on Earth," </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 01:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alan Tudyk on playing Batman's ridiculous cousin on NBC's Powerless </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 01:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 00:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know. It's rather weird that regardless where he goes, whether it is at the CIA or CentCom, he always bring up his election win, the ratings and the huge numbers ..etc  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 00:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  For now, Republicans will stick with Trump. But even they must be asking themselves: What does Russia have on him? Video of sexual shenanigans, as that notorious dossier suggested? Big bank loans? The only way to find out is an FBI investigation, as called for by House Minority Leader Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.). What business ties does Donald Trump have with Russia? The American people have a right to know. And Congress has a duty to find out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Press: Trump  to Russia with love </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 00:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 00:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "largely based on an accumulation of data" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 00:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He hung pictures of the inauguration in the press room at the White House.

[A picture with the wrong date!](https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/823937936056008704) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 23:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you can check the accuracy of the list with Agent Jack Bauer at CTU.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 22:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right on, I'm going to borrow this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 22:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Why everyone keeps focusing on their attention on such unimportant bullshit is beyond me.


[Trump speaking to the troops at U.S. Central Command](https://twitter.com/cspan/status/828681692466515968)

 "We had a wonderful election, didn't we? And I saw those numbers and you like me and I like you." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump claims media is covering up terror attacks, citing no evidence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 21:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 21:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm beginning to worry that they're planning a false flag major attack on US soil.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 21:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then who's going to tell us about the T-Virus outbreak in Raccoon City?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is some serious Orwellian shit coming from POTUS.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'John Wick: Chapter 2': Film Review - Keanu Reeves reunites with Matrix co-star Laurence Fishburne in this action-packed underworld sequel. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Trump seemed particularly incensed by reports and parodies about chief strategist Steve Bannon being the actual decision-maker in the White House. I call my own shots, largely based on an accumulation of data, and everyone knows it. Some FAKE NEWS media, in order to marginalize, lies! Trump tweeted. The message came at 7:01 a.m., 52 minutes after Joe Scarborough, whose MSNBC morning show the president is known to watch religiously, had suggested that "maybe Bannon's calling all the shots."

The most thin-skinned POTUS in the recent history of the Republic.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump leans on fake news line to combat reports of West Wing dysfunction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "Aides confer in the dark because they cannot figure out how to operate the light switches in the cabinet room, the Times reported Sunday. "Visitors conclude their meetings and then wander around, testing doorknobs until finding one that leads to an exit."

Team of idiots.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Trump seemed particularly incensed by reports and parodies about chief strategist Steve Bannon being the actual decision-maker in the White House. I call my own shots, largely based on an accumulation of data, and everyone knows it. Some FAKE NEWS media, in order to marginalize, lies! Trump tweeted. The message came at 7:01 a.m., 52 minutes after Joe Scarborough, whose MSNBC morning show the president is known to watch religiously, had suggested that "maybe Bannon's calling all the shots."

The most thin-skinned POTUS in the recent history of the Republic.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 18:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure we do but Trump doesn't care about separation of powers and the Republicans are doing nothing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 18:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sure looks like they're trying to destroy the other branches of the government. 

 Bannon: Im a Leninist, Lenin wanted to destroy the state, and thats my goal too. I want to bring everything crashing down, and destroy all of todays establishment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 18:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the NYT article: 

 Aides confer in the dark because they cannot figure out how to operate the light switches in the cabinet room. Visitors conclude their meetings and then wander around, testing doorknobs until finding one that leads to an exit. 

WH is runs by idiots.

 From now on, Mr. Trump would be looped in on the drafting of executive orders much earlier in the process. Another change will be a new set of checks on the previously unfettered power enjoyed by Mr. Bannon and the White House policy director, Stephen Miller, who oversees the implementation of the orders and who received the brunt of the internal and public criticism for the rollout of the travel ban.

Seems that talk about 'President Bannon' got under his skin.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 18:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Spicer told Fox News in an interview conducted Sunday but broadcast Monday morning. He utilized that power in a very legal, constitutional manner to ensure that we are safe, our people are safe, our country is safe, our institutions are safe. And its somewhat sad to see a judge go rogue like this. Its a shame, Spicer continued, that were not focused more on making sure that were applauding the decision by the president to make a renewed focus on keeping this country safe.

This is NOT normal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spicer: Judge who blocked Trump's travel ban went 'rogue' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 18:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Aides confer in the dark because they cannot figure out how to operate the light switches in the cabinet room. Visitors conclude their meetings and then wander around, testing doorknobs until finding one that leads to an exit. 

WH is runs by idiots.

 From now on, Mr. Trump would be looped in on the drafting of executive orders much earlier in the process. Another change will be a new set of checks on the previously unfettered power enjoyed by Mr. Bannon and the White House policy director, Stephen Miller, who oversees the implementation of the orders and who received the brunt of the internal and public criticism for the rollout of the travel ban.

Seems that talk about 'President Bannon' got under his skin.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  his most frequent tweets are between 9 a.m. and 10 a.m.  which sometimes coincides with his daily intelligence briefing

Trump: Iran is playing with fire, but our new super secret weapon will launch soon from Haifa. "Evil" will be stopped. Strong!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Sen. John McCains (R-Ariz.) son, Jack, deleted a tweet Sunday that appeared to criticize President Donald Trumps comments on Russian President Vladimir Putin. My nation of laws just got compared to one that murders journalists that dont fall in line and kills political opposition. Awesome. the younger McCain wrote on Twitter in a post that was later deleted. [...] McCain, a member of the Navy, later tweeted, "I just don't want to cause a fuss," apparently in response to the focus on the deleted tweet. 

Edit: Guess Sen. John McCain, the leading Republican *dissenter* wasn't too happy about it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John McCain's son deletes tweet slamming Trump's Putin defense </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> McCain all talk, no action.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> McCain, do something or just STFU.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  In mid-December, with Donald Trumps ascension to the presidency looming, former Republican congressman Jack Kingston flew to Moscow. Kingston, a senior Trump surrogate, was dispatched to liaise with American firms working in Russia. The topic on everyones minds was the U.S. sanctions imposed on Russia in response to its 2014 annexation of Crimea and support for a pro-Russian insurgency in eastern Ukraine.[...] On Feb. 2, the U.S. Treasury Department announced that it was amending the sanctions against the FSB to allow American electronics companies to again import electronics to Russia  something AmCham was explicitly lobbying OFAC to address.[...] For the moment, the visit by Trump surrogate Kingston is the only acknowledged contact the group has had with the new regime. Both sides have been evasive about these discussions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> American Business Lobby In Moscow Sees Sympathetic Ally In President Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course, the so-called President is still attacking the Judicial branch. He knows that the Republicans will do nothing whatsoever to stop this madness.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Siberian gulag.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really should have watched 'Event Horizon', the ONLY good movie by Paul W. S. Anderson, again rather than this mess of a movie!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 01:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like someone is preparing the ground for a False Flag attack.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 03:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The movie was actually based on a TV show from the 70s.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 00:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, hopefully we'll get back control of the Senate in 2018.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 23:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Democrats should listen to what [Sen. McCain said last October.](http://www.npr.org/2016/10/17/498328520/sen-mccain-says-republicans-will-block-all-court-nominations-if-clinton-wins)

 Sen. McCain Says Republicans Will Block All Court Nominations If Clinton Wins - Speaking on WPHT-AM radio's "Dom Giordano Program" in Philadelphia, McCain pledged to obstruct any Clinton Supreme Court nomination for the current or any future vacancy. "I promise you that we will be united against any Supreme Court nominee that Hillary Clinton, if she were president, would put up," he declared. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 23:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The damage is done! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 23:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The movie came out in 2003 and apparently there was a direct-to-DVD sequel in 2011.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 19:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Obama's team is also wondering why Trump, who repeatedly criticized the unemployment figures issued under the Democratic president, is suddenly taking credit for new job growth at the end of Obama's term.[...] "Don't believe these phony numbers," Trump said in February 2016. "The number is probably 28, 29, as high as 35 [percent]. In fact, I even heard recently 42%."[...] And Obama officials -- many of whom left their offices weeks ago -- were left to laugh at how Trump is taking credit for the jobs numbers. "**It was, indeed, remarkable that the unemployment rate fell from 42% to 4.8% on January 20th,**" said Austan Goolsbee, the former chair of Obama's Council of Economic Advisers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 19:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  After we are shown that there is really no interstellar expedition and that it's all a crazy science project

There was a short story by J.G. Ballard from the 60s called 'Thirteen to Centaurus' with a similar theme.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 19:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The worst was that the show was advertised as Syfy's return to the space odyssey genre.

But they did that. Now we have 'The Expanse' the best space-based series out there, also 'Dark Matter' a fun space show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 18:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the hell? 50 bomb threats in just one month.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 18:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  MSNBC and Fox News are capitalizing on President Donald Trumps TV watching habits, dramatically increasing issue advocacy advertising rates in recent weeks as companies and outside groups try to influence Trump and his top lieutenants. The ad rates for Morning Joe have more than doubled post-election, according to one veteran media buyer. Trump, who reportedly watches the show most mornings, has a close relationship with Morning Joe host Joe Scarborough, and they talk regularly. Fox News The OReilly Factor and other primetime programs on Fox News have boosted their rates about 50 percent. Trump also is a frequent viewer of the networks primetime shows. The presidents media habits are so predictable, advertisers migrate to those areas, said one media buyer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TV networks hiking ad rates for shows Trump watches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 18:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 18:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  MSNBC and Fox News are capitalizing on President Donald Trumps TV watching habits, dramatically increasing issue advocacy advertising rates in recent weeks as companies and outside groups try to influence Trump and his top lieutenants. The ad rates for Morning Joe have more than doubled post-election, according to one veteran media buyer. Trump, who reportedly watches the show most mornings, has a close relationship with Morning Joe host Joe Scarborough, and they talk regularly. Fox News The OReilly Factor and other primetime programs on Fox News have boosted their rates about 50 percent. Trump also is a frequent viewer of the networks primetime shows. The presidents media habits are so predictable, advertisers migrate to those areas, said one media buyer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TV networks hiking ad rates for shows Trump watches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 18:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> S.W.A.T. Reboot Directed by Justin Lin Picked Up to Pilot at CBS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 17:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 17:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Steve Mnuchin may be headed for U.S. Senate approval as Americas next treasury secretary, but hes getting a big thumbs down from a film lending company that alleges in a lawsuit that the Wall Street and Hollywood financier helped cheat it out of more than $80 million. In a legal filing late Thursday, RKA Film Financing accused Mnuchin and eight others of allowing money intended to release films from Relativity Media to be misspent for other purposes. Some $50 million of the misspent money went to a bank that the treasury secretary-designate founded, the lawsuit contends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steve Mnuchin Faces Fraud Claim Related to Relativity Media </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 17:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 17:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, /realitycheck123456 is a Trump supporter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 17:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The little-noticed section, appearing immediately after the travel ban, calls for the government to develop a uniform screening standard and procedure for all individuals seeking to enter the United States. As written, it appears to require all visitors to go through the same vetting measures, regardless of where they come from or how long they intend to stay. If interpreted as broadly as its written, It would basically shut down tourism, said Stephen Legomsky, the former chief counsel for U.S. Citizenship and Immigration Services during the Obama administration.[...] Former government officials from both parties pointed out that enforcing it would be virtually impossible with current resources, either forcing the administration to abandon the standard or dramatically reducing the number of foreigners who travel to the U.S. They just cant physically do it. It really cant happen, said Legomsky, who also pointed out that if they did, it would cause blowback that would hurt American travelers as well. Other countries would reciprocate some of our constraints on U.S. citizens seeking to travel, he said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 17:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None,  the miniseries ended on a massive cliffhanger.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 16:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the update, I was under the impression it was true until I saw your comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 16:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is citing support from non-democratic Gulf countries Kuwait, UAE and KSA. All expressed their support for Trump's ban, and Kuwait ~~imposed its own travel ban as well~~!     

Edit: The Kuwaiti government denied reports about its travel ban.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 16:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually there are more than just those two. 

Carnivale, Rome, Boardwalk Empire, The Borgias, American Horror Story, Bates Motel and others that I've not seen but are listed on [Wikipedia](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Incest_in_film_and_television#Television).

I don't think that TV is "obsessed' with incest but there seem to be more shows with that theme, perhaps as a result of GOT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 05:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another amateur hour at the White House. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 04:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Swedish Deputy Prime Minister Isabella Lvin on Friday posted a photograph of her signing a climate change law surrounded by an all-female staff, in what many are calling a dig at U.S. President Donald Trump. The picture looks remarkably similar to a picture of Trump signing an executive order to restrict access to abortion while surrounded by five male advisers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Swedish government pokes fun at Trump with all-female photo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 04:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 04:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I've started to think we need a nuke or two before we become your goddamned Poland.

How about a [Canadian wall](http://i.huffpost.com/gen/3463484/images/o-CANADA-WALL-SOUTH-PARK-facebook.jpg)! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 03:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A key to this enterprise will be good intelligence on the U.S. This isn't a call for spying in the clandestine sense; Canada hasn't spied on the U.S. in any serious way since the 1860s and isn't about to start now. What Canada does need to do is to draw on our existing intelligence system, not to prise out U.S. secrets, but to assemble the best possible analytical picture of developments happening in the U.S. We need a full exploitation of open sources, diplomatic reporting, messaging from high-level contacts  friendly and otherwise  and expert views. This analytical effort needs to be at the heart of our networking strategy, to ensure that we are calibrating our Canadian messages for maximum effect  mindful of the president and his inner circle of political appointees such as Chief Strategist Steve Bannon, and son-in-law and senior political advisor Jared Kushner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Opinion - With Trump in the White House, Canada needs better intelligence on the U.S. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 03:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 02:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  When the president-elects son, Eric Trump, jetted to Uruguay in early January for a Trump Organization promotional trip, U.S. taxpayers were left footing a bill of nearly $100,000 in hotel rooms for Secret Service and embassy staff.[...] Despite the use of public funds, government agencies would not provide key details connected to the trip: including the duration of the stay, the name of the hotel or the number of booked rooms. A spokesman from the Secret Service, citing security concerns, declined to comment. The money for the hotel rooms was paid through the State Department, but a spokeswoman there declined to comment on the trip. She instead referred reporters to the White House and back to the Secret Service, whose spokesman once again declined to comment. The White House also did not respond to requests for comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eric Trumps trip to Uruguay cost U.S. taxpayers nearly $100K in hotel bills </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 02:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 02:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Until we make it normal that brothers and sisters can fuck, she continued. "I think that'll still be the only interesting aspect of sex that remains. Maybe. I don't know. "I've never tried it... yet!", she joked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Taboo' star Oona Chaplin: Where does the taboo lie now? I think it's in incest. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 02:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 02:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't wait to see more of Upside Down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  [Trump](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tk6icmI5QLM feature=youtu.be): We expect to be cutting a lot out of Dodd-Frank, because frankly I have so many people, friends of mine, that have nice businesses and they cant borrow money. They just cant get any money because the banks just wont let them borrow because of the rules and regulations in Dodd-Frank. So we'll be talking about that in terms of the banking industry.

Trump is a good man, looking after his rich friends! /S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1984, the Hot Book of the Trump Era, Is Coming to Broadway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, thanks for the correction.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, [32% of the total votes that Obama received in 2008 came from Republicans](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_States_presidential_election,_2008#Voter_demographics).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * In 2008 election [74% of Obama voters were white.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_States_presidential_election,_2008#Voter_demographics)

* In 2012 election [72% of Obama voters were white.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_States_presidential_election,_2012#Voter_demographics) 

Edit: I read the numbers wrong, see SarcasticallyAShill's comment below.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vancouver artist's anti-Trump cartoon takes off on social media: Pia Guerras image has been retweeted over 27,000 times as of Thursday evening </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 15:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Democratic playbook"? Are you fucking kidding me? 

Who blocked a Supreme Court nominee for a whole year and refused to even allow a hearing? Are you so dense that you're arguing about a hypothetical block from Democrats in the 90s that NEVER took place, while ignoring what the GOP did last year. 

The GOP obstructed Obama in every step and we sure as hell should do the same with Trump.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 03:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Trump in June 2014](https://twitter.com/realdonaldtrump/status/474134260149157888)

 Are you allowed to impeach a president for gross incompetence?

You betcha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 03:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 03:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may want to finish the quote: 

 It would be our pragmatic conclusion that once the political season is underway, and it is, action on a Supreme Court nomination must be put off until *after* the election campaign is over.

Biden didn't object to resuming the process after the election. 

The Democrats are following the GOP playbook in 2016, and the GOP are whining about it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's hypothetical since there was no Supreme Court vacancy to fill   the Democrats didn't delay anyone. 

The GOP didn't give Merrick Garland a chance at all, and now they're irritated because some Democrats won't meet with Gorsuch? Fuck them and their fucking hypocrisy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 01:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Republicans spent much of the last year ignoring Merrick Garland. But just two days into the latest court fight, and conservatives are already irritated with Democrats who havent yet agreed to a private sit-down with Neil Gorsuch, President Donald Trumps nominee for the Supreme Court.

The never-ending hypocrisy of the Republicans.

Edit: And here is what [Sen. McCain](http://www.npr.org/2016/10/17/498328520/sen-mccain-says-republicans-will-block-all-court-nominations-if-clinton-wins) said last October: 


 Speaking on WPHT-AM radio's "Dom Giordano Program" in Philadelphia, McCain pledged to obstruct any Clinton Supreme Court nomination for the current or any future vacancy. "**I promise you that we will be united against any Supreme Court nominee that Hillary Clinton, if she were president, would put up,**" he declared. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP, Dems at war over Gorsuch meetings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 01:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 00:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Andrew ['I like beautiful women eating burgers in bikinis'](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2AdViveJYD0 feature=youtu.be) Puzder approves this message! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 22:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rubber-stamp Congress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 22:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll find more shows, such as 'True Blood'   'American Horror Story', listed on [Wikipedia](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Incest_in_film_and_television#Television). It's not just those seven shows. 

Edit: And no, I'm not saying that TV is "obsessed' with incest but there seem to be more shows with that theme, perhaps as a result of GOT.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 21:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Until we make it normal that brothers and sisters can fuck, she continued. "I think that'll still be the only interesting aspect of sex that remains. Maybe. I don't know. "I've never tried it... yet!", she joked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 21:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Donald Trumps reported favorite for EU ambassador is already facing headwind in Brussels, with some officials keen to teach the American president a lesson over a potential diplomat they say is anything but diplomatic. Ted Malloch, an economist with ties to the presidents inner circle, has raised eyebrows by comparing the EU to the Soviet Union (which he claims to have helped bring down,) saying that the bloc needs taming. He has also spoken disparagingly of Jean-Claude Juncker, suggesting the European Commission president was a very adequate mayor, I think, of some city in Luxembourg and maybe he should go back and do that again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brussels threatens to block Trumps EU ambassador </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 21:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 20:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carnivale, Rome, Boardwalk Empire, The Borgias and Bates Motel come to mind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 20:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Digging into hard truths (as Chaplin puts it, your worms) of human relationship, Hardy has come up with an incest plot as the ultimate will-they, wont-they, should-they love triangle of Taboo. Until we make it normal that brothers and sisters can fuck, Chaplin says, returning to the theme of taboo subjects, I think thatll still be the only interesting aspect of sex that remains. Maybe. I dont know. Ive never tried itshe pauses and laughs. . . yet. Thats an answer that could make even a Lannister blush. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Game of Thrones' and 'Taboo' Star Oona Chaplin Explains Why TV Is Obsessed with Incest: Where does the taboo lie now? I think its in incest. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 20:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 17:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  While committee rules typically require at least two minority lawmakers be present to conduct business, Republicans suspended that rule to allow Pruitt's nomination to proceed. Since Republicans have only a one-seat majority, Sen. Jeff Sessions had to appear for the vote to go forward. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans advance Pruitt to floor despite Dem boycott </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 17:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dutch will hand count ballots due to hacking fears </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 02:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 01:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reuters:

 The program, "Countering Violent Extremism," or CVE, would be changed to "Countering Islamic Extremism" or "Countering Radical Islamic Extremism," the sources said, **and would no longer target groups such as white supremacists who have also carried out bombings and shootings in the United States.**

By the order of President Bannon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump plans to reshape counter-extremism program to focus on Islam: report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 01:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 01:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to AP and a Mexican site called Aristegui Noticias Trump used those words:

 "You have a bunch of bad hombres down there," Trump told Pena Nieto, according to the excerpt seen by the AP. "You aren't doing enough to stop them. I think your military is scared. Our military isn't, so I just might send them down to take care of it." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 01:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  President Donald Trump threatened in a phone call with his Mexican counterpart to send U.S. troops to stop "bad hombres down there" unless the Mexican military does more to control them itself, according to an excerpt of a transcript of the conversation obtained by The Associated Press. The excerpt of the call did not make clear who exactly Trump considered "bad hombres,"  drug cartels, immigrants, or both  or the tone and context of the remark, made in a Friday morning phone call between the leaders. It also did not contain Mexican President Enrique Pena Nieto's response. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump threatens Mexico over 'bad hombres' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 01:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 01:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russia, if youre listening, I hope youre able to find Trump's tax returns and leak them. I think you will probably be rewarded mightily by our press! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 00:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great, who needs clean water anyway?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 00:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're following the same philosophy and act as rubber stamp Congress. They don't even mask it anymore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 23:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe the 400-pound hacker from New Jersey!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 23:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  **Ive been asked by both my party and my caucus to commit to not criticizing the president for the remainder of his term and to take a more partisan approach to working in the Legislature.**

For people still waiting for Republican controlled Congress to serve as a check on Trump, there is your answer. 

Edit: Some people seem to think that the actions of the Hawaii Republican Party are not reflecting the thinking of the GOP-led Congress in Washington. All you need to do is watch what they were doing since January 20. Congress is practically rubber-stamping Trump nominees; and both Paul Ryan and Mitch McConnell are unwilling to criticize Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 23:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump: "I went to the best schools. I'm like a very smart person." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 23:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most likely someone from Earth 2! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 22:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The Three Musketeers is like 400 years old 

Must be in your alternative universe since in our universe 'The Three Musketeers' was published less than 173 years ago, in 1844!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 22:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But Douglasss work is already well known among historians, commonly taught in high school history classes, and championed by some Republicans (because Douglass was a Republican when the party was still the party of racial justice). Hes not at all unknown. That made Trumps comments that hes only recently being recognized a bit strange, so a reporter asked White House press secretary Sean Spicer what Trump meant. The answer did not inspire confidence that Spicer knew what Trump meant, or that either Spicer or Trump even know what exactly Douglass did, or that Douglass has been dead for more than 120 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do Donald Trump and Sean Spicer know who Frederick Douglass is? Its not really clear. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 22:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 20:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the event of a war Iran will definitely close the Strait of Hormuz, blocking a third of the world's oil supply.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 20:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Flynn says that "we are officially putting Iran on notice," although it's not clear what he meant. 

Take a guess!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump White House says it's 'putting Iran on notice' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 20:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 03:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Fox News has taken down a tweet about the Quebec City mosque shooter after a complaint was lodged by Prime Minister Justin Trudeau. Trudeaus office had asked Fox to retract or update the tweet, which described the alleged Quebec City mosque shooter as being of Moroccan origin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quebec mosque shooting: Fox News removes tweet after Trudeau complaint </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 03:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democrats line up against Trump's Supreme Court pick </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 03:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 03:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Via The Hill, Democratic super-PAC American Bridge opposition research on Supreme Court nominee, Neil Gorsuch.

[Neil McGill Gorsuch: First Look - Research Report.](https://americanbridgepac.org/app/uploads/Gorsuch-SCOTUS-Report.pdf)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 00:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our Robot Overlords are doing it!!


[The New York Times: How to Destroy the Business Model of Breitbart and Fake News](https://www.nytimes.com/2017/01/07/opinion/sunday/how-to-destroy-the-business-model-of-breitbart-and-fake-news.html?_r=0)


 The activists back-and-forth with companies reveals a fog of confusion surrounding online advertising. Many organizations have no idea that their ads may end up next to content they find abhorrent. You might blame this  in part  on robots. According to the research firm eMarketer, American companies are now spending more than $22 billion a year on programmatic ads, the kind of advertising that is bought with little human oversight.[...] When you click on a link, in less than a second, a call goes out, and algorithms and automated software bid in an auction to put their advertisement up on your page, he said. So maybe the Nabisco algorithm wants to put an ad up there; so does Macys and so does Honda. The algorithm that places the highest bid wins the chance to appear on your screen. Programmatic ads can also follow individuals around the internet, based on their browsing history, as happened with Mr. Philips. A single targeted ad could cost just a fraction of a penny, but the pennies add up to a billion-dollar industry. Even when ad placements are automated, companies still have the power to control whether neo-Nazis or fake news hucksters profit. In fact, its actually rather simple for companies to impose ethical policies, according to Mr. Zeitz. Indeed, his own company (which handles programmatic advertising for other organizations) recently decided to get out ahead of the issue by removing Breitbart News from its advertising marketplace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Two Canadian universities are among the organizations that have removed advertisements from an ultra-conservative news website formerly headed by a top adviser to U.S. President Donald Trump. The move is part of a campaign spearheaded by Sleeping Giants, an American activist group, aimed at diverting advertising dollars from Breitbart News, a far-right media outlet that came under fire during the 2016 presidential race. [...] Sleeping Giant says so far 750 advertisers around the world, including some in Canada, have blocked Breitbart from their media plan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canadian universities pull ads from hard-right news outlet Breitbart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 22:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Trump had been expected to sign the order in the Oval Office on Tuesday afternoon. Its unclear whats behind the delay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump delays signing executive order aimed at strengthening cybersecurity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 22:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 21:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  While Spicer was adamant on Tuesday that the executive order not be represented as a ban, that is how he personally represented the policy as recently as last Sunday. Speaking to ABCs This Week, Spicer described the executive order as a 90-day ban to ensure that we have further vetting restrictions so that we know who is coming to this country.

You can't fix stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 2015 both Sorkin   Lowe said that were willing to to revive West Wing. 


[Rob Lowe](http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/entertainthis/2015/10/15/rob-lowe-aaron-sorkin-west-wing-reunion/73980514/): If Sorkin writes it, I'm in. 

[Aaron Sorkin](http://www.radiotimes.com/news/2015-11-13/the-west-wing-reunion-could-happen-says-aaron-sorkin---but-only-if-rob-lowe-is-involved): Rob Lowe said hed do another episode of the West Wing if I wrote it, Sorkin told RadioTimes.com. If I ever got an idea for another episode of the West Wing, I would do it  but only if Rob Lowe promised to be in it.

I think it is a matter of finding a network/streaming service that is willing to finance the project as well as fresh stories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Star Trek: Discovery teases new uniforms, sets, captain's chair </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 19:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 18:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Under Trump the pharmaceutical companies are 'getting away with murder'. Very Weak!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 02:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time delay between Moscow and Washington, D.C. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 01:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Israel is home to around 140,000 people born in the seven countries covered by the decree, including around 45,000 Iranians and 53,000 Iraqis, according to official statistics. [...] The US Consulate in Jerusalem referred a question by AFP to the US State Department, which several hours after being asked to respond was still unable to clarify whether the ban includes Israeli Jews. The Israeli authorities were also seeking clarification, foreign ministry spokesman Emmanuel Nahshon told AFP.

Edit: CNN's chief national security correspondent Jim Sciutto [tweeted](https://twitter.com/jimsciutto/status/826105186162790405):


 Israel seeking clarity on #TrumpTravelBan - 145,000 Jews born in 7 countries listed in EO incl 54,000 in Iraq   45,000 in Iran ... Answers to these questions will be indicative: preference for Christians + exceptions for Israeli Jews = (by definition) religious test </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israel seeking clarity over US travel ban: ministry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 01:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 01:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Defense Department spokesman Maj. Jamie Davis said that it would violate regulations to fly that flag on a military vehicle. "That is not standard procedure, he said as quoted in the report. Davis said it would also violate regulations to run a military convoy with no unit markings on the vehicles, and said he did not think the vehicles belonged to any service branch. Per the report, he suggested that they were military surplus. Tracey Metcalf, administrator for the Military Vehicle Preservation Association, said the color of the convoy suggests the vehicles did or do belong to the Army. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mystery Convoy Of 'Military' Vehicles Flying 'Trump' Flag Spotted In Kentucky </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 01:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 01:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  almost like a shadow NSC

More like a shadow government.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 23:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're correct that it is not precise to put In the Loop in the timeline like that; however, I re-watch the entire series, TV specials and the movie in that order. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 23:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really, 'In the Loop' is written by the same team and it fits rather well in 'The Thick of It' universe with similar characters   situations. We have both Malcolm Tucker   Jamie McDonald, also Ollie but with a different name. 

So not a different universe altogether, but rather a Sideway Universe!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CNN Beefs Up Investigative Reporting: The legendary investigative reporters Carl Bernstein and James Steele, both Pulitzer Prize winners, will serve as contributing editors to advise the team on their work and executives on hiring. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 23:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 22:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First they came for the media: 

[Steve Bannon](https://www.nytimes.com/2017/01/26/business/media/stephen-bannon-trump-news-media.html?_r=0): "The media should be embarrassed and humiliated and keep its mouth shut and just listen for a while, I want you to quote this, the media here is the opposition party. They dont understand this country. They still do not understand why Donald Trump is the president of the United States.


[Kellyanne Conway](http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/316750-conway-on-the-media-when-are-they-going-to-fire-these-reporters): "Not one network person has been let go. Not one silly political analyst and pundit who talked smack all day long about Donald Trump has been let go," I'm too polite to mention their names, but they know who they are, and they are all wondering who will be the first to go. The election was three months ago. None of them have been let go."


[Trump](https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/825690087857995776): Somebody with aptitude and conviction should buy the FAKE NEWS and failing @nytimes and either run it correctly or let it fold with dignity!

Then they came for the dissenters in the Senate:

[Trump](https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/825823217025691648): The joint statement of former presidential candidates John McCain   Lindsey Graham is wrong - they are sadly weak on immigration. The two senators should focus their energies on ISIS, illegal immigration and border security instead of always looking to start World War III.


Then they came for the diplomats.

The message is loud and clear, NO DISSENTERS are allowed in Trump's America.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
