<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3750</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should be called for it even more. Rafa, Murray and Nole especially spend a ridiculous(spellcheck someone) ammount of time getting ready. Disregard my flair but I think that Federer is one of the quickest  to get on with it, atleast in the upper ranks of tennis.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 11:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Cited". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 11:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a choke when you have an advantage and the momentum going your way and the match going to your strenghts but fuck it up anyways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 11:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao virtually no injuries, like that should be an argument. Its not Rogers fault that Rafa has a physical style of play as opposed to his so he gets more injuries, plus Federer has had back and knee injuries and mono to top that off. Dont forget that Rafa doesnt have more than two titles on any GS besides the French when Fed has 7,5,4 on Wimby, US, and AO respectively. More consecutive weeks, more GS finals, semis, and quarters, more total weeks on top, and definitely a more consistent player. And isnt Davis cup a team competition, and the only good player either in singles or doubles to come out of Switzerland is Stan besides Roger. Not discrediting Rafa but i think Rog has the better resume. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 11:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I understand that, every single match was the forehand-to-backhand experience which was only interesting when Federer defied it. Clay was especially boring, but I will always consider it the greatest rivalry of all time even though it scarred me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably the application for the move to Vegas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 00:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How bout dat Rondo guy?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 16:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dont you mean #18?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 17:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah my bad, I keep forgettin what year is it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 17:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no ah, you dont see an a anywhere in his name so you dont say it. Thats why I said its closer because its a lot smaller difference if you say joh-koh instead of jock, than if you sad djok - o - vic, instead ov djok - a - vic. I mean I hear his name atleast 25 times a day now so trust me on this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 15:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, its not. Im from Montenegro, right next to Serbia, we speak the same language and Joh-koh-vich is lot closer than the other pronunciation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 13:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2014 Roland Garros is carved in my memory.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 21:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Voted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 14:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah well need screenshots, your social security number, blood type, fingerprint scans and your mothers maiden name if you want us to verify your outrageous story mister.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 14:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont know if thats my dream or my worst nightmare considering Rogers form... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 14:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cant help but feel I have seen the same syndrome on some swiss guy with three grandslams, I could ve mistaken though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 15:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why the fuck would you stand like that? If you have no intention of playing the point anymore, just turn around, no need to act like a badass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 02:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its Federer. They'd put him on Centre Court even if he was in a casket with a racquet on top. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 22:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And he scored against them in the cup 3 days ago. Proud to say thats my national team captain, and an all around nice guy, I even met him a few times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 03:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck is happening right now?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 19:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even NBA is hit with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 21:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where does Moss rank on that list, atleast in your personal opinion?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 18:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do flags have to be thrown every play? Of course not. Plays that you can challenge are ended with a decision that has to be made, they have to decide if its a catch or not, first down or not. Flags of course are necessary but dont have to be thrown constantly, however these calls have to be made constantly. 
I agree that you should be able to challenge plays, just that is unlikely, cause the organization and the refs would hate to be wrong on something they dont necessarily have to be. 
I should probably say that I started following nfl since the last season and this is based on my watching so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 17:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im guessing because when you challenge a call as of now the call had to be made, for instance the reciever was either in or out of bounds so the refs were forced to make a decision. If they challenge flags, they dont have to be thrown, and are the refs direct influence on the game. If you challenge them it would either be mostly confirmed or when they are overturned would cause an outrage because someone would interpret it as refs intentional tampering with the play. 
TLDR; 
Flags arent a necessary call and refs would hate to be wrong about something they didnt have to be, as well as the NFL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 01:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or a football.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 17:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean a trade can be completed without Boston?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 20:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tom Brady. Cause he's pliable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 02:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LeBrown Jaylen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 20:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just quit betting. Number one rule of betting is dont bet the money you cant afford to lose. If things arent going well right now, and you lost a significant ammount of money that its do or die for you just lay low.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 17:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trading one of the worst defensive centers to one of the worst defensive teams? What could go wrong... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 11:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The same level? Yeah, I agree Embiid has a hell of an upside, The Process and what not, but AD is already a superstar, putting up 50 points more than once a season, and just a year older. He is in another league, so the Embiid comparision is just wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 23:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw a comment that it was just a bad ankle sprain, no need for another long term solution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 23:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dont want to be rash or anything but Emerson is the best left back of all time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 21:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just fuck me up fam. The curse of the right back strikes once again, the only solution now is for Taddei to come back from retirement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 07:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HE THINKS HE'S PEOPLE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 15:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isnt the suspension just for the FA competitions?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 00:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This feels like the time when Nemanja Vidics(world class soccer player) father pulled out his dick in a bar and said "This dick made the best defender in the world".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best betting sites with a sign up bonus? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 19:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need a betting site with a signup bonus, easy verification and withdrawal of money. European based so I dont have any problems, and already have an acc on bet 365 so something like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 23:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah man, you dont want that lockerroom cancer with your young core that loves basketball. We will gladly take him, in exchange for Kelly 'the clinic' Olynik and a 2020 second rounder, who says no?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 01:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cashed out for considerably less money tonight cause I had the Pats on money line, when we were down by one. We looked kinda shaky, but I forgot that the piercing baby blue eyes of a God always find a way when trailing in the fourth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 20:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you are saying Kawhi worked out with Kobe this summer? Thats amazing, no wonder he is playing better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
