<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2069</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has his plan to clean up the streets of drug dealers actually worked? Are the streets there any safer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love in the "horror" part of conker hes dressed as van helsing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The guy deserved it for robbing dominos. At least go for pizza hut, not that crap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I just find him hokey and lame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just think strange is a character from the 70s whos never evolved. I like the idea of paranormal hero, but more like constantine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mad, girl? Fuck the EU :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved that ending </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hated dr strange. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leaving the EU long term will be an excellent decision.

Looking at the rest of europe outside of the UK, and the path they are going down, I have zero regrets about leaving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This shit needs to stop. Political correctness has gotten fucking insane. Its madness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Yes but Dr Who is critically acclaimed.  None of the reviews mention what a great story cod zombies has. And ok ill conceed it has a story. Its just a terrible one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anime is garbage imo. And the "story" might be there, but its god awful. Literally every sci fi trope thrown into a blender. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a shit story. They threw in everything they could think of  . Dragons, fantasy, time travel, etc. Absoloute nonsense with no restraint,

And dont get me started on the easter eggs. What an obtuse, crappy way to jump through hoops for scraps of story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You handled it far better than this dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Youre right, what she did was shitty but he completely overreacted. You gotta realise theres no honor or strength in destroying a woman not even half your size </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What she did wasnt right, but attacking someone a third your size doesnt make him look any better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weirdest fucking request ive seen here lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont remember this comic, do you have the cover? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually quite liked what i saw of yagers version. Id love to know what went wrong. I wonder if its a similar story or scrapped from top to bottom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im with you, the new one isnt as great at the reviews would have you believe. Weak gunplay, meh story and horrible alien designs. Honestly just lazy alien designs, just inky blobs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try the wolverine game. Its superior to the movie, has more fleshed out story and totally r rated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok dont think youre getting what I mean lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it looks interesting.  But would have prefered newcomer rather than cruise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trolling? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brendan fraser mummy pop would rock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  What, not expecting a massive franchise to have merchandise?

Imagine hugh jackman when x men first came out saying "nah no figures", or any of those huge movies, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Story" lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calling it a story is a massive stretch  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats weird he took such a huge franchise role and didnt want merchandise </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Nick Morton mummy pop got cancelled? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah let me know how that works out in the next massacre.

France chose and deserves its fate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats when i was going to. They dont seem to have advertised it well!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And france will ultimately lose </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They announced it for psrv nothing since </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are at war already. This guy just makes it easier for them  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda a shame its not like zombi, a fps zombie game in london in vr would be amazing. Does it have a decent story mode? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happened to arizona sunshine? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looked so good but nothing since it was announced for psvr </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol might see you there! Been looking to get his action figure for ages! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else going? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im not even far right, nicr assumption lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im not alt right, but its not my people getting shot up over a cartoon lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont like trump but he dropped the biggest non nuke on them. Hardly a win lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lost what? Its not my country! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its great news for ISIS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Londoners! Meet AJ Styles tomorrow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was tempted to keep this to myself lol but naww i aint like that.

Aj styles will be at selfridges toy section in london at 11am tomorrow. Wristbands avalible from 9.30 first come first serve

I finally am going to get my hands on his action figure and hopefully get it signed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More imported male  refugees of fighting age= a win for isis.


Its like france never learns, no matter how much blood is shed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on who you mean for. EU? Yes. Terrorists? Yes.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 10:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I genuinely dont understand why it got such bad reviews. I enjoyed the story too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 10:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> France's new leader, Angela Merkel, is pleased </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did anyone else really enjoy xcom declassified? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 10:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved the original xcom reboot a few years back. And i remember when this was intitially a fps by 2k marin before getting totally rebooted.

It got crapped on at release but i gotta say i really enjoyed it. It was a solid squad shooter, with great retro style designs . 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 10:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the aliens have really bad, bland designs. Makes it hard to find them or the story interesting, they are just inky blobs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 10:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its growing on me. Its not game of the year, and nowhere near as interesting as the initial prey 2 concept, but its solid. Not gonna take RE7s game of the year, so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 10:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because some crimes deserve no rehabilitation. I will never accept a mass murderer nor rapist or child molester deserve a second chance. Its not about cost.  Its about justice.  I see other countries that kill rapists and murderers and wish we had that. Our prisons are luxurious in comparison to others. Yet victims are scarred for life , if they are even still alive, and families lose loved ones. Fucking human rights give these scumbags the same rights, if not more, as the families they destroy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 10:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, they are bad games </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well i believe in strong punishment then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont like the tories either tbqh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Posions you and does attacks that smash your guard. I gave up on it when i had to fight three cheap sourcerers in the woods at once </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think im left wing most social issues, and shes an embarassment. I could not vote for any party with her in a prominent position </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im not even right. I just find it mind boggling to see people defending idiots like diane abbott </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats true, the donald are pathetic for that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wish there were more like you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant in terms of echo chamber spiel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In bloodborne that giant church beast was insanely badly balanced </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its like the donald just total opposite. Youre either fully left or downvoted or drowned out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When your dictator pretends to stop being tougher than he is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah raise your kids in one of the european countries with higher terror attacks. Smart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is this forum just a left wing echo chamber? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Notice the much bigger guy struggled for a few take downs. He got him eventually but considering the size difference  thats no surprise </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Played it , played all three. The grinding and tedious dying over and over ruined it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really surprised. Thought you guys were tougher </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same thing lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive played it, its grinding to get better stats and even then stupid one or two hit kill bosses </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would you ever go there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thought russians were tough, not pussies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The lanky kid may have lost but made dude work for it. Had decent take down defense considering other dude was way bigger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With putins military might couldnt he just flatten chechneya?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So much for russias hard man image! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Writer said otherwise </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats amazing. Did he get his life back on track? I hope so. That was moving </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im simply saying if you want to insult my taste in games or imply i dont try new games, lets compare trophy lists. I can prove i likely play more varied games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didnt like dragons dogma at all.

And i loved a lot of games this year. Resident Evil 7 is a modern masterpiece as was horizon zero dawn

And JRPGS never change so i found your comment ironic LOL. And compare our trophy lists and tell me who plays more diverse games </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 12:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate those genres.  I hate the designs of those genres, i hate the gameplay trappings. And most of all, the stories dont interest me in the slightest. Why would i spend money on games with mechanics and stories i know Id hate? 

And the problem with nioh is that exactly. It borrows the worst part of souls. Its not that its a clone, i dont mind that. But the difficulty ruined the souls and bloodborne games for me. So why would i want something that takes the worst parts of it? I genuinely dont mind "inspired by" games. Nioh asthetically looks good, seems interesting story, but i dont have the patience for souls style difficulty. Had they given it an easier mode, would have been interested. Same with the Surge. Looks great story wise and world wise, but again, difficulty borrowed from souls turns me off.

If you know a jrpg with a good story and gameplay which is NOT turn based, tell me and ill look i to it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 11:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its sad that people dont think like this untill it effects them personally </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 11:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a garbage country and garbage leader. It makes me so happy Im born in the west. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 11:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dont see a problem with this. Need to be tougher with this stuff instead of victimising people defending themselves </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 11:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get the feeling youre right on walking dead. Sumo digital is working on dead island 2 so i have hope for that. The retro revenge and escape dead island were garbage spin offs though so they have a lot of work to do to get series back on track </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 11:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dont what </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 11:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But its not different from outlast 1. Significantly worse even. It doesnt work in open settings, theres no real atmospheric downtime like the first, it mixes docile enemies with violent ones,  you pretty much are trial and erroring thru the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 11:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How so? Explain, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 11:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Id love to enjoy souls and bloodborne, but the difficulty kinda ruins it for me. Great asthetic design though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 11:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Resident Evil 7 is mine. Dont see it being topped </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed it did. And these guys seem just as shady. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think turn based works in RTS but not story based RPGS imo

Hmm i might check out nier then. The obtuse stories is what hurts anime style games usually </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed 100%. All the rest of the shitshow around them just confirmed it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My issues were the broken solo mode, and then they said "if you dont like it buy pc version". That shows their character and lazyness . And then the dlc fiasco...

Im guessing there are problems behind the scenes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except when it comes to actual voters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. Even though i didnt like payday, they are incredibly shady. 

I honestly cant believe these guys are the ones that got the walking dead license  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If these politicians didnt write dodgy emails, they wouldnt need to worry about leaks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So is nier worth a try even if i dont like the anime style?

And exactly, turn based doesnt work in an rpg imo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only problem with this is its from the lib dems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That game was broken if you wanted to play solo. I know it was mp focused, so was left 4 dead, but that works solo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The original had an excellent opening too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah its def not unplayable or anything. Its decent enough.

I also think part of me wishes it were more like the original prey 2. Thats not fair on the game i know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Footage

https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=WsrOcUiBXr0

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overkills walking dead delayed again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To me, Niers style and persona are both anime. To me, anime is crap. Does that sum it up?

And jrpgs are terrible too . thats how i genuinely feel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have little confidence in overkill to be honest. This is gonna be another colonial marines. Its 4 years from announcement to release and thats even if it makes 2018 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Walking Dead by Overkill delayed to end of 2018 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would people be pissed off at my opinion? Are we not allowed different opinions? What part of what i said are you referring to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great comics. A fantastic trilogy and one of my earliest comics read </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Luckily I only care about going to America! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He'd be arrested for rape nowadays </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah its a well made game for sure. I feel guilty for not liking it more. Felt the same about dishonoreds. On paper they have stuff i love...but some reason doesnt click. I wouldnt ever put someone off playing it though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dont let me put you off, give it a try. You might like it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
