<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2257</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 19:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe George Orwell had a good phrase for this: perpetual war. Welcome to 1984 guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 18:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did something similar with a few of my friends, but it only lasts for about 15 minutes. If you go to Nash Grier or one of those kinds of teenage heartthrob Instagram accounts, and comment "OMG. THIS IS NASH'S REAL NUMBER I JUST TRIED IT: xxx-xxx-xxxx," their phone will blow up with about 5-10 calls for every time you do it. From experience, there are additionally some pretty insane teenage girls that will call you.

EDIT: The best time to do it is at 2:00 AM, it's bound to wake whoever your victim is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 17:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sad ad for fishing buddy has spread like mad

jeez chill out dr. Seuss this isn't a time to be glad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 01:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This dog really kind of looks like a seal. Given his love for water, he might be a seal. You should get Dash tested to see if he's a seal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every one of those photos was taken in Missouri... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 00:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 00:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am no history major, but from what it appears to me, Greece seemed to be the ideological foundations for Rome, and Rome is widely considered to be a far superior implementation of those ideals. Because Greece was primarily independent city-states, there was no sense of your stereotypical 'civilization,' as there was no single ruler or concentration of power. On the other hand, the Roman Empire was the most extensive empire in western history, because it was all unified under one governing body and one ruler. This allowed for much more concrete progress to be made, whereas much of Greece's progress was solely ideological. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 02:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The disaster can now drink. I need a drink. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Royals pitcher Danny Duffy is reportedly buying all of the memorabilia he can find involving Yordano Ventura, his late teammate, so that he can send it to Ventura's mother in the Dominican Republic. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 20:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 07:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want to have nightmares tonight, just imagine that they didn't clear off the ground well and he slid over 3 inch wide jagged rock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 23:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No no no no no. Hold up a volleyball with a smiley face written in a bloody handprint. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 23:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you meaning to tell us that you're an author AND the best WR on the AFC champion Patriots? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what is the weirdest way you have found to make money? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone who uses "I was drunk" as an excuse. You chose to get drunk, now own up to what you did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who wear shorts on a cold day and then complain about the cold. If you're so cold, how about you accept society's thousand year old development to keep you warm? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, you must've loved this [AskReddit prompt ](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/5q6afi/serious_people_who_had_an_affair_that_ended/?st=IYEIP5G8 sh=14fd9c3d) then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you saying that daily Golden Showers and Cleveland Steamers contribute to an unhealthy relationship? Because I sir, would say otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 05:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but if we are magically able to ask for stats after our death, I'm making the assumption that this scenario allows for this holy statistician to compile unbiased advanced metrics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 03:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we're going to have true statistics, then I believe we should have some advanced metrics as well.

Human Living Index: measures your amount of life experiences and compares them to the average human lifetime, and then your score is how many "lifetimes" you have lived.

Human Love Index: similar to the Human Living Index, except it measures the amount of love you've experienced in your lifetime and measures it in relation to the average person.

Morality Index: Measures how your decisions were on a moral basis in relation to the average human.

I feel like these would give me a pretty good indicator if I really lived a good life or if I was just lying to myself the entire time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 03:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> KD ratio, including all those I inadvertently killed by setting off some obscure chain reaction of events. Hopefully it's still 0. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 03:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that I can message someone 5000 miles away and they will receive it within seconds is utterly astonishing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the most unintentionally ironic you have ever seen someone be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 03:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 03:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before you begin criticizing me, do you actually know when Hurricane Katrina happened? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 02:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if u paralyzed from the neck down dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 01:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, beings that she's a quadriplegic, that's probably pretty hard for her </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 00:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When they ask me to repeat something, I repeat a small fragment of what I said, and then keep repeating hay small part whenever they ask.

EXAMPLE:

ME: Who was that you were talking to?
PERSON: What?
ME: Who?
PERSON: What?
ME: Who?
PERSON: What?
ME: Who?
PERSON: What?
ME: I'm an owl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 00:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does your wife know about your PM's full of boobs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 00:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, because that additional 'i' totally exists and should be pronounced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 00:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're telling me that if a female quadriplegic Hispanic Medal of Honor recipient who has a child with Down's syndrome and a husband with cancer, it's okay to make fun of them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 00:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who drive Supercars. It's apparent that they have a fair amount of money, so it's okay if they deal with the occasional small dick joke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 21:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was very clearly going off-script whereas Mike Myers was on a teleprompter. Also, he was saying something very controversial and he probably recognized that, and that probably made him nervous. Further, he had just released his first studio album the prior year, so he probably wasn't all that experienced under the spotlight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 21:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In honor of Brent Musberger's retirement announcement today, we can't forget the time *during the national championship* that he took 30 seconds to [practically worship Katherine Webb.](https://www.youtube.com/shared?ci=H0Q1uUjTVRs)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 20:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whatever you like by TI was an absolute banger. Also see Whatcha Say by Jason Derlo. 2 of the greatest songs ever written. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it's a Giant Eurasian Rhino from 1914. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it's a Eurasian Giant Rhino from 1914.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That Jarrod Dyson series of quotes was what really hit the feels for me. Very well written article for a vey, very tragic event. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHO'S A GOOD GIRL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 02:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> or 100% wrong, 20% of the time  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 01:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was in my junior year of high school, so I don't know if I'd necessarily call her such an endearing term like SO, but nonetheless after we had broken up I found out that she had been running a very dark bdsm blog that even escalated into her posting multiple fully nude pictures of herself online, despite the fact that she was underage. Gotta say, I dodged a bullet there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which songs would have their meanings the most distorted if Kids Bop did a remix? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 23:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 23:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> more like she can fuck me

EDIT: oh wait, just got finished </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 23:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, no, you've gotta have your back to them, and then line up someone tip to tip on either of them so you can get four in one stroke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you drive far enough you'll probably hit a cow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kansas is not 100% farms. It's more like 80%. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure the brilliant folk over at r/relationships would have a lot of wholesome suggestions about this topic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brickleberry. A lot of people have told me you have to be high to like it, but I thought after a slow first season, the second and third seasons were very funny. And no I was not high while watching it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bit about the spacebar/tab dilemma had my programmer father rolling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright so I see some people citing the fact that there is a lack of certain weather phenomena and that's better than the cold, so let me introduce you to Kansas.

While the cold may be much worse in other parts of the country, let me still remind you that Kansas is home to the windiest city, Dodge City, and I can assure you all those fucking hills out in the middle of fucking nowhere do nothing to stop the wind, so yes, when it's 15 degrees and there's that fucking wind, then yes, my face does indeed hurt.

What's worse is that we never get enough snow, or it's cold enough for enough days at a time to do anything fun in winter sports, like skiing(that's already impossible because Kansas is so fucking flat), or snowmobiling, or hockey. So we're mostly just stuck with an inconvenience of cold.

Being that I've already started this rant, I am going to finish it by addressing some of the weather positives that other people are citing as to why they don't mind the cold. I see many people saying "At least we don't have tornadoes." Middle of fucking tornado alley.  Two tornado warnings a year.

I also see people saying "At least we don't have earthquakes." Thanks to he beauty of fracking, we're starting to get those now, so hell yeah fucking right, man.

Also, our July temperature average is just as high as Miami, so it's not even like summer is all that enjoyable. Further, in the heart of Kansas, we get to very uncomfortable heat a considerable amount, considering Wichita had 53 100 degree days in just 2011. That, and to compile on this frustration, there's not an ocean right fucking next to us. It's just a fuck ton of grass. Oh yeah, have I mentioned that? There's a fuck ton of nothing.

Many of you are probably asking, why hasn't this self-putting Kansan answered the question yet? 

Well here it is: the people are nice. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 06:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ass Wipers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 05:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Virgins R Us, it's a hookup network that helps virgins who want to remain confidential finally have that special experience. After you lock in your first meeting, you also automatically get banned for life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 05:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Single moms/lesbian couples are stressed enough, why would you want to give them a kid with a guy who has a striking resemblance to Dog the Bounty Hunter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 03:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems as if you spent a while studying this guys penis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 03:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so you're telling me that you argued with a furious guy who had been charged with attempted murder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 03:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All served with a *very* Bloody Mary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 02:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this picture on the link to the tweet is suboptimal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I royals fan, I'm seriously about to cry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 22:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean this is kind of obvious, but the 1919 World Series really sucked considering *both teams* wanted the Reds to win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I went to sleep in 1917 and I just woke up today. How did I get here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 19:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 19:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Def just went on r/IAmA and said "I AMA from 1917, woke up in 2017. AMA." Let's see how this goes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I went to sleep in 1917 and somehow ended up here right now! AMA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 19:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 19:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was going to write some dumb comment, but then I read this one and realized how futile my sense of humor is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 08:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/im14andthisisdeep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 21:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a sign for 2017: mailmen and dogs are getting along. We will endeavor into the future with prosperity and understanding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Strong career inventory test is pretty great. It's 80 bucks usually, but most schools/universities can get you a discount, so for me it was only $20 bucks. It's probably the most comprehensive career survey out there with almost 250 questions, and it lays out almost any career imaginable and your compatible rating with that career. It convinced me to switch to a finance major from engineering because it's results overwhelmingly said I should pursue finance. Also, because of this, it could have a profound impact on your life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me and OP's mom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you said a little bit more expensive, I thought no big deal, but I wasn't expecting 260 dollars *for a bottle of glue* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WWII def didn't last 8 years for the US </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Married Redditors, was there a specific moment that you realized 'this is the one?' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 16:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 08:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *and after, highlighted by the one last week </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 07:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *when your mate tasted really good* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 00:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is "congrats on the sex" considered an NSFW comment  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 08:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean bro, those are pretty small tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 08:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *congrats on the sex* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 06:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would isn't necessarily past tense, it's a hypothetical, meaning it's used with present tense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 05:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> congrats on the sex </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 05:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smh, this way more romantic that it is now. For Christmas one of the girls on my foot got her boyfriend a framed(unused) condom and she added art to the wrapper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 04:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what did I screw up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you have an absurd amount of free time while at college, how would you spend it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 04:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 04:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> better butter croissants </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 04:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you should do it again but butter

Heart made out of butter. Regardless, it will go down well, but if she's from Iowa, her family will love you forever
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 04:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean I personally wouldn't have expected a smooth proposal from a man with the username dick-nipples </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 03:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rick Astley. Reddit would go full meltdown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 00:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any highlights you can think of? Specific links? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We lose yet another legend. Rest easy sweet queen. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 21:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 21:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I realize he initially did, but hadn't finished the eastern front and thus opened up a two front war  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 20:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hitler essentially saying that the French/English weren't valiant enough of opponents, so he went and attacked the Russians, *the country he had already signed a non-confrontation agreement with*, simply because he was bored and impatient. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 20:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How the hell is Reddit not rickrolling the shit out of this. I'm so disappointed in you all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 19:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean the username is weird_teengirl so probably a 40 year old man, but that's my guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 19:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't like what's attainable. As soon as you can have it, it doesn't really become a desire anymore, it becomes attainable, which means you can't romanticize the notion nearly as much anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 19:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> guys there is a specific subReddit (if you've been living under a rock, it's r/TheDonald) for this shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 19:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/KurtCoBANG </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 19:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm eating lunch and I def just got self conscious while eating </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Blackjack dealers of Reddit, how hard is it to get kicked out for card counting, and what are some good stories of people doing it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 16:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 03:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cards against humanity is predicated off the fact of people not having a soul, and I would have to say that it is indeed successful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 03:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pluto. To this day, because of my stubbornness, I will always tell you there are *really* nine planets </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He had one of those basements that open with a garage door </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 20:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/nottheonion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 18:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *finds the entire Baja region coated in flan* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 18:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, without white people, how else was the Apartheid supposed to happen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 18:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah ik, I watch baseball. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 07:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dude cougars are dangerous watch out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 07:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, I can't imagine what it would've been like going the first 14 years of your life without meeting a girl. That's rough dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 07:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not necessarily a joke, but I was once playing Cards Against Humanity and he prompt card was What's that sound? so I proceeded to play "the Virginia Tech Massacre" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 07:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Treating sex like it's an accomplishment that deserves congratulations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 07:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Oh my gosh! I've got my arm stuck in the aquarium, and I'm so wet already!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 07:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my brother's story, but he works as a furniture delivery man, and one older dude came in and bought the cheapest dishwasher that his store sold, and then they all go back to his house so my brother can install it. This guy was from Independence, Missouri, also known as one of the meth capitals of America, and he was living that sort of lifestyle. My brother gets into the house, and it's very rundown, and goes downstairs to see if the plumbing is all in sorts, and right there is siting a practically brand new 1963 Chevy Corvette.  Considering it was worth more than the everything in that house, and the house itself, combined, my brother being a car guy, asked about it, and the guy just responded with "it's been the only nice thing I've ever owned, and I can't bring myself to ever selling it." So ya, you never know what you'll find. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 23:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This reminds me of a friend who lives in a million dollar house but gets his water shut off three times a year because his dad(who ironically is an accountant) forgets to pay his water bill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 21:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FBItruck was a pretty good one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 20:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Kansas-Citian, I was infuriated when they put Cole slaw on the pulled pork sandwich and then said to put ANY sauce on it. If you put KC sauce on sandwich that NEEDS Carolina sauce, that is barbecue blasphemy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 09:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely the words to Down in the DM. Not just me listening to the song, but I made a conceited effort to memorize each word of the song. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 09:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sleeping. Still takes an hour to fall asleep, hence why I'm on Reddit rn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what is your worst case of the one that got away? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 09:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 09:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Back in my day" if a kid punched a kraut, he was really punching a prussian </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors living with romantic regret, is your worst case of 'the one that got away?' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 09:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 08:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> congrats on the sex </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 08:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You and every person who has ever taken a trip to Thailand  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 08:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, this experienced aged OP so much that he was a full 2 years by the end of the story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> *logs into facebook, immediately logs off* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 20:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 18:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Broccoli: 6/10
Broccoli with rice: 7/10

Would recommend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 04:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or it's like getting a hole-in-one in a girl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 02:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> congrats on the sex </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 02:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/wholesomememes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 01:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it was your camaro wasn't it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 01:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then why are you welsh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 01:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> congrats on the sex </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
