<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1989</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are there suddenly pictures of large hand tools all over the internet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 05:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 04:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well yeah, but sometimes the generalization doesn't hold. I know for example that the bad part of a fruit of cheese can be cut off and you still have good fruit or good cheese. Is tobacco, in this case more analogous to the fruit or to the meat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 03:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the least sarcastic voice you can read this in : Is the strain of mold that grows on tobacco *really* that much worse for your health than the tobacco itself?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 02:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Romeo y Julieta  very similar (Identical by all appearances but I can't say for *certain*)  to this one: 
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Romeo_y_Julieta_(cigar)#/media/File:Romeo_Y_Julieta_Churchill_Cigars_Tubo.jpg   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 01:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just posted it. 
Take a look and let me know what you think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has it gone bad? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 00:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone just showed me a cigar that came out of it's individual metal case. The first thing I notice is white, spider-web looking patches all over the end of it and I don't know if it's mold or what. 

http://imgur.com/a/tHI0m </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a good thing to throw out there in a game of Never-Have-I-Ever? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 19:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 22:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But price gouging doesn't just happen in shortages when supply is low and demand is high. It also happens when business people like Martin Shkreli simply think they can get away with charging what they want. What then?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 22:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, that's the go to reaction. But if the company that makes Epi pens lobbies to make the competition work harder to bring viable alternatives to the market (which they do) or car dealerships get laws passed to make it illegal to buy a new car any other way (which they have) or textbook companies pressure schools and professors to pressure students to buy the newest edition (which happens a lot) then it's hard for me to buy your argument (pun definitely intended). It's not a matter of the item being replaceable, it's how the ones that stand to profit make it difficult to replace.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: What is the best way to deal with price gouging? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 21:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Imagine you had a panel of professionals from multiple fields. What would you use them for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 18:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 17:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This brings something to mind.  
Who's line is it anyway?  
Scenes from a hat.  
"Bad things to do in a submarine."  
...  
"Oh it sure it stuffy in here. Let me go open a window!"  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> College graduates of Reddit, any advice for those who are still in college? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 08:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So Sheppard... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 08:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 00:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it's still possible to get your money back into your account if someone used your debit card to clean you out?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is it easier to forgive fraudulent purchases made with credit than with a debit card? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 23:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 20:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I almost bought the Audio Technica ATH-ANC9 because they are:

closed back

foldable

noise canceling (noise isolation is okay too)

over ear (on ear is also okay)

memory foam (nice but not a deal breaker)

$200

Features that they didn't have that I was looking for:

Durability (from what i have heard)

bluetooth/wireless capability

minimal noise leakage

All in all, I am looking for something to invest in for both my travel 
and my student lifestyle.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How are astrobiologists able to simultaneously be so sure of what to look for and that it will be drastically different from anything we recognize as life on earth? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 09:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A birthday is just a celebration of the fact that you were able to circumnavigate the sun one more time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 09:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 22:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realized that after I took a second look at the lips on the top of the mag. Haha.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 21:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is your ammo loaded backwards?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 17:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought I had a good pair lined up, then I noticed it was missing features I would like.

I almost bought the Audio Technica ATH-ANC9 because they are: 

closed back

foldable 

noise canceling (noise isolation is okay too) 

over ear (on ear is also okay) 

memory foam (nice but not a deal breaker) 

$200


Features that they didn't have that I was looking for: 

Durability (from what i have heard) 

bluetooth/wireless capability 

minimal noise leakage


All in all, I am looking for something to invest in for both my travel and my student lifestyle.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 07:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought I had a good pair lined up, then I noticed it was missing features I would like. 

I almost bought the  Audio Technica ATH-ANC9 because they are:
foldable
noise canceling (noise isolation is okay too)
over ear (on ear is also okay)
memory foam (nice but not a deal breaker)
$200

Features that they didn't have that I was looking for:
Durability (from what i have heard)
bluetooth/wireless capability
minimal noise leakage 

All in all, I am looking for something to invest in for both my travel and my student lifestyle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 06:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It just seems counter intuitive that bad press translates to increased sales.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How do successful celebrities attract so much bad press and remain successful? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 06:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are, in my mind at least, two different gorups here. One group contains Putbull, Gwenith Paltrow, and Nicholas Cage that just get a lot of hate but still get a lot of work. The second groups of celebrities are the Justin Bieiber types that, although they are performers and celebrities that have a brand, get in a lot of trouble and yet still have a solid following despite all the ridiculous situations they end up in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 09:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You thought after over 20 instilations of Bond films, we couldn't step it up? Well you were wrong! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if someone has to phonetically spell a word that stands for a letter in the phonetic alphabet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 08:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When searching posts, what's the difference between searching ALL and searching r/ALL? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 06:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm using the rif app in case that helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 06:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's seriously surprising. Every labradoodle I've ever seen (if you don't count these memes, apparently) has been blonde.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] The dog breed that gets confused for fried chicken and teddy bears. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 06:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The memes made their rounds on the web a few months back but I wanna actually know what breed of dog it is because no one is saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What little known website is good to know about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 10:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the least sanitary thing you have witnessed in a professional setting? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 10:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 10:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah! And the orange snake print her friend is wearing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 10:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone was right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do Pokemon suffer from Stolkholm syndrome? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 21:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does a tap transition from a solid flow of water to becoming really airated when you increase the pressure? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 21:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What song have you not yet bothered to learn all the words to? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 19:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 09:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool gun, sure, but I upvoted the title.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I balance wanting to change my physique with not wanting to change my wardrobe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 09:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the clothes I have, I just bought some, and I like slim fit and the snugger side of things. On the other hand, I don't want to be so skinny and not muscular. I have been granted the academic schedule of a lifetime with mornings off and will probably start working out in the mornings with the end goal of losing a little fat and gaining a little muscle. To the point of that latter goal, I want my measurements to change but am having a difficult time reconciling the investment in a new wardrobe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 07:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't inhale and I go for the milder flavors. I think if anything, I am smoking too fast out of fear of it going out. I already have yet to perfect my lighting technique to get a perfectly round burn without torching the end of the cigar to all hell. I don't wanna have to go back and relight. What frequency are you referring to? Is there a sweet spot or does it depend? And what does it depend on? I know, for example, that today was pretty windy where I am now. But I can't seem to make up my mind as to how to hold the damn thing when I'm not taking draws.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 06:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first impression, given by the fact that you are going an AMA, is that you are white hat hackers. How mellifluous do you get, can you get, and what stops you from abusing the power your skill set gives you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amateur here with an amateur problem. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 06:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dove into the world of cigars head first with my old man. He enjoys the finer things in life and I started enjoying them with him. I have enjoyed some decent cigars over the past couple years but embarrassingly enough, have not enjoyed them to the fullest extent. The larger ones go nearly halfway unsmoked before I get too nauseated to do anything. On on particular occasion, we went to lunch, came back and had a drink with some cigars, and then I lost my lunch in the sink. I know enough to admit that I  probably don't know enough about smoking 'technique' and want some advice. Is this a common limitation of a light weight or am I doing something wrong? Do I need to just walk away from cigars entirely?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 04:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leif's Auto Collision Center. The other driver's insurance company reminded me that I have the right to go to that shop anyway but because they weren't on the list of approved shops, I would not have the insurance company behind me if something went wrong and boy did something go wrong. I dropped my car off and was promised a call later with an estimated time. Thank god the other driver's insurance was paying for it so I was able to get a rental car and everything. I would get a couple calls a week explaining new delays, ever increasing costs, and apologies. I wasn't stuck with the bill but I was stuck with not having my car for nearly 6 months because of the delays. It got so ridiculous that the rental car company started harassing me. I told them it was out of my control and I almost got a heaping bill from them as well. When I got the car back, I found several issues with the paint job that no one wanted to take responsibility for and the adjuster just played dumb and said that he didn't see it. I was there with the adjuster and pointed to the problem areas. He simply toggled his glasses around and still acted as if it was flawless. Moreover, I asked the shop for a timeline of what the car was doing for 6 months that I was promised and never got even though I stopped by an extra few times after picking up my car. Instead, I was given a warranty paper that isn't worth the paper it's printed on. When I called them to act on the warranty, I got no response.  It's a mechanically sound repair, I will give them that much, but that, and the free coffee in their lobby are the ONLY good things I can say about my experience with that shop.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where did Sia come from? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 19:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Sia had a comfortable career, not as a performer, but as a writer of hits for other artists. Furthermore, I was under the impression that she never showed her face. I don't *think* I'm thinking of someone else entirely but that wouldn't shock me either. Why/when did she start performing and what was she doing before that? 

Edit: So the answers coming in so far are about her music career. [Insert thank you here for the answers] I'm still curious about the gimmick/schpiel/thing about her hair covering her face *except when it doesn't* and I just don't even know why or what to keep track of.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why are here so many different names for administrative districts within a country? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 10:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a *functional* difference between states, provinces, oblasts, cantons, etc, or is this just a case of translating gone... 'wrong'? 

Edit: There*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I had an amazing interaction with an elderly couple because of PokemonGo. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 04:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I was walking around town with my little cousin catching Pokemon in the evening. Ya know, the usual. He loves to remind me of what is on my radar and psych me out when he sees something on the radar that I think is finally in front of us. It's very hit or miss. Does he mean that there is a Geodude *here* or that there is a Geodude *somewhere*? Well for once, There turned out to be a Crabby in front of us. "Ooh. a crabby!" I hear from right next to me.  

Not 3 seconds later "Ooh. a crabby!" I hear from right behind me.  It was a grandma and grampa! So I started skeptically talking with them and it turns out that they weren't just mocking us! They were genuinely playing. They have a couple young grandsons and wanted something to bond with them over. We even went along the same road for a while catching some of the same things as we chatted. I gave them some pointers and they gave me some inspiration to get through the night with my cousin without getting mad at the psych outs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 09:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think that's a consideration anyone makes when reporting those numbers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 05:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A bunch more than just Martha come to mind but I was looking for a number.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the official headcount on the number of characters that told either Kate or Rick they are good for each other? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 03:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why, when tragedy strikes, is the number of wounded often significantly higher than the number of dead? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 00:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God forbid it was the other way around, but this seems like a general rule regardless of the cause; natural disaster, military conflict, mass shootings, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many evolutions do I have time for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 05:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, the first time I had a lucky egg, I evolved everything I could and still had pleanty of time left over. This time, I have run into the reverse problem of having probably too many things to evolve. Pidgeys as well as a few evolutions that will be simultaneously adding to my pokedex. How do I maximize those 30 minutes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by traveling and playing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 08:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I am traveling with the family right now and have played pokemon kinda off and on and have slowly been losing interest in it. We get into town and the little bro whips out his phone when we are walking around and LURES. LURES EVERYWHERE. So I caught a buuuunch of stuff today and got hooked back into it. I don't have enough data to sustain me through the trip and am kinda just screwed and sweeping my soon-to-be phone bill under the rug right now. Wish me luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just purchased Big Foot repellant. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 17:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Er, sorry, a camera. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some of the quintessential, must have arists/albums? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 08:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why not Johnson? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 08:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seriously seems like most of the Trump voters are swallowing the Trump pill because anything is better than a Clinton presidency and the Clinton voters are swallowing the Clinton pill because anything is better than a Trump presidency. Yeah, I know, the Johnson campaign said that almost verbatim, but I honestly thought it myself before I even heard of Johnson. Anyway, Johnson is now on the ballot in every state at least as far as I'm aware, so who is changing their allegiances and if not, why?

Edit: Soon after posting this, I learned that there have been developments regarding Johnson and even Stein ending up on the debate stage alongside Clinton and Trump. thoughts? I personally don't think they'll get the opportunity to sway enough voters even if they end up on stage purely out of the clash of the titans that we have been anticipating all year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many political positions are held by animals, why, and are there any that are not democratically elected into office? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 08:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 10:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds like you would recommend the fruit roll up.... but it also sounds like you wouldn't recommend sex in the living room soooo I'll get back to you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some common shortcomings that are often addressed with a prescription that don't have to be and what is the alternative to the medical approach? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 10:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some common shortcomings that are often addressed with a prescription that don't have to be and what is the alternative to the medical approach? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 10:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 05:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gnar gnar gnar  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 05:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> blip </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 04:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like $8 went a long way. They even took the patch off his left sleeve! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 04:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 in the hand is better than 1.5 in the bush.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 04:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of good books out there are designed for continuing education for inspectors. The last one I purchased, when read in it's entirety, gave me a good idea of how to revamp my checklist on inspections and even a few new techniques for inspecting. A good place to start is definitely your state's approved list of accredited educators and purchasing reading material from them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you have any particular opinions of any particular pasta shapes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 03:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Positive or negative, I'm all ears. I'm just curious what opinions are out there, and no pressure, but I made a bet with a friend, so lets see what the results yield. 

Edit1: I'm actually learning a lot from the comment section but the particular argument with my friend hasn't been won or lost yet so keep it coming. 

Edit2: So in light of finding out that different shapes actually do serve different purposes, and have not purely been created as a consequence of the sheer amount of time Italians spend in the kitchen as per my previously held belief, I'm losing the bet. The verdict is still out on the exact pasta shape that we were discussing, which, hint, has actually (and only jokingly) been talked about in the comments so far. I'll keep you posted.

Edit3: I lost the bet. Friend has yet to be informed. Macaroni noodles, despite being the de facto option for mac n' cheese, don't do the good job they 'pretend' to do of getting entirely coated in cheese as the cheese option is usually too viscous to get into the tiny holes. I stand corrected. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Use it or lose it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 20:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This hit me pretty hard today. My first language is not the one I speak most of the time but it's the one spoken at home with family and I grew up with the culture and all. Today, I had 3 separate interactions with heavily-accented people from the same part of the world as my family, and with my lack of accent, the only way they would have known is me telling them, or if they maybe took a look at my last name and guessed. But even so, I was so embarrassingly insufficient with that language that I couldn't muster enough up to carry the conversation so we reverted back to English. Lesson learned, of all the things in the world to be the final straw, interacting with strangers was it. Use it or lose it guys, every part of every language you know is an invaluable part of you and the potential you have to reach out to others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 07:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But there has got to be more than stylistic differences. I'm also talking about the different color palettes that different animators seem to use. If you have ever seen a cross-over of characters into different universes, the character who leaves home into the new universe and is often animated differently is, I guess drawn by whoever but colored by the host universe...if that makes sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How are animators of different shows and movies able to come up with completely distinct visuals? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 07:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There has got to be a name for it but I don't know how I can look at a scene from two different animations, completely absent of characters, and still be able to pick up on what show it belongs to. Assuming you know the show, you can just match up at a glance a still-frame to the corresponding show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you become more assertive without becoming aggresive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 07:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have decided to *try* to be better but the failed attempts have so far worried and bothered loved ones. I am pretty damn ready to stop being a pushover in certain areas of life but whenever I try to leave that non-confrontational comfort zone of taking it and lamenting it, my missteps really shock people, especially family, who drop the topic at hand to ask what the hell is wrong with me and it's so maddening that it ends up being counterproductive. Thoughts? How have you successfully changed parts of your personality and let your loved ones in on the change in a way that they stopped being worried for you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much abuse can a watch realistically take? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 03:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 01:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cal (a calendar app that syncs all your email accounts), Evernote, Photomath, myHomework, Merriam Webster dictionary app, Productivity Challenge Timer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 19:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So does that mean that particle accelerators like CERN are colliding nearly infinitely hot particles?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If rising temperature is the result of particles moving faster and more violently, then what temperature do we reach as that movement nears the speed of light? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 18:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 08:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, that difference between watts and amps is what I was looking for the explanation on. I figured as much that it was a simple matter of addition, and I understand, on principle, how a breaker works, but actually getting the rundown of knowing why you don't see 64 power strips connected to 8 power strips connected to 1 power strip is really great. haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 07:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just have a hard time visualizing 12/15 amps in on one end of the power strip being that same number out on EVERY outlet along the strip.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 06:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HE LOOKS SO HAPPY TO BE THE ESSENTIALS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 06:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did that. The error I get after following the instructions I found reads the following.  

"Blu-ray error:
This Blu-ray Disc needs a library for BD+ decoding, and your system does not have it.


Your input can't be opened:
VLC is unable to open the MRL 'bluray:///E:/'. Check the log for details." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 06:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The audience doesn't dismiss the validity of the claims though. He prefaced his own speech with that, his background, and the fact that he didn't know why he was speaking at a marketing conference besides the fact that he was asked to. If that takes any legitimacy away from the point he was making for the entire rest of the speech, then I guess we have to agree to disagree.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How are power strips able to draw enough from one outlet to adequately feed multiple devices? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 06:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Short conversation with a friend. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 06:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 03:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've installed it and followed the instructions. There are even tutorials online how to download it correctly because it does get kind of convoluted. Still no success.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that millennials don't exist. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 03:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The average pencil is just seven inches long, with just a half-inch eraser- in case you thought optimism was dead." - Robert Brault </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 02:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What thing did you not think you needed until it became indispensable? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 02:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 01:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too soon?  

Too soon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 00:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never heard of it. Does it check the quality, trusted, and free boxes?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 00:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally as in that's what the flag has been *crowned*. If you want to be pedantic about it, then I'm doubly sorry for personifying an inanimate object and giving you the impression that I think flags have vaginas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Norway literally has the Mother of all Flags. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 23:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Windows 7, Blu ray, and Codecs/drivers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 23:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I just learned about the fact that Windows 7, by design, doesn't support Blu ray and anm trying to work around that. I have an LG bp50nb40 disk player plugged into a Dell Laptop (Latitude series). Credit to the older post that brought up the same issue here.  

https://www.reddit.com/r/windows/comments/lfman/stupid_windows_7_question_is_there_native_support/  

Does the driver for this player double as a codec or what? What are some good, trusted, affordable/free options?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am traveling a lot this summer and am giving myself the bag space for 1 24-disc CD wallet. What should I pack it with? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 22:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want to suggest it, assume I have it, and if you want to assume that I have or haven't seen it, go ahead there to. This isn't a top-movies of all time request list, but more of the 'Your house is burning down and you can only grab a couple things, what would they be?' type of survey. 

EDIT: Christ! Thank you u/kile35 for being the ONLY one to give me an answer instead of shit for the mere mention of CDs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 21:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you rather is a fun game. Would you rather have mesothelioma or have your house burn down faster?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 21:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this price gouging or just currency conversion rates?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What song lyric really surprised you when you found our what it really was? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 17:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If DiGiorno's pizza isn't deliver, then how is it delivered to the stores? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 06:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Troubleshooting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 04:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, firstly, I have contacted tinder about this and haven't heard back from them yet so with the minimal amount of pissieness possible, here is the problem.. 

For the last two weeks, not one of my matches has saved. I'm talking about getting the notification, opting to message later instead of message now so I can take a second look at the profile, and then the match disapears entirely into thin air. (Which is just beautifully madening considering a friend changed some things about my profile and I finally started getting a good amount of matches.) So like any normal person, I logged out and back in, I force restarted the app, I restarted my phone, I even deleted some old matches that went nowhere, all the meanwhile, checking new matches between the steps with no success. So okay, I have already lost a lot of matches, what have I got to lose? I try something different, hit message now THEN go into the profile and hit the back button. That works! But it shouldn't be the ONLY way I can save my matches. Something buggy is happening. Am I the only one? Any advice? Is this a common problem? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What repetitive action would make for a confusing gif? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 01:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE have a hard time giving nonverbal ques with the facial expressions that say something other than what you want? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 00:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like resting bitch face only definitely not JUST that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 21:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's also a good chance that the companies paying for the ad realize that and go ahead anyway because they still have to advertise. I mean, I don't like ads either, but reminder ads actually do wonders for some companies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 20:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can sometimes catch glimpses of vloggers talking about their income stream. As far as I know, it is all up to the channel. The unskippable ads are the more lucrative ones for the channel but because they take away from the YouTube experience, a lot of channels try to find sponsors or go for the skippable ads instead.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 11:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, the good ol 4 Ss. Back in my day, we had the 4 Hs. Herpes, Hepatitis, HIV, and HPV.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we pretty pretty please get an unbiased, non-opinionated, level-headed look at all the candidates? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 08:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll preface this with yeah, wrong sub probably, but if you feel like participating in the comment section, cool, if not, I'd love some direction on where to go with this.  

2016 American presidential elections in case that needed clarifying. It doesn't even have to be on issue stances. I can find that myself. What I haven't been able to find is a news outlet that I trust to give it to me straight and tell me the merits and shortcomings of each option. Not like cannon-fire coming from the other side of the aisle, but like rational, reasonable human beings that don't want to crucify the criminally dumb that disagree with them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the difference between golfers and skydivers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 06:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Golfers: *smack* Shit!  

Skydivers: Shit! *smack* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What should men make of what Jenna Marbles has to say to us? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 04:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I, as a guy, watch some of her videos and think that it's some really good insight into a woman's perspective on things. On the other hand, I am constantly wondering how representative her advice and opinions are. She talks about everything with such a matter of fact tone, which may contribute to her success, but I genuinely want to know if I should eat it up, take it with a grain of salt, or not take it at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should guys listen to Jenna Marbles has to say? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 03:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the closest world capitals are Brazzaville and Kinshasa. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 03:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If alcohol lowers your core body temperature despite feeling warmer, is it okay to drink to cool down in hot weather assuming you are well hydrated? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 03:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 02:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tonight on the Darwin Show; top posts in r/holdmybeer all get honorable mentions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 01:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't paying attention in a merge lane and the lady that was behind me and on my left was flipping me off and expecting me to continually be an aggressive driver so I cut her off like she probably expected.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After all these years of the same old thing, how come no one has had success in attempting to reinvent the wheel. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 00:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stupid question about a car I spotted. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 22:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm working on an entire album of cars that I have r/spotted over the years and will publish it all when It's 'complete'. The album so far consists of a Bentley, McLaren, Audi r8, GTR, Lambo, and a few Ferraris to name a few. Anyway, I pulled up on a Mazda SRX7 the other day and thought 'aw, what the heck.' and took a couple pictures. Is it r/spotted worthy or nah? It's got an older body style, I'm going to guess that it's from the 70s, with a 40 spray-painted onto the side.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are Darwin Award acceptance speeches so rarely televised? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 21:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 20:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.ptable.com/#Orbital shows you the actual shape of the atoms. I like your wallpaper but if you are feeling up to a redesign, I think it'd look really cool.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What celebrities (of the sfw variety) have the best subs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 19:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 19:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in the same boat basically with my fam. Would you mind me fielding some of the questions they asked you just to brace myself and not be a deer in the headlights?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's talk about changing majors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 08:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I started my college experience right our of high school at community college so that I could afford to be indecisive. Once I, well, settled into a major out of sheer impatience with myself and a little pressure from the family, I found a good university to transfer to, I love the place, I'm moved into the town, and am starting at the new school next month. It actually turns out that it's a good university for both the major I switched from and to so I got lucky there. Problem is that after all of the major changes, I went with one more at the 11th hour and have been wierdly selective about who I tell about the new one but default to the previous one and just feel guilty about the lie. Its almost completely unwaranted but I got the idea from a friend of mine who changed so many times that they felt unaccomplished every time the switch was brought up. That's at least the impression I got. Anyway, what to do? How do I break out from this hole I've dug for myself? I imagine telling my family about my new major as if I was coming out of the damn closet but I don't want it to be a big deal either. I can't be the only one in this boat! What are some of your experiences with this? Any advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What will we leave behind for future civilizations to piece together our lives with? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 22:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 18:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything you buy on an airplane, college, anything you buy in a movie theater, anything you buy from a student store, anything you buy from a dealership other than the car itself, and anything in a specialty store.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 18:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you self employed as?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 22:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long does this gif last for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An old post of mine that didn't get any love in r/jokes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 02:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some grammar Nazis told me about a seminar they are going to attend about cause and effect.

They're there to affect its effect and it's there for their two affects too.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 02:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this is what golf was more of the time, I think more people would appreciate the sport.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How do the studies that disprove the ability to multitask dismiss the ability to do multiple simple tasks at the same time such as walking and talking? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 00:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is definitely a Butter Face car if you have ever seen one? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 23:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 07:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Low Key Loki </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 05:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, respectfully, what about it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 05:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's better than teacup pigs in teacups.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A friend of mine started watching the LOTR movies for the first time and we spend twice as long as you would normally as she realized that something from that movie was source material for a pop culture reference. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 05:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 05:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this a thing that exists?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 05:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cycle because college and parking passes are more expensive than a year's worth of bike gear and maintenance. Even if I wanted to still have my car with me and exclusively use my bike for the commute between class and home and car for everything else (which I do), It's less money, more convenient, and I guess we can throw the health and pollution benefits in there too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What random thing always makes you smile? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 05:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a bug or can I change settings to stop my phone from randomly lighting the screen up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 00:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 00:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fixed it! lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is cultural appropriation a bad thing in an ever-interconnected world? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 23:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why is cultural appropriation a bad thing in an ever-interconnected world? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 23:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your all time favorite album cover art? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 07:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite album art of all time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 06:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wonder how many crime plots have stolen elements from cinema and executed them successfully. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 06:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 22M, college student, watched Brave for the first time today. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 05:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I legit teared up at the end when Elanor turned back into a human. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 04:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And from your explanation, I gather that skin and hair don't ever appear green or blue because they are opaque and don't refract the light that hits them...?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If melanin is the same thing that pigments skin, hair, and eyes, then why are there vastly different color options? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 04:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just don't see people walking around with naturally green hair, or (disregarding racial slurs) red skin, etc. So what gives?Why does brown seem to be the only constant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 00:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To the grammar point, I'm mobile and messed up the line entry. I didn't think I needed commas if every item was on its own line.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the worst, darkest, or most corrupt thing about the industry you work in? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 17:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the hidden meaning behind Monsters Inc.'s 2319. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 16:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So here is a list of alternatives. Let me know if I missed anything. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 09:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soy, almond, coconut, oat, hemp, flax, rice, cashew, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 08:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HK as a brand, I'm familiar with and respect, it's just that no particular firearm of theirs stood out to me. Thats why I was asking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help me complete a list of 'definitely must shoot' guns. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 07:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not necessarily guns to own, just a bucket list of guns that I can realistically expect to be able to shoot, decide if I like it, then own if I do decide I like it.  

Here is my list so far. 

Glock 17  
Glock 19  
1911 (any brand)  
Springfield xdm  
Walther ppk  
Walther pps  
Desert eagle  
Baby eagle  
Beretta m9  
Thompson  
500 magnum  
12 gauge shotgun (any)  
AR 15 variant  
AK variant  
Sig saur p226  
Any mil surp   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone who is on the fence between Trump and Clinton please explain? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 07:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that there is error detection build into the 10-digit ISBN code of books. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 19:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 09:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks a lot like Gemma Arterton's redheaded Bond girl role in Quantum of Solace  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 07:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That fact is genuinely new to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 04:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time to add 'Singer' to Hank's resume. Damn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for help on a list of alternative shopping choices. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 01:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shopping for clothes at thrift stores instead of retail.  
Shopping for groceries at farmer's markets instead of grocery stores.  
What are some other examples of this kind of saving?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your crazy story that you are still waiting to tell your parents about in hopes that they'll laugh at it with you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 01:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your crazy story that you are still waiting to tell your parents about in hopes that they'll laugh at it with you. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 23:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 21:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #ShowerThoughts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Can someone build a Chinese Zodiac calendar with 12 Pokemon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 21:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thoughts on a USB RAID system? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 20:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard someone suggest buying a USB hub with upwards of 8 USB 3.0 ports on it and an 8-pack of high capacity flash drives and setting up a RAID backup system like that. Has anyone tried this and had success? What should I pay particular attention to with this kind of setup? What would be the best kind of RAID level to implement with said hardware?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 05:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 22:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I, with some judging and coaching experience, will say this. I have never taken issue with laptop decals, granted I haven't seen any that were grossly offensive or inappropriate. The other side of the coin is that whatever that decal says may play with your judge's preconceptions of you before you open your mouth in the first speech so just be aware of things like weather you live in a blue state or red state, weather the judge is a mommy judge or college judge, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 22:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SlowMo Guys should tooooootally do their own take on this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best, least creepy way to let a stranger know that you think they're attractive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 21:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] A breakdown of the women who have made the most appearances in r/celebs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 21:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 21:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if anyone else is having issues with this but the first 10 seconds of audio played twice so here is the YouTube link where there is not audiovisual mismatch. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tLtNatuVSjw  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What saved post(s) could you stand to have a printout of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 18:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 16:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What flipped it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE on one hand, have a whole list of things to feel self conscious about, but on the other hand, feel comfortable in your own skin that it doesn't affect daily life too much? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 08:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 04:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read other entries in this thread. He was a professor in years past. Just a professor of other things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 04:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't make you a good American, that makes you an average American and mediocrity is not good quality sir.  

#MakeAmericaGreatAgain  
#AllKiddingAsideThough
#IAlsoGotATwittterJustForRowling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 01:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last I heard this joke, it was all of congress. Point for timeliness but downvote for reposting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 00:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. Too late. Can't be unseen. Voldy with Bella by his side and Dolores UmBitch in the ministry vs Dumbles with Haggy and Slugy-Wugy by his side.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 23:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *caugh caugh* Pettirgew *caugh caugh* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 23:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am looking for a pretty utilitarian gun that can cover a bunch of bases. I'm not a hunter or competition shooter but in the name of putting my apocalypse preparedness hat on, I want to know how far I can stretch one investment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 22:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My main takeaway from your explanation is that it is okay to say "Voldy' and 'Dumbles'  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 22:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the tax stamp is still $200 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE, when learning a new skill for the first time and overcoming the learning curve, think to themselves 'It's all in the wrist.' even when it's not? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 22:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 22:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Real talk: I remember a few years back when Rio was announced to be the host city. I was in high school at the time and everyone was talking about how Brazil was slated to be the next upcoming nation and America needed to watch out. Their economy was showing signs of booming growth, the major city is going to host a huge event, etc. Then between a virus breakout, political instability, and all of this, I don't think anyone is feeling threatened by Brazil anymore. If history, both in recent events and in Olympics past can teach us anything, is that the IOC only ever gives countries the opportunity to position themselves well, not a golden ticket.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 22:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, So I'm not super well versed in this but someone explain something to me. Why would Voldemort curse the teaching position for the defense against the dark arts only to take Quirrell's body over himself on Harry's first year? Obviously, every teacher though Harry's attending Hogwarts only was able to hold onto that position for one year, but what about leading up to his first year?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you differentiate between something being difficult and not being cut out for that something? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 20:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For all the college students out there hell bent on a major that might not be for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comcast Copyright Alert! #1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 20:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this pop-up has shown up on a few different web pages now, which is making me less and less suspicious of it but not enough that i clicked yet. It's AN IMPORTANT MESSAGE FROM COMCAST.... I'll quote the rest of the window now:  

"As part of the Copyright Alert System operated by the Center for Copyright Information, a copyright owner has sent Comcast a notice claiming that your internet service from Comcast was used to share a movie, television program, or song improperly. We have sent an email with more information about this notice [an email that I haven't gotten but I'll ask my roommates] to the comcast.net email address of the primary account holder in your household [then why notify me like this?].  

Click the button below to confirm you have received the Copyright Alert to close it. Please review the Frequently Asked Questions about the Copyright Alert System at http://www.comcast.com/copyrightalerts/ to learn more about it.  

For a better way to find Movies, TV and Music, visit http://www.copyrightinformation.org/a-better-way-to-find-movies-tv-music/"

EDIT: My roommate cleared things up for me. It's legit, we had a bit of a scare, everything is fine. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 18:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, so we might hit a brick wall with why, can someone at least attempt to rationally explain to me what the reasons even might have been for these seemingly pointless regulations?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 17:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the millennium goals update should be a regular thing. This isnt the first time we have heard John report the numbers on these things and I dont want it to be the last.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 08:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ERS
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 08:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I'm actually on the fence with the candidates but here are my Trump-leaning reasons...]  

1) He's not Hilary (in that he isn't a corrupt political/criminal.)  

2) The people in his inner circle that he has managed to not alienate are positioned to be extremely influential in the roles that they are in line for when Trump delegates and for better or for worse, would probably do more than a Clinton administration could manage.  

3) As far as economic issues are concerned,  a candidate with a business background is hugely more attractive than one with a political background.  

4) For all the outlandish, bigoted, wrong, or 'not PC' things he has said, at least sooome of the time, you can say that a lot of people were thinking it and he is only getting the heat for being the one to say it into a microphone. Not a defense of what he says, not a justification, just an observation.  

5) Both candidates have been on the record on both sides of many issues over the years. You can look up the compilation videos on YouTube if you don't know what I'm talking about. Trump at least has the excuse that he was working a businessman's angle for whatever was in his best interest at the time. Clinton just straight up lies about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 07:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taking James Earl Jones's narration away from Darth Vader in the original trilogy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 07:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work either my body or my mind hard enough during the day that one of those things is bound to put me to sleep out of sheer exhaustion before I can think about staying awake too much longer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 07:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> zip codes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you won the lottery (on the condition that you would actually have to spend the money on yourself) what would you do with your winnings? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 07:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 00:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you talking about the book or my paraphrasing it? Here is the real text verbatim.  

"No. Jews are definitely not a race, because human races do not exist. In terms of biology, there is only one race: the human race. The idea that Jews comprised a separate race was instrumental to the occurrence of the Holocaust. The notion was based on a theory that Jews the world over had a number of racial characteristics in common; features that had been determined biologically or genetically and were therefor unvarying. This theory is unsound. Racial doctrine and race classification appeared in the eighteenth century on the heels of the classifications that were created for plants and animals by the Swedish biologist Linnaeus (1707-1778). Based on external characteristics such as hair color, hair structure, or the shape of a person's nose, all sorts of characterizations were making their rounds then - one even more far-reaching than the next. Racial classification always divided people into four basic categories: "the White race", the Black race", "the Yellow race", and "the Red race". To distinguish the races from each other, all different human characteristics were ascribed to people. In addition, a concept of inequality was instituted right from the start: influential European scientists were interested in proving the superiority of their own race - the white race. In Europe, particularly in the nineteenth and first half of the twentieth century,  race classification was very popular. Almost everybody - rich or poor, conservative or socialist, Christian or Jew - refereed to groups of people as races.  This word race was also frequently used without any reference of bias, meaning nothing more than sort of blood relationship. Pseudo-scientists attached a huge amount of significance to race classification. Scores of personality traits were connected to different races, which resulted in a variety of bizarre and dangerous ideas. Many people considered Jews a 'pure race', given that they had managed to survive for centuries as a separate group, a "nation apart". Race classification became very controversial because of the way in which the Nazis used it in the 1930s and 1940s to distinguish the Aryan race from the Semitic race. Following WWII, scientists conclusively established the irrelevance of race classifications. There is no such thing as a Jew-gene; you cannot identify 'real Jews' by examining their genes " -Fifty Questions on Antisemetism by Jaap Tanja and the Anne Frank House  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 18:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll paraphrase a book I read on antisemitism. "There is one race and that's the human race. Any subdivision beyond that is what allows genocide to happen. " </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 05:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes it's missinformation. Sometimes it's a lack of information. I just dont want to go through life assuming I know that what I am doing is what is best. I wanted to pool some ideas from people on here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 05:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well saving gas is a pretty click-bate-y way to get attention and it's worked for a lot of malicious content creators because it's not a penis pill.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What driving/maintenance habits can someone potentially have that, although not illegal, may not be good for the car? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 04:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much gear is too much? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 21:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I picture having a gun (for the sake of giving this imagination as much of a chance as possible, I'm not going to specify what kind of gun just yet) and having a separate case full of all the accessories in the world that could possibly got onto that gun. We are talking a bipod, surpressor, barrel extention, optics, laser sights, bayonet, extended mag/drum, interchangable barrels, maybe even some chokes, you name it. Obviously not anything so outlandish that everything would be on there at the same time and have some sort of Franken-gun, but just being able to say that you are prepared for *absolutely anything and everything* with this one firearm. Does such a unicorn exist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 19:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm definitely not. Even oligarchism comes to mind but I don't even know if there is a word for what I am describing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 09:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always keep a Roman Candle in my night stand just in case. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "So that's my advice for navigating the treacherous waters of life after school; find someone who's doing something you want to do better than you can do it and listen to them." - John Green </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 06:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
