<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2997</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  they care about live viewership because they're the only ones 'forced' to watch the commercials.

Technically they care about anyone who watches the commercials, hence paying for C3 and C7 ratings, it's just that most DVR viewers skip commercials. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arrow S4 is multiple levels worse that Supergirl S1 when it comes to crappy romantic drama; Supergirl got worse at that in S2 and is still not at Arrow S4 levels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He'll watch shows with a live audience that laughs, like I Love Lucy, but has never seen friends.

Most sitcoms from recent years with laugh tracks are from live audiences (including Friends). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I thought that wasn't possible

It appears you're not familiar with how the CW works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are saying live views are the only ones really that matter, which is false. Most commercials are are sold based on C3 or C7 ratings, not Live ratings. So if you watch the show on DVR (within the appropriate time) and don't skip the commercials, that is the same as watching it live when it comes to contributing to the ratings that matter (which is why it *does* matter if you skip commercials when playing from DVR). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the DC shows on the CW, but not every show on the CW. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Anything viewed on a delay gets tallied in the +1 or +3 category. It doesn't matter if you actually skip commercials or not. 

Incorrect.

Most commercials are sold based on C3 or C7 ratings; that is, viewers who watched the commercials within 3 or 7 days of the original airdate. These are different from the Live+3 and Live+7 ratings, which count all viewers of the show regardless of whether they watched the commercials (and are thus largely irrelevant). C3 and C7 numbers are just rarely released to the public so we don't typically see them (although AdAge will occasionally put out articles with them; [example](http://adage.com/article/media/good-news/306346/)). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 08:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah these predictions are not that good. I mean, Fresh Off the Boat, Last Man Standing, American Crime 'on the bubble', Dr. Ken 'nearly dead', and Agents of SHIELD and Once Upon a Time 'almost renewed'? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 08:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or just don't skip the commercials if you're watching it on DVR (and have a Nielsen Box).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 08:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I wouldn't get your hopes up too high on that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC the last time the tried that it leaked before the episode anyways, so I doubt it matters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The show made it very clear that Barry did not and could not restore the original timeline. 

Yes, he was *trying* to fix what Eobard did by changing the timeline back to its original state, *but he did not succeed*. Instead he merely created yet another alternate timeline. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eobard changed the timeline by going back and killing Nora, but Barry did not restore the original timeline when he went back to stop Eobard. That's what he was trying to do, but the whole point is that it *DID NOT WORK*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 11:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Where were you people calling Bryan a genius when my beloved HANNIBAL was on the chopping block?

They were presumably there, but since Fuller's genius apparently doesn't translate into decent ratings it didn't matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 08:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, it had more episodes than last season.

Really the key is mostly just the writing quality. There are shows that do 20+ episodes a season and are strong, and shows that do short seasons and are weak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 08:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want Black Lighting to get more than a single season then don't wish for it to be relegated to summer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 07:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Is there a hiatus that I missed the memo for?

Yep (though there was a similar hiatus last season). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The whole purpose of Legends is supposed to be shorter seasons in general.

Again, according to what? 

Last season it was a midseason premiere so it couldn't have been a full season, but how do we know it wouldn't have gotten a full season order for S2 if S1 hadn't underperformed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Likelihood of this happening: nil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 11:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about 'The Matrix'?

But yeah, while a lot of these have made for some great episodes/storylines, that doesn't mean we have to act like their ideas are completely original. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 11:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I don't like any romance dramas

Then stay away from the Berlanti CW DC shows, period.

But in all seriousness, the first season of The Flash is legitimately good. However after that it slowly degenerates into a combination of retreads of the first season and generic CW bullshit. The Rogues are largely squandered as villains-of-the-week and by the third season the romantic drama has become the main focus of the show.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 10:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The idea you dont lose unless you sell is absolutely incorrect.

The only difference between unrealized gains/losses and realized gains/losses is taxes and commissions, but good luck convincing most people of that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 03:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we stop calling every alternate reality scenario a 'Flashpoint'? Flashpoint only first came out six years ago and was neither the first story to do something like that nor the most iconic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 03:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Americans' viewership this season is middle-of-the-pack for FX, and that's after falling a decent amount over the years. So it's not a megahit by any means, but also not accurate to say that "literally no one" is watching it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 02:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet oddly enough nearly all the actual physicists and engineers I know like TBBT (granted that's just anecdotal evidence but still). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 02:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  prestige dramas like Downton Abbey, The Knick, Orange is the New Black and Transparent that no one watches

[Downton Abbey has a huge global audience](http://www.nytimes.com/2013/01/06/arts/television/downton-abbey-reaches-around-the-world.html?_r=0), and Orange is the New Black is reportedly one of the most popular Netflix Originals (according to [Symphony](http://variety.com/2016/tv/news/stranger-things-tv-ratings-netflix-most-watched-1201844081/) and [Nielsen](http://www.businessinsider.com/nielsen-shines-a-light-on-netflix-viewership-2016-7), since Netflix doesn't release its actual numbers) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 00:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get it, none of them appear to be wearing rouge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 00:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think any difference in marketing would have helped, it was never going to have mass appeal (and as such would have been much better suited for cable than broadcast). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 00:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was for Hannibal's second season, not its third and final season.
And the 2.5 million viewers Hannibal had that season ranked [dead last on NBC that season](http://tvseriesfinale.com/tv-show/nbc-tv-show-ratings-for-2013-14-season-30264/), so fans are lucky that it got a third season with such poor viewership. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 00:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So why mention it

Because it's one of the most common plants used as feed for cattle (and other livestock). You claimed "we eat the same stuff as cows", but that isn't true in general. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  TBBT- hated by critics

Critics generally like TBBT, it's reddit that rates it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any sort of alternate reality plot is now a "Flashpoint" according to some people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  we eat the same stuff as cows

Maybe for soybeans, but the corn we feed cows is different from the corn we feed ourselves. And then there's stuff like hay that isn't generally consumed by humans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  After figuring out Wells was RF, Barry thought he had the upper hand.

But he didn't have the upper hand, Eobard was playing him the whole time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this were "What's the biggest gap between critical reception *on reddit* and audience indifference?" then this may be correct. But out in the real world Chuck Lorre's comedies are for the most part reasonably well-received by critics and have won numerous awards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 18:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And meat substitutes will eventually be able to trick your mouth into believing you are eating the beat steak you have ever tasted in your entire life, there is no doubt in my mind.

I don't know what a "beat steak" is and I'm not sure I'd like to find out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 17:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I hope the show-runners move it to theCW

The showrunners aren't the ones who make that decision. 

Also the CW doesn't really do sitcoms these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 17:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of the credited writers for Arrow S5, the only ones with writing credits on the Flash S1-S2 are:

* Greg Berlanti, who's obviously involved with all the shows.
* Ben Sokolowski, who has three times as many credits for Arrow S3-S4 as he does for Flash S1-S2

So the theory that Arrow is better this season because Flash writers moved to Arrow is completely unsupported by evidence.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 05:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cast changes, but the genre and style don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 05:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It was never going to get a full 22.

According to what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 00:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~It being on Earth-38~~ *Poor writing* kills it. The setting is fine.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 00:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Not every episode uses the same exact budget

Because they can borrow from one episode's budget to increase another's (hence bottle episode), but the total season budget will still be the per-episode budget times the number of episodes. So like when the CW ordered 4 more episodes this season they paid for four more episodes, they didn't make the producers stretch the original season's budget to cover 4 more episodes. Also remember that broadcast shows make their money primarily on a per-episode basis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 00:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Let the extra budget go toward showing more Firestorm.

What extra budget? It's not like they have a fixed season budget regardless of the number of episodes, it's on a per-episode basis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 00:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LoT didn't perform as well as the CW has hoping last season so it only got a 13 episode initial order this season instead of a full 22-23, which then got extended to 17. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was sometime in season 3, I don't remember the exact episode.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Imagine how cool it would be if in Arrow S5 Barry came over and have Oliver a note from his father, saying he was proud of his crusade.

The thing is we already had a very similar moment with Robert's video message to Oliver. Just because it made sense for Batman in one setting doesn't mean it makes sense for Oliver in Arrow (despite the many similarities). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kreisberg was heavily involved with Supergirl last season as well, so that's not a change from S2 to S3. (Likewise for Berlanti, only he has a bunch of ther shows as well) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [imgur link to the pictures](http://imgur.com/a/wwnaR) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they're certain might as well buy a bunch of puts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So... what, you can tell which posts are from "shills" and which ones aren't?

Evidently they could not, otherwise they wouldn't have been 'tricked'.

But in all seriousness it is actually pretty easy for people/companies to use reddit for disguised advertising. How much of that is actually happening on /r/television I can't say but I'd be surprised if it was completely absent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [When you assume...](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=REeEbSb9gio t=10s)

But seriously, the comment you were responding to made no mention of supporting the Kara/Mon-El relationship seemed to be generally opposed to the show's romances overall. Yet you up Kara/Mon-El on the unfounded assumption that they supported it simply because they expressed a negative opinion of Alex/Maggie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean that it made no sense (on multiple levels) for the purpose of Flashpoint to have been moving Supergirl to Earth-1.

From the logistical side of things: the decision for the Flash to do Flashpoint happened long before CBS dropped Supergirl and it was picked up by the CW. Neither Flash nor Supergirl would have written their season endings with the network change in mind.

From the story side of things: Flashpoint is entirely a Flash story. Yes other characters show up, but they only ones with any continuity are Barry and Eobard. The story is entirely about their actions, and at the end of things the alternate timeline gets erased and only Barry knows about it. So it would have made absolutely no sense for any show other than The Flash to have spent any time in Flashpoint or be significantly affected by it. 

Furthermore the 'universe merging' aspect of Flashpoint is almost completely irrelevant to the main storyline of Flashpoint, and was the result of outside forces (later revealed to be Doctor Manhattan) not Barry's actions. So there's little reason to think the TV take on Flashpoint would necessarily include that at all.

Lastly, Supergirl had its own storylines including a cliffhanger coming into this season (which again was set up prior to the network change). It would have made no sense to ignore those for the sake a story from a different show; opening Supergirl S2 with Flashpoint would have been a great way to completely tank its transition to the CW. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, just because some doesn't like the Alex and Maggie relationship *doesn't mean they necessarily like the Kara and Mon-El relationship*. Stop framing everything as a shipper war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Not a big thing but better fight choreography. Season one had Kara doing cool wire-fu stuff in the air and I think was the only DCTV hero that used her legs to fight. 

This is also likely a budget issue, wire work can be quite expensive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 16:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  and how it might affect other shows

I'm sorry but anyone who thought Flashpoint was going to have a major effect on any show besides The Flash or that any show besides The Flash would spend as much as a second inside the Flashpoint timeline was being completely delusional. If people were disappointed because those didn't happen they played themselves.

Now that said, the show's Flashpoint was still disappointing for other reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 16:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I also thought one of the reasons they were doing a "Flashpoint" story arc was to help facilitate the integration of Supergirl into the CWVerse, instead of just having her on a different random Earth.

The thing is, this idea made absolutely no sense at the time if one actually thought it through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 03:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [You see...](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BsMSiVn6vpQ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably not; the DCEU has the budget to film in more places than just Vancouver. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> During the last strike Letterman didn't improvise his show, but Letterman's production company made their own individual deal with the WGA so they were only off air for eight weeks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If I was invested in that fund during that time it seems like I'd still be getting a dividend every month and since I am not selling the fund it isn't clear to me how my return would be negative.

The fund has a value at all times, even if you don't sell it. Your return is the change in value of the fund plus the payouts you've received from it, so if the value of the fund goes down then your return can be negative.

Also you can replace "fund" with "bond" in the preceding paragraph and nothing changes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Presumably everyone interested is already over at /r/PrisonBreak </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stein's daughter was the result of his own time fuckery, that had nothing to do with Barry.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not everyone who dislikes Mon-El does so because they they're fans of an opposing ship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flash *didn't* ruin other shows' timelines and neither will Legends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That breach had been closed and the speed cannon (if it's still even there, which I want to say it isn't) is operated from the Earth-1 side.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 08:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've seen her come to Earth-1 without Cisco opening a breach ([3x03 for example](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6yry4ZGTpKg)). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 08:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  reruns of Quantico and Beyond The Tank. 

It was *People Icons*, but the point still holds (although now I'm curious as to how terribly Quantico reruns would do on Tuesdays at 10; I'm thinking like 0.2-0.3). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 07:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice /r/humblebrag you got there...

But seriously, 5'10" and 155 isn't even that skinny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 07:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it's easier that way. But it's not necessary, we've seen Zoom, Jessie, Jay, and Barry himself travel between Earths without help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If that's the case why even worry about fluctuating rates or prices or anything if you just buy and hold till it matures.

Because your holdings don't exist in a vacuum. If you buy a ten year bond at 2% and then the rate jumps to 3%, you've effectively lost money by not waiting and buying at the higher rate and the resale value of your bond will drop accordingly. Saying that the current value of your bond doesn't matter because I'm holding it to maturity doesn't negate that opportunity cost, it only means you're ignoring it. And in real terms you can still lose money holding a bond to maturity if inflation rises high enough (and bond rates tend to be related to interest rates).

 do you focus on PRICE or do you focus on YIELD?

Why must your focus be a binary choice between these?

Really what you seem to be asking is "why buy a bond fund with constant maturity rather than buy individual bonds and hold them to maturity?", and there are many reasons for doing that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 03:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bond funds are just a bunch of bonds, the value of which is determined exactly the same way as the value of an individual bond. Bond funds have interest rate risk because individual bonds have interest rate risk.

Now holding a bond fund that maintains an average maturity of 10 years is not the same as buying a ten year bond and holding it for ten years, because a ten year bond does not stay a ten year bond for its lifetime (after a year it becomes a 9 year bond, and so on). So you shouldn't expect the same performance between those two scenarios, because they're not equivalent. However as /u/fakerfakefakerson pointed out, there are bond funds that maintain a fixed maturity date and thus perform comparably to holding a single bond to maturity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 03:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're matching known future liabilities then it can make more sense to use individual bonds than bond funds, but mostly because it may be more convenient rather than because interest rate risk is somehow mitigated by only holding individual bonds.You could get pretty much the same result from bond funds; bond funds typically maintain a pretty constant average maturity while an individual bond doesn't, but you can just adjust your fund allocations so that the average maturity of your bond holdings goes down over time like a single bond would.

And if you're not matching specific liabilities then your point is moot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 03:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The DEO has known her identity since she first arrived on Earth, it was never a secret. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 02:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Point 2 seems to be mitigated if you simply just hold the bond to maturity.

This isn't mitigating interest rate risk, it's just ignoring it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Didn't he go to college?

IIRC he pretty much partied instead of studying and flunked out as a result. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 00:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The world of S1 is deeply incompatible with the history of Earth-1, so retconning Supergirl into Earth-1 would necessarily destroy much of it (for pretty much no payoff). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 00:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Perhaps they could've had the Flash sticking his dick in he timeline to have caused a change which meant that Kara existed on the same earth as the Flash and Arrow.

Na screw that, there is no need to destroy the backstory and worldbuilding from season 1 just for what, slightly easier crossovers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  0.40 in unrounded.

Considering how CW ratings have fallen across the board this isn't bad, pretty much in line with last year. Hopefully they don't fall too far in weeks to come. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They've already moved the order around before.

Because they needed room for Riverdale, not because of any plot developments on one of the shows. I wouldn't be surprised to see schedule changes next fall but they would again be for business reasons (such as possibly moving LoT to Wednesdays to free up the post-Flash plot for a new show) not plot reasons.

Even minor effects on the other shows would serve no purpose other than to appease Leends viewers while confusing non-Legends viewers, and would be particularly pointless since we know that stuff like the dinosaurs will only be temporary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol they're not going to rearrange the entire schedule just because of something that happened on one of the shows. The changes brought on by the Legends finale will be contained to Legends, they're not going to mess with the plots of three other shows just to service Legends viewers (just like no shows other that The Flash spent any time in the Flashpoint timeline, despite rampant speculation by fans). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are so many people surprised that the show is taking a break at around this time of year? It does this every year (as do many other shows). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Think about the sheer physics of that "save" (given how fast Barry was travelling plus the fact Kara was in freefall) and it's patently obvious that an ordinary human wouldn't have survived.

Barry's pulled that sort of thing on regular humans as well and they do fine; speedforce allows him to mitigate the negative effects of high speed/acceleration on things he's carrying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 06:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The games will still be on TV as before, this is just the streaming rights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  but they don't

They absolutely do. If networks held their current shows to the same raw ratings standards as 10 years ago they'd have to cancel like 90% of their shows, which they are not doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why you should look at how a show's ratings compare to other shows on the same network, not to shows from previous years when ratings were higher across the board.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 04:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Seinfeld was far more popular than Friends. 

Seinfeld and Friends only aired together for less than half of either show's lifetime. Both were arguably the most popular show on TV at the time towards the end of their respective runs (and both finished #1 in viewership in at least one season).

 New Girl, one of the most popular shows on any streaming platform

You have zero evidence to back that up, and there is very little to suggest that it's not completely false. 

And looking at live numbers, New Girl is nowhere close to the level that Friends ever was. Friends was within the top 10 most-watched shows on TV every season it aired, while New Girl is currently barely within the top 20 just on its own network. If New Girl were comparable to Friends we'd be hearing about how Zooey Deschanel was negotiating a contract for $1 million an episode, not that the show was potentially cancelled after 6 seasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 04:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  New Girl is not only insanely popular

TBBT is far more popular than New Girl. TBBT is much more comparable to Friends in that regard, and as a result its cast are making similar amounts to what the Friends cast made in the last few years of the show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 04:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Will this change the other shows?

Nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 04:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see the CTV2 schedule for Toronto listing a new Flash episode at 8:00 next Tuesday (with TBBT and etalk at 7:00 and 7:30), with [CTV's page on The Flash](http://www.ctv.ca/TheFlash) saying the same thing. 

Now it could still be an error (which is what I would guess), but that's what CTV is currently listing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One way or another Eobard will show up on the Flash again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 01:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no reason to sign him as a main cast member if he's only going to be in a small number of episodes; being a guest star is typical for a former main cast member making a brief reappearance on a show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 01:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would he become a main cast member again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can walk into a pawn shop with a guitar and leave with a currency MCDs will accept, doesn't mean guitars have value as a currency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not personally opposed to putting all the animated shows on the sidebar, I'm just explaining why Constantine is not there currently.

 Preacher is still a DC TV show.

In your opinion, but it's possible that others think otherwise since it's not cut-and-dried. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP should care; investing in a specific company without any regard for its valuation is moronic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Constantine *was* a live-action show, but it was cancelled two years ago. It is now an animated show on CW Seed just like Vixen and The Ray.

iZombie and Lucifer are produced by DC and WBTV; Preacher is not. So depending on how we're defining "DC Television" it could make sense to include iZombie and Lucifer but not Preacher.

Black Lighting will probably get picked up (though their choice of costume designer says nothing about it's chances), but as of now it has not. If/when it is officially picked up it should then be immediately added to the sidebar at that time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sidebar appears to only have live-action shows, so Constantine's absence is in line with that. If Constantine get added then Vixen and The Ray should also be added.

Preacher, despite the comics being published under DC's Vertigo imprint, does not appear to be owned by DC and neither DC nor WB is involved in the production of the show, so it's debatable whether it should be included in a 'DC Television' list.

Black Lightning has not been ordered to series. Krypton and Scalped are other DC shows that are currently in the pilot stage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drops of 14% and 20% YoY aren't that bad, seem about in line with how most shows are doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It still gets the best ratings of any scripted show on TV. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  11.3 Million is still pretty good.

And a 5.9 in the 18-49 demo is massive

 I hope they don't drag the show out for like 10 more years.

I'm pretty sure their plan is to do exactly that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Looks for where OP actually mentions the company's valuation...*

 For all I know the stock price is overvalued right now and may drop a good deal

Uh, okay... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AoS and iZombie are back, so I'm totally fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also the older and more talented actors tend to be the most expensive, so getting rid of them can be a good way to implement budget cuts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're going to have a long wait </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 09:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reasonable criticism is fine, it's the circlejerks of hatred that we want to avoid here.

And yes, revisiting in depth what is widely considered one of the single worst moments of the show does not make me at all optimistic about this episode. Like, this has the potential to be terrible on multiple levels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
