<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3535</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 10 yrs later aspect would be interesting to say the least, but I don't like the idea of bringing in more people. I like the idea of have a small team that we get to see grow and develop over time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think there is a cop show in existence that hasn't done the first one in some way, shape, or form.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sometimes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll probably end up forming some kind of galactic coalition with the rest of the Andromeda races who have been fighting the Kett in their own individual clusters, not to mention the Initiative having access to Remnant technology and two people who can use and control it with the Ryder twins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And based on your thumbnail, dramatically dabbing before doing so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With no backup or tactical gear that could prevent a life threatening gunshot wound. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope this cliche dies out at some point. I can't stand characters like this. Abby is the reason I quit watching NCIS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've already started down that path with shows like Castle and Rosewood, where you have someone who's not a cop, but are doing investigative work anyway. 

Also, ou might have given Fox or CBS an idea for a new show. 

*Coming Mondays this fall: Judicial. Private Practice by day, Cop by night* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They didn't to an extent, in my opinion. While I love what they did do, I felt like there was much more they could have done, and still could do. Remember, we have the rest of an entire Galaxy to explore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the boss is usually middle aged, throws in a comment about their ex husband or wife, and has a case that still haunts them that the protagonist eventually solves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be awesome. Maybe get into some ethical debates with your crew ala Star Trek. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finally, I get to see my hometown get some good press for once.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me neither. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  True, they did use instances like famine and disease. But I thinking more in regards to the interactions between the Initiative and the natives of Heleus. Imagine mission where, for example, an Initiative colonist killed an Angaran, and you had to decide wether to turn him over to the Angarans to face their justice system in order to keep good relations, but be accused of betraying your own people by the Initiative, or keep him, but further dissolve relations with the Angarans on that planet, or one where a fellow Pathfinder seized Angaran territory by force to settle his people, and you have to decide whether or not back him up, try and negotiate a middle ground, or stand up to him and get the Angarans their territory back. Missions like these would better define the role of a Pathfinder and would to define the role of the Initiative as opposed to what kind of outpost you put down on Eos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And criminal minds, and every iteration of NCIS, and the rebooted Hawaii Five-O. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cop show cliches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These past few months, I've managed to get into Blue Bloods on Netflix. I really like the show, but man there are some cliches in it s. This got me thinking about what are some of the biggest cliches in cop shows, and which shows are the biggest perpetrators (no pun intended) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> J.J Abram's Alcatraz and Almost Human. Yes, they were Police procedurals, but each had good premises, the casts weren't bad (Sam Neil and Micael Ealy were the standouts, respectively), and both had big cliffhangers 

Also Rome on HBO; That show was GOT before there was GOT. For years, i hoped to see another show in the same vain but focusing on another civilization </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ME:A spoilers] I hope the Andromeda series maintains it's spirit of exploration and discovery in future games </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever since I finished my first Playthrough of Andromeda as well as my NG+ playthrough, I've been worried as to where the overall story of the Andromeda series is going. Specifically, I'm worried that with the [Spoiler](the reveal that the Kett are a greater threat in the Andromeda Galaxy, the Jardaan, and the idea of a Remnant terraforming network that expands the cluster), future Andromeda titles will be focused on a huge galaxy-wide war on the Kett empire with some universe changing secret involving either the Jardaan or the Remnant, similar to the war with the Reapers and the revelations about the Collectors, the Leviathans, and the Star Child. The initial premise of the Andromeda series, as told by Bioware, was one of discovery and exploration, and I hope that doesn't become lost in their sequels. 

A few things I think Bioware can do writing wise to make sure they still maintain their core premise while still planning for bigger things are:

1. Make Andromeda itself an antagonist: I completely agree with those that say that the Kett are not the best or the most original villains and the Archon was a massive pain in the ass to listen to and interact with. I think the biggest threats in Andromeda should have been the hostile native species of Heleius and the dangers and hardships that come with trying to live in a hostile new environment, similar to real world colonization efforts and frontier living. In fact, I wish the main story had revolved solely around finding the other arks along with trying to find homes for them (No terraforming network, no remnant vaults, just harsh environments that you need to try and survive on) while interacting with the native helius species, some who view you as friends, others as hostile invaders. I still think this can be done as the rest of Andromeda becomes explorable in either DLC or in sequels. 

2. Look to history: I'm a big history buff, and as many people may of may not know, there have been hundreds of exploration and colonization efforts throughout history, and I think Bioware could pull from a lot of these in terms of interaction between settlers and natives, the risks and dangers that come with exploring and living on dangerous frontiers, etc. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] I know this isn't ME related, but please be true </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 06:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine the day Gil takes his tinkering with the Tempest too far. 

Gil: "So, Ryder, you up for a game of pok-" *begins choking, grasping at his collar*

Ryder: "Gil, are you ok?"

*Gil falls to his knees grasping at his throat* 

Kallo: *Over intercom* "Be careful not to choke on your modifications, Gil." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given how well H:ZD performed critically and financially, I'm pretty sure if she wants a role in a ME game, she'll get it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 11:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Josh Keaton would be a good Salarian too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 10:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few more names I would add to the list would be:

Bruce Greenwood as a failed former N7 who knew Alec and takes on a sort of Anderson mentor role for Ryder.  

Tim Daily as the Benefactor. I figured since we have Lex Luthor as Alec, its only fitting Superman should play one of the villains. Plus, despite playing the ultimate superhero, Daily can be intimidating and threatening when he wants to be. 

Jason Issacs as a villainous Turian. 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 09:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still remember hearing Temmuera Morrison's voice in Star Wars Republic Commando, so hearing Delta 38's voice again would bring back waves of nostalgia. And I can see Bennett channeling Deathstroke from Arrow to play a bounty hunter. 

Tony Todd as a Batarian is a stroke of Genius. I'm surprised this hasn't happened already. It would be cool if your community leader turned pirate joined the Pathfinder team, as a form of repentance for the crimes he committed in order to get to Andromeda. 

Sam Witer could play anyone he wanted to, but I can see him as a new human squadmate. Plus, with his voice, the romance scenes would be something else. Hell, I wouldn't mind if voiced a protagonist down the line. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would need to here a Joe Swanson esque "Let's do this!" before getting owned by Ryder. Also, he would try douchy pick up lines on your LI if they were in your squad or if Ryder's female.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be mind blowing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not familiar. What has he done? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Biotic bro? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be surprising to walk up to an Asari only to hear either Snake or Marcus Fenix's voice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for reminding me about Dorn and Sirtis, but the entire TNG crew would be awesome. Maybe throw in Wil Wheaton and Kate Mulgrew for measure? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better yet, disgruntled Elcor Pathfinder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can such a thing even exist among the Asari? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I came up with this post because I saw the trailer for Destiny 2, and thought that Fillion would make for a badass Turian voice, maybe as a smuggler, Han Solo type of character. 

Patrick Stewart would be an amazing addition to the series. It'd be even more amazing if we could get another TNG alum like Michael Dorn, Jonathan Frakes, or even Marina Sirtis to come with him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] What voice actors who haven't been in the series would you like to see and what kind of characters would they play? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 07:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No need to apologize, and thanks for the clarification.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. I think OCP/UCP could be done, as well as type 2 and 3 NWU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice. I wonder if anyone's done the same with ACU or ABU. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No spoilers] Apparently, someone brought trap music to Andromeda </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I'm currently using. I also add either black or grey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] Any good color combinations for the Pathfinder armor? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ME:A Spoilers] A few comments about Andromeda </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 10:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

1. I completely agree with those that say that the Kett are not the best or the most original villains, in addition to the Archon being a massive pain in the ass to listen to and interact with. I think the biggest threats in Andromeda should have been the hostile native species of Heleius and the dangers and hardships that come with trying to live in a hostile new environment, similar to real world colonization efforts and frontier living. In fact, I wish the main story had revolved solely around finding the other arks along with trying to find homes for them (No terraforming network, no remnant vaults, just harsh environments that you need to try and survive on) while interacting with the native helius species, some who view you as friends, others as hostile invaders. 

2. In regards to those that say that the AI should have been founded on the idea go back and forth on this. On one hand, it does raise the stakes of having to colonize, and it would, as others have pointed out, raise some interesting questions as to how far would the AI be willing to go ensure their survival. On the other hand, I don't think everything in the ME universe needs to revolve around or be in reaction to the reapers. Overall, I think with [spoilers] (the various hints they've dropped about the real reasons for leaving the Milky Way and the mentions of Earth and Palavan being hit by the Reapers just before the AI left the Milky Way in Alec's memories or logs), fleeing the Reapers will play some role in the forming of the AI. 

3. I think future games will open up the rest of the Andromeda Galaxy to us, and Bioware will really let their imaginations go wild in regards to planets, new species, etc. 

4. I also believe we'll see more political situations. Now that the AI has been established in Helieus, there's probably going to be a lot of Political strife in the form of Outposts wanting independence from the Nexus, debates over whether or not the Initiative should be militarized in wake of the Kett attacks, worry over Krogan expansion, internal conflicts between Tann and the rest of the Nexus leadership, whatever role[spoiler] (the Benefactor and their faction is going to play,) and interacting with rest of the Andromeda galaxy 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In terms of traveling, both for work and deployments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the elaboration. I'm also considering trying out for either the 75th Ranger Regiment or SF. I know intel is a MOS that would allow for transfers into both the 75th and SF, but would it lend well to being prepared for either? 

Also, kind of a superficial question, but does being an Army O allow for frequent traveling?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 02:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok. Thanks for the clarification  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 02:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in college and thinking about getting a commission via OCS with the intent of going into either intel, specifically HUMINT. The only problem is that there isn't a whole lot of info on the HUMINT field, especially for officers. Can anyone let me know about what exactly HUMINT officers do and the Likelihood of an becoming a HUMINT Officer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello Captain Fry. Currently, I'm a sophomore in college with the goal of becoming an Officer, which has been my dream for most of my life. The only issue is that I can't decide on what branch to join. I initially wanted to join the Navy and become a Special Warfare Officer or an EOD officer. But, recently I've begun learning about both Army Special Forces and the 75th Ranger Regiment, so I'm currently torn between seeking a commission in either the Army or the Navy. I'm hoping you would be able to help with my decision by answering a few questions: 

1. What career fields in the Army would best lend themselves to a career in Army Special Operations? If I were to become an Army Officer, I'm contemplating Intelligence (specifically HUMINT), Law Enforcement, and Combat Engineering. 

2. One thing I am hoping to do regardless of whichever branch I choose, is to travel. Do SF soldiers get to travel often?

3. One mission SF does that that isn't touched on by most are humanitarian missions. Do you know about the role SF plays in these types of missions? 

4. Can you describe the role of a SF Officer verses that of a Naval Special Warfare Officer? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [COD] Should COD try a premise like Rainbow Six: Patriots? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 08:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those of you who don't remember, Rainbow Six: Patriots was the idea for the next RS game that would ultimately be replaced by Siege and had a campaign revolving around Team Rainbow fighting a U.S. based terror group striking out at big business and wall street ( here's some early gameplay footage https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q7tdrvIsLo4). From what I l remember, the premise was pretty unique and was going to present the player with a lot of hard moral choices and questions.  Do you guys think that COD could/should handle subject material like this. I know this kind of Idea isn't in COD's wheelhouse, but people have been asking for an in depth, emotional COD campaign for years now, and this could be a way to do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 08:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. Now make that into an animated series, and you've struck gold.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 07:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few things: 

1. I completely agree with the fact that the Kett are not the best or the most original villains and the Archon was a massive pain in the ass to listen to and interact with. I think the biggest threats in Andromeda should have been the hostile native species of Heleius and the dangers and hardships that come with trying to live in a hostile new environment, similar to real world colonization efforts and frontier living. In fact, I wish the main story had revolved solely around finding the other arks along with trying to find homes for them (No terraforming network, no remnant vaults, just harsh environments that you need to try and survive on) while interacting with the native helius species, some who view you as friends, others as hostile invaders. 

2. I go back and forth on whether or not fleeing the reapers should have been the reason for the founding of the AI. On one hand, it does raise the stakes of having to colonize, and it would, as others have pointed out, raise some interesting questions as to how far would the AI be willing to go ensure their survival. On the other hand, I don't think everything in the ME universe needs to revolve around or be in reaction to the reapers. Overall, I think with [spoilers] (the various hints they've dropped about the real reasons for leaving the Milky Way and the mentions of Earth and Palavan being hit by the Reapers just before the AI left the Milky Way in Alec's memories or logs), fleeing the Reapers will play some role in the forming of the AI. 

3. I think future games will open up the rest of the Andromeda Galaxy to us, and Bioware will really let their imaginations go wild in regards to planets, new species, etc. 

4. I also believe we'll see more political situations. Now that the AI has been established in Helieus, there's probably going to be a lot of Political strife in the form of Outposts wanting independence from the Nexus, debates over whether or not the Initiative should be militarized in wake of the Kett attacks, worry over Krogan expansion, internal conflicts between Tann and the rest of the Nexus leadership, whatever role the Benefactor and their faction is going to play, and interacting with rest of the Andromeda galaxy 

5. I ultimately hope that the Andromeda trilogy doesn't go the way of the OT and become this huge story of galactic extinction and war. I hope that at its core, Andromeda still remains a story about people trying to survive in a strange new world and all the moral, political, and personal struggles that come with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 07:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone give this man a pilot on FX. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought everyone would get a kick out of this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 07:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 06:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One that plays on old 80's Sci-Fi tropes? That'd make for some awesome DLC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 06:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be ok if each studio switched it up from time to time, where Treyarch works on a Modern era ga and IW works on a Vietnam game. I also think Treyarch should work on the more out there ideas (I can totally see them working on a alternate history, post apocalyptic, or even a time travel COD) After all, these are the guys that created Zombies, and they seem to have a more developed sense of humor compared to the other two studios. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 06:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My only problem with Of Their Own Accord was that we never got to fight in Moscow in MW3. For me, its a tie between Hotel Bravo from MW2 and  SOG from BO1.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
