<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3788</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea building is a different scenario then typical home buying. 

You have to remember if your building your dealing with their employees and they just want to sell you. I doubt you have a realtor negotiating for you. And even then, the Realtor just want you to buy they don't care what you throw your money at. 

If you do want to go down the buying route I would suggest consulting with real estate attorney. Find one in your area that offers a 30min free consultation and have them at least put eyes on the deal before you sign anything. Realtors and Builders Employees just want you to buy and there is no one really in your corner. Having an Attorney on your side will cut the bullshit to zero on their side as well. 

$250,000 is a lot of house though, at least where I'm from in Mid/Southeast Michigan. 

Also you may want to consider looking into having someone come along with you and looking at the models. I would hire a inspector to come along, only if your serious, and have them really look at the quality of the construction. A lot of the homes now days are cookie cutter homes that don't get quality wood/components because they have to keep expenses low to maximize profit. 

If your having trouble with 20% you could look into a smaller home to start, I don't want to pry into your specifics, that's my opinion. You'll find many others on here with different advice.

PM me if you have any questions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your dad is straight up stealing from you. Stop giving him beer money and have a man to man conversation with him. If you can have someone there with you so they can witness the conversation. 

You can go to the cops and file a police report. 
You can go to small claims court as well. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take it in sections. Sounds like they are confusing the hell out of you in order to make a sale and they might not even know that part of the process. 

You went to the builder to negotiate/price out to build your dream home. 

Based on the conversation, we can safely assume you don't have the cash to pay for the entire project--so your going to have to get a loan for the remainder. 

The builder is saying they need a deposit to lock in your site and design to mark it off the master plan, otherwise they will be able to sell it to another homebuyer. 

The builder is seeking a deposit of $2000 for a preferred lender that they probably work with or have worked with and have a relationship with. The lender isn't going to be on your side and will not give you a favorable interest rate if you go with them for the loan. 

The builder is seeking a deposit of $5000 for a non-preferred lender, one of which they don't work with and do not have a relationship with. 

You can go anywhere to get a loan for a house. I would suggest a credit union first because they typically have lower interest rates which are used to help the community they service. Larger national banks tend to have slightly higher interest rates because they are a national chain and they don't really care about helping the community. 

The bit about 30 day closing is just something you can negotiate. If you go with the preferred lender then they will know, more or less, what your qualified for and if your going to exit. The non-preferred, they are operating essentially in the dark and don't want to start a build if your going to jet; so they lock up $5000 for the risk. 

I would just read all the paperwork closely and take the time to really consider what you want to do. If you have the cash to build the house then I would shop around for a low interest rate.  I wouldn't put any money down until you know whether or not it is a non refundable deposit regardless. I wouldn't mess with anything non refundable if your just considering who your going to get pre-qualified from, that's  just another way these places make money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking the exact same thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yesssss. That looks amazing! Great job on the crust! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go with a used car. No sense in locking yourself into a contract and having a liability if your not going to use it. 

If you don't use a used car, it just sits there. 
If you don't use a leased/financed car, you still pay for insurance and monthly fees. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My vote is for the LEFT pizza. Looks amazing, great job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly! Looks like he has two kids, each kid could have their own cubby.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sometime check it because my wife will leave me love notes sometimes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea but that's like worst case scenario. I'm MI you can't sell the property without the wife's approval anyways--MI has Dower Rights. (Mi resident here too)

So I'm a short sale both would have to agree. It wouldn't be a way to force her to sell. The home value/condition/equity/lien amount is and should be taken into consideration. He doesn't want a short sale because he is going to accept less for the home then he is getting half of the less amount, hat would be settling for a super discount. 

I would say take half the amount and then use that as a nest egg or downpayment on a piece of property or rent for a while to save up a little more. I don't know the employment status, job history, education level, etc. there are a lot of variables to consider.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do ittttt! I try to put a twist on all my projects. You could at least put a hollowed out book on there for your kids. I have one I put candy in for my nephew, every time he comes over he goes into my office and grabs the "candy book" as he calls it. 

Growing up with Scooby-Doo made me always want a trap/hidden doors all throughout my house. Haha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enforcement of the refi is the same thing as enforcement of the divorce order. He's going to have to petition the court and seek enforcement, a lawyer would be able to file a motion seeking specific enforcement. 

Ideally you want to work with the wife to get this done and behind y'all. But when push comes to shove she is going to have to pay him for his portion of the home; whether it's cash or he buys her out, there are a lot of variables. The house might even be at a point where it's not worth what they bought it for, again, there are so many variables that go into considering what steps should or may be taken.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dang I would have built a secret storage space in the dead spots on the bottom of the floor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, my life means nothing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't suggest getting a house until the refi. He is going to be on the original loan regardless of the court order. Once she gets the refi he's going to have to make sure he is released from the original loan and she is only on the refi. If he doesn't get off either and then goes out and purchases a home then he is liable for both. 

If she doesn't get a refi he can seek to enforce the judgement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can buy an antenna from Best Buy to get some free HD TV. Or, you can take a cable and strip the cable down to the copper and place it next to the TV and get the same amount of channels that way. 

I'd second the Salvation Army for furniture. Craigslist for furniture as well. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. There is a lot left unknown to the world in the archives.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to remember also the legal aspect of everything. Yes it's in the infancy, but these are state laws and federal law trumps (no pun intended) state. The federal government can come in at any second and stop business, seize all your "product," and lock you up in federal litigation-costing you thousands in legal fees. 

I would go towards the medical side more then recreational, but then it's the same argument. 

If I was looking to get into that industry I would suggest going to work for someone who already has something going. Talk that opportunity to learn everything and save money, then as times change you can branch off depending on the climate of the industry/formation of laws. 

It is up to our law makers to enact legislation based on public needs/focus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Negotiating.
Delegation.
Communication. 
Accepting failure. 

Just to name a few... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 15:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only for an in-store Meijer purchase. 

The coupon lists an exclusion as to use on the manuf. website.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 15:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I'd say stick it out as long as you can and just continue to save your money. You don't really need a car, honestly. You could get a bike or take a mass transit system.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 14:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to register the car and pay for insurance too, don't forget about that. No you shouldn't pay for the internet bill. Period. Let her be a sad and maybe she will do something about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 04:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to see it. Makes me know that I placed the item in the right category and my photos and title are working to draw people in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 04:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah man! You should have snagged the sweatshirt for cheap! Around Christmas time those things sell like hot cakes for roughly $15-$30; there is a huge market for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> $25.00 Off (1) Keurig Brewer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 04:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in line today at Meijer (MI Grocery Store) and came across a coupon for: 

"Save $25.00 on any (1) Keurig Brewer"

Expires 04-08-2017 

If you want it I will mail it to you, my wife and I won't use it.

Valid in stores only, and cannot be used Keurig online. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 22:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 21:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure about that site specifically. Your going have an age requirement of 18 years old.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 21:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your question is very very open ended. Can you be more specific? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 18:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Understandable. Thanks for the info.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Starting an LLC is a way to shield yourself from potential liability your business would incur. For example, if your company is unable to fulfill a contract, you individually will not be held liable and only the companies assets will be on hook in a breach of contract claim. 

That being said there are other tax implications that allow for more opportunity to write costs off as deductions against expenses. 

Sounds to me you could just be a sole proprietorship. Doesn't sound like your going to be marketing these skills to other people and would only be on the hook for this one gig with little to no expenses of operation. 

Everyone is eager to jump to start up an LLC now days. While it is important to do so in some situations, not all businesses need corporate protection to insulate their individual capacity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 15:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that total for the year or overall?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 03:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What level do you have to start paying taxes at? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 03:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rentafriend.com got me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 02:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea...focus on what you don't know. If you've been studying your sure enough to have topics you can talk about easily. Focus on what you don't know. Just reading the essay, writing out what you think the issues are, and then matching that to the answer is enough practice. You don't have to sit there and write out a full essay or take the 20min to Dream up something. I wrote about 50-60 full essays but I read all of the essays Themis provided, I ended up reading/outlining 120-130 essays over the time I studied. 

With the MBE...know as much as you can cold. Remember the sequence of the answers. You can go through my post history and view some of my posts about Property, Contracts, and Evidence. You have to be able to know exactly where your at in the sequence to be able to answer the problem. Break everything down into bite sized issues if you can and just learn enough to talk about it. 

I ran out of time on my last essay during the morning session. I outlined my last essay. Luckily I knew the law and just threw it down with no facts applied and a basic bs conclusion. I got a 5/10 just for rattling off the law. If your running short don't be afraid to write something down. They will give you points, but they can't if you don't write it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 02:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you just want to go the best route. I would suggest pausing on saving for your retirement and focus on paying off the loans, then you can focus on saving for a house, car, and retirement. 

I would suggest taking the current savings you have and using all of it, but leave $1000 for emergency. That will while out both smaller loans and leave the $10,000 loan. Then your monthly payments you would have made one the smaller interest loans can be combined and payed towards the $10,000 loan. If you can make bi-weekly payments to maximize the amount paid towards the principal. 

I would borrow against your retirement or take out more loans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 02:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same. My wife and I average $1.30-$1.50 per meal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 02:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude don't be afraid to spend the money you saved, that's one of the biggest mistakes of savings--knowing when to use your savings. You can knock off both of the other loans and then take the money you spend on those each month and attack the one that's left. If you take the savings away you will just have to start saving again it's part of the process, but at that point you'll be able to save more because you'll be in less debt. 

DO NOT BORROW TO PAY OFF WHAT YOU BORROWED!

I can't stress that enough. I would refer you to Dave Ramsey to get a basic idea of how to save/pay debt. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's probably why it was never used! Lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure there are ways to make this pointless. Just the concept is a fear. It's like modern day IP banning! Haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 18:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has pretty much every one ever made. He gets them from people at church who get them at garage sales and what not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cruel Joke...I think not! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 18:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose we could refi or HELOC, but would certainly be conditional on getting life insurance to cover it all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm actually in a similar position (also went the legal route; in the process of licensing with my state to be Esq.). 

So one reason I'm not going to refi my home and dump the money on my loan is the fact of protecting my loved ones. I have a higher amount of student loan debt and about $80,000 of equity in our home. I know this may sound morbid but if I die my wife/family will not have to worry about paying back any of my loan since I'm the only one on the promissory note.

If we refi'd and used some/all the equity in our home obviously my wife would be stuck if I were to die. I would only do this if I could get life insurance that would satisfy our debt outright. My wife doesn't have as lucrative job as yours, that's my concern.

We have stopped saving for our retirement while we pay down the student loan. I think you have enough combined retirement savings to pause as well. 

Also, why don't you hold onto an emergency fund and dump the rest of the cash on your loan. That way if you still want to use some of your home equity you could get a HELOC for the remaining principal. That way your leveraging your homes value while paying at a much lower interest rate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. 

On the back of the check sign your name and write "pay to the order of (insert friends name)" 

Your basically writing a check to that person, or whomever they choose to endorse it to...which would be the bank they choose to cash it at.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I finished at 65% on Themis and passed the first time. I did all of their essay practice, but skimmed the MC questions. I skipped over some of the lectures all together (Sales/Secured Trans) because I had just had those classes before graduation. 

You will do fine. Just continue to pound it down and practice. Find the flows of issues in the essays, which issue usually goes with what. You got this! Only a little more to go bud! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree completely. Trump has a disadvantage because he did not go to law school; he can't comprehend the separation of powers concept. Comprehend or respect, I don't know which, but it just doesn't work how he wants it to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 01:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Off to the SCOTUS...don't they wish Gorsuch was in already.  

History in the making boys and girls, sit back and watch. 

This is unprecedented-court is tied, Dems don't have majority anywhere, GOP can go "nuclear" and change the rules if need be...this is AWESOME!

 I love being a nerd! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anytime. I'm going to cruise around the world one day, one a cruise ship, not giving a F. Haha! (You can actually do it) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We buy them and keep them stocked in our freezer. I easily have 5-7 in there right now. Thy have a enchilada one as well that is my favorite. It's not forever but while your on the go and young, paying down your bills and saving is key. I plan on retiring and just going on a bunch of cruises so I won't have to worry about preparing my meals then. Haha!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this is your final home I would contact each of the financing options and work out solid numbers. You could combined a few options to get a low cost. 

I'm assuming there isn't any in your basement now. But if there is don't be afraid to offer to your GC your services of helping or doing demo-labor is the number one cost when it comes to home improvement. 

HELOC will probably be the best option since you've worked up some equity in the home and your assumption on the value of the home rising; your current lender may give you a favorable rate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't be afraid to ask questions. 

Don't be afraid to challenge your RE Agent, they work for you, and you don't work for them. 

If you smell something fishy and no one is explain shit to you--find a RE Attorney in the area who offers*free consultations* and go have a free chat with them--they won't bullshit you. 

Go to every open house and find out what you are exactly looking for. Try different price ranges too, you've been approved for a high value, but that doesn't mean you need it. I live in an area that offers nice family homes with 3 bedrooms and a basement for $90-$120,000-just depends on what your looking for. Do you want land? Do you want your neighbors right up on ya? Do you want a larger garage? Do you want cheaper taxes? Good school? 

I would STRONGLY suggest getting an inspection of the home you want to buy. Inspections are critical to your protection. If your getting land or where the blundered are not truly defined, then I would suggest a survey to determine those boundaries. 

Shop around for the best interest rate you can get and don't be afraid to negotiate with a bank. If you can start with a local credit union, they will sometimes have lower interest rates because they are not national chains and help local customers more often. I would suggest starting out with a 30 year FIXED rate. I say fixed because if you have an adjustable rate the rate may be adjusted if the Feds choose to raise the interest rates (which they have been doing slowly for a few years now). 

Find a good place to bundle your insurances and don't be afraid to shop them as well. Again local companies may offer some discounts and lower prices to help out local customers. For example mine offered a $50/mo reduction because I had opened a bank account with a local credit union they were affiliated with. You don't have to use it just keep the minimal amount needs to maintain the account. Some banks/credit unions will offer the same thing with mortgages if you set up auto pay with them, they might give you $300 to have it set up that way. 

On your payments since you don't have any other debt, learn what an amortization sheet it and don't be afraid to make bi-weekely payments to kill that principal amount owed. If you pay more up front on the 30 year rate your going to have more principal taken off. 


Most importantly enjoy the process, have fun with it, and don't be afraid to say no.   

Feel free to ask any questions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unhealthy much? 

I guess it would have to be based on your perception and overall goal:

If your poor and on the ropes with starvation, boom bottomless fries and soda from Red Robin is the way to go. 

If your just looking to have a decent lunch and leftovers for dinner, then good job with the coupon. You could have eaten half the burger for lunch and saved the other half for dinner; thus a $4.50/per meal estimate. 

My wife and I bake a stouffer's lasagna on Sunday night for the week. She portions them out for her and takes them to work. Lasagna ($9.99 on sale) is split in two, and we both eat for roughly $1.10 per day for dinner. It's a large portion too, just have to eat in moderation. (I'm 6'5 220, it's enough).

(Go with the sweet potato fries, much better for you!) 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Live frugal my friend and you could have it knocked out in 2-3 years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, don't assume a value increase. You should have had a tax evaluation done sometime since you purchased. Take that valuation and look at it compared to the current market conditions of your surrounding area. 

Then you can go from there and negotiate with your lender. You're going to want to find a competent GC if your not going to do it yourself. Also, thinking ahead if you want to count the basement as square footage your likely going to need an egress to meet code requirements; my state requires such, so be sure to ask your GC. 

Think about your long term plan as well. Do you plan on staying in the house for 3-5-10-15 more years? You don't want to invest in a home your not going to be able to enjoy the benefit. You want to add value instead of adding too much cost.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think about this all the time. How much knowledge/history do they have stashed away...just sitting there...waiting? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Suppose your right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Essentially it's the ebb and flow of the Internet and business around the world for centuries. To me eBay was the first real marketplace for anything you needed on the internet; with a combo of flea market, bazaar, and a general store. 

Overtime internet "stores" evolved into Amazon and Etsy. These companies came in and found a spot in the market where they saw a gap in services/market. 

As time goes on, other companies will see their opportunity and take action to provide what they believe is the next best thing; it may fit or it may flop, only the market will tell whether it catches on. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like that idea actually. I would like to see the resellers/infringers kept out to allow quality products to be in the spotlight. 

Looking at it from a business perspective though, I don't think they care. The more people who flock to their website the better, that's just how the website business works. Plus more sales translate into bigger profit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your will is your choice. Her demanding anything undermines the fundamental right by you to transfer property as you like upon your death and amounts to duress. 

Find a estate planning attorney near you that will offer you a free consultation. Go speak with them individually about your concerns and see what they direct you to do. Don't let your mom push you around, if you want to give your property to your brothers son, be the uncle you want to be and do it.

Good luck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've made their money and self policing would create less profit. I think a premium would drive a lot of sellers away. I've been selling on eBay for years and no listing fees is key for me using it; if I had to pay a fee to sell on there, I wouldn't use the service. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just keep him company, really. He doesn't ask I just help when I see him struggling. He does everything on his own: tends to his garden, pulls his own weeds, cuts his own grass, drives, goes to church every Sunday, etc. 

He has a ton of grandkids, but they are all off at school and don't come around much; I'm like their surrogate.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely agree. When it first started it was a good marketplace for DIYers and other creative individuals. But now, your correct, it has been overrun and does not have the same quality it did when it began.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha. He still has a rotary phone. No cable, just watched VHS Tapes (John Wayne, War Classics, Westerns, and no "mushy I love you movies.") He can't even comprehend my cell phone. We have abutting yards and we cut the lawn at the same time; we both have riding lawnmowers. He goes "ask that phone when it's going to rain." 

He was in WWII and was over in France. He still does mostly everything himself, I'm just there when he needs someone to talk to or hangout and drink a beer.

Here is a photo of him making me dinner: [PHOTO](https://imgur.com/gallery/O9dFD)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure you could start with Etsy, most of what's on there is personally made. 

I would say if you have an idea that you think is capable of being marketed to a large market, first write it down. From there you can start to design it yourself and make a prototype. Then you could set up a meeting with a patent attorney to determine the patentability of your product. If your idea is able to be patented, then you can go through the loops of creating a company, manufacturing, and building your brand if that's the route you would like to take. 

It really depends on what your idea is; you want to devise a strategy that best serves your goals. I would begin reading as much as you can just to get your mind wrapped around the different routes you could take.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 13:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell them the truth. They have rights under the contract you signed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 12:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just "*lol'd*." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 12:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen worse. Some people think their marketing is a good idea, this is an example of when it's *not*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 01:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just spitballing, what about the placement of the bracket on that knot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 01:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you also pay fees? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 21:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great work, I was thinking about making one of those today!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instead of my race car bed I want this to be my bed! 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea absolutely. You never know she might be stellar and just needs that one shot to show what she's got. It's a win win. 

I don't agree with it personally, but there is this bankruptcy firm near my area that offers internships. The caveat is the Intership is a 3mo unpaid gig which *may* turn into a paid position. I see their ads *almost every* three months; their basically getting free employment, which I think is wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Everything* is a *thing* on Reddit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 17:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/lawschool

Just go read a little bit. 

I would suggest taking the test and try to get the highest score you can; shoot for a full ride somewhere.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 17:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/flipping

Best thing I would suggest would be to broaden your scope of items. People do this all over, and some (most) make good money doing it. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please consult an attorney in your general area that specializes in real estate law. Find an attorney that will give you a free consultation; we don't here. Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 15:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a nice one! I've been looking for one like that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 15:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can second this. I'm pretty close with my neighbor, I look after him he is 95 and lives alone. He wanted a new alarm clock because his one from the 70's finally went out on him. He went through seriously 9 alarm clocks before I finally found a retro one on eBay for him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect! Thank you so much for the leads. I truly appreciate it. 

Since he was wounded, he had to get treated, I wonder if there is any data/report of his treatment? I found out he lost his eye due to his wounded from a US Census document that listed him "disabled due to injury resulting from Civil War Service; left eye lost." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think those services can come close to offering a paralegal type service. I would again suggest using craigslist. In your CL listing I would just make it clear you are looking for someone to embody a dual role. The receptionist that worked at my firm was a paralegal/receptionist, and was also their notary (2 Attorney firm, very unique). 

Also remember going with either Abby or Ruby your not going to be able to control them like a true employee. Plus how would manage the conflict/confidentially issue? I suppose you could hire them as an independent contractor and have them sign a NDA, but even then it's still a stretch. 

If you have a law school nearby see if you can find someone who will work for cheap, and then take a little time to train them on exactly what you need. Even though this may see like a time waste, they will be a lot more eager to learn and apply themselves instead of a paralegal (IMO). It's a win win for both you and the student. You save money and they receive experience and connections.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 22:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, my GW doesn't use this random bin nonsense. They pick through it in the back and then bring out all the stuff; no fair! (*crying inside with jealousy*) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 22:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next time why don't you just dig a hole, build a bathroom, and then just build a house around it. Jeez, you deserve a prize. I bet every shit feels like you won the championshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Company H of the 110th Regiment, PA Volunteers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been researching my lineage and discovered my Great Great Great Grandfather took part in the American Civil War. 

I've read quite a bit about the regiment's and companies' history. I really don't know what else to look for to find something tied to him personally. I would love to have a photo that I could point to him. 

Anything interesting would be welcomed, here is the information I have: 

Name: Peter Franklin Cochrane, PVT
Unit: Co. H 110th Regt. PA 
Volunteered/Mustered date: 02/27/1864 (17)
Info I've found: Wounded at Boydton Plank Road, VA on Oct 27, 1864 (Shrapnel to the eye/lost eye).
Birth date: 08/29/1847 
Death date: 01/19/1915 (68)
Buried: Carson Valley Cemetery in Duncansville, PA 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 02:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is sad but not uncommon I feel. I live in Michigan and one of the counties here told their residents NOT TO FLUSH during the Super Bowl Halftime for fear of overload. 

Here is the [STORY](http://www.detroitnews.com/story/news/local/macomb-county/2017/02/03/fraser-sinkhole-flush/97458438/)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 02:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude congrats on the 140lbs loss! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 17:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Engineering.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love that blue! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. I would much rather support the guys out there doing the actual digging.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, alright. That's ironic I was watching a Fluorite piece on EBay too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha really?! I need to look into this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 17:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Find some things laying around your house to sell on Letgo/EBay. 

Edit: Be honest first, then try to make it up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 14:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect. Thank you so much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 13:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was going to say a smashed AAA...haha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 13:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I worked at a law firm that had Ruby. After about a month they switched to Abby. Then about two months later, they hired a "at-home" receptionist off craigslist and it worked significantly better. The craigslist worker used google calendar to sync their schedule, they were more enthusiastic about working as well.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 12:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it realistic to "fake" these or other minerals? I'm just curious because I've been making a list of what I'd like to collect, and eBay seems to have a lot of low prices, but I don't always trust the item/buyer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 01:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pony...couldn't they come up with a better name?! Bunch of F'd up people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 01:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, thank you. I do like to read.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 22:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect, thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 16:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bankruptcy. Most of the attorneys I work for loathe bankruptcy and they outsource their bankruptcy issues to another firm. I think it would be a good way to understand another facet of business related issues.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 16:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2) is KEY. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 16:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just about everything, good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 16:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just read all the comments here, you have all the advice you need. Do whats right for you and your family, that is all that matters. You are living in your own world, choose how you want to move through it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
