<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2240</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unlikely Las Vegas Shows </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 02:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Local Man Undecided On Ska [Onion-style article] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 02:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PITTSBURGH, PA  Alvin Avery, 23, announced today that he has not yet made up his mind on ska music. This came after he purchased Reel Big Fishs Turn the Radio Off album and Streetlight Manifestos Everything Goes Numb album.

It was good, I guess, he started. I can see why people like it, its justhorns in rock? The world is moving too fast for me.

It all began when Mr. Avery heard The Impression That I Get by The Mighty Mighty Bosstones in a restaurant. He was so intrigued by the guitar playing right alongside the horns that he spent the next three minutes and fourteen seconds in a complete trance, quickly frightening his Tinder date away. 

I didnt get it, replied his date, Megan. He didnt notice anything else besides the song! I dont know why he was so hooked, its not like it was Bon Jovi, or something, she finished stupidly.

Mr. Avery does have a tendency to dislike uncommon combinations. The first time I saw a peanut butter and banana sandwich, I had to Google if that was even a real thing, he explained. The first time I saw a goldendoodle dog, I called the local pet store to make sure I hadnt lost my mind. What a world we live in!

At press time, Mr. Avery was seen purchasing Goldfingers Stomping Ground album while eating a slice of pineapple pizza. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 21:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got nothin' but love for Schenectady. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 08:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would if it wasn't wasting my vote. I fully support this country having viable third (and more!) parties. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 08:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "She could be earnin' her man, and learnin' her man, and at the same time burnin' her man." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 20:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Much luck to you in your endeavors as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nave Man Believes Pokmon Go Will Get Him Chicks [Onion-style article] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 01:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SCHENECTADY, NY  The Pokmon Go craze has taken the world by storm, and local man Ken Bell, 24, has the perfect way to exploit the gaming phenomenon.

Im gonna get so much tang from this game! he exclaimed. Mr. Bell has even provided his own justification for how this will happen. Women love a man in a powerful position. Well, Im a Level 32 Pokmon trainer and I control two gyms! Also, evolving and powering up the Pokmon is like science, and chicks dig smart guys, so Ive got that going for me now! Pokmon is going to make me such a catch!

Testing out his theory in the real world has led to several disappointments for Mr. Bell. Ive tried three times to hit on women using my Pokmon prowess, and to no avail. The first one, I said I was a Level 32 trainer, and she just walked away. The second one, I said I had a level 2354 Gyrados, and she just continued looking at her phone. Does she know how impressive that is?! The third one I just said I wanted to get a Pikachu  but sexily, like peek at you  and she slapped me. Maybe the world just cant handle my Pokmon skills after all.

At press time, Mr. Bell remained single and ready to be the very best like no one ever was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 00:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! Do you study sketch at all? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 20:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right now, as a hobby. I hope to make it a full-time job as soon as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 07:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently interviewing for jobs and performing/writing comedy. And yourself? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 21:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I perform comedy. Does that count? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 21:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you like hockey and/or history at all, there's this book called "Black Ice" about the Negro league of hockey in the Maritimes in Canada. Really fascinating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 21:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I perform comedy, hence the funny guy. Very ego-inflating, I know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 08:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah that sounds fun! I may have to check that out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 07:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha thanks! You should do one! I did it for shiggles really, I'm surprised it had this much of a following haha. And yeah, it's best to not feed their "game," just to play their game against them.

Glad you liked the movie! I'll have to check it out.

Well I love where I live now (the great state of New York), but I'd move to Boston if I had to. Beautiful city, rich in history, great food and people. Can't beat that*!
*Hate most of the sports teams though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 07:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're clearly a Simpsons fan, so all is well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 05:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're an interesting one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
