<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3323</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everybody made fun of how I lost a race to the fat kid in school. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 20:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If only my wheelchair was faster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't trust stairs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 02:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're always up to something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Several clowns trespassed into my school today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 08:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the police shot them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 08:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> neither of them are musicians </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 07:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/antijokes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was chased by a clown today during P.E. class </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 06:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He ran after me with a bat, laughing "I'm gonna get ya!" I don't know what's worse. My life being at risk as I ran for my life from a scary-ass clown, or the part where the whole class watched me do my mile-run with a scary-ass clown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 05:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is just great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the one Halloween costume that can't be worn slutty? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 02:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was going to say George Washington, but then I realized that was sexist and that all men can be equally slutty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the difference between a social justice warrior and a boxer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 00:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're allowed to punch the boxer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interviewer: What's your worst fear? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 07:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Applicant: Have you been keeping up with the politics?

Interviewer:Yeah, are you worried about the presidency?

Applicant: Mostly how much it's going to cost me to move to Canada. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 01:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone please explain to me the joke, I don't get it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 06:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah what he said! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I had all the money in the world to do whatever I wanted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 01:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be the next US president </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I had $1000000 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 22:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be a millionaire </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ugh I hate going to school, the kids there always bully me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 09:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why'd I decide to get a job as an algebra teacher in Detroit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There was a school shooting... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 05:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Uncle said he witnessed the worst school shooting of his entire life. He said, "A boy decided to shoot his father, then went to an Elementary school. He never killed anybody, but he shot four 5th graders and one teacher, all in different body parts; in the knee, shoulder, and arm."

I asked him "How's this the worst school shooting you've ever seen? I'm pretty sure there's been much more bloodshed and deaths in other shootings."

"No I literally mean this was the worst school shooting. The kid had like four rounds of ammo and missed almost every shot, with no kills."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What did the cow say to the other cow? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 00:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's kill the farmer, moo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My gf loves the 80s music </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 08:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played Take On Me, and she decided to go out on a date with me.

Later I played More Than a Feeling, and we confessed our love for each other.

Shortly after I played Beat it, she punched me and said I was getting ahead of myself.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 06:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> clearly you didn't watch the debate, but the headline was "two minutes," being completely ignored. And If I could get $40 in two minutes, how much do I get in an hour? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I had one dollar for every time Trump mentioned China... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 06:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd quit my job, because I earned $40 from just "two minutes." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think I'm going to vote for Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 02:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He did prove his penis is bigger than Hillary's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you confuse an AP student? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 07:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make the first 21 questions all be the answer C. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A black man walks into a bar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 05:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's 3 pm and he starts his shift. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What type of perfume do kidnappers use? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 08:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> chloroform </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do Hitler and Harambe have in common? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 03:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neither of them are musicians </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A man finds himself in hell. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 07:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Well this isn't heaven," the man said to himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 07:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> omg this guy just doesn't get it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hate baseball, I never have anybody to play with </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 04:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 06:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mindblown </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 06:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pretty sure this is an antijoke, but it's still funny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girl I think you should become a makeup artist. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 06:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Said the Abusive Father. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What did Uranus say to Saturn? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 06:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hate jews </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 23:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is just one of the very interesting chapters in Adolf Hitlers newest book "Mein Kampf". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 09:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well sir, I tip my hat to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you call a bad magician? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 09:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best insult you can think of, to get him off the stage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interviewer: How would you handle a complaint from a customer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 09:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Applicant: Well that depends, what's the complaint?

Interviewer: He's complaining that his burger had onions on it, even though he specifically asked they were to be removed.

Applicant: Well I'd start by telling him he's in the retail section. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 23:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/antijokes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I die, tell my dad I'm dead. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 08:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Punch him before he says "Hi I'm Dad!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interviewer: What hobbies do you have outside of school? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 03:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Applicant: Well I often perform at local hubs doing stand up comedy.
Interviewer: Really? Do you write your own material?
Applicant: Not really, I just copy quotes from the US elections.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why was 6 afraid of 7? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 08:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 7 had a gun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 08:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> omg yes, I love reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 08:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't have the title be the punchline, this is good
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You each will be granted ONE wish. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 08:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Three explorers find a magical wishmaker who is willing to grant the explorers one wish for the greatest desires.

The first explorer walks up and says,"I wish for a time machine, so I can go to the future and live in a more advanced world." The wishmaker grants the wish and sends the explorer to the year 3016 where it probably got better.

The second explorer says,"I wish for a soulmate who will love me for the rest of my life." The wish is granted and the explorer goes to a church to be wedded with the love of his life."

Finally the third explorer, contemplates then says, "I wish to have a glock 43 pistol." Confused with a wish so small, the wishmaker grants it and gives the explorer his gun. The explorer points the gun at the wishmaker and yells, "Give me more wishes or else!"
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
