<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3232</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been studying proctoarchaelogy my whole life, and that guy doesn't know his ass from a hole in the ground. Trust me, I'm a professional.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you should add strawman to narcissism on your list of "words I should look up the meanings of today." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peruvians.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, isn't it great? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I don't think that happened, but if it did he must have been *super* overweight to begin with. That's about 2600 calories a day--your body is not actually using *all* of those calories, but that's still a significant number a day. To lose weight consistently, he'd have to be a pretty heavy guy to start with. And I weep for his protein intake. Anyway, this whole topic is insane.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You keep using that word. I don't think it means what you think it means. 

Also, thank you for the compliment on my comedic skills, I thought it was pretty funny myself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To me he'll always be Eddie Malvin from Punky Brewster.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He's just disgusted by the watering down of grammar. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This again? [C'mon now...](http://i.imgur.com/1Xn5cXU.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The entrails I cast upon the ground just now are disagreeing with you, friend. Dare you contradict the tried and true sacrament of the Etruscan haruspex?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are certain disorders that make high fiber diets detrimental. That said, somehow I think he just means he doesn't like them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unusual argument in /r/OpenSignups when one subscriber complains about the number of porn torrents in the sub </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quiet, you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, I think that's where the whole "calories in - calories out" argument is overly simple.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll be fit as a fiddle with my recommended regimen of gin, Postum, milk baths, and arsenic salts!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If that's true, you should be honored that you've inspired a copycat. Maybe you could start a Special People's Club and put out a newsletter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about we not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, I love how he links to a Vox article without having actually read it, because the point of that article appears to be a criticism of journalism, not scientific research! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try Greek yogurt instead of butter if you'd like to cut the fat. I find it's a great substitute. Or you can do half butter, half Greek yogurt. Another good addition: salsa.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shut up and drink your gin, it'll put hair on your chest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Humankind is simply materialized color operating on the 49th vibration. You would make that conclusion walking down the street or going to the store. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, you *could* go on an all-potato diet, I'm just not sure it would be the most balanced choice. For a while my senior year of college I had a potato every night for dinner because they were so cheap. I ate other things, too, though. I can't imagine adopting a diet that doesn't involve eating some greens.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do believe that you are genuinely nuts. 

EDIT: BTW, he was totally that "girl."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Archive](http://archive.is/MCn00) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Why are you on a potato diet?" Starchy bickering in /r/cooking over the benefits of the noble spud </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a picture of a [baby whose thrifty parents have learned to save money on clothes](http://i.dailymail.co.uk/i/pix/2014/10/27/1414428910529_wps_28_Halloween_photos.jpg). See, this is what more poor people need to learn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sound like one of those fat, poor people they were talking about. Now go eat your bowl of tapenade and stop complaining.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The demented mother calling out for her necromorph baby in Dead Space 2. WTF, that's not okay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What, don't you remember the plushie love section of your SATs?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Archive](http://archive.is/c6Ie5) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Commenter in /r/GifRecipes does not appreciate it when people say "chai tea," declares war on yuppie coffeehouses everywhere </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked this comment:

Everyone should know by know wtf a Furry is in this day and age, ESPECIALLY if it's your job to talk about the things that are going on in this day and age. News people can sometimes be very ignorant. In another example, we had a photographer who had to stop a reporter from calling 911 because he saw a train going in the opposite direction the day after he saw it going the other way...on the same track. 

Yeah, that's totally the same thing as not knowing what a furry is! You know, I get it, it's annoying when people pretend to not know or understand something because it's "weird," but I don't really think these people should be expected to know what Furries are. It's like expecting everyone to know what Bronies are. Guess what, it's not mainstream and that's probably part of the reason why it attracts the people it does, and that's okay. Not everyone has to know about your subculture. 

With that, I'm off to my pony play island fetish retreat. *clop clop clop clop* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen a lot of people mentioning Django, and I love Django, but I'm surprised no one has mentioned the Hateful 8. The more I think about that movie the more I love it. It's so damn good, and there are numerous moments of revenge.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Archive](http://archive.is/jqdfr) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The general ration you're going to want is 1 cup sour cream to 3 cups cake flour, 1/2 tsp baking soda, 6 eggs, 3 cups sugar and 2 sticks butter. Normally you'd use baking powder, but the acid in the sour cream will react with the soda. This is a guideline, you can tweak it as you see fit, but it should give you the texture you're looking for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't want to know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "If you can get so fat by eating fast food/boxed food, you clearly have enough money to make pesto or pumpkin soup for example." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His point is that things come in boxes, but most boxes have no recipes, so I'm not really sure what his point is. 

I think he's just arguing for the sake of it. No one is that dumb.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arguments over furries abound in /r/Videos. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a [popular post](https://www.reddit.com/r/videos/comments/674qel/news_pundit_learns_what_furry_means_live_on_camera/?utm_content=comments utm_medium=hot utm_source=reddit utm_name=videos) in /r/Videos in which News hosts on MSNBC bust out laughing over a furry convention. Naturally, this lead to some arguments in the comments about how common Furries are, what they are, and whether or not the people giving us our news should already know what they are. 

["Don't ever be surprised by the number of people who work in the news business that are completely ignorant to common culture."](https://www.reddit.com/r/videos/comments/674qel/news_pundit_learns_what_furry_means_live_on_camera/dgnv4rt/?st=j1w9gxju sh=c47a1a08)

["Not really sure how significantly different this is to any other costume related convention."](https://www.reddit.com/r/videos/comments/674qel/news_pundit_learns_what_furry_means_live_on_camera/dgo1c4k/?st=j1w9fp0i sh=7a902e96)

["How do you host the NEWS and not know what a fucking furry is? "](https://www.reddit.com/r/videos/comments/674qel/news_pundit_learns_what_furry_means_live_on_camera/dgnpmbx/?st=j1w9l2pf sh=cb6a2af0)

[But what are furries?](https://www.reddit.com/r/videos/comments/674qel/news_pundit_learns_what_furry_means_live_on_camera/dgnru5p/?context=3 st=j1w9o506 sh=0aab8f4e) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> May I recommend [red lentil fritters](http://www.foodandwine.com/recipes/red-lentil-fritters-with-mint-yogurt-sauce). 

Also, I highly recommend making a warm lentil salad with fresh parsley, olive oil, lemon, red onion, and arugula. 

Important point: what kind of lentils did you get? Green lentils will be firmer and stand up to cooking better, so they're better for salads and sides. Red and yellow lentils break down more are better for sauces, soups, fritters, dal, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can oil your steak, but use a higher smoke point oil. My two favorites for this are avocado oil and clarified butter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A leg of lamb is lovely, especially in spring. That said, I think with 16 people two proteins makes sense. You could a side of broiled salmon with a couple of sauces, and then either the lamb or a pork loin or roast capon or something like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A big factor in cake texture is the type of fat used. With butter you will get a denser cake with a smaller crumb than you will with oil. Oil cakes will be a little lighter/fluffier. So it sounds like you're wanting a butter cake. 

In addition, you might have good luck with the addition of sour cream. I do a sour cream pound cake that is very dense and moist as you describe. In addition, you may also be able to boost that dense/moist texture by adding an extra egg yolk. 

It might be easier to give specific advice if you describe the cake you ate in a little more detail. What kind of cake was it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't really a gimmick so much as it's a trendy thing right now, by my sister and I have talking about getting some Transglutaminase to make shrimp pasta and other "meat glue" dishes with. They sell it by the kg, though, so we're going to get one bag and split it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The portrait painter--she was only there briefly but I'm a fan of her comedy so I noticed her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, that's so emo Kylo Ren.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, the old work vs. force issue--tripped me up a few times, for sure. 

Most of these arguments would be easily settled if people were able to just admit they're mistaken.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting fact about gamut--it comes from the Latin "gamma ut" and originally referred to G an octave and a half below middle C, then was later used to refer to the complete scale. In the past century it's increased in popularity to use it to refer to various spectra--I'm not sure who coined the term "run the gamut" but I think it works beautifully. Because it's often heard, however, people mistake it for "gambit." It's like of like "hone in on" vs. "home in on" in that way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A strange game. The only winning move is not to play. How about a nice game of Chess?

I was waiting for someone to break out the WarGames reference and there it is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, "There's zero inbreeding in my family..." "my uncle grandpa..."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like June Diane Raphael was super pregnant when they filmed this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for explaining, I guess I didn't think he would get so pissed over that, so I thought I missed him making a big mistake or something. 

Well, I guess I shouldn't be too surprised by Gavin's response. He's a petty douche.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oooh, I heard him mention needing to meet up with his family, I missed that he redirected the flight. Thanks!

I think Gavin hasn't thought this through--it will come back to bite him, I swear.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would definitely say that counts. That's one of my favorite movies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I missed something--what did Jack do to warrant that kind of smack in the face? Also, seems like an unwise move to screw with him... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that was Dolan's Cadillac, and that it was from Nightmares and Dreamscapes, not Night Shift?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, it's excellent. He's amazing in it. It's about a piano prodigy who leaves his wealthy family to work on an oil rig--but he goes back when he finds out his father is dying. He was nominated for best actor for it but lost to George C. Scott who won for Patton (and famously turned down the award).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a great movie, no denying it, and he's always good, but when I was thinking of my favorite performances of his, out of *all* of his movies, it wasn't one of the top ones I thought of for me, personally. I'd include it in a top 10, though. I would definitely call Chinatown one of Faye Dunaway's best performances, along with Network.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah, well he's only a baby, so he didn't *say* that. But he took a bite, looked perplexed, then smacked his lips and took another bite, then squished it around in his hands for a minute and then shoved the rest in his mouth. 

So I think he'll eat more, is what I'm saying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure what your comment means? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I said elsewhere in the thread, I agree that the time-limiting idea is a poor one. That said, I take issue with this:

you have to learn to not be easily irritated by ones rooomate's within-reason actions.

1) I would argue that it's your job to *not irritate your roommate* rather that expect him to not be irritated.

2) I actually don't think the roommate is behaving within reason--I think he's being inconsiderate and OP should say something about it. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I don't understand--his roommate isn't sleeping or studying. 

You're saying that instead of communicating about his needs like an adult, he should just go somewhere else. People need to feel like they have a space of their own, it's really uncomfortable to spend all your time in public. Part of going to college is learning to share your space respectfully with your roommate. That includes being aware of your hygiene, your clutter, your noise pollution, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk, to me I think you should just leave the room then

He has just as much of a right to relax and enjoy time in his room as his roommate does. He shouldn't have to leave. Why not tell the roommate to go play somewhere else? Because that would be unreasonable--just like telling OP to leave and go to a coffee shop is unreasonable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's very reasonable for you to make this request, although I wouldn't necessarily put a time on it--I would start out by bring up the issue that it's disturbing you and see what he says. Maybe he can stick to times you're not there to use Discord.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's a fork and knife sandwich right there. 

I'm interested in your recipe. I'm actually cooking a turkey meatloaf right now, coincidentally.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds like a great idea in terms of contrasting textures and complimentary flavors. Coconut and lime is one of my favorite combinations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not the asshole. It sounds like after you calm down you should just set a boundary with him: "You're not making our friendship a priority and that hurts. I don't want to be friends with someone who doesn't keep their word." If he blows your concerns off, you're probably better off not being friends with him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't sound like you or Karen is the asshole. The only potential asshole here, if I'm understanding your text right, is Phil.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tako in Pittsburgh?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That filter wasn't necessary. 

Crust looks awesome! Are those white chocolate shavings on top? Or desiccated coconut? I've never seen anything on top before besides whipped cream or meringue, that's interesting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, I had forgotten about that one! I haven't seen that film since it was in the theaters, but the final scene in the bowling alley is amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not usually a doughnut fan, but these look great. It's good to know the tip about freezing the dough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My son had a tater tot for the first time today and he was intrigued. I think I'll try to make these for him and see what he thinks. He likes broccoli when it's cut up fine like this. Maybe I'll make a yogurt dipping sauce for them, that would work well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, her scheme was pure, evil madness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, Giancarlo Esposito and Samuel L. Jackson? Count me in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, WAHAPPENED? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would definitely say so, yes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'm not a huge fan of those, either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A little sweet, sure. But donut sweet? I'll  pass. I think a pineapple or honey glaze on the chicken would been enough for balance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure I have. I love that movie, it's just not one I'd pick for his top performance. Just my opinion, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't seen it yet! It seems like a great idea, but it looked like it might be a little *too* silly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be warned, Art Garfunkel's not exactly a stellar actor, but Jack Nicholson and Candace Bergen more than make up for his weaknesses. It's kind of a depressing film in some ways, but definitely worth watching. It also has its funny moments, as most of Mike Nichols' films do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you, I think that *A Mighty Wind* is less accessible for that reason. But the songs are such perfect parodies of specific artists (The Kingston Trio, the Rooftop Singers, etc.) that I can't help but be impressed and amused by it. It's incredibly well done, the way Spinal Tap perfectly parodies Black Sabbath and Led Zeppelin and the like. They really understand how to distill the essence of a thing and then skewer it lovingly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None of that talk, now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohh, [nooooo](http://i2.kym-cdn.com/photos/images/newsfeed/000/583/041/d5c.jpg).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw the post about that, which got me thinking about some of his work that's affected me most. There are so many, but this film, *Carnal Knowledge*, *About Schmidt*, *One Flew Over The Cuckoo's Nest* and *The Witches of Eastwick* are probably my favorites.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His crew is seamless--not one weak link in the bunch IMO. Parker Posey said later that she was stoned in every scene in the movie, but it never stops her from being on point. And of course, Michael McKean, Fred Willard, Eugene Levy, Catherine O'Hara, Christopher Guest and Harry Shearer are all geniuses. 

Because I grew up listening to my mom's folk music, I truly love *A Mighty Wind* and I feel like I really get what they were going for. It's funny even if you don't know anything about folk music, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks lovely, except for the bun--I just don't get the whole "donut and fried meat sandwich" trend. However, that chicken looks perfect, and jalapenos are the ideal topping. 

Is that some kind of ranch-like sauce? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's just too much. Give me a brioche bun or an onion roll or something, don't ruin it with greasy, sweet dough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm surprised the director, Bob Rafelson, didn't make more well known films. He directed the amazing, wacky *Head*, which I love, but overall his filmography is pretty sparse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny ones I love: How Did This Get Made, The Flophouse, Doug Loves Movies

More serious ones: Maltin on Movies, The Projection Booth, and if you like horror films, Faculty of Horror.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jack Nicholson's monologue to his father in Five Easy Pieces is one of the more heart-wrenching scenes in film </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Michael Higgins and Jane Lynch in A Mighty Wind. Their delivery is perfect. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good one. It's a bummer of a film all around, but at least the abusers received punishment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bathtub scene, in particular, is just too painful. It's almost *too* much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I felt like *John Wick* was what *Payback* was trying to be, except it was about 50 times better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Big or small, what's the greatest revenge you've seen in a movie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously, there are great films that center around revenge, like *Oldboy* and *Kill Bill* and *Inside Man*. Then there are smaller moments of very satisfying revenge within films. For example, I think that scenes in *Amelie* in which she gaslights the fruit vendor are very satisfying. Or Milton burning down the company in *Office Space*. What are some of your favorites? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rilo Kiley - Portions for Foxes [pop/rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Diamonds are forever, but this drama about a $20K engagement ring is only three hours old and is already exploding. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 02:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Long argument in /r/videos over whether or not Eddie Murphy Delirious is still funny </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Walmart waffles inspire a Wal-o-text fight in /r/ExpectationvsReality. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 22:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A community survey in /r/MandelaEffect triggers a slapfight about conspiracy theories </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 19:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A fight about what color orange juice is </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "[My in-laws] brought their own fucking ketchup. I have since had no respect for their opinions." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The pizza police, they live inside of this thread! The pizza police, they're coming to take my pineapple and lecture me about what I'm allowed to like, ohh nooooooo! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bad history meets Indian food </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A trust fall gone awry starts a fight in /r/ChildrenFallingOver </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's a normal reaction for a child who gets their face shoved in a cake? People in /r/Funny argue about it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/NYC lights up over cigarette costs. One commenter says he's glad, gets his butt extinguished </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Like boxed brownie mix? Well, "people love mediocrity." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> French protests inspire a massive fight in /r/AccidentalRenaissance. "Welcome to reality, snowflake." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL a man bought 5,000 Bitcoins in 2009 for 14 and forgot about them. Four years later they were worth $850,000, and he used some of the money to buy an apartment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beer in a can? What am I, a peasant? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone gets salty over Japanese bread in /r/FoodPorn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cheese means it's not "authentic Mexican." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woman in /r/relationship_advice says she can't imagine having a conversation with a 23-year-old, but her perspective is poorly received. "You're only 7 years older than them and love the smell of your own farts." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "It's one thing to claim your food is culturally superior, it's another entirely to bastardize another culture's and claim it's better." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Slapfight in /r/HDTGM over the comedy stylings of June Diane Raphael </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heated argument about cotton swabs in TIL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Denizens of /r/news buckle up in the armchair of the law as they discuss United's new policy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OP in CasualAMA says he's about to break up with his GF. Then he mentions they are poly and the drama starts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 13:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is polyamory a [character flaw?](https://www.reddit.com/r/casualiama/comments/65qlkb/ill_be_breaking_up_with_my_gf_of_5_years_in_about/dgcmbo6/?context=3 st=j1m22163 sh=79b4a90d)

One guy points out that [lots of people make it work](https://www.reddit.com/r/casualiama/comments/65qlkb/ill_be_breaking_up_with_my_gf_of_5_years_in_about/dgcreo3/?context=3 st=j1m1z6kd sh=57b6887c)

[Is it a raw deal for the guy?](https://www.reddit.com/r/casualiama/comments/65qlkb/ill_be_breaking_up_with_my_gf_of_5_years_in_about/dgcok4s/?context=3 st=j1m20a4n sh=4d414c5f)

Here's the [whole post](https://www.reddit.com/r/casualiama/comments/65qlkb/ill_be_breaking_up_with_my_gf_of_5_years_in_about/?st=j1m25yln sh=2c226c99) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ragin' Cajun doesn't like Cajun seasoning blends. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 23:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Quick and easy roasted potatoes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 21:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quick technique for excellent roasted potatoes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am making meals for the week and my husband requested I include roasted potatoes. Typically I have a two step technique that involves par boiling the potatoes and then roasting in the oven in cast iron to get those loves crispy bits. But today I wanted to try something different to see if I could save time and steps. 

I cut my red potatoes into wedges and put into a large ziploc bag I added some vegetable oil and tossed them to coat. Then I added some salted, seasoned panko and tossed again to coat. I arranged them quickly on a wire rack over a roasting pan, and cooked them at 400 F for 30 minutes. What I got was a delicious roasted potato with minimal effort or time spent. I wanted to share my success! [Here is a link to how they turned out.](http://imgur.com/a/S22FK)

Next time I have some chicken fat stored in the fridge, I am planning on using that instead of vegetable oil.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This guy is all over the place spreading his misunderstanding of IQ assessment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 15:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Korn recruits Metallica bassists 12-year-old son for South American tour </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 04:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guy in TIL says Mensa isn't that hard to get into, scores Drama Quotient of 130 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 02:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That bread is like pop music </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 15:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Petty slapflight in /r/CrappyDesign over whether or not one commenter has actually read any "Eat This, Not That" books. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Using a thermometer in the kitchen is "less authentic." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The heartbreak of paella </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This drama is brought to you by the Dairy Farmers of America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a TIL post up about milk in school lunch programs, and naturally that has generated some bickering about cows' rights and milk's nutritional contributions. 

[How do the cows feel about it?](https://www.reddit.com/r/todayilearned/comments/64xizl/til_milk_must_be_offered_at_every_meal_if_a/dg5xwdy/?context=3 st=j1fdik99 sh=56e01f22)

["you could just go outside during the daytime for 20 mins and not drink fatty white sugar water."](https://www.reddit.com/r/todayilearned/comments/64xizl/til_milk_must_be_offered_at_every_meal_if_a/dg62bkb/?context=3 st=j1fctrdx sh=06754ddc)

Someone points out that [humans are not baby cows](https://www.reddit.com/r/todayilearned/comments/64xizl/til_milk_must_be_offered_at_every_meal_if_a/dg5rphk/?st=j1fdrrfk sh=40cef152) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This removed comment in /r/sushi is prime sushi snobbery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I have news for you, cooking is about improvisation." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/FacePalm debates the justifications for stating height preferences on Tinder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Commenter in /r/AskReddit weighs in on porn star anatomy, his karma gets gang banged </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I have bedded dozens and dozens of women with my cooking skills." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Commenter in /r/itookapicture wants to make it clear: it was Photoshopped. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girthy drama in /r/Relationship_Advice. "Maybe he is sensitive, but you sound like a size queen bitch." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OP wants her husband on the stroll, but /r/sex tells her to slow her roll </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anti American pepperoni pizza tirade in /r/shittyfoodporn. Yanks love it! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Enjoy your burnt cheese, you amateurs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Massive argument about customer service in /r/PettyRevenge. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Italy, apparently when you're born they hand you a diploma </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 14:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This guy is all over a post in /r/eatcheapandhealthy, acting as the arbiter of carnitas. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 02:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gourmet lets it be known he has no patience for "subpar fast food fries." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey, you got nutritional yeast in my Parmesan! You got Parmesan in my nutritional yeast! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 14:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The tragedy of refusing cold beef broth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 04:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sub superiority slapfight in /r/eatsandwiches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sesame Street Peanut Butter Factory Song </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let them eat processed cheese! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nothing like a deep dish to bring out the pizza master race </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two people in /r/pics rehash an ancient argument about that Beyonc photo. "You lied" vs. "You're trying to split hairs." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fish keeper carps about the state of /r/aquariums, but the community thinks it's a load of pollocks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This post](https://www.reddit.com/r/Aquariums/comments/62qwic/not_happy_with_this_sub/?utm_content=comments utm_medium=front utm_source=reddit utm_name=Aquariums) was made by someone who states he does not appreciate hostility in the sub. 

Someone tells him ["you know where to find the door"](https://www.reddit.com/r/Aquariums/comments/62qwic/not_happy_with_this_sub/dfoolih/?st=j12c40l9 sh=df9a4e43)

["Why should I have to tonguefuck your ass for you to take criticism seriously?"](https://www.reddit.com/r/Aquariums/comments/62qwic/not_happy_with_this_sub/dfoy7j3/?st=j129qdig sh=edfbb628)

[Someone steps in to defend the sub but OP argues](https://www.reddit.com/r/Aquariums/comments/62qwic/not_happy_with_this_sub/dfomk42/?st=j129omkx sh=022465a3)

And here [OP argues with a mod](https://www.reddit.com/r/Aquariums/comments/62qwic/not_happy_with_this_sub/dfoqxoa/?st=j12b0vd1 sh=f986aa19) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A chef and a food writer duke it out over poached eggs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 16:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [CRYPTO] The Honey Island Swamp Monster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 03:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "If you are a true connoisseur of southern breakfast taste..." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 01:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This guy really hates the fact that Detroit style pizza is a thing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 01:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People get snippy, nitpick in /r/ShowerThoughts about man buns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 22:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it [functional](https://www.reddit.com/r/Showerthoughts/comments/630r5e/the_man_bun_is_the_mullet_of_the_millennials/dfqk4yi/?st=j114w9oa sh=f2355432), or should you just cut your damn hair you hippie? 

[This guy wants to cut them off](https://www.reddit.com/r/Showerthoughts/comments/630r5e/the_man_bun_is_the_mullet_of_the_millennials/dfqg1tv/?st=j114zlnr sh=42993aa0)

[But what about the mullet?](https://www.reddit.com/r/Showerthoughts/comments/630r5e/the_man_bun_is_the_mullet_of_the_millennials/dfqh4f6/?utm_content=permalink utm_medium=front utm_source=reddit utm_name=Showerthoughts)

["Man buns are douchey..."](https://www.reddit.com/r/Showerthoughts/comments/630r5e/the_man_bun_is_the_mullet_of_the_millennials/dfqfw35/?st=j1152jpa sh=eba39681) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cotard delusion -- the belief that you're dead/a rotting corpse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 22:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Argument in /r/WTF when one commenter states that Jerry Sandusky was innocent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 17:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stool Chart Cake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 02:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Food critic deigns to offer criticism of a slowcooker recipe, but his feedback receives zero stars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 02:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone's feeling salty in /r/GifRecipes! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 02:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Commenters in /r/AdviceAnimals investigate the case of the counterfeit Ugg slippers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> User in /r/cooking presents the history of pepper. Source: his ass. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Commenters in /r/ProRevenge are nursing a grudge -- is it okay for nursing preceptors treat trainees like crap? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that there is a lexicon of profanity in Russian called "mat." There are poems, jokes, and entire plays written using mat. As of 2014, mat has been banned from all movies, theatrical productions, and concerts by the government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 16:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chocolate cake with peanut butter buttercream </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 16:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Chocolate cake with peanut butter buttercream </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unhappy cooks in /r/GifRecipes flip their woks over a rice dish </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 05:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A stir fried vegetables and white rice dish triggers numerous meltdowns in /r/GifRecipes.

[Do "tiny details" matter?](https://www.reddit.com/r/GifRecipes/comments/61u9bu/nice_spice_rice/dfhjb29/?st=j0t02fmg sh=2e967f26)

Argument about [coconut oil](https://www.reddit.com/r/GifRecipes/comments/61u9bu/nice_spice_rice/dfhjgbs/?st=j0t04sjn sh=accf60b8)

["Are you the type of person..."](https://www.reddit.com/r/GifRecipes/comments/61u9bu/nice_spice_rice/dfhoc1u/?context=3 st=j0t09fkd sh=1121ed16)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Self-described "Logician" does a perplexing AMA in which he does not answer anything </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A guy who calls himself "The Dragon" and a "logician" posted an AMA which has since been removed--and none of the commenters are having any of it. 

[Here's the full thread](https://www.reddit.com/r/IAmA/comments/5yy95e/iama_logician_which_is_like_being_a_wielder_of/?st=j0sww6zd sh=e1fe7fab) which is now locked and filled with skepticism and scorn. 

[This nugget of delight](https://www.reddit.com/r/IAmA/comments/5yy95e/iama_logician_which_is_like_being_a_wielder_of/deunvtk/?context=10000 st=j0swufhi sh=4ce18d80) starts out with the question "When did you first realize that your parents were related?"

And if you want to see the original post before it was removed, there's a copy of it [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/justneckbeardthings/comments/5yyoos/the_dragon_is_smarter_then_all_of_us/?st=j0swtja3 sh=2be1cdd8) in /r/justneckbeardthings. 

[He also made an appearance in /r/AMAdisasters](https://www.reddit.com/r/AMADisasters/comments/5yzibt/the_genius_known_as_the_dragon_is_simply_too/?sort=controversial st=j0sx80tj sh=c16ef4fa) which is confusing as well. 

[Archive 1](http://archive.is/ErM71)

[Archive 2](http://archive.is/N8tiC) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Argument in /r/ExpectationvsReality over whether or not yeezies be lit AF </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conscientious objector does an AMA, inspires protests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's a bitter bake-off in /r/GifRecipes over sugar in pizza dough </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amusing drama in /r/Economics when a commenter starts his financial advice with "as a high school dropout who earns 6 figures i always feel ahead of most but im nothing special." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 16:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There can be only one (lobster roll) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 01:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Argument in /r/PettyRevenge about the financial impact of stealing toilet paper. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> French Onion Penne </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Toasted marshmallow cake` </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Decorating a mirror glaze cake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 15:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Decorating a mirror glaze cake [1066x600] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 15:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3-Ingredient cookies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 14:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can't be the only one with a fondness for the handsome Mark Ruffalo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 23:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Commenter in /r/PublicFreakout argues that speed ain't nothin' but a number, causes multi-comment pileup </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 12:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A "live action video game" about...awkward dates! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man in /r/Roadcam is found guilty of "driving like a cockend," sentenced to negative karma. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 17:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Raindrop cake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 03:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drama in /r/WTF over whether or not it's okay for a teacher to bite a student's hair. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This noodle gatekeeper knows all! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your salmon is not very fresh... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Popeye presents Eugene the Jeep (1940) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The continuing saga of a self-described "music nerd" who takes numerous stylistic issues with the show "Big Little Lies." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a user, DeathbyOstrich, who often posts in /r/biglittlelies. This user takes issue with some of the stylistic choices on the show (particularly the music) and argues with everyone who disagrees. 
I'm linking to the full posts because they're fairly small and his comments are scattered throughout--you need to see all of it in order to appreciate the drama. 


[Why don't they drive Teslas?](https://www.reddit.com/r/biglittlelies/comments/5xvy8j/all_these_wealthy_californians_and_no_one_drives/?st=j0iaaqos sh=f1e37176)

[This post takes issue with the music being too old for the characters. Other commenters start calling him "Big Little Troll"](https://www.reddit.com/r/biglittlelies/comments/5zkisd/more_unrealistic_60s_music_by_the_producers/?sort=controversial st=j0i9v3k3 sh=5477932d)

[This writing is NOT SUBTLE](https://www.reddit.com/r/biglittlelies/comments/5xukvw/the_writing_is_not_subtle_i_dont_like_being_hit/?st=j0iabq0d sh=22dda511)

[This post doesn't like the choice of a Buick, or Neil Young](https://www.reddit.com/r/biglittlelies/comments/5xsotg/buick_over_mercedes_fleetwood_macneil_young_soap/?st=j0i9irfa sh=3d7e787c)



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Silent film star Theda Bara, circa 1917 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 03:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Its Head Lights Up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 01:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A few small nips in an /r/OldSchoolCool/ post about Frida Kahlo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ["I think her art is garbage..."](https://www.reddit.com/r/OldSchoolCool/comments/603uim/a_17year_old_frida_kahlo_poses_for_a_family_photo/df3deg4/?st=j0fmayuq sh=c5a880e8)

[This comment contrasts her with Bob Ross](https://www.reddit.com/r/OldSchoolCool/comments/603uim/a_17year_old_frida_kahlo_poses_for_a_family_photo/df3g3kb/?st=j0fn69ap sh=25c22d1a)

[Argument over her sexual orientation](https://www.reddit.com/r/OldSchoolCool/comments/603uim/a_17year_old_frida_kahlo_poses_for_a_family_photo/df3eihs/?context=3 st=j0fncrj3 sh=efbc7625)

Was she [really ahead of her time?](https://www.reddit.com/r/OldSchoolCool/comments/603uim/a_17year_old_frida_kahlo_poses_for_a_family_photo/df3cqee/?st=j0fna51w sh=3881eaa1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that in the lineup scene in The Usual Suspects, the actors kept cracking up because Benicio Del Toro kept farting. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I'm white and I'm offended on behalf of Japanese people." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 16:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [GTM] It's bad outside </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 16:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
