<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2728</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most memorable dream you have ever had? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk man, i saw a video where a crackhead did a backflip of a 2 or 3 story house for $1...landed like a cat too. Crackheads have 9 lives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On of my favorite stu scenes is when theyre in a room with atticus at a party and stu describes marcy by saying "shes built for speed, born to fuck" i died </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was funny as shit. Just the way he talked made me laugh my ass off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am i the only one who questioned why the hell runkle had cameras watching him in his private office? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone else feel that stu beggs got the worst fucking ending? The man was eating dinner with a sex doll, how much lower can u get? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 08:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering they looked mre like harambe then humans today i dont think they really gave a shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 07:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know most people dont know this movie but it was on disney back in the 90s, its called camp nowhere. Apparently, it was jessica albas first film although you dont see much of her. Anyways i watched in when i was in grade 5 back in like 2008 and it just gave me this really good feeling. Going back and watching it today i feel so nostalgic. Great film, childhood dream.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 06:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it the kind of baseball college movie recently released? because if it is i think ive watched it it was also pretty decent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 06:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive had to take long breaks from watching that show, im over a year in and only halfway through the episodes, i love them but the 40 minute episodes 9 seasons and 20 something episodes per season is way too much. One day i will finish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 05:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you some much! You just quoted my favorite movie OF ALL TIME!! dazed and confused...man i cant describe what that movie made me feel the first time i watched it...ive watched it over 10 times over 5 years maybe more. Truly a classic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 05:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lowkey a good movie haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 05:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha ik ironic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 04:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If i watched waynes world when i was a kid i defintely wouldnt know what was going on  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 03:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Armenian power!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 03:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah cmon its a classic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 02:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Example: your crush talks to you for the first time ever, you just ate a tuna sandwich.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 02:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or the whispering eye </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 02:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never understood that reference. Explain? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 02:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You dont have to go to bed early to wake up early </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 02:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The benchwarmers. I always refer back to a certain scene at the end where he says he and his wife "went all the way" and are having a baby. One of the cluless guys asks what all the way meant, and some guy whispers it to him, and he had some crazy reaction. I asked my parents and they wouldnt tell me, and a few years later i figured it out for myself haha. Just an example l. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sometimes, ill watch a movie that i watched when i was younger and realize that i had no idea what the hell was going on when i first saw it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 02:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 01:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya i think im gonna end up doing that when it gets out of hand, right now its still ok but in about a year...oh well. Anyways lucky for you it stopped, because now ou are able to have a hair transplant treatment which is what im gonna do when the time comes. Relatively cheap in some countries. My dads friend did it, looks great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 01:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Started losing hair at 16 slowly, im now just turning 19 and lets just say i wish i was 16 again. Its going downhill very fast  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you wake up earlier on weekends then u can sleep in 5 days a week instead of two </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 01:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 01:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brain fart ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you live to be 70, you will spend 10 years of your life on Monday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 01:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You would be able to fine way way more than that, imagine the u discovered life that van only live deep down in the ocran where no amounts of like or oxygen can reach. Some spooky ass shit is definitely down there. Release the cracken motha fucka </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ocean does facinate me, the fact that weve only discovered less than 5% of the ocean is u real. Imagine whats lying at the bottom of the ocean... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You picked the most boring one haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
