<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject366</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 06:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a professional massage.  For less than $100 you can have a skilled professional work on your body and make you feel great.  It involves great feeling, great smells, and relaxing sounds.  I think a massage is definitely something you should do before you die.  Don't be self conscious, people of all shapes, sizes, and ages are welcome.  Massage therapists take an oath of non-judgement and want to make you feel better.  (I'm not a massage therapist, but I go to one monthly and have given lots of friends the gift of their first massage).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone beat my time at solving a Rubik's Cube? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 04:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-30 00:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I own and run Vibrators.com.  I got here by being nerdy and starting an internet company that sells things and doesn't tell anyone afterward called Shop In Private.  That business gained notoriety as an early Internet retailer.  It eventually bought the Vibrators.com name from the original registrant.  So now, although I'm more a technologist than I am a pervert I run Vibrators.com.  I'm not sure it is a repeatable story, but I thought I would share.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone want to see a barn-find P-51D Mustang with an N-number? It's an estate sale. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 21:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is Jesus's favorite beer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 04:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 04:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People smoked tobacco for centuries.  Google it.  I think his comparison is quite valid.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 04:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree.  Coffee.  Just like cigarettes it is a HUGE industry that has completely addicted almost everyone.  People LOVE coffee just like they used to love cigarettes.  It is largely unregulated and the companies that make the product mess with the concentration of the addicting substance.  Starbucks is successful because their coffee has more stimulant in it.  Everyone thinks they can't function without coffee, but do coffee drinkers accomplish more than non-coffee drinkers?  Doubtful.  The final comparison, most of the studies being done on coffee consumption are funded by the coffee industry, just like the initial smoking studies.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 05:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ended up hanging out for an evening with Emmit Smith, just he and I.  I had never met him previously and we have no mutual friends.  Here is the story.  I was in Santa Monica, CA.  My wife was there on business and I was sorta free-loading.  She had a dinner, so I walked to a local steakhouse, alone.  There was a 30 minute wait.  5 minutes into the wait, Emmit Smith walked in, also alone. We were standing next to each other in a crowded restaurant and I could tell he was uncomfortable.  After about a minute or so he asked if I was staying at the hotel I was staying.  Emmit Smith didn't seem like the stalker type, so I admitted that I was.  He was too and he mentioned he saw me give some woman 25 cents for a parking meter outside the hotel.  

We got to chatting, just small talk in a crowded spot.  He had his back to everyone else, but it didn't work.  A crowd of fans were sorta starting to notice him and ask for pictures and that sort of thing.  Well, my table got called and I didn't want to leave him there alone and defenseless, so I asked if he wanted to have dinner with me.  He said yes, really quickly as in "dude, save me from waiting here for 20 minutes and doing an impromptu autograph session.  (I'm a dude by the way, 45 years old).  Anyway, I had dinner with Emmit Smith.  I picked up the tab but he ordered two desserts to go, one for my wife, one for his.  Then we both walked together back to the hotel we were staying in. He's a really nice guy. We are now Facebook friends although I don't think he is on there much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 03:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I run a company that sells sex toys. Does that cover all three? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 06:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife and I went to a white elephant exchange this year. We brought our matching set of "painting with a twist" paintings.  If you haven't heard of "painting with a twist" it is one of these places you go to drink wine and make painting with a few friends.  But your painting isn't a painting of a thing, it is a painting of another painting taught in a step-by-step fashion by a shrill old woman.  So, this holiday season someone had to go home with two similar paintings of a cart full of pumpkins.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here is a Kickstarter for a new bulletproof hat. Would you wear it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 23:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 06:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a tip for you. With my project I jumped the gun a bit and learned a lesson.  

I started alerting the press and friends as I finished putting together my video, writeup, rewards, etc. I even had a few inquiries back and was ready to go. Then I realized that Kickstarter wants to give the project one last approval. That process took 5 days and although during the 5 days the project pitch was improved with their help, I lost a bit of momentum with my press contacts. People of the press do not like to wait. 

So, my advice is to wait until you can launch the project before getting everyone excited. My project is published here in case you are curious. https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/CalmTom/the-bulletsafe-bulletproof-baseball-cap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 05:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kickstarter is the larger of the two.  The top fundraisers on Kickstarter have raised approximately 10 times what the top fundraisers on IndieGogo have.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-06 06:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I run a website that sells condoms in total privacy.  We studied the buyers and found that females like to buy their larger condoms online while men like to buy their smaller condoms online.  I guess that not only are men embarrassed to buy small condoms in person, but women are embarrassed to buy large condoms in person.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The proper order to take off your clothes in front of the opposite gender. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 17:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My series of videos compare how bulletproof different objects are. Episode 1 - Plywood vs. bulletproof vest. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 16:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 16:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I carry a Glock 23.  I'm not sure why people prefer 9mm to .40.  Personally I prefer .40.  My CPL instructor suggested long ago that you carry the largest caliber weapon that you can shoot accurately and I couldn't shoot a .45 accurately.  I chose Glock because I usually operate in a dirty, filthy environment and the professionals I spoke with suggested that Glock makes the most robust weapon for these conditions.  I've never looked back on my decision. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> .50 Desert Eagle vs. $299 BulletSafe Bulletproof Vest - Video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 23:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 01:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an alligator, and the alligator is hungry, so it wants to eat the side that is larger.  So  AB  (A is greater than B because the alligator is eating A).  CD  (C is less than D because that silly alligator is now eating D).  I hope that helps.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At my job I help people pick out bachelorette party supplies through online chat. I'm a guy. Here is the best conversation in a while. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 21:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-09 05:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to run a subscription service and Paypal was really easy to use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm exhibiting at the 2014 SHOT Show. I've never been to it and could use advice. Thanks! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-09 05:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-09 05:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop by and say hello.  I'm with BulletSafe bulletproof vests, booth number 3948.  My name is Tom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
