<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2621</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to the Punch House. Best bar in Chicago for the price. It's in the basement of Talia Hall, get some tickets to see a band while you're there. Usually around 30 bucks for a show and it's a nice place. 

The Punch house will get you drunk...it's good at that  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would t be worried but get the testing anyways. And I love you too lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happened to an ex, we went to the hospital together. Seems he was just allergic to my spunk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They make my tummy get into knots :)

I love em  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't cheating, but you two really need to sit down and talk out your ground rules. Don't let something that bothers you slide because you're afraid it'll ruin the relationship, if you do the. The thing will come back and ruin it for sure. 

Communication is the most important thing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was with an Irish guy from Chicago named Danny for a while. He ended up ghosting me so don't take my advice lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do enjoy the attention I get from it. 
I looked bad for a long time and I worked hard to look the way I do now. There is still a lot of work I have to do to get myself where I want to be, but it's nice too see people's reactions when they see where I started from. 

I hope you get where you want to be in life, sorry from my snarky response earlier.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of it has to deal with attitude...I'd start there if I were you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope that's a good thing lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks xD 

My eyes are my favorite feature  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are both me lol

Here are some more  http://i.imgur.com/BR5CJp7.jpg http://i.imgur.com/GIcH26o.jpg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably, though in your shoes I'd be curious if the nudes they send out are anything like the real thing lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but an ugly guy with a good haircut and that's fit is better than an ugly guy without a good hair cut and that isn't fit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a report option on the app, but it's really hard to keep them from coming back...congratulations though on being attractive enough to be the victim of catfishing 

Edit: just checked, apparently the report option isn't where I thought it was  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you look like lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plane tickets are cheaper than you think. Go surprise him with a visit every so often. It'll do you both a world of good...when I say surprise him I mean with like a day or twos notice lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My older brother made a joke once but that was it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're cute but in need of a haircut lol

Go to a hair stylist and say "I'm gay and have bad hair, fir the love of god help" they will set you up. Don't forget to ask then to teach you how to style it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I get this. I'm going through it now and let me tell you that having sex with a bunch of random people is only an ok coping mechanism...best one I've found so far

Though you might just want to get a new bf. That's what I'm trying for right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something like this happened to me. 

I went on Facebook and tagged my family and said "someone got ahold of my private (aka sexy) videos. They are threatening to show it to family...I don't think you'd be interested so this is just a fair warning...if you are interested then we have bigger issues than this lol Sorry for the inconvenience, I vote we pretend it didn't happen and talk about this never." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You will be groped by EVERYONE on the dance floor. 

If you look masc you won't have to buy drinks. 

Just relax and flirt, if you catch someone checking you out invite them to sit and join your group.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :) 

It was a lot of work  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I changed my hair, grew a beard and got into shape. Here is a before and after  http://i.imgur.com/MmA4ox3.jpg http://i.imgur.com/vDvl0tz.jpg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad it's all working out for you :))) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks :) 

I'm sure you will, you're starting out much better than I did ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm bi and an ex would beg me to get a girl to sleep with him whenever we were drunk. I did it one night. He cried into one of my best friends vaginas... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...I have a really nice voice. I can't help it...but it only happens on recordings  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cheapest Walmart pomade. After a shower with your hair mostly dry put about a dunes worth of pomade on your hand and rub that into your fingers then all your hair. Put the bangs down with the comb then comb straight up and back from the forehead. 


Ps here are pics of me before I knew how to style myself and some from after.  http://i.imgur.com/yKyH8XM.jpg http://i.imgur.com/ZKkIIOx.jpg http://i.imgur.com/C4QIL06.jpg http://i.imgur.com/LfGMNIa.jpg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grow your beard out a bit and trim it up like mine. Trust me it will look way better and help frame your face. Keep it at a guard length two. Put a bit of product in your hair and move it up. I know you feel like you should be covering the forehead more to hide the balding but we can tell that's what your doing, so instead of hiding it use it as part of the look. You want to create volume with your hair now. Try pomade and if that doesn't work then moose. 
 http://i.imgur.com/hHr2ZXE.jpg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 16:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look like someone I'd come up to and say "are you into guys because you're super cute and I'm hoping to get to know you" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 16:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're really cute ;) 

Thanks for introducing the sub to me :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you certainly noticed lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guy I've been seeing posted something that is probably supposed to be sweet and about me but I'm overthinking it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It did </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. She isn't religious, comes from a somewhat conservative family but never really shows it. She is college educated and has 3 sons/ 3 daughters. Two of my sisters came out as bi a few years ago and she was fine with it...not so much with me lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 08:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom had no idea and my coming out didn't go very well, but at the end of the day she is still my mother and I love her. If you are having a really though time then send her a text saying "I'm gay" send it to her while you're near by so you two can talk about it if you want  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm freaking out over something that's probably nothing, please cheer me up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 08:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 19:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to run my body against the bath tub every night during my baths since I was 4 or maybe even earlier. I don't remember my first time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 04:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm out by Chicago send me a pic lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 05:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a switch (leaning dom) the most important thing is moaning. Work on your moan and make sure it's sexy, the more innocent the better ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 04:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That happens sometimes, some of my exes were like that  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell him you had an allergic reaction to a new scented soap so you'd rather not do anything sexual right now...lying shouldn't be relied on in every scenario but this is a good example of a time where it's very useful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 20:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn straight  http://i.imgur.com/v5Z8ods.jpg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 16:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It totally is worth it, I go with a group every Sunday when it's warmer. Message me if you wanna join us  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 16:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Confuse part yes

Excite part...definitely ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 15:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 15:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My god that sounds hilarious, I'd invite you out every time lol

You have to leave Chicago a bit to find the good ones. If you take the south shore you'll find amazing courses. The best ones are out by south bend...there are like four off the top of my head out there  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 15:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah let's do it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 15:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol yeah that's not one of my languages  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 08:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much :)

It's super exciting that your novel is getting published xD  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 08:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm out by Chicago too I agree it was warm lol

I spent the day disk golfing :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 08:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happily will lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 08:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you use oils water or acrylic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 08:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 03:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sound like a blast xD  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 02:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well now I want to help you with more off that list ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 00:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever around Chicago I'll take you to dinner ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 00:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the feeling I'm 6'4" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 00:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can help with one of those lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 00:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit...you single? Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
