<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3297</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Say my name."

"Cooking Papa."

"You're gosh dang right." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, as long as you're friend is okay with you playing it, I'd recommend the game.

The story stands on its own and does provide context for the characters and conflicts in the world (even more so if you're into reading the character bios and books of the world). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I am in big trouble, mmm-hmmm." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Throw it." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More like flooding </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 06:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This is part of the ongoing plot of this Marvel universe; it's not over.

Why in the world would they dedicate so much time into teasing this element and NOT have it be important in the Jessica Jones story? It makes no sense and it brings so much attention to itself. And merely teasing it for another property in the future without having any relevance in the current story you're telling is outright lazy. Even with Madame Gao in Daredevil served a purpose within THOSE seasons of the story. Off-handed references are one thing, but making HUGE plot points about characters that are in no way ever related again to the rest of the season or storyline despite the narrative investing huge chunks of time to these elements is just so haphazardly written.

 Sort of covered, sort of set up for the next season to discuss

No. That's not a good excuse. And I don't see how it's "sort of covered", especially since her and Tricia BLAZE right past it into the jarring superhero costume stage. Saying "they can answer it later" is absolute poor writing, especially when her powers are such a centerpoint of the story (including her and Kilgrave's relationship to one another with their powers) and are so ill defined. 

 I believe the assumption is the her immune system fought him off

Why then? Is Kilgrave's power bacteria based? Why did she become free of it after killing Luke's wife? Is it emotional based? Psychological? Did she have to be in the right head space to "heal" herself? Do you see what I mean? And just saying "oh, it's superhero stuff, just role with it" doesn't work when the showmakers want me to take the story seriously. If this was something like The Flash that prides itself on producing the fantastical and weirder side of speculative fiction live-action superhero shows, then being broad concerning the power settings is one thing, but to take a story that features a recovering support group who committed terrible actions, horrific scenes of gore, discussions of rape and abuse, kidnapping, murder, violence, harsh language, ABORTION (which they mishandled as poorly as a show could by making the aborted fetus a POWER-UP FOR THE SUPERVILLAIN), and other adult elements, and then say "yeah, well, we kinda just have the powers work however we need them to in a scene" is so removed of substance it collapses in on itself. They wanted a serious tone with serious subject matter? Fine by me. But they have to stick with their own parameters. 

 A vast majority of your problems with this show seem to be that season 2 hasn't come out yet.

You can't use that as an excuse because neither one of us knows what's in the next season. We can only judge what was presented to us in the first season, and, in my opinion, it's an incredibly huge mixed bag of quality, erring on the side of negative attributes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 03:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is this rated T? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 02:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The original run of Arrested Development is a MASTERPIECE of comedy

If you're looking for a great show LIKE the comedy of Arrested Development, I'd recommend checking out "Smart Guys" (it's an online series). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 02:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I respect your opinion, but while the season was fine for any other comedy show, it was (in my opinion) incredibly disappointing as the new season for Arrested Development. It doesn't help that they removed the best part of the show to accommodate schedule issues - the family dynamic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 02:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How the Hell did she get that information? Why is it relevant to her? Why was she even interested in keeping it with the info about Kilgrave? If we're talking about the USB's connection across shows, how the Hell does it go from having plot relevant data to Kilgrave to having plot relevant data to Luke? We're Luke and Kilgrave connected BEFORE Reva's death? How did she even discover the drive? How did Kilgrave discover she knew about it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The whole subplot with Luke's wife and the flash drive which has no relevance in the JJ show, how in the world Jessica's bizarre Kilgrave trap would be admissible in court, how she could prove he did it AND that it couldn't be anyone else wth that power, how Jessica even got her powers, why Kilgrave's powers don't affect her anymore yet affect others who have been around him longer, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did Kilgrave want her to do that and get the flash drive? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but everything in a season should be relevant to that particular story being told, like Madame Gao's involvement in Daredevil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not looking for perfect science (which is a straw man argument), I'm looking for consistent plot which doesn't leave dumptruck sized plot holes big enough to drive through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that's not point. My argument is why in the world they'd focus such a huge chunk of Jessica Jones on Luke's wife's flash drive and never address it until the Luke Cage series </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How? Weren't his parents exposed to his control for FAR longer? Why suddenly after killing Luke's wife? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But why have it in Jessica Jones if it's not going to be apart of the plot? With Madame Gao in Daredevil, she at least had her purpose in THAT show's narrative of being one of Fisk's associates trying to help take over Hell's Kitchen.

What was the purpose of the flash drive? What's the purpose of introducing that? It has no pay off! Especially since it's tied to Kilgrave, Jessica, AND Luke and none of them seem talk about it ever again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I don't think you understand. In the flashbacks of the show and the entire basis of their original relationship, Kilgrave is literally controlling Jessica and then the reasons why she suddenly is able to break free from that are never addressed, ever. It's bad storytelling, it's a lazy narrative thread that is never solved, and frankly, if they really wanted to have the "controlling Jessica through threats of manipulation, while he literally controlled everyone else" type of storyline, they needed to do that with the before and after portions of the story.

This is just confusing and unnecessarily so. That is just poor writing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, I did not like those first two seasons of breaking bad, not to mention the characters of Walt Junior and Marie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it wasn't  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Charlie Cox is brilliant as Matt Murdock. He has such a layered performance, and that shows so expertly written. The only thing I wish is that they should've stuck with the original reason why stick left from the contacts, rather than being emotionally attached to Matt as it would've made for a much more harsher departure from Matt's life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the side stories were terrible. Between the actor who played nuke becoming a progressively worse actor as a series one on, to that unbearable kilgrave support group, subplots like what Luke's wife had on the flash drive or why Jessica was able to resist the mind control being totally swept under the rug and unanswered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except, he was controlling her Directly. She just somehow manages to magically not be affected anymore because Plot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally thought that the storyline could've been so much more interesting if it actually dealt in the concept of free will, choice, and acceptance, but really screwed up the landing. And the Jigsaw trap she had for Kilgrave? Oh, my god that was terrible. How would any of that be admissible in court? Or better yet, even if she proves kill grave has that power, how can she prove beyond a shadow of the doubt that he's the only one with that power?

The show is just so incredibly off kilter in execution in writing, that it's absolutely painful. They even tip toe past really interesting ideas concerning Jessica actually accepting Kilgrave's relationship to and extent. I don't even get me started on how Jessica basically used Hope as a surrogate for her own vengeance, let other people die, and only decide to kill when it was beneficial for her. And yet, the show never goes into any of those interesting areas. It's infuriating </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, stop. I liked the show and Jones in the role. It wasn't a great series but it was fine, especially the drunken master fight.

If anything, I really didn't like Jessica Jones out of all the Netflix marvel TV series. The first couple of episodes established a great crime noir feeling, but then it went off the deep end. I cannot fathom why in the world the show would treat abortion with such lack of care for understanding for either side of the debate and make it just a power up for the villain. The acting gets screwy, Jessica's motivations make absolutely no sense towards the end of the series, plot lines like why Luke's wife had that flash drive or what was on it or how Jessica was even able to brake away from Kilgrave are never explained, and so many of the side characters, like that annoying "Kilgrave support group" that goes nowhere, drag the show down to an absolute screeching halt. I don't know why iron fist get so much crap, admittedly it does need some criticism and places, and yet Jessica Jones gets off Scott free </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know there was this much poetry in the whole galaxy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just a simple man trying to spin my way across the galaxy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they might even have a Spiderman cameo in there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only if you say "no homo" when you cuddle afterwards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Out", am I?!?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A BIG GRAY BUSHY BEARD! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but the show at the start of the second season seemed to emphasize his love of her before that and it sort of comes out of nowhere </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For real world news, the coverage of 9/11 and the news that followed he next few days of people not knowing what the Hell was going on.

For entertainment, I would have to say "Pierrot Le Fou" in Cowboy Bebop.

"Hello, gentlemen. I have come to take your lives." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHAT'S YOUR OFFER?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 13:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  YouTube itself says viewer counts are unreliable and variable.

Much like the reporting from WSJ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 13:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  a movie or television production with characteristics (as conflict ) of a serious play; broadly :  a play, movie, or television production with a serious tone or subject a police drama

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I really think Jar Jar gets a bad rap. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 06:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 00:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not for Samurai Jack fans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 00:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about "Daddy's Home 2: It's Actually The Sequel to "The Other Guys""? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 00:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely 2 and 3. I personally loved Mass Effect 1, as well, but the combat isn't as immediately engaging as ME2 and ME3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an argument as to what KIND of show it is. Some see it as a mini-series, others as a one-season show, others as a season-long book adaptation, etc.

I don't think anyone is decrying it's quality (to me, it's one of the greatest pieces of entertainment/storytelling/what-have-you ever made), it's just how to classify it being the main problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, I got to find out where to see the series.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ONLY problem I really had with that season was why Wilson had suddenly become head over heels in love with Shado.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Daredevil. Hands down. An excellent superhero show that delves into the nature of crime, justice, vengeance, death, faith, and the systems that uphold society.

Stranger Things is also great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drama: LOST, Daredevil, Band of Brothers (I consider it a 'show'), or The West Wing. 

Comedy: Original Run (Seasons 1-3) of Arrested Development, Smart Guys, or the Original Run (Seasons 1-3) of Family Guy.

Animation Cheat: Trigun, or Cowboy Bebop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 06:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They couldn't even give Samurai Jack fans the 11-11:30 slot?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 06:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As somebody who's a bigger Samurai Jack fan than a bigger April Fools or Rick and Morty fan, I'm not as thrilled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 05:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the only problem is that they took away Samurai Jack's slot tonight. That sucks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 05:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else absolutely pissed that they decided to have an entire night of Rick and Morty's new episode, and Samurai Jack gets pushed back an entire week?

Seriously! They couldn't let Jack have the 11-11:30 timeslot when it's ADVERTISED for that timeslot? That's messed up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 05:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it ain't. I don't mind that they premiere the episode, but instead of getting a SINGLE new episode of Samurai Jack, we have to watch Rick and Morty all god damn night. WHY CAN'T THEY JUST LET THE 11-11:30 SLOT FOR JACK?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 00:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The time period is supposed to be an ambiguous mish-mash of different times. They talk about technology that wasn't back in the 60s.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 00:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's all so damn good, that no matter who picks what episode, it's going to be correct.

For myself, I'm going with the first one I watched that got me hooked - Pierot Le Fou. An excellent action/horror hybrid that has some of the most tense fight scenes I've ever seen in a show.

"Hello....boy...." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 15:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOOK AT HIS TUFTED EARS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 07:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally? I don't think so. Especially since silent protagonists have such limited utilization in narratives. They'll either have to really re-tool Gordon Freedman for a great narrative, or it's going to be disappointing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 01:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love Ninja Theory's work. Looking forward to the game

Post-edit: I guess it's not good to have a positive opinion on a developer on Reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 01:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Press X = Yes!

 Press O = Yes, but slightly dickishly

 Press B = Yes, politely

 Press A = ~~Looks like no, but is still yes~~ Sarcastic yes

FTFY 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 23:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, our thing is crippling guilt over everything we do and don't do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have a lot of fun shows and things like Riverdale and Crazy Ex Girlfriend actually surprised me with their quality. I don't think they're the best channel on right now, but they have solid lineup of shows </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd probably go with Netflix if we can consider that a channel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conker's Bad Fur Day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think public school teachers have taken over that role. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No luck catching those swans then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When I saw the design of the Mud people paying tribute to Aku, I immediately thought of this... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't arguments for Whedon. He was just tired doing enormous Avengers films. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Witcher 3: Wild Hunt (with all DLC)

Life is Strange

TellTale Games (Tales from the Borderlands, The Walking Dead Season 1, The Wolf Among Us)

Wolfenstein: The New Order

DmC: Devil May Cry

The Mass Effect trilogy 

Assassin's Creed IV: Black Flag

The BioShock Collection </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'd prefer more of a fast paced crazy stylish game. Maybe a platinum game with Samurai Jack presentation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's quite a cheeky comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're drift compatible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know why you're being down voted since your comment does contribute to the conversation, even if I don't fully agree with it. Not to mention WB is notorious for messing with their DC films during the production </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing that in theaters is going to be my awakening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Halo 4 is my favorite, but I think all of the first person shooter Halo games range from very good to outstanding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK. I liked the show, but I really enjoyed the hell out of the movie and how over-the-top it was while also having such and endear characters and great humor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She doesn't even go here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The A-Team </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, if that's what you feel. I think some people get too hung up on classifying genres and types of stories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's incredible! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's my only complain too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree on that. I personally loved Halo 4 and really enjoyed Halo 5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here are my suggestions:

* Clone High, Moonbeam City, American Dad!, Harvey Birdman: Attorney at Law, Red vs Blue: The Blood Gulch Chronicles (aka "Red Vs Blue: Seasons 1-5"), Chozen, Frisky Dingo, King of the Hill, Aqua Teen Hunger Force, Metalocalypse, Black Dynamite, Mike Tyson Mysteries.

Right now, Samurai Jack is on Adult Swim if you're craving action/drama with mature sensibilities on violence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Genuine question out of curiosity: why?

I understand that good storytellers don't need to be fully experienced in one particular genre in order to make a good film (Irvin Kershner with Empire Strikes Back), but Sorkin hasn't even tackled fantasy or science fiction before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  hundreds of my brother
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some people think the weapons breaking system works, while others find it to be a pain in the neck. Just bringing it up and talking about it doesn't negate your perspective on the system </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the love of God, stop spamming the Gaming section of Reddit with the same message, please! I like the idea of a dedicated place for Halo 3 custom games, but these constant messages on this subreddit have become an annoyance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pitch Black and Predators are great films in that sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Toot toot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But the entire point of the argument stems from Peter's direct confrontation with the smugglers, and the escalation therein, risking hundreds, if not thousands of lives of innocents.

How is he supposed to know that would have led to the escalation? Not to mention that Peter's M.O. is "with great power, there must also come great responsibility". If Peter sees something wrong and he has the power to right that wrong, he has the obligation to do so, regardless of the consequences. It's what Tony had even done in the Iron Man movies, Age of Ultron, and Civil War. 

 And it's a lot more direct than the collateral damage that happens in some of the previous missions. 

I side with Captain America in this case. If you let what you failed to do keep you from action, next time, you might be choked by hesitation, and maybe NO ONE will be saved. 

 Smugglers, by their nature, operate in secret. And if Peter hadn't exposed them, then nobody would have been hurt.

That's a stretch. Exposing them could have caused them to scatter. However, it also seems like Peter handled the smugglers pretty easily, with only the Vulture appearing out from a container to cause devastation. Also, Tony is an enormous hypocrite. He took it upon himself to kill the terrorists from the first Iron Man film instead of relying on the U.S. military to do their job they risk their lives for because, as a character flaw, he thinks he knows better than everyone else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If you think about it, Tony is saying that to precisely because he made that mistake and doesnt want it repeated - its not moral high ground, its experience.

Every time he has tried to control other peoples' behavior, it's backfired in his face. His M.O. is to preach at others about he knows better only to be proven wrong (as a weapons manufacturer in Iron Man, his congressional monolog in Iron Man 2, taunting the Mandarin in Iron Man 3, creating Ultron in Age of Ultron, forcing everyone to accept the Sokovia Accords in Civil War. If I was Peter, I'd be pissed that this son of a bitch was chastising me for risking my life to save other people when that's the purpose of heroes (as the Avengers learned in Age of Ultron).

 Tony is also a rich adult that can actually fix a ton of his messes, unlike some kid in spandex.

Who's naturally stronger than him who could take on Cap in a hand-to-hand fight without Tony's fancy AI helping him, and who was smart enough to manufacture his own webbing. 

Peter's philosophy is "great power, great responsibility." That means correcting a wrong being done, regardless of the consequences if you have the power to change something. 

 spidey is doing heroics in a world with dozens of far more experienced heroes. 

So what? That's what Tony was doing when he decided that instead of relying on the U.S. government to take down the 10 Rings in Iron Man 1, he put it upon himself to do so. Tony's philosophy here (at least what we can see so far) is "do what I say, not what I do." He's a hypocrite and what's worse is that he's placed others in danger by hindering Peter's ability to fight crime.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm the dude playing the dude disguised as another dude!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, you wouldn't download a car </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still don't get how he can take the moral high ground of "you can't just save people and do what you think is right just because you have the power to do so" when he himself literally builds a suit of tank armor and kills terrorists in his first film.

I REALLY hope the explanation is better than what we're given in the trailers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was....kind of disappointing. None of the jokes were really gelling for me. I liked some of the character moments, but I still have a big sticking point with how much they seem to be cramming in Tony into this film, especially since I really can't see how he's giving Peter grief for putting his life in danger for others when THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT HE DOES IN EVERY FILM. I'm not really gelling with Vulture in this movie.

I know these are just small initial impressions, but it's not really helping the fact that I'm not totally onboard for this movie, and I LOVE Spider-man (favorite superhero and one of my favorite fictional characters ever). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay. I do enjoy superhero stories, but I wouldn't consider myself biased towards them as I only like ones that are told well. 

For example how is Iron Fist not terrible? 

I didn't say it was great or even good. For myself, I think it's competent enough not to be bad, but not interesting enough to be good. Although I feel it's a bit mediocre, that doesn't immediately translate to it being considered "bad" (once again, for myself). I'm probably never going to watch the series again, but I'm not mad that I did. It didn't leave me angry like Jessica Jones did after watching it. 

 I get that DD is "fighting for actual justice" but I just think that's kinda lame. I prefer the Punisher's approach.

Okay. I think it's a great take on the superhero storyline, especially with a character who's torn between his vigilante approach, his legitimate job as a lawyer, his suppressed love of violence, and his Catholic teachings. The Punisher is a good character in the show, but his way is anarchy and destruction with wanton killing. The moment where Frank is about to execute a completely innocent man who was framed for being the Blacksmith showcases that his form of a vendetta goes through no process besides his own, so he's even more likely to screw up on a personal level. 

 I don't expect you to agree but that's my take on it at least.

I do respect that point of view, even though I don't personally agree with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOOK AT THIS PHOTOGRAPH! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 08:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Riverdale, Dark Matter, [Smart Guys](http://smartguysshow.vhx.tv/), and Occupied are some under the radar gems, in my opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 08:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arrested Development, Police Squad!, Bob's Burgers, [Smart Guys](http://smartguysshow.vhx.tv/), Spaced, Moonbeam City, Clone High, Archer, Chozen, American Dad!, Family Guy (the original run; seasons 1-3).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 08:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, I consider it a series. Too long for a mini-series, in my eyes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 08:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You can fly?!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 08:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's similar to the way that good sci-fi like Star Trek uses space exploration as a backdrop for more serious issues.

Yeah, those stories CAN be about that, but they can also be fables, mythological tales, avatars for points of view on justice, etc. Kraven's Last Hunt, House of M, The Infinity Gauntlet. All of those stories, and much more, are about telling these myths of heroes simply beyond having domestic issues with a layer of people being able to move things with their mind, or shoot lazers from their eyes. 

As a side-note, I did not like Jessica Jones. It began with promise, but the longer it went on, the more unfocused and unhinged the story became with some really spotty writing and acting (outside of Jessica, Luke, and Kilgrave). 

 (at least once it developed in the 70s-80s past the pulp-fiction dime novels that started it). 

The golden age of comics is, once again, that's more mythological and 'pure' in storytelling and akin to Beowulf and Samson. There are still great stories in there, such as Spider-man's origin story which is one of the most wholly complete and satisfying superhero tales to this date full of character, pathos, and emotional depth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 08:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Anyone who appreciates comics for the true storytelling power of that medium should be blown away by shows like Legion that take full advantage of everything a video medium has to offer.

As someone who is a fan of superhero comic book stories, not everything needs to cohere to a specific look or feel for an adaptation. The show is great and I certainly like it the visuals. I just wish they took more time with the antagonists and supporting characters of the show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 08:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say keep going with it. It's rewarding the more layers you experience and reflect on with each episode.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 08:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Other comic nerds aren't very interested because it's not squarely in the superhero genre, 

I'm a comic book nerd and love it. It's a different interpretation of the material with different sensibilities. It's not what I would think is the best/favorite superhero show on right now (for me, it's Daredevil), but it is a near close-second.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 08:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I don't think Daredevil deserves to be out next to Arrow.

First two seasons of Arrow are pretty damn good, some minor quibbles here and there notwithstanding. Recent years haven't exactly been the most kind to it, but I think it refound some of its lost footing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 08:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I liked the action scenes but the acting is pretty mediocre. 

Okay. I disagree here. Everyone from Charlie Cox, Deborah Ann Woll, Elodie Yung, Vincent D'Onofrio, Elden Hensen, and the rest of the cast are fantastic. 

 DD is just good, not great. Not complete garbage like Iron Fist though.

I think it's superb, in my opinion. Iron fist is....alright. It starts off so incredibly bland but does start ramping up after about 3 or 4 episodes in. Not terrible (that's reserved for something like season 3 of Arrow). 

 I think The Punisher with Jon Bernthal might be cool though. He made DD look like a little pussy.

I think that's the part of season 2 of DD so many people miss out on. DD is fighting for actual justice, not personal vendettas. The courts and systems of balances that keep everything in line without corruption, and it's easy to cut loose and say "forget about the consequences" with Punisher, but it's not that easy. The rooftop argument is a clear indication of how differently these men see the world and their complex counter-points with one another.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 07:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree with this. I would say that Legion is the best FILMED superhero show, but in terms of character depth, narrative, pacing, and antagonists, I'd say that Daredevil is still the #1 show, for myself anyway.

I enjoy the Hell out of Legion as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 06:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay. Outside of that amazing Pilot episode, I wouldn't consider the series worth watching. However, I absolutely respect that point of view you have. It's a well shot show with great gore effects, but I just want to see more character depth and story than either the show or its comic counterpart currently have.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I do because at least they didn't screw up so badly at launch that it went into crafting some of the most hilarious screw-ups I've ever seen from a professional developer: [Mass Effect Andromeda and the magnificent screw-ups](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7KWkao73HuU) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All right boys, let's get some pictures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Why does everyone always laugh when I say that?! They ARE after me lucky charms!!!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Ha ha ha! "King Gay"!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yarp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "There wasn't even an awning or anything." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rush Hour 2


"His name is Lee, goddammit!"

"What's the matter with you?! You don't jump in front of a black man in a buffet line!"

"I'll bitch slap you back to Africa!"

"God DAMN! What happened to Reign?!"

"Lord Jesus! I don't want to die!!!"

"I said "bmmm"."

"She likes me because I'm tall, dark and handsome. And you're third world ugly."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 14:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Come down to the coast, we'll have a few laughs!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
