<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1137</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 08:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, never leave your mask in direct sunlight! That kills them, and also Moist and Warm conditions will kill your masks after a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 08:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont do too much to them, but for example, when i see a mask has cracks from dryings, I rub some coconut oil on the cracks to keep it from cracking even more.

Also Olive Oil is a good way to "refresh" the rubber especially when they are dirty! :)

Infant masks can be difficult to get but they pop up from time to time, pretty sought after. Im not really into them but i know alot of collectors who has them. 

And we are also usually into Civilian masks too, i just purchased a Korean Civilian mask! :D 

I found the M72 Launcher in the attic LOL, they dont seem to be too expensive here in Norway, but im not sure where you can find them elsewhere, since I heard that they are now ilegal to sell in Norway.

The shoes are supposed to go over a soldiers boots, so they are hard to setup without those boots, so i ended up messing it up a litlle bit :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 08:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think i started back in 2013, and the first mask i got was a czechoslovakian M10M! :) My masks are from all over the world, Norway, USA, Canada, Germany, Russia, Korea, UK, Poland, and more countries :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 08:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 23:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We love the History behind these Items, and its an interesting type  of equipment too, its the only thing that can save you from Gas attacks! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 22:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey dude,

There is alot of other Collectors, we have our own facebook group called ''Gas Mask Collectors Community'' wich we share info, etc! :)

Sad part is that the community is flooded by Non-serious collectors who barley care about it at all, so many weird ppl who just have a super small intrest. So there is alot of shit in the group but the few people who actually post serious stuff and collect for real are awsome!

And yes, most of us that collect masks collect other types of gear. We are not just interested in Masks, we also want all the accessories for them! :) 
We also love getting chemical suits too. 

Also fun gathering all the parts of a military kit from, for example The Vietnam war. you collect the whole Uniform of a US soldier and all the correct equipment and you can display it with your mask (The correct mask ofc)! :) 

You'd be suprised to see that there actually is alot of people collecting gas masks, at least i were when i first joined the community :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Gas mask Collection! Around 45 Masks and a ton of extra stuff. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 19:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Army Surplus Stores </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 07:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys im interested in some Army surplus stores. Hopefully one that has Gas masks and stuff like that. I mainly collect gas masks (yeah i know its weird af, fuck off) and i've Been to Mad Mans army surplus and Manhs Surplus. Any other good shops? :) Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 06:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks guys, I've given up hahah, not anything to go to without being 21 :( Just gonna have to survive. I'll get drunk as soon as i get back. Thanks guys!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 18 in Vegas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 04:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone know of a place in Vegas tjay does not check ID? Like a pub or Club whatever. Im from Norway and i drink alot of alcohol and Im so annoyed with the 21 year old rule. Any help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 15:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I will! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 13:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> never </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 21:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'll die </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 19:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks fun! :)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 19:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao im ready for some heat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 14:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats sounds fun, I'll check it out:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 14:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks cool! Thanks! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 12:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds cool, thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What can an 18 year old Norwegian guy do in Las Vegas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 10:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im going to Las Vegas 1-9 January to attend the CES convetion with my Brother and my dad. Im from Norway and i've never been to Las Vegas before. Does anyone have an Idea what would be cool to see and do? Im 18, so i wont be able to drink over in the US. Im open to do anything, so if you know of anything cool beside CES going down in early january please let me know! :) Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 09:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a cute couple of prostitutes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 10:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 09:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! Im sitting at work sipping Tea for the first time in years right now :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 09:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the tip, i Made a plan on what to eat last night and today is the first day of following it! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 17:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, i will start doing this :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
