<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1497</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's only if you actually value Iraqi art. How does it affect you personally, anyway? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. No sympathy, here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shouldn't even be an issue. Good day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 11:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it's been happening for many, many years and I don't really believe it's a concern. I've been driving with cannabis metabolites in my blood for 20 years. Not a single accident. Most of my mates are exactly the same. It's just not that big an issue. I don't think it ever was. 

Alcohol and fatigue are the real killers. Cannabis and other drugs are way behind - although I'm sure the authorities can skew the data enough to make it look otherwise. I tire of this futile and ongoing pipe dream of getting the road toll to zero. It's as good as it's gonna get and people should be happy with that. I don't want more liberties taken from us. Enough is enough. 

And no, enough research has not been done with regard to 'how stoned is too stoned' to drive. Far, far more research is needed. Especially in country where it's extremely difficult to do such research because weed is illegal. MDTs are just a proxy war on drugs. It's absolutely pathetic. They don't need it in most other countries and we do not need it here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 09:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tough question. I mean, she's not dead buuuuut... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 09:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, thanks mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 09:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not many people want to close the door entirely. People only want to open the door for certain types and there is absolutely nothing wrong with that. We should be taking our stocks from people and places that are most like our own. We need to prioritise, not slam the door shut. Immigrants *can* be great - doesn't mean they are by default. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 09:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I've completed all that stuff. And I just finished it. Great game. I think I will play again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 09:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can somehow verify that they were/are 'insanely stoned' then by all means punish them. But merely having cannabis in your system does not indicate any level of impairment. That's why I keep saying make a proper test and not some arbitrary, blanket bullshit. I feel it's a reasonably simple concept, don't you?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 09:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I just did it. Good game. Now, when I start again will it over write my save files (as in, should I save them somewhere else)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Witcher 3] I've just completed (spoiler) - how much longer does this game go on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 08:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just defeated the Wild Hunt and received the special sword from the guy at the old castle. How long does this game continue on for? It's starting to become a bit of a drag, really.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 08:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Until a test to measure this supposed impairment is created, yes. Which bit do you not understand? We have a test for alcohol with regard to driving and impairment. It's very well researched. It actually indicates the level of impairment. It's used the World over. 

What we have with cannabis is, "we found any amount of it (from a little to a lot) - you can't drive", which is clearly bullshit. Measure or deduce the level of impairment or do not test at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 08:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The dole is an entitlement. You do not work for entitlements.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 08:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can't determine that without a proper test, yes. A proper test is perfectly possible to devise - spend the money and do the research. And until you do you, don't test anyone. We have exemplary road statistics. This beat up over people have weed in their system is a joke. You are allowed to drive with a moderate amount of alcohol in your system. I see absolutely no different with cannabis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 07:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, what they are saying is they want us to actively flout any and all new laws regarding this in any way we can? I'm on board. No worries. This will be about as effective as stopping me trying to visit the pirate bay. Good luck, cunts! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 07:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 07:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Abandon the tests. We didn't need them before and we don't need them now, if they cannot be accurate. We have one of the absolute best safety records for driving in the developed world. Drug testing is nonsense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 07:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have personally been suspended for over 1.5 months from work because yes, cannabis can be detectable in urine for that long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 07:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 06:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be interested to try that, just to see how shit it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 06:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WTF does that mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 06:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I've completely fucked up my question. Let me try again:

Question: A researcher gets two groups of people. He measures their LDL levels at the start of the study. He then assigns one group to eat oatmeal. The rest continue with their normal habits. 

After some time the levels of LDL in both groups are measured again. 500 people are in each group. The change in LDL for the two groups is given as 8 and 12 'units'. 

So, we have two groups on different diets and their LDL is measured at two points in time. I'm thinking the data is paired - each person is tested twice. 

The data is numerical but I think it's not continuous because the values are given in whole numbers. But I'm not sure if that matters. 

I think you might be right with the paired t-test? Would you mind just reading over it again?The question is very simple - almost too simple. I'm nervous about this. 

Thanks for helping, by the way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you can do that. Everyone should be doing that. They need to behave or be suppressed. Fuck their parallel societies. Fuck their treatment of women and non muslims. Fuck the violence that comes with them, wherever they go.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And where does it officially encourage that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Answer the question. When did Le Pen encourage violence against them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they'd fucking behave maybe it would have been different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, sure. It's whatever I don't personally like. My country's government makes a rule/decision I don't like - fascist! McDonalds takes my favourite item off the menu - fascist! Someone said they don't like the colour of my car - fascist! Some people don't like cats - fascist! Everything I don't like/agree with must be fascist. Don't you get it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got any links? I didn't see anything in /r/sydney just now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, I'm still working on the suspension. Got a set of camber plates to install. Clutch is next. Looking at that diagram, I'm wondering where exactly that spring goes - one end looks like it goes through the hole in the lever itself but were doe the other end go? Should I be looking at this from inside or outside the car? It's hard to tell.

Thanks for your help, by the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you rollerblade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For public toilets that had a chain to pull for flushing:

If you want a cool surprise, pull the chain before you rise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, around the time Jesus played fullback for Jerusalem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was that when you could actually punch information into a computer or a woman? Can't do that anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about police officers not being retarded and actually saying no, we will not arrest this person because our discretion allows us to make a reasonable judgement? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 15:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does that article even make sense?

"It was the WikiLeaks data dump that thrusted the public into bouts of paranoia.

Known as Vault 7, thousands of documents from the CIA detailed covert programs in which devices like smart TV's and smartphones could spy on people.

Now CBS News is reporting that a manhunt for the leaker is underway. The CIA and FBI are joining forces to investigate what has become one of the worst security breaches since Edward Snowden."

Absolutely abysmal writing.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 15:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should put the first pic back at the end, to tie it all in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 15:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never cares for their smokes much but the RYO tobacco is pretty good. Reasonably heavy smoke with good nicotine levels, I reckon. Sixty bucks for 50 g, FFS. No idea how much a pack of 25s cost. I shudder to think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 15:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should do time trials! Like qualify all day for the whole weekend or something. You could really see the better drivers shine, I feel. I guess I can dream... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 12:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't it true for a long time that no Williams car had ever been able to get around Fairmont hairpin without deliberately using oversteer and flicking it around? I remember hearing something like that somewhere. Could be all of them. I know I saw something like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 12:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's plenty. They've had GT3 races there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 11:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started a fire in a tree like that (but about four times bigger) while my parents were out. Had a mate over and we decided to have some fun. 

But mum and dad came home early and we thought we'd get in the shit. So I told him to throw a big bucket of water into the hole. The steam explosion knocked him clean off his feet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 11:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once it's on the net, it's *mine*. All you are doing is making it annoying for the average person to make it a wallpaper or something. If others are going to 'steal' it and supposedly make money, they will do that anyway. You should be happy people actually want to save it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 11:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have given them untold amounts of money, military equipment and training to use it over the years. No one can reasonably explain why, apart from trotting out this "we don't want to piss them off" Bullshit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 11:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't care. Stop muslims emigrating to Western nations is what I'm saying. International affairs have to go on, regardless. Start somewhere and work upwards.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 11:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta start somewhere. The sooner, the better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 11:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. That is not fair. They need to do the research and invest in developing proper testing if they want to take peoples' licences away. Nothing less will suffice. It's no better than workplace testing. Just because I get on it at the weekend does not mean I am unfit to work or drive on Monday and I will not hear different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 11:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 11:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I just came back from Toussaint and discovered an absolute fuckload of stuff I stashed in Novigrad and Skellige. It's proving quite difficult to get rid of in a reasonable time frame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 10:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it's stopping fuckheads who *aren't* on drugs from driving. Do they test for a hangover (acetaldehyde, acetone and so on in your blood) from consuming alcohol? No. Yet you could be shattered and still legally drive. Cannabis tests that are currently used provide absolutely no indication of impairment, as the time frame surrounding such a drug's influence is so wildly variable. And how many medications do you want to test for? There are thousands. Fuck that shit. 

So yes, they are using their new drug testing powers as a proxy war on drugs that they cannot hope to win. Innocent people are getting caught doing nothing wrong. It's a joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 10:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And there you go. You said it yourself. There is no reasonable test to see if you are affected by cannabis. So don't test for it if you can't determine impairment. Just like I said, they are using it to fight their little drug war in the pettiest way possible. No, just because I smoked a few bongs three days ago, it does not mean I am under the influence, whether you can detect it at ridiculously low levels or you can't. The whole situation is ridiculous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 10:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should be racing F1 at Macau. That would be fucking insane. Like this:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-GLXAne-c64 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 09:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Programs that cost two months' wages? Fuck that - I'd be pirating it, too. Why should they pay that much? It's highway robbery and those companies deserve to be pirated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [PC][Witcher3] I keep waiting 5 days for the merchants to get more money and every single time I do it, they have less than the previous time. Will this continue? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 09:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's fucking annoying. Why have loot if you can't sell it? On the merchants I have tried this out on, waiting five days does indeed let them re-stock and get more money. But the more you do it, the less they have, each time. Is this the same for anyone else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 09:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With cannabis completely illegal, you have not a leg to stand on with these bullshit tests. Once cunts can have it legally, they might see their way to employing tests that are actually meaningful. At the moment, it's just a war on drugs by proxy. And it needs to fucking stop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 08:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 08:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welfare and the chance to make a new place just like their old place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 08:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well stop Hezbollah firing, fucknuckle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 08:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wat? I couldn't get past the second paragraph of that pretentious garbage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 07:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same with sambuca and ouzo. Foul shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 07:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck that. They can stay and rebuild their own shit. And keep their abortion of a religion to themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 07:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you get a program that prevents them doing what they do? I fucking hate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 07:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why Trump was trying to exclude them. But everyone got all pissy for some reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 07:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And this isn't a joke. They are responsible for an appalling number of birth defects in Britain, even though their number are low:

http://www.bbc.com/news/uk-england-leeds-23183102

http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/health/news/7957808/700-children-born-with-genetic-disabilities-due-to-cousin-marriages-every-year.html

http://www.express.co.uk/news/uk/591577/British-Pakistanis-13-times-more-disabled-children

http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-1394119/Its-time-confront-taboo-First-cousin-marriages-Muslim-communities-putting-hundreds-children-risk.html

That's only a cursory search. You can read all about it when you have time. Fucking disgusting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 07:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that is why people who revere that piece of shit should stay the fuck out of Western society. Trump tried and people pissed and moaned for ages. More leaders need to exclude these people. Starting now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 07:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And why islam and Western society should never be mixed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 07:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another islamic triumph!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 07:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me guess - you'll have to be half dead before you can get it. And then jump through 500 hoops, on top of that. I really hope it fucks up the drug driving tests, though. That shit needs to stop immediately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 07:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't understand why we give them aid, equipment and training. Or anything. They have repeatedly spat in our face, while we have been very good to them. They should be cut loose. They can go scab off someone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do programmers insist on making it so you can't 'get out of' an active window? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 07:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have seen this many times. You open a program/window to do something and once window is active, you can't get out if it until either whatever is being done is finished or you close the active window? You just get that stupid sound and the border if the active window flashes. I'm not sure how else to describe it.

Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 07:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can mix in various quantities of other hydrocarbons to change the consistency. Various types of oil, grease, kerosene, diesel, etc. Some combos make it much firmer and less sticky and other make it like melted mozzarella. I had a lot of fun with that as a kid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got a letter, here in Australia. It was 10 years ago. I sent it straight back to them with some smartarse comment daring them to do something. Nothing happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet you've had a lot of torpedoes in your tube. That sickly look isn't scurvy, it's AIDS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone recommend me a decent, free file shredder for Windows? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wanna scrub some stuff off a portable HDD I borrowed, before I give it back. Lots of results come up but I'm not sure what's Dodgy Brothers shit and what isn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds hard. I play on easy, coz I'm shit. I just like to look at the graphics in games, mainly. Sounds interesting. Might look into that. Can't see myself making it any harder, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's AMK? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got to the end of that and just couldn't figure out what to do. Gave up. Maybe I'll have to revisit it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Castlevania IV for SNES had a fucking ball-tearer of a soundtrack, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oops, yeah. I'm not gonna challenge the laws of thermodynamics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now you're gonna go buy some and eat it all within a few hours. Because you can't help yourself, like me. Enjoy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't know? Man, you've been missing out. It's a yellowish powder that comes in a can. It always near the Milo. And it tastes fucking great. You end up with something far better than whatever Oak are selling. But it's nine or ten bucks a can, which is outrageous. Hence my question.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Takes too long and I haven't got any good cards because I haven't played it from the start. Maybe next time I play, I'll give it a proper go. This is my first play through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, thank you very much, indeed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 17:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This reminds me of the nonsense people carry on with when they say Indonesia is a big, scary rival. They couldn't do fuck all to us. Absolutely nothing. They could have the biggest standing army in the World and lots of the best jets - and none of them will ever reach our shores. They're a joke, just like NK. Plain and simple. We should continue laughing in their faces. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Submission of the woman. If she let's him do that, she'll pretty much do anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries. Is that per smoke or for the whole night? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this another pic where you 'can't' download the full resolution? Sigh. Right click -- View page info -- media -- save the pic you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same. We had to take turns with those things. Only one Fruit Loops and one Coco Pops in each pack. It was always at Grandma's house or one of our aunties places. We weren't getting that shit at home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but the increase in price over the last 5-10 years is like the fucking housing market in Sydney. Completely unsustainable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a bad idea. But I'm not sure how to do it. Do you have any info on that? I shall be in your debt, if you do. I really don't want to pull the whole hydraulic system apart, apart right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're bigger than I imagined. Surely, that cannot be comfortable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the ratio of menthol to non-menthol smokers? I always wondered that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They still sell the 1 L ones at my Coles. And they're usually on special. Hard not to sit there and drink the whole thing but I don't wanna end up a fat cunt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. Heat always, always flows from cold to hot. To think of it in any other way would be like saying you can make a light 'shine' dark on other things. It just won't work that way. 'Cold' is the absence of heat, just like dark is the absence of light. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Box jellyfish has 64 anuses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, your shoes remain on your feet forever? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't drink much of them but I love me a Coke in a glass bottle. I'll buy it on special but fuck paying those cunts the full price.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the fuck is Malted Milk so expensive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fucking love that shit and it's nine bucks a can or some shit. WTF? The price has skyrocketed so much I'm beginning to consider hoarding it and dealing it at street level. Jesus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same. No Coco Pops. No Fruit Loops. Severely deprived. Considered contacting welfare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't get me started on Milo Bars. Those fucking CUNTS changed them from being a full-on solid bar of Milo, coated in a thin layer of chocolate to whatever the fuck they are now. WTF? What a travesty. Why would they do that? Fucking marketing cunts need to find a new job or some shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swear the bottles taste better. But the cunts still want $5 for a four pack - on special. WTF? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'll charge ya, though. Measly cunts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My best find ever was a big can of Milo that had been in Grandma's cupboard for years. Pretty much was there for us kids, when we came to visit.

I found this can that must have had a slight air leak. The Milo had turned to a hard sort of mud. The adults tried to turn me away from it, but I knew I had struck gold. I munched on that perfect, perfect shit until I was sick. Then I went back for more.

A glorious day in the life of an Aussie seven year old. I'll never forget it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like the quests hanging around without being completed. So I used the console commands for the gwent stuff. It worked very well. Plus, you get the experience points. 

What really pisses me off is the bugged quests where you can't use console commands to complete them. But that's another story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry. It's Windows 8.1 and it is the latest version of FireFox at the moment but it was probably one or two updates ago that the PC failed. I should have said that. My apologies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I've heard that. I personally take valium in low doses for it. I never take it more than twice a week. I could take more if I wanted but  I'm exceptionally careful never to build a tolerance. Yeah, it feels good when you take it but the thought of it not helping when I really need it is terrifying. I can't let myself do that. It's been a couple of years and I still stick to my allowance. Some weeks, I don't take it at all. It's good but it's not *that* good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 13:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which isn't going to help it when ploughs into a huge wave at the wrong angle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 13:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happens if there's a big fuck-off wave coming? Could it be slammed back into where it came from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 11:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One can only hope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 10:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still can't find it. I've tried searching like that and nothing like the path I want comes up. It's like it's completely different to the path I found my old data in. I can go to program files/mozilla firefox and there are no files called places.sqlite. I don't know where else to look. There is not trace of any of this in my users folder. This is weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 09:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they want to carry on about cost so much, why not allocate a certain amount of funding and let the teams do what they want? Why do they all have to do exactly the same thing?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
