<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3835</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 16:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No? Where'd you get that idea? It's just for pointing out "dramatic" discussions on reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 16:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh look, another useless redditor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ha, that's silly. The three cups of flour obviously go in the cake *before* the gallon of gasoline. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 15:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 11:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed - off topic

As was explained on Modmail, actually reading the messages automod leaves instead of ignoring them is a good way to see how your post was submitted incorrectly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 09:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed - recent repost

https://www.reddit.com/r/asmr/comments/5fofzm/asmr_let_me_cut_your_hair_role_play_hd_female/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 09:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed- recent repost 

https://www.reddit.com/r/asmr/comments/5fn0bj/gibi_asmr_saying_your_name_name_trigger_asmr/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 23:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, that's silly. The three cups of flour obviously go in the cake *before* the gallon of gasoline. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 18:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This submission has been automatically removed because it is a [recent repost](https://www.reddit.com/r/asmr/comments/5fjpx5/everything_is_going_to_be_okay_intentional/). Thanks for your submission, but to prevent spam on the subreddit videos are limited to one submission every three months. Please search before submitting, or at least check /r/asmr/new, and see [the wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/asmr/wiki) for details. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 13:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  2016

 no adblock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 11:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those sort of things usually only apply to very old batteries. Modern batteries have very sophisticated charging circuits and are built using different tech than many years ago, so don't need any sort of care like draining or special charging habits. Try to keep your battery at a sensible temperature - not very hot or very cold - and if you're going to switch the device off for a long time (weeks or more) then try to have the battery about half full. Otherwise charge it however suits you best and don't worry about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 11:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've just downloaded it and it does seem to have the feature I'm looking for. Thankyou :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 11:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.apple.com/uk/batteries/maximizing-performance/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 11:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm also *used to* it now, but I still don't like it. Offer me an old home button and I'd go back in a heartbeat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Viticci? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New name.

"iOS " and numbers 2-10 were good names. Not so sure about 11+ as names. Hoping they'll start doing "iOS Polar Bear" or "iOS Maple Syrup" like they do with macOS.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 20:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, before I've even started talking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] I'm looking for a reminders app which allows me to schedule a regular reminder, but only creates the next one AFTER I check off the previous one. Can anyone help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 16:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So for example I might want to set a reminder every 6 weeks. Say the first one is due to go off on the 9th of January. That would *usually* mean that the next one is due to go off 6 weeks later on the 20th of Febuary. But when I'm reminded on the 9th of January it might take me a few days to complete the task, so I want the app to nag me about it with notifications until I mark it as completed. Say I don't get around to completing the task for a week, on the 16th of January, *only then* should the next reminder be set 6 weeks later, to on the 27th of Feb rather than the 20th. The 6-week gap should be from when I complete the task, not from when the previous reminder first went off.

Does anyone know of an app which allows me to seet reminders in this way? I looked into omnifocus but it seems like swatting a fly with an industrial bulldozer, and I can work around it with Reminders without paying 30. I don't mind paying for an app but that's clearly overkill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 16:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why you calling me darlin'? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 16:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where the fuck has this tip been hiding? Thank you! I've been having a lot of trouble getting siri to listen to me in iOS10. Hopefully this is the solution </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 16:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gallowboob has 10.2 mill in 2.1 years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 15:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very very mildly, yes. 

I often think that *thinking about* triggering my asmr goes quite far to actually triggering it. Like when I'm not thinking about it I rarely get triggered, and for a video to trigger me I usually have to want it to. Thinking about it doesn't trigger me, but not thinking about it seems to mostly prevent me from being triggered, so being cognisant of the possibiliy of being triggered is necessary but not sufficient to trigger me. When I'm thinking about being triggered and imagining the feeling, I can *almost* feel it on the back of my neck and I think at that point I'm very sensitive to being triggered. For example when I'm getting my hair cut I can sort of *make* it trigger me by thinking about it, where otherwise I'd have felt nothing: neither the thought nor the haircut independantly trigger me, but together they can set off my tingles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 15:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> !RemindMe 1 year "married yet?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 15:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're married now and OP resents his success. Could have been 700 karma but NOOO she just had to go along with the joke and have his babies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Only poor people are made out of flip flop. Rich people are made out of wallet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 23:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 20:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apple thinks that's too much

The particular skylake chipset doesn't support more than 16GB of LPDDR3, that's why RAM caps at 16. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 17:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed - recent repost

https://www.reddit.com/r/asmr/comments/5ec8l8/satisfying_hot_knife_vs_compilation_1


Please search before submitting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 16:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could always give him gold if you think he deserves it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 00:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry about that. Approved.

edit: I removed it again as you resubmitted and the resubmission has a higher score, so I left that one up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 21:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to know the setup for that punchline </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 20:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course, I'm not denying that. But I'm saying it *feels* far more scripted in ep2, like they're just reciting lines. It felt forced. I'm hoping it's just teething problems with the new series rather than something fundamentally different.

Also: [it **is** top gear](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=G1dZRNxvsGo) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 18:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who's used windows for my entire life and has used macos briefly on other people's machines, I've always found the "Mac is so much better than windows" people to be a bit of a meme. I've never used Mac enough to judge but it seems different, not better or worse, to me. I follow a lot of apple fans online - mostly the RelayFM/ATP/etc crowd - and they often complain about how bad windows is compared to Mac without actually giving any examples, or complaining about trivial stuff. I've never had any real problems using windows - it's far from perfect but I don't resent using it. I've always wanted to see a good, neutral, side-by-side comparison of the good and bad points of each platform, but the neutral part seems to be difficult to find.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 17:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, that'd explain it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 15:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you find is better on Windows than on macOS? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 15:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a train from London to London depending on which parts you start and finish in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 15:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought my 3-year one a few weeks before I bought a car. Sort of stupid really. I've never used it and I'm now in year 2 of 3 and I probably never will. Complete waste of 70-odd quid. And you can't sell/transfer them because they have your picture on. And it's a terrible picture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 13:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I can see, everyone except: the UK, Germany, France, Italy, Japan, China, India, South Korea, Brazil, Canada, and the [US](https://youtu.be/Amt9mLvQM5w?t=30)

Oh and French Guiana? But I suspect that's a colouring-in mistake.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeremy Clarkson interview: BBC DIDN'T LIKE THE GRAND TOUR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 15:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 15:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, filtering the shite out of /r/all is a decent perk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 15:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always downvote those people. If you mention upvotes or downvotes about your own comment/submission, downvote for you. 

Those infuriating "upvote party" submissions on /r/all? Downvote. 

"Wow, my most upvoted comm-" Downvote. 

"Don't upvote this post but.." Downvote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 11:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he was probably remembering [this clip](https://youtu.be/FJB7gbjiJKw?t=10m2s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 11:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, interesting. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 11:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't want them to act though, I just want them to dick around like before and have a laugh. I did think ep2 felt very forced and scripted and that put me off it. I nearly turned it off! I know it was scripted before, but it didn't *feel* very scripted - some moments did but in general it felt natural. I know it's only their first attempt and of course I'm not put off the series as a whole, but I do hope this isn't a precedent being set.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 10:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus man take a breath </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 09:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why so smooth? Where's the grip? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 22:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agent smith has just a perfect voice for asmr. Also the way that he's always so calm when he speaks. ASMattR's [Smith](https://youtu.be/SdvytCqOc5M) is great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 20:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Land of the free" hahahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 00:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i2.kym-cdn.com/photos/images/original/000/554/670/1a5.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 13:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excuse my ignorance: cupping?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 12:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/96YDa0owtRc?t=28s

No Danthology this year :'( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Danny Docile) ASMR Call Centre Roleplay [male] [softly spoken] [roleplay] [15 minutes] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 00:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 00:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually 6am on  Friday morning that it usually goes up ;)

I've changed it to midnight UTC now though so you Muricans will see it around 4-6pm on Thursday. But it'll be up all week from now on anyway so it's more of a free-for-all-permathread-that's-refreshed-every-week than a free-for-all-friday, so it doesn't matter too much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Meta] New shiny flairs! Mod applications! Subreddit-hosted Game Nights! We've got it all! | General announcement and feedback thread. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 23:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey everyone, it's been a while. Hope you're all doing great. Let's get to it.

###First order of business: flairs!

This week /u/sopixil suggested in [this thread](https://www.reddit.com/r/asmr/comments/5d5gde/can_we_get_a_new_flair_for_roleplay_videos_meta/) that the subreddit should allow [roleplay] flairs. It was discussed in the thread and at length behind the scenes between the mods, and we decided it was a great idea. We've implemented it in the subreddit and the feature is now live, as a trial for the next month (until exactly 19th of December.. ish). During the trial, we will be enforcing the use of the new [roleplay] flair on links to videos in the roleplay genre, meaning links to such videos should be tagged as [roleplay] (or [role play]) instead of the usual [intentional] tag. (The [intentional] tag will still be there for non-roleplay submissions just like before.) It will be mostly up to the OP to decide what is or isn't a roleplay, but the mods will have the final decision if we feel strongly that the submission is flaired incorrectly. This allows users who don't want to see such posts to filter them out using RES or other third-party filtering services including their eyes, and allows users who like roleplays to see exclusively roleplay submissions using the link in the sidebar. Feedback/thoughts/resentment/reverence for the above should be left as a comment to this thread.

###Second order of business: mod applications!

We'll be taking applications for a new mod to the subreddit: leave a comment below if you'd like to apply. Make sure you let us know your experience with asmr, content creation, CSS, riot control, automod, modding, and anything else you might think is relevant. We're looking for something in particular so let us know why you're the right future-mod and tell us all about yourself - the more the better. This is being left pretty open-ended, so go wild with your applications, but please include your daily availability and your timezone.

### Last order of business: game nights!

After /u/NvaderGir created the [Discord server](https://www.reddit.com/r/asmr/comments/3q0bl3/meta_rasmr_discord_server_a_howto_introduction/) more than a year ago, the small community over there has flourished and is a great place to hang out. If you've not had a look, check it out [here](https://discordapp.com/invite/0aPMRwTjjn7F446x) and get stuck in! Have a chat with content creators and viewers and discuss your favourite videos, or really anything you like as there's no set topic so feel free to strike up your own conversation. If you qualify as a subreddit Content Creator, your flair will also be visible in Discord with a unique role that will differentiate from regular users. Just let /u/NvaderGir know in the Discord to verify! Anyway, since it's been going so well we've been thinking of hosting some game nights as a community bonding sort of thing, where any multiplayer game is on the table, from FPS's to RPG's to card games to puzzle games. If you'd be interested in joining in, leave a comment below and let us know what games you'd like to see hosted. 

---

I'll stick around for the next hour or so to receive feedback and /u/NvaderGir will be around for a while after that. We'll check in periodically over the next few days and this thread will stay stickied until the [roleplay] trial is complete. After that, the new mod will be chosen and we'll make a decision about whether or not to proceed with the new tag. You can also use the comments below as a general discussion/feedback/ideas/conversation thread. It's all good here.

Peace, and as always happy tingles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 20:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 970s are 2.5 years old now..  so equivelant of that ish today.

edit: actually 2.2 years, but who's counting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 23:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This VR game requires the use of a gamepad.

Lol, ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 20:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got the reference. Well done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 14:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the red pill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 23:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say very unimportant personally. I almost exclusively listen to videos without watching. The content creator could be dancing the conga for all I know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 21:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand what you're saying but this is kind of like saying "well just don't smoke then. Stop putting cigarettes in your mouth." It's all easy enough to say but actually doing it is an emotional battle that's not easy to win. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 15:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, and we tried it for a while. We've discussed this at length: see the link above :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 15:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That only applies to comments, not submissions  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 13:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course we care. There's just really nothing we can do about it. It's such a shame to see good content downvoted but it's not something we can enforce. 

/r/asmr/wiki/downvotes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 05:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Entry. Good luck all :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 15:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh the solution here is easy. Simply get the Canadian government to change the country's name to something that doesn't start with an existing 3-letter word. Sorted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 15:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you can search in that subreddit by e.g. [[uk]](https://www.reddit.com/r/NetflixBestOf/search?q=%5Buk%5D+self%3Ano restrict_sr=on sort=new t=all) or [us] to find things available in your location </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 10:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was planning to do it anyway. They wouldn't *actually* demolish his house over a bet would they. He'd got permission to demolish and reconstruct it months beforehand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 10:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the studio sections looked quite orange. Like the contrast was turned up slightly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 13:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's really tough on her fans

Yeah her mental health must be so hard for you to deal with.

Removed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 12:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google+=1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 00:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well then we agree: the obvious errors are changed by the mods and the rest is uaually up to the OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 23:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really see why it should be ok to modify intentional/unintentional flairs but not roleplay flairs. Let's assume a blazingly obvious case - a creator is roleplaying a doctor and is dressed up as a doctor and is using a stethescope and such, and the video is titled "doctor role play ASMR" on youtube. If this gets submitted to reddit I don't think anybody is going to complain that we add the Role Play flair if the OP doesn't. As I said, we'd lean toward letting OP decide but reflair in obvious cases like the one I described. I can't see a difference between reflairing my example video and reflairing an incorrectly tagged unintentional video as intentional. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 22:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed - recent repost. Please search before submitting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 21:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   If we don't currently enforce the use of tags that describe objectively-measurable triggers (such as tapping or whispering), why should we enforce the use of a tag that people disagree on the definition of? 

I dont agree that it'll cause confusion. I think the main way people infer what sort of content they're watching is by the flair, and we *do* currently enforce the use of correct flair tags. Submissions are removed if they're new, or if they've received a bit of attention I usually just change the flair and let it stay. Have you ever noticed this? I doubt it, because people mostly pay attention to the flair. I think there's *more* cause for confusion if a post is tagged as [intentional] but has an unintentional flair -which happens occasionally, maybe once a week or so - than if the post *doesn't* have a [role play] tag but *does* have a roleplay flair. I think 98% of people won't even notice the inconsistency, and of those who do maybe 80-90% will understand what's happened anyway.

I do think that the job of the mods is to ensure the posts are relevant and correct, which is what we'd be doing by correcting the flair. I'm only talking about if something is *obviously* incorrect. As with the title rule mentioned before, I'd be quite lenient toward letting OP decide, but if there's an obvious case where a video is clearly a roleplay but not flaired as such, I'll just update the flair and move on, and vice versa. I don't think that's unfriendly to users or will cause confusion, as it's just a changed flair. I think very few people are both attentive enough to notice the discrepency between the flair and the tag, **and** don't understand why that's the case **and** care about it enough to let it cause confusion rather than just accepting the flair as the correct label. And as I said it'd only be changed in clear cases, rather than being used as an overrule in less clear cases such as your example of your voice impressions. Anyway, it'd almost certainly be changed from an "intentional" flair to a "Role Play" flair, which don't conflict as all role-plays submitted are necessarily "intentional" anyway. It'd certainly be far less confusing than relabelling an [unintentional] tagged post as [intentional], which I've been doing for a while and nobody has ever so much has mentioned it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 20:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You make some great points, as usual! You always give great feedback and that's really appreciated. 

How about this then: we say that role play posts should be flaired, but if the mods disagree about the flair we can change it without removing the post. In the case of people disagreeing about whether it is or not, someone needs to be the arbitrator because ultimately it has to either have the flair or not. Either OP or the mods should have the arbitration rights, and giving it to the mods allows correct categorisation of posts whose OP didn't know the role play flair is a thing. So the mods can overrule the flair but we won't remove indirectly categorised posts. Sound fair? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two Corn Chips who are Friends [unintentional] [female] [soft spoken] [joke-telling!] [humour] Loudish music at the end </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 13:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 13:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/asmr  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 12:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We do already do this, although it's difficult to enforce. If someone's title is completely non-descriptive or doesn't contain relevant tags it'll be removed, but on the other hand I do like to be quite lenient with that rule because it feels a bit nitpicky sometimes to remove good submissions because of a poor title. If the submission isn't caught for a few hours and it gets popular I'll just flair it as "bad title" and leave it. No point removing a submission people are enjoying over what I see as a technicality. It does more harm than good at that point. 

So it's a difficult rule to enforce, but we do what we can to encourage descriptive and well-tagged titles. The few seconds of effort to put the right tags in can really help people find great content. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 12:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This would mean a new rule: roleplay videos must be tagged as [roleplay]. So we'd have to define a roleplay - I'd suggest something like 

anything where the host is acting, i.e. pretending to be anyone other than themselves. 

It would only ever be a subcategory of [Intentional], so it can only be a [roleplay] if it contains intentional triggers and would previously have been tagged as [intentional]. So going forward, any triggering content must be tagged either [unintentional], [intentional], or [roleplay], where unintentional is the same as it is now, intentional means triggers are purposefully created in the video but the content creator is not expressing a character - they're just being themselves in the video, and roleplay is anything with intentional triggers where the host is acting/pretending to be someone else.

We'd also have a filter in the sidebar to show **only** roleplay videos - unfortunately it's not possible to filter **out** roleplay videos in this way, however RES may be able to filter them out.

I think this would do a lot to satisfy the complaints we've been seeing recently that the front page is mostly the same sort of videos. Roleplay videos are always explicitly mentioned as a major cause of this problem, so the ability to filter them out will allow those who dislike the genre to more quickly find what they like. It will also help those who like the roleplay videos find them more quickly.

It should be noted that we don't like adding flairs because they're designed to very broadly categorise the *type of submission* to the subreddit, rather than describe the video. The additional tags that we encourage users to include in the titles are there to describe the video's content, while the flair tag (and flair itself) are designed to indicate whether the user posting a video, or asking for help, or talking about the subreddit etc.

That said, the overwhelming demand for something exactly like this has been difficult to ignore especially over the past year. To be honest I do agree with a lot of the feedback we've received in that the front page does tend to be a bit samey, and roleplay videos in general do little for me personally. With the above in mind I think this is a good one-off exception to the "we don't add arbitrary flairs" rule, as it will improve the experience of the subreddit for basically everone. I'd be willing to trial it for a couple of weeks and see where we go from there.

Does anyone have any additional feedback or thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 00:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting idea. I'd be interested in what the community thinks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 23:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The real apk is always in the comments </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 22:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you considered using a secondary channel? A lot of youtubers have one and it sounds like that would be a good place to put something like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 22:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There it is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That result-deleting whispered part at the end was intense. Very tingly sounds :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Misread as dogecannon. Much disappoint. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a joke in there somewhere.. Something like "Why did the music teacher get fired? He was caught playing with A Minor".. or something.. Someone who's actually funny improve it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 13:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From [reddiquette](https://www.reddit.com/wiki/reddiquette#wiki_in_regard_to_comments):

 Please don't [...] **Announce your vote**. "Upvote" and "Downvote" aren't terribly interesting comments and only increase the noise to signal ratio.

From English:

laugh

Probably explains it. Just guessing. Who knows on reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 18:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't have to sell it like that. Say you've been really embarrassed about it so you didn't want to say anything, but you're now close enough with her that you trust her not to laugh. Something like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 18:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are the association justifying saying that? Surely the winner is the winner, no questions or challenges? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 15:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone explain what's going on? Saw this on /r/all and this is the first I've heard of any of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 15:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does it add?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 14:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This type of comment needs more downvotes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 13:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'll be cloudy in the UK. It always is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 00:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed - music isn't allowed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quantum Computing 'Magic' - Computerphile [unintentional] [male] [german accent] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 15:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 12:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't speak for worst *ever*, but they were pretty awful movies. I can't immediately think of any worse ones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 21:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [well, maybe](https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=MShv_74FNWU) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 20:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Additional picky feedback: the phrasing "write the group" is a very strong Americanism. To those outside America it sounds very jarring. The missing "to" seems nonsensical to others, so maybe consider changing the phrasing to "send a message" or something more internationally neutral. Just my two cents (ha).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 20:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who fake screenshots for internet points? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 20:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/anticlimax  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 19:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the sidebar for info </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So You've Just Elected Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 00:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 00:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) Play game at internet cafe

2) become addicted

3) /r/thisismylifenow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 00:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was 1994. I know because it was happening while I was being born.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 19:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/ProgrammerHumor/comments/29cs63/a_meme_i_made_in_my_freshers_year/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 19:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad to help :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 12:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gave it another try and managed to sign up by reformatting my number like: +447xxxxxxxxx. I think most users aren't techy enough to think of doing this though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 02:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few thoughts from my initial impression:

I don't like being forced to choose a profile picture. Maybe have the option to choose from a set of default cartoon avatars or something as an alternative to a photo. At least allow a photo to be taken live from the camera rather than forcing a choice from the photo library.

Once the photo is chosen I have to wait for it to upload before I can proceed, but there's no UI to indicate when it's done or its progress. The upload should really happen in the background while I proceed, but at the very least show a progress bar or percentage on the screen instead of in a message box.

After that I was forced to enter my phone number. I don't like entering my number into apps at the best of times, but I figured since I'm helping with the beta I can put it in. I should point out that I'd have deleted the app at this point if I weren't testing a beta, and I don't think I'd be alone in being greatly put off by this. Anyway, I entered my UK phone number in the format 07xxx xxxxxx, and it was rejected for being invalid. I tried different spacings but no joy. So I couldn't complete signup.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 16:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried it with the /s but no joy.

However rd works great, didn't know about that. Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How can I delete a whole specific folder? "del folder" only deletes the contents, NOT the actual folder. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 16:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm running 

    del "pycache" /q

to delete the folder `pycache` and all of its contents. The command is deleting the files and subfolders within `pycache`, but not the folder itself. I'm left with an empty folder. 

Ideas?

Windows 7 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What product gets a lot of hate but is actually pretty good? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 14:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 12:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. Haven't heard those words in years and didn't expect to hear them today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 00:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If interested I solved with the following function (tested with unit test). Seems more verbose than the regex but it works and runs very quickly so I'm happy :)

    def remove_comment_lines(input):
        in_command = False
        line_has_command = False
        line = ""
        output = ""

        for c in input:
            if c == "[":
                in_command = True
                line_has_command = True
                line += c
            elif c == "]":
                in_command = False
                line += c
            elif c == "\n":
                if in_command:
                    line += c
                elif line_has_command:
                    output += line + "\n"
                    line_has_command = False
                    line = ""
                else:
                    output += "\n"
                    line = ""
            else:
                line += c

        if line_has_command:
            output += line
        
        return output    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 23:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you just draw that? Haha, thanks.

I'm only stripping standalone comments, ie comments on a line of their own. Comments before or after commands don't match. e.g:

    [command] comment (no match here)
    just a comment - matches!
    comments can also be before [commands] so no match here

I was thinking of basically what you said - just `for` through the string and keep two boolean flags, `in_command` and `command_in_line`. The first obviously keeps track of if I'm in a command, so don't delete anything while that's true. The second tracks if I've seen a "[" on this line so far. If I get to the end of a line and both flags are false, I'll delete that whole line. Repeat for whole string. Should work I think.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 23:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. I'm basically stripping out comments from a scripting language - all commands are [within brackets]. But commands can span multiple lines. Comments are anything not within brackets.

Might need a bit more thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 23:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I might be able to do it line-by-line, but I'll have to write a tricky little function for it which scans character by character. Watch:

    [this is a command so doesn't match]
    [this is a multi-line command
    so shouldn't match
    but it looks like it does on line 3]
    [command with a comment-] no matches so far
    first match! since there's no command
    another match here
    [no match again]

What I want to do is remove the matches. I've been using `re.sub(comment_lines, "", input)`to remove them. But it's actually more complicated than I originally thought, because removing lines with no bracket will chop up multi-line commands as above. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 22:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to remove them from the original string though, so extracting them isn't enough. I'm using `re.sub(comment_lines, "", input)` to remove the matching lines. Is this possible with `String.replace()` or similar? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 22:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm interested in what it is about look(behinds|aheads) that causes them to take such a long time. I'd have thought it's more of an afterthought for the match - does this match string end with this other match? Good, done. Why does that take so long?

I'm trying to match like this:

    [nothing on this] line matches
    this does though
    [this is a command so doesn't]
    this matches despite the close bracket here -]
    [no match here] despite the comment here

I'll try the single line approach, thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is my regex taking so long to execute? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 19:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>     (?=\n)[^\[\n]+?(?=\n)
 
I'm scanning a script for lines which don't contain commands, where a command is always [within square brackets]. So I want to match just the contents of the line. So I'm looking behind for a newline character, matching anything that's not an open square bracket or a newline, lazilly, then looking ahead for a newline. Seems simple - why's it taking forever? It just took 88 seconds (49.98 *million* steps, according to regex101.com) to execute on a 10,000 character (264-line) script. What gives?

I wondered whether the lookahead/behind could be causing trouble, and noticed that with *only* the lookahead *or* the lookbehind it executes in under a second at around 25k steps. But with both it takes 50M steps and a minute and a half. ??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is this regex taking so long? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 19:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>     (?=\n)[^\[\n]+?(?=\n)

I'm scanning a script for lines which don't contain commands, where a command is always [within square brackets]. So I want to match just the contents of the line. So I'm looking behind for a newline character, matching anything that's not an open square bracket or a newline (lazily), then looking ahead for a newline. Seems simple - why's it taking forever? It just took 88 seconds (49.98 *million* steps, according to regex101.com) to execute on a 10,000 character (264-line) script. What gives? 

I wondered whether the lookahead/behind could be causing trouble, and noticed that with *only* the lookahead *or* the lookbehind it executes in under a second at around 25k steps. But with both it takes 50M steps and a minute and a half. ??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 11:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One fewer leave vote if it gets put to a parliamentary vote </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 11:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can do that. Be happy to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 21:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a joke. Rule 11 says spoilers must be marked with a [spoiler] tag. You posted a spoiler without a spoiler tag. Except a different kind of spoiler. That's the joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 21:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rule 11 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [A] Countdown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 21:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 19:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> removed - more suitable for /r/nsfwasmr </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 17:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 16:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the name of that if found tweak? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 14:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sorry  #44; what was that again #63; </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 14:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 10:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://ring.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi I'm Tom From Australia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 10:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 17:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is beautiful. I love the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 17:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. And I choose ignorance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To Kayley, Who Is Sad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 16:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 15:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You link is broken. I think you need to use "http://www." at the beginning for it to be recognised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 14:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glados knows that feel :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 15:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you tried `pip install skype ` </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 15:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I've asked for this before but no joy. I'd love to see it. Would pay significantly too. Very annoying to have apps tracking background location just because they can.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 15:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, as arsey as it was for him to correct you I wouldn't use it all the time intentionally. It's like using "u", it comes off as tacky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 22:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I tested it by having it repeatedly play against itself overnight. The final score was 

`Computer_1` 43,000 - 0 `Computer_2`

And yeah I think I've seen that blog post before. I quite like the idea of UTTT but I feel like it could be a dull game also - see the video in the last comment. It'd most likely also end in a draw most of the time, from a quick thinking through, although I'd like to see/play some actual games. The main point in the original video was that the fundemental problem with TTT is that it allows draws, which makes it dull. X-only ends quickly with player 1 winning, misere is basicaally impossible to win if you move second, but misere, x-only, 3-board TTT is a much more interesting game, but there's a mathsy way to ensure a win.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 19:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Code is read more often than it's written

Yeah this is true. When I'm scripting at work I do prefer readable code over shorter code, and I comment very well. I was just being lazy and I should know better! 

I think my subconscious "rule" was to concatenate if I have a single variable in the string, e.g. `print(winner + " wins!")`, but for more concatenations I would use formatting. Those literal format strings in 3.6 look like a great compromise though, and I look forward to using them. 

So if you skim the inner functions, it's actually harder to argue about what data it accesses. 

I'd never considered this, and it's a good point. I guess I never really questioned it, and it's always good to see stuff from new angles. 

I wouldn't say I *want* to embed other people's AI - it was just a throwaway project one boring saturday afternoon - but I like to write things in a more general sense where I can that *allows* that sort of thing, even if I never intend to use it. Maybe that's just my programming style? I'm not sure, but I like to modularise my code and give each module an intent. The Player's intent is to win (by any means), and the Controller's intent is to enfore the rules and make sure the game is fair. Again this is a philosophical decision which is probably just creating unnecessary work, but it's nice to think about.

 I'm happy to help! Glad you could learn something 

Thanks again! I do really appreciate it. 

 I've played a quick round, but didn't really manage to achieve much :(

I got the idea from [this video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h09XU8t8eUM), and (assuming there are no bugs) it's mathematically impossible to beat the AI if it moves first. If it moves second you have to make perfect moves from start to finish to win; one mistake and it will take over the game and win. I don't really know how it works but the guy in the video published a paper [here](https://miseregames.files.wordpress.com/2012/04/x-onlyttt.pdf) which sort of explains it in a more verbose way than the video. Basically you assign certain board configurations certain algebreic expressions, such as "a", "b^2", "bc" etc, and multiply the expressions of each board to get a longer expression for the whole game state, for example if the first board is in position "a", and the next two are both "b", the overall position will be "ab^2". You then aim for moves which create certain overall expressions - [these](https://github.com/Theonefoster/X-only-misere-3-board-tic-tac-toe/blob/master/NaughtsAndCrossesBot.py#L223) are positions from which you can guarantee a win, and all other positions are equally lossy (you just have to wait for a mistake from your opponent). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 14:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He lives on a farm now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 21:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit. I didn't expect an answer this detailed! So firstly thanks so much for taking the time to look through my code - I really appreciate that! I'll reply to your comments in order below.

I didn't realise you could just pass an exception - for some reason I thought you had to set a value. I'll replace that line with a pass.

I didn't even think to use global constants for the length, width, and board count. As you say it's a small point but it's probably better design, and would allow an easy way to add more boards. As I assumed it'd only ever be me reading the code, I though "b", "r", and "c" were self-explanatory in the context. ^^I'm ^^also ^^very ^^lazy.

I've used string formatting before, but for some reason I just never really liked it. Maybe I'm in a minority but I vastly prefer for readability:

    print("Hello " + user.name + ", how can I help?")

I'm aware of the string formatting but I guess it's a stylistic decision. I've used formatting [in other projects](https://github.com/Theonefoster/asmr_bot/blob/master/asmr_bot.py#L329) because the strings got pretty messy and hard to read, and formatting was much clearer. I feel like I use it if I have a need to, but otherwise I just concatonate. Would you say that's the wrong approach?

I didn't know about the all() line, that's a nice shorthand. I considered using a loop but I thought for three cases it's probably not worth it. As you point out, if I'd used a global constant for the board count a loop would make way more sense, and I'd definitely use the all() function.

I've always been slightly confused by the way that variables are actually pointers, and things like this seem counter to the programmer's intent:

     a = [1,2,3]
     b = a
     b.remove(2)
     a
    [1,3]

I do understand how it works as of quite recently but it's not intuitive so I guess I forgot while writing the kill_board function.

Regarding defining functions inside other functions, I try to define things in the smallest scope they're needed in. Since the rotate and reflect functions are only ever used inside the make_move function, I defined them there for the smallest scope. It's just how I was taught a few years ago I suppose, but you're right that they could - and think about it probably should, since they're board operations - have gone in the board class. I defined the is_win function twice because one takes a board_num as integer and one takes a board object. In the context I thought it was simpler than trying to convert between boards and integers since it's a fairly short function, although I'm usually quite strict about preventing code duplication. Still, nice catch.

You say that the below are equivalent:

     if turn_player == player_2:
        winner = player_1.name
     else:
        winner = player_2.name
.

     winner = turn_player.name

Notice that the winner is *not* turn_player, which I think you missed (the *loser* is the player who makes three-in-a-row). I initially swapped the turn_player and *then* announced the new turn_player as the winner, but I deleted that and changed it to this which is easier to read, but I was also having some odd bugs with the other method. Howveer I much prefer the itertools.cycle() method, which I wasn't aware of and seems widely useful, so thanks for that pointer :)

The reason for the deepcopy is kind of philosophical. The "controller" (the main loop at the bottom) says to the player, "Here's the state of the board. What move would you like to make?", and the player does some calculation and replies "I'd like to make move (0,1,1)" or whatever. This means that the player never has access to the board, so can't cheat. You could write your own Player object and integrate it with my program, and I could have no idea how you'd written your Player but I know that you can't illegally manipulate the board since you never see it; you only ever see a copy. This is useful because the Bot player tests various different moves against the board without actually making those moves. It's perhaps a bit nitpicky and definitely out-of-scope for what I was going for, but I like thinking about the relationships between the objects in this personified way, and giving each object an intent and a purpose....

...that said, I assume that players' moves are legal since the move validation is inside the player, not inside the controller..! :/ That's partly because I didn't really plan anything, I just started writing. If I'd planned it I would have had the validation inside the controller instead so that players can't make illegal moves. For example there's nothing stopping a player moving onto a dead board - only the validation inside the Player object. You could write a Player object with no validation and my controller would accept any move you try to make.

Regarding the UI, I've had about an hour's experience with tkinter about 6 months ago and really didn't like it. I'd much rather use a graphical UI editor like Visual Studio, but it seems that doesn't exist or isn't possible with python. I'll definitely have a look into PyQt on your recommendation though and give it a go.

Thanks so much again! I expected throwaway comments if anything, so the depth of your comment is amazing to see :D

^(Did you try playing? Could you beat my AI? (: )
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors who've had to hire employees: what did you look for in the candidates and how did you make your decision? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 12:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> meirl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 14:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who got a lot of hate that they didn't deserve? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 10:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who did you lose a lot of respect for after their fame went to their head? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 17:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3-board misere x-only tic-tac-toe challenge: how could you simplify a function to return a rating of a board based on a long list of board scores? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 22:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to implement a perfect player of 3-board x-only misere tic tac toe. For a full description of what that means see here:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ktPvjr1tiKk

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h09XU8t8eUM

The list of scores for each possible board are given at the bottom of this document: https://arxiv.org/pdf/1301.1672.pdf

Ok, so given that list of 102 possible boards, how could I implement a function, board.score(), which returns the correct algebreic expression for a given board? I've defined a board as follows:

    [["-" for c in range(3)] for r in range(3)]

The value in the cell will only ever be "-" or "X" (or "O" on a "dead board", but this function will never deal with that). 

I made a start by saying:

        if self.is_win(board):
            return ""  # an algebreic score of 1 is returned as an empty string
    
        if squares_taken == 0:
            return "c"
        
        if squares_taken == 1:
            if board[1][1] == "-": #middle square is empty
                return ""
            else:
                return "cc" # algebreic score of "c squared" or c*c

This covers a few of the simple cases, but it gets rather complex to define each case after that, and as there are 102 such cases in total I think there must be a better way. Note also that the list of expressions at the bottom of the document is only the nonisomorphic permutations: rotations and reflections are not included. That means the two boards below should have the same score, but only one of them is included in the list of expressions in the document:

    -|X|-      -|-|-
    -|-|-      X|-|X
    -|X|-      -|-|-

Both boards should be scored "a". 

Any ideas on how this could be implemented in less than a few thousand if's? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roomba 980 - interesting error and fix story </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 21:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was getting an "error 16 place roomba on a flat surface". My roomba 980 was definitely on a flat surface in the middle of a mostly-empty room. Here's the chat I had with support.

      Support: Hi, my name is Support:. How may I help you?
     me: I'm getting Error 16 when trying to start a Roomba 980 clean of a single room. I usually have it run from the charging station, from which it navigates around the bedroom, hallway and living room. I tried manually placing the Roomba in the middle of the living room floor - a flat surface, as verified by a spirit level - and pressed Clean (from the app or the physical button). It spins around on the spot briefly, then says "Error 16". It cleans my living room completely fine when initiated from the charging dock - it navigates into and around the living room with no issues. However manually placing it on the floor - anywhere, not just in the living room - results in Error 16. The floor is hardwood so there's no carpet to worry about.

    I've tried moving it to a different starting spot. It's not obstructed or anything - there's not even much furniture, just a rectangular room with few obstacles. I want it to clean ONLY the living room as I've spilled a few bits on the floor, but it seems the only option is to clean the whole apartment starting from the charging dock.
     me: I wanted to close the door while it runs in only the living room, then replace it on the charging station.
     Support: Hello subject3835! How are you doing today?
     me: I'm good thank you :)
     Support: Oh no! We're glad you came to us for support. I will be happy to assist you with this error 16.
     Support: Would it be possible for you to provide me with the serial number from your robot?
     me: sure, sec
     me: Where can I find it?
     Support: That's a great question subject3835! Please remove the dust bin and turn your robot over you'll see a white sticker on the robot itself with the serial number. Please also include the three letters that appear before the serial number.
     me: ok I'll look there
     Support: Thank you.
     me: KYN980*************
     Support: Perfect! Thank you.
     Support: Ok! Let's follow a few simple steps. Do you currently have your Roomba and home base available?
     me:  yes
     Support: Let's place Roy on the home base. Press and hold the CLEAN button for 10 seconds until all the indicators illuminate. When the button is released, you will hear a series of tones.
     me: The base is in the other room so I'll be a moment
     Support: No worries!
     me: ok, done. It beeped
     Support: The cause of error 16 it means Roomba is not able to start cleaning because it is tilted. Move Roomba to a flat surface then press CLEAN to restart. Avoid moving the robot when pressing the CLEAN button. If Roomba says this message on a flat surface, we recommend rebooted the robot.
     Support: Once we have rebooted the Roomba, let's press and release CLEAN once then wait five seconds.
     Support: After completing this step, let's press CLEAN to start a new cleaning job.
     me: Ok, I've just been doing some testing while I waited for your reply and I've found the answer
     me: this is actually really interesting
     me: I'm assuming it uses infrared when it's scanning the room
     me: I also own a HTC Vive, which is set up in the same room. The Vive uses some infrared lighthouses which spray infrared beams into the room for the Vive to work.
     me: I tried the roomba again after the reset you suggested and it gave the same error, twice
     me: I then switched off the Vive lighthouses and the Roomba worked no problem!
     me: So I suppose the were interfering with its infrared
     Support: Well, there we go!
     Support: That could cause the little guy to not work properly.
     me: anyway it's fixed and working as we speak. So spread the word that sources of infrared interference can cause issues
     me: Thanks, I suppose! :)
     Support: Your welcome! Please free to contact us any time! :)
     Support: Is there any additional support I can offer today?
     me: That's it, thanks.
     Support: Thank you for chatting with iRobot. Have a great day, subject3835.

The support guy was really friendly, I thought. Although he didn't solve the problem - I doubt he'd ever have thought of the interference - I got my solution and I thought I'd let anyone else know in case it's useful to anyone. I'd be surprised if I'm not the first person to have this issue - the intersection of markets between the Vive and the Roomba must be a handful of people at most! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 11:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What did you do "the hard way" for years before realising your mistake? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 14:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most unjust punishment you were given by your parents as a kid? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 12:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What did you buy, thinking you were getting a good deal, but later realised you'd been ripped off? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 16:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Pixel Unboxing [female] [unintentional] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 13:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/asmr is trending on Reddit! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 11:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> unicom is TOTEZ AMAZEBALLS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 23:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Threddit - I want to write a single function that will take up to a few minutes to execute without pausing the rest of my script. Is this possible with multithreading? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 16:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm using praw with python 3.5. I know praw is funny about multithreading so I've always stayed away from it. 

I need a function that will run once per day to perform some checks and actions over the course of about 10 minutes. I don't want the rest of the script to be unresponsive in this time, as my script relies on real-time interactions to help moderate a subreddit. 

Can anyone direct me to some resources about writing a mutlithreaded praw script?

---

edit for future visitors with the same question: http://praw.readthedocs.io/en/stable/pages/multiprocess.html tl;dr look into praw.handlers.MultiprocessHandler or just use a different instance of praw.Reddit() </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your story of trying to help someone but only making things worse? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 13:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the worst experience you've had in a restaurant? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 12:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the worst experience you've had in a restaurant? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 11:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Batch Syntax. Nice easy one. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 11:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need to copy the following text to the clipboard using a batch file.

 [ Call hisca.chase, input="", input="7"]

I'm currently using the following command:

 echo [Call hisca.chase, input="", input="7"] | clip

Which works fine, but notice the missing ampersand character. I've tried every sequence of escaping various characters and I cannot get it to copy the exact string I need. When I add in the ampersand, it interprets the word "call" as a command, and I get "*hisca.chase not recognised as a batch file or command*" or whatever. I've settled for manually adding in the ampersand when I paste later, but *surely* there must be a way to copy it correctly with the ampersand included? 

Ideas? It's not hugely important but I'd like it to work correctly as it'd save me a few seconds mutiple times a day. ^(Far less time than it took me to write this post but sshh.)

\ Windows 7 server

\ running executable .bat file

----

Things I've tried:

\\ echo [ Call hisca.chase, input="", input="7"] | clip

command hisca.chase not recognised

\\ echo [\^ Call hisca.chase, input="", input="7"] | clip

command hisca.chase not recognised

\\ echo [\^\^ Call hisca.chase, input="", input="7"] | clip

command hisca.chase not recognised

\\ echo [\^\^ \^\^Call hisca.chase, input="", input="7"] | clip

command "\^call" not recognised


\\ echo "[ Call hisca.chase, input=\^"\^", input=\^"7\^"]" | clip

"[ Call hisca.chase, input=\^"", input="7"]" | clip


I've also tried escaping every other non-alphanumeric character in various combinations. I'm obviously approaching this wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I stumbled upon this fan theory site from 2006 (pre- deathly hallows release) speculating about R.A.B and other plot points. It made me smile so maybe you'll enjoy it too. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 14:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The worst scripting language in history. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 13:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TalkTalk fined 400,000 for cyber theft of customer details - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 15:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My girlfriend is like an iPhone 7. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 15:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She doesn't have a headphone jack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 21:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's going on in /r/exmormon right now? Why is it important and a big deal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 16:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's some sort of document leak exposing some people who covered up a thing. That's all I know.

^(Maybe I'm naive but what are mormons and the LDS?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Domino </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 23:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your brain gets a software update to v2.0 - what do the patch notes say? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 13:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Genius feels like an outsider </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 19:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [request] A mono/stereo audio toggle for control centre </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 14:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I often switch between one earphone and both earphones while listening to music. When only one is in some songs sound odd because one channel is missing, so I sometimes toggle the audio into Mono. But it's something like 3 menus deep into the Settings app which is a bit of a pain to get to. Any chance of getting it into CC? I have Polus already, and looked into creating a Custom button, but the mono/stereo toggle doesn't seem to be an option. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do not post, or ask for, personal information anywhere on reddit including here. Personal information should be sent in a personal message or via a trusted webform. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 15:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's basic internet awareness guys, come on. I've been seeing a lot of people posting their email addresses and even phone numbers (?!?!) in comment replies. There are bots that crawl the web looking for contact information and then they send spam to that contact information. There are also people who want to try to steal your identity, and an email address is a great starting point for someone to take over all of your accounts if they wanted. 

As usual, people who post personal information will have their comment removed so don't waste your or my time. People who ask others to *publicly* provide their contact information will be permanently banned.

Suggested ways to collect testers' information is by using a Google Form or by asking them to PM you. This way only you can see it rather than it being broadcast on the internet. This is for your own, and testers', safety.

Please report anyone who asks for or provides personal information in a public place. 

Happy testing :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With iOS 10 to be released soon, I'd like to remind everyone that you can find beta testers for your app, or beta test others' apps, at /r/testflight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 15:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/TestFlight 

Beta test pre-release App Store apps. Find testers for your app. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With iOS 10 to be released soon, I'd like to remind everyone that you can find beta testers for your app, or beta test others' apps, at /r/testflight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 15:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/TestFlight 

Beta test pre-release App Store apps. Find testers for your app. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With iOS 10 to be released soon, I'd like to remind everyone that you can find beta testers for your app, or beta test others' apps, at /r/testflight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 15:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/TestFlight 

Beta test pre-release App Store apps. Find testers for your app. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With iOS 10 to be released soon, I'd like to remind everyone that you can find beta testers for your app, or beta test others' apps, at /r/testflight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 15:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/TestFlight 

Beta test pre-release App Store apps. Find testers for your app. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are Apple Music playlists supposed to sync between devices? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 13:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have two iPhones: my personal device (6) and my work device (5S).

I use Apple Music with my 5S, and have a playlist of music on there. I don't currently have it with me, so I signed into the same account on my iPhone 6 expecting the playlist to be there, but it hasn't shown up. I've signed out and back in but it didn't make a difference.

Are playlists local to devices? That seems like an odd behaviour if it's true. If not, can I access my playlist that I created on my 5S without having my 5S with me? I'd have thought it would be synced to my account but apparently not.

Any help is appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A detailed analysis of what happens when a toothbrush is taped to the ceiling. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 12:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When moving into a first new home, what's the most useful thing most people wouldn't think about buying? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 12:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Mathematician's Office - Numberphile [unintentional] [accent] [7 minutes] [male] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 19:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best customer service experience you've ever had? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 11:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most unjust punishment you received as a kid? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 11:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PsBattle: Barack Obama and Kim Jong Un Lookalikes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 10:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> USB cable through the body </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 20:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smithy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 23:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smashing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 20:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These totally legitimate reviews for Roombas on their website. Some are even perfect word-for-word translations of the others. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 17:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suicide Squad Sales Pitch (spoilers) [unintentional] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 01:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best customer service experience you've ever had? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 12:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Poetry] They don't stop coming </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 13:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What law has had the most positive impact on your life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 15:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I compiled an album of frustrations I have had when Siri behaves in unexpected ways. Siri HAS to improve. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 14:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://imgur.com/a/oLIYe

The phone numbers were all valid phone numbers, and were recognised and even formatted correctly. But Siri just decides that it doesn't feel like calling those numbers for some reason.

The "Juice and Carrots" one.. I can sort of excuse, but I'd like it to have recognised that they were two separate items. But it's not so bad.

I don't really remember what the "third of a minutes" reminder was for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
