<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1143</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 22:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Monk? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 22:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 21:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Little Girl Gives Coins To A Street Musician And Gets The Best Surprise In Return </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 21:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wait for it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 02:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 04:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I learned something new today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: how are movies pirated? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 02:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 23:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many stitches? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 23:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You worked in a submarine? Cause that's the only place I can think of that uses nuclear in the military. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 04:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You actually got it sharpened? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 04:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that the reason why you are not working there now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 02:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> arwen

You've been reading Lord of the Rings haven't you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] You hurried into the time machine. This is it. There is only enough power for one more trip. With trembling fingers, you adjusted the time dials and tried to calm your nerves. This is it. You readied yourself and pushed the button. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 02:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 23:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress voted to strip all power from Obama for the rest of his presidency </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 22:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 03:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 06:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just surprised anyone's still awake at this hour... Hmm, draw me an extremely sleep-deprived person? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 04:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's something of that sort, called [infinite pools](https://web.archive.org/web/20150518092440/http://travelingsage.com/14-enchanting-infinity-pools/). They produce the illusion of a swimming pool with no boundaries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 03:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> High C's is my new favourite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 03:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> woah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> water upvote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 01:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 00:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just checked it out, thanks, saved it for later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 20:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're my new favourite artist ^ ^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 13:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny how Shakespeare lives in England, but set so many of his plays in Italy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 03:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are the FBI. Freeze. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 03:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they want to hack you, they would have done so already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 01:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Achoo!



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 01:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My English teacher said to me once, writing an essay and writing a novel are completely different things, to be good in one does not guarantee being good in the other. I personally find it hard to write fiction, it is much easier for me to write about something that's **real**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> sprial wooden christmas tree </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 01:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 01:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The CIA just released [map archives](http://imgur.com/gallery/JorJQ), [go check them out.](https://www.flickr.com/photos/ciagov/albums/with/72157672693466384) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Russian Front 1941-1942 [2500x2131] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 01:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> riptide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 02:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 01:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> damn, i actually didn't see that. found this from quora, guess the other guy did too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A BOOB, a VAGINA and an ASSHOLE are debating as to who is the greatest of them all </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 00:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The four stages of life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 02:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. You believe Santa Claus

2. You don't believe Santa Claus

3. You are Santa Claus

4. You look like Santa Claus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 04:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a little story here. I met an exchange student from Germany. We were talking about national anthems, and she said that they (or you guys, since you are German) rarely play their anthem, she doesn't like it cause it's the same song from the nationalistic era, and she thinks that everyone hates Germany,  which is totally not true and I told her that. "The struggle is real," is what she said.

I came out very thoughtful after that conversation. It's sad and unfair in my opinion that you guys are still sometimes blamed for events that your great grandparents did. I for one have a very positive view of Germany, you guys owned up to what you did and changed, unlike the Japanese. I think you guys should be proud of your nation, in a good way. I know I am proud of mine, despite all the fuckups we had, and probably still going to for some years.

Story over, I hope I didn't offend you in any way. I have a very limited view on your country, since I only ever talked to a few Germans. But here's my two cents, take it in whatever way thou wilt.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who records modern history? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 03:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 02:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spiders. Fuck spiders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 02:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't believe mine was already said! What are the odds? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 02:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Canadians burning down the white house in 1812 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 00:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to make you happy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 16:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A plane carrying a Brasilian football team on their way to regional finals crashed. It killed 75 people, and only 6 people survived. All their teammates are probably dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 16:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait till you see the stairs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 16:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sleep on the floor. Checkmate monsters! Where ya gonna hide now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 04:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know. Nobody knows until they've tried. So I guess the answer is yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 02:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah totally. Prompts only serve as inspiration. Welcome to this sub, [here's a story to get you started.](https://www.reddit.com/r/WritingPrompts/comments/3pyg3h/wp_a_day_before_the_earth_is_destroyed_by_a/cwali3n/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 00:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] You woke up in a place different from where you slept. "Beat the game to exit," the message said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 20:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] As long as you keep traveling, you will not age. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 02:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 19:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am listening to Dan carlin's podcast- blueprint for Armageddon. In it he talks about how Germany has changed the rules of war in WWI. Before, armies usually stayed in the tens of thousands men range. Armies are usually privately funded, and weapons are kept from civilians and the general public. Germany poured a whole nation's resources into war, conscripting over 2 million people, training civilians to fight, making all factories make ammunition and helmets, you get the idea. 

Suddenly, life was cheap. Before, where generals have to be more conservative in spending men on assaults, now they can pour waves and waves of men to take down that one fort blocking the way. Correct me if I'm wrong, but I think that's how trench warfare started. 

Before, men thought dying for your country in war was a great honor, something to look forward to. But that ideology changed when you are just one in thousands mowed down by a machine gun trying to overrun that Belgian fort blocking your way to France.

"What will I die for?" Soldiers wondered. "Am I just a replaceable pawn sacrificed on a giant Chessboard?" And they are not wrong. 

Napoleon was the first to utilize an entire nation for war. But it was really the start of WWI that changed soldiers opinion on war. Before going into WWI, many countries still held on to war concepts from the 1800s. The French army had *red pants!* Some armies don't have helmets, others are missing boots, and the French still thought charging with your bayonet is fashionable. Well, they had to scrap all that after WWI. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 15:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Choose what is right, not what is easy. Its not really easy to define a brave choice, as everyones idea of brave is different. I think the first sentence sums it up well enough. If the path you want to follow is disapproved by many people, and you chose it, you are either brave.... or stupid. The line is thin, it depends on whether you succeeded or not *in the end*. Bill gates dropped out of university to start a business, and he became rich. Thousands followed in his footsteps, and failed. Are they crazy? Maybe, and maybe not. Who knows. Whats my point here? I dunno, chose carefully. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 07:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read it, it's interesting stuff. 

You are up very late or really early depending on where you live. But who am I to judge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 06:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This map only includes websites and services frequently used and prevalent in the English-speaking world. Websites like Baidu were not included because of that.

Read the map man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 05:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to be happy all the time. Or the ability to know where any object or person is at anytime. Handy when I want to find my phone or friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 03:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Relevant article](http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2014/01/30/map-of-the-internet_n_4697389.html), also, this map was made in 2013. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Map of the Internet [4829x3207] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 03:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
