<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2519</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I was getting confused he was injured in 1941 but 'Kalashnikov decided to design an automatic rifle combining the best features of the American M1 and the German StG44.' - I take your other points though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not definitive. You could describe SS who didn't surrender as 'Nazi resistance'. If they were against the Nazi's used say anti-Nazi resistance - it's the what your resistance movement stands for. you can still say 'there has been Nazi resistance in the area' but again can mean both things, so I choose to use anti-Nazi to avoid confusion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quite a lot of British were killed by V1 and V2 attacks on London so I wouldn't say the damage they did was 'little' 

And the guy who made the AK-47 said he based his design on the STG. He was in a tank crew and he saw how well the Germans used them and it inspired his design  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Season 4 is the worst but I still enjoyed it especially  the Richard and Eli stuff  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting people telling me Nazi military technology was actually inferior to the allies who is right? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 07:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So on a post on the Man in the High Castle Reddit we were debating what a future world would look like if the Nazi's won.

Someone said the idea that the Nazi's were technology advanced was a 'myth' created by Hollywood. While I am not certain they were in all aspects I cited some examples to show how they were superior.

-I said the Tiger tanks were better than the American Sherman. (German tanks are what most American ones are based on today) 

-I said the MG42 generally performed better than the American browning (higher RPM, more portable, easy for a single person to use) 

-I said the STG-44, the worlds first assault rifle, was better for assault manoeuvres than the BAR. (Also what inspired Kalashnikov design for the AK-47)

-I said the panserfaust, the RPG predecessor, was better in combat for being operated by a single user and it's portability than the M2 bazooka. (Debatable I know)  

-I said the Nazi's rocket program (missiles and planes-V1 and V2's) was unparalleled and many of their scientist would be driving forces behind the Soviet and US space programs.

-all cited some of their wonder weapon programs like night vision etc 

I was told all of the above is inaccurate. I am a third year history student and a really good UK university, I would be very surprised if everything I said ^ wasn't at least up for debate rather than being told Hollywood has brainwashed me into thinking the above is true.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 06:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Panserfaust could be used by one man and didn't need a second operator like the M2 how am I wrong? Maybe you should go and ask if the Tiger was better than the Sherman - it was  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 06:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is it wrong ? Tiger tank was fucking notorious for being one of the best and hardest to destroy. STG-44 was known for how well it worked in an assault situation  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 05:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't believe i nmagicccc... ONWARDSSSSSSS!!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 04:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> During the 1800's Germany was largely left out of the land grab of Asia and many other parts of the world (I guess partly because it wasn't unified until 1871)

Germany motive in WW1 was about created their Empire in Europe - so maybe that's why it's relevant to Price-the ambition to create a greater global empire for himself? Thus growing his power  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 04:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a lot of the technologies that were essential to the war-Germany was ahead. The Tiger tank was years ahead of its time and completely outdid all the other nations tanks. Their weaponry was superior - MP-40 was better than the Thompson, Stg-44 was better than the BAR, MG-42 was better than the Browning. Panserfaust was better than the M2 Bazooka-sure America were ahead in some respect in a lot of technology but Nazi's were superior than most of world in a lot. Rockets, missiles, rocket planes were all unmatched.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 04:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Germans had a couple of prototype that ran on rockets essentially including suicide craft - so I definitely believe they would have that kind of 'rocket plane' but could have developed normally too. It impossible to tell but Nazi's were far ahead in many respects - I take your point about they getting rid of a lot of scientist and Hitler didn't focus on the A-Bomb - theirs was nowhere near complete by the end of the war  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 03:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah well I am a student and cba to cook loads and hate my flat mates so try to stay away from social areas of the house when I can-but that's why I can't understand why my weight stays the same  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found something interesting about 'White Rose' when looking into anti-Nazi resistance in Germany </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 03:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Of the Germans who opposed Hitler's dictatorship, very few groups openly protested the Nazi genocide against Jews. The "White Rose" movement was founded in June 1942 by Hans Scholl, a 24-year-old medical student at the University of Munich, his 22-year-old sister Sophie, and 24-year-old Christoph Probst. Although the exact origin of the name "White Rose" is unknown, it clearly stands for purity and innocence in the face of evil. Hans, Sophie, and Christoph were outraged that educated Germans went along with Nazi policies. They distributed anti-Nazi leaflets and painted slogans like "Freedom!" and "Down With Hitler!" on walls of the university. In February 1943, Hans and Sophie Scholl were caught distributing leaflets and arrested. Together with their friend Christoph, they were executed four days later. Hans's last words were "Long live freedom!"'

I know White Rose is a character and not FSociety but find it interesting that the White Rose movement is an anti-Nazi/Govt movement led by a man and his younger sister (like Elliot and Darlene). It may not be linked at all but interesting nonetheless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 03:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Wolfenstein the Nazi's control the world in High Castle Japan rule Asia  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 03:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I strongly disagree with you - the Nazi's were technologically advanced in many ways - who had the best tanks; which today's modern tanks are based on? The Nazi's. who created the worlds first assault rifle which the AK-47 is based on? The Nazi's. who invented the first proper rockets/missiles? Who invented the best portable rocket launcher?The Nazi's. who had developed night vision? Who knew smoking gave you lung cancer? Who had the best weapons? Who had, generally, the best vehicles? Apart from America (who they were a head of), militarily the Nazi's were far more advanced than any other army in The world.

Guess what scientist were instrumental in creating the US and Soviet space programs? Yep the Nazi scientist captured after the war.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 21:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh so because some people you know didn't know what it was that means that everyone doesn't know one of the longest reigning Empires in history - got it!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah okay well you arnt horribly overweight if your pretty tall  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay so lunch I have a wrap and a bag of crisps. Dinner I have chicken breast and mash potatoe or rice. I know it isn't the best but by my standards it's pretty good - I don't want to make my life depressing and I hate veg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So apparently the cap being raised to 50 will not count your current score... so many hours wasted!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 08:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Running a lot and eating pretty well-nothing seems to be changing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 07:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm not out of shape or anything. I'm 6'2, 200Ib and have very muscular legs with pretty muscular arms too. I've been running intensely for about a year and a half- Last six months I've been doing 10km's (in about an hour) with a 25km cycle after 4 times a week. Not really seeing a difference in my appearance or weight-I have abs but I'm not shredded. I have also been eating pretty well for the last 3 months-any insight from anyone ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 07:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How tall are you might I ask? I'm guessing you are quite small if 300 pounds is a big risk to your health?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 07:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weight lifting is really good if you're pretty overweight-when you slim down you could do more hardcore cardio but walking diet and things like weights is a better place to start  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 04:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're young who gives a fuck just go with it freaking Mormon  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 04:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are jerking off way too hard if it hurts on the second go haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 04:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's your best friend so no don't cut him off for saying silly things about you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 04:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cmon I'm not a bad influence I only got us arrested ONCE!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 04:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol this is serious nothing - he pushed your shoulder big deal. If it ever gets worse than yeah your should worry. My gf has slapped me before, emotions can make you violent. I know this pc culture makes you think whenever some slightly touches you you should get away from them but this is hardly anything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 01:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got a higher score then anyone on the other team and I was playing support - how did I not play the objective!?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 01:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My point that he was crazy I'm not really mad he won just don't understand the gloating when I got a better score and KD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 20:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do not send that !!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 20:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happens to me sometimes (if you wank a lot of might have caused this) just go until your tired  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 20:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mmmm it's a tough one. I had a lot of close female friends and my old gf used to get pretty jealous like I was interested in them^ I did some of the stuff he's doing but I never liked them. You might be overthinking it sometimes it's just nice to talk to someone from the opposite sex who isn't your partner-if he starts being inappropriate then he's interested but it seems innocent   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 20:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gym shuts at 10pm I get there at 9pm for an hour run. All treadmills taken up I pass the time doing other things-waiting. Two girls finally step of their treadmills at 9:45-they had been walking on it for 1:20mins.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 20:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With her teleporting power Ciri would win  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 20:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah man I'm waiting on this screen just in anticipation. Episode VII levels of excitement when this game came out. Abit disappointed with the story but it was such a ride! Gameplay made me feel so much  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 22:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay so I'm a person that is genuinely sick or Cod. When I first saw the trailer with that awful David Bowie cover and saw the name it seemed like a parody. When I actually played the game I loved it and thought it had the best story in Cod since Black Ops. It's a shame that this is the one people finally said enough too. Now Sledgehammer will probably takes IW place which sucks because AW is one of the most generic and bland shooters I've played.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 18:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it's Mafia 3  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 18:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^ this comment is everything what's wrong leftist outrage. The guy just explained why someone might steal from a children's hospital - out of desperation-and says we should help fix problems of poverty and drugs. And then for some reason you jump straight to that he's justifying stealing from children. No he's taking a step back and explaining why it's happening it's a lot of difference from condoning it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or get rid of bullshit micro transactions wholesale!?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get out of there quick there is way better out there for you!!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guy who came first on the winning team messaged me asking if I was 'mad bro' and telling me that I was shit at the game. I came second on the other team -look at the scores! Trolls are deluded! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 13:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hehe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 04:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gay meme  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 04:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah okay thanks for the tips will do! Any advice for getting better at blocking?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm sure I'm not the only one but this game is hard!!!! Any tips to get better? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 04:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This game reminds me a lot of a traditional fighting game which I suck at rather than a third person action game. My reflexes are just not quick enough anyone got tips for a newbie?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 13:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'The Pacific was an afterthought to the US during WW2'are you insane!? An afterthought? The guys who bombed pearl harbour? So Landing on Iwo Jima with 5000 casualties in the first day was an afterthought!? Lots of people signed up to fight the Japanese for attacking America, heck the US didn't even join the war until they were attacked.

'Meandering' I think it's the point of the show-island hopping means there was no straight forward goal towards Japan. They capture Peleliu at great cost only for MacArthur to not even use it as a proper airbase-there was no clear cut route to Japan like there was Germany </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 07:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BoB's can't be that much of a triumph if you don't know what that^ means... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 07:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Show her Resident Evil 7 and Witcher 3 and ask 'is this childish bitch!?' - seriously though she is the one with the problem you haven't done anything wrong  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 07:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you should have told your girlfriend that you were bisexual beforehand!? Probably a big shock  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 07:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be a man  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hamstring recovery - can it be done wrong? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 04:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like a movie!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay I don't really have any help for you but I absolutely hate people like that. I go to the gym I work hard at it and I never talk about it. What's the point? I do it for me not to show off - some people need to learn this-i hate naturally skinny girls doing what your friend is^ just so annoying  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the nature of the war in The Pacific or 'island hopping' lends to a more disjointed narrative. Band of Brothers and the Airborne was literally 'drop in France move to Germany one day' so there is a clear narrative and path for the soldiers. I guess it kinda reflects each War well  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Band of Brothers Vs The Pacific - which is more entertaining? Which depicts war better? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 23:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've just re-watched them back to back. Band of Brothers certainly does have a better narrative and more memorable characters overall, but I feel The Pacific is a lot better in really showing the horror and randomness of war. Characters like Snafu are amazing and the morality of war is a lot more in question in this series I think. The savagery of the fighting in The Pacific makes it a harder watch and to me it's a lot more impactful. What do you guys think?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 22:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listen I get that, most of us have exes and stuff but you can't let it affect you that badly when you seeing someone else. She should end it with you if she does stuff like that because she seems like she isn't ready for a new relationship  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 21:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the point ? Me and my GF are abit older and going out about the same time - marriage is nowhere in the cards we haven't even finished Uni yet-you're so young just wait and see how it pans out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 21:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If she is still hung up on her ex after a year I wouldn't bother with her - only gunna cause more problems for you in the future </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So angry that genuinely good shows get cancelled and most garbage gets renewed indefinitely  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I love that one sets the mood  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Help! They're behind me!!!' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 07:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Help! They're behind me!!!' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 07:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 03:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never skip a theme song of any show. My favourite ones are Daredevil, Sopranos, Boardwalk Empire, Vinyl and this shows one is also pretty good  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 02:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump's press secretary told a massive lie about the crowd sizes at Trumps inauguration and then said period at the end haha     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 22:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Martyrdom has been prevalent in Arab/Islamic society for centuries it didn't just randomly start in the 1980's. suicide bombings on the rest grew from the 80's onwards but they were hardly the first.

Plenty of Islamic extremists during British and French colonial rule of the Arab world who would martyr themselves by carrying out suicide missions-this goes back to the time of the Assassins in the crusades  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 22:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was good until about episode six then got stupid. Whoever wrote for Luke in that show was so bad he was so cringey  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could the soldiers of the Empire of Japan (During WW2) be considered religious fundamentalists/extremists ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay this doesn't look good and after Luke Cage I'm not confident everything Marvel puts out on Netflix is going to be awesome like DD and JJ were.

That being said the premise and the story look interesting just feel this trailer is kinda bad. (The music wtf!?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't you love it when two periods/figures of history share a cool link? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 16:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 06:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you Amish!? It's more weird you never had coke do you live in a bunker or something ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 04:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many single mothers have raised great kids without having masculine figures? Didn't one of the most popular presidents in recent history (Obama) only have his mother!?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 04:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay so not everything can be changed but just say to him it's an important moment and he's meeting your parents just wear something appropriate and not shorts and a SnapBack. Jeans and a tshirt isn't too much to ask is it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't mind a new Witcher story set somewhere far away from Velen with a new school.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jealous both are great but B and W is the best  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it very accurate in depicting a medieval world despite it being a fantasy one- it a world of shades of grey there are no black or white moral decisions which is why I think a lot of people got shitty endings on their first play through a  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dam I only have about 300 I think need to read the books though!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Witcher soundtrack always makes me want to play it more  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha 'no it's it the best ending. Period.' Sean Spicer 2k17  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha that's how I feel - I love a lot of other games but none as much as the Witcher  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No not yet I will have to though - I read the metro books which were translated from Russian and they held up so gunna give Witcher a go  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah me too I just wish they update the original and bring it to consoles !  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard the books are very different to the game - like Gerald and Yen are not really as the same  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah fucking love that moment such a great reward for finishing the DLC  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha yeah the resistance blew up one building how can you like them (say some fans) where the Nazi's exterminated millions  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 01:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a game the same way a foot soldier can't just jump into a tank and start driving it or throwing ammo at someone instantly replenishes their stock.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 01:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think he's called SGt Stone he's always chewing gum and is Leckie's officer. The last you see off him is when he tells Leckie to get a stretcher for Runner when he gets injured  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone else constantly think about this game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 00:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've beaten the game twice, hearts of stone twice, and Blood and Wine once. I think about this game a lot and I've first played it on release day. I remember playing 12am-6am for 7 nights consecutively and just absolutely loving every moment. I finished my second play through in the summer choosing a different ending (empress one aka the best one) and just can't stop thinking about it.

My god that last moment in B+W made me so happy, I wish I could play it again for the first time. Now I just remember all the cool moments, great characters and just the feeling I got when playing it. Sorry for my rambling but I guess many of you guys feel the same! Just wanted to share it is the greatest game of all time - no debate  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't 'tis' birch spotting is great in BF1 they have redone it so if you can't see them your team can't either  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never realised but he is quite a major character in HBO's The Pacific (World War 2 series) it's really good you should check it out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is a cunt  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slavery predates the US government to! Let's bring it back  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 21:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a really good question and a really hard one - I guess it's really going against a narrative.

Take ISIS yes crazy fundamentalist Islamic terrorist group-and that's what they are to most people. 'Crazy' Muslims who hate the west for...? Most people don't know. The 'other side' would be to show why ISIS exist - both sides are 'true' in a way but more often than not the other side is not shown  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 16:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah man MG15 can't get used to that one - bar storm is good but needs to be reloaded too much and if I wanted long range I'd use the Huot  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 16:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to think so too- come over to optical !  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 13:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah okay I get that, in a way it's kinda of true - Britain and the European basically divided China up between themselves and used puppet rulers to maintain control - I guess the Communists did strengthen China at a huge cost-so framing it in this way makes it seem like it was worth it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lewis Gun optical - am I the only one who uses this gun? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 13:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I am about to hit my 7th star on this variant (have six star on the low weight) and I can't remember ever being killed by it when someone else is using it. I've been killed plenty by the other Lewis Gun's but never this one - is it not popular ? Does anyone else like using it ? I feel it's the best gun in the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 12:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that is a good one would definitely be too good to linked it to other immigration and refugee policies - have you seen the recent stuff about Jewish refugees to US who were turned away in 1939 only to be killed by the Nazi's when they went back? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 00:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have done the opium wars at Uni but what's the main significance of it today? Didn't Britain gain Hong Kong after ? Or (Singapore I forget) so why is it still relevant ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 00:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be more helpful if you could link it to events today but other than that any q's about the last 500 years would be good  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 22:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm starting my own podcast on History/Politics-can people ask me some good questions to respond to? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 22:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm starting my own podcast/Radio show at my University. I've always believed in balance and showing both sides of the story (Trump supporters, Islamic extremists, Marxist etc) - so would people please give me some good questions to respond to because I will mostly be doing it alone and would like something to bounce off-thanks!

(I'm not asking anyone to listen just to give me some questions)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Starting a podcast - can people please give me some good questions in relation to UK/US politics? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Legacy of Vietnam on Jimmy Carter's foreign policy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm writing my dissertation on this subject. I have plenty of primary sources (cabinet meetings, speech transcripts etc) but I need books on it to get different historians opinions-can anyone suggest good books in general about Jimmy Carter? Or US Foreign Policy Post-Vietnam?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 16:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't wait for ArsenalFanTv  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 04:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just go with it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who wants to see Boba Fett make an appearance in The Last Jedi? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 23:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I was thinking they could make a small plot point based around him to re-introduce him. I think they should get Temuera Morrison to play him probably with grey hair, a beard and an eye-patch (thinking Deathstroke). Maybe he doesn't work for the First Order like he did the Empire because they want him because he's he last template for the Clones. So he could help the Resistance (give them information whatever nothing major) What do you guys think?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Putin is a master of foreign policy - yes Trump is easy to manipulate but he is doing a great job (not a morally good thing but good for Russia) in destabilising the West and making it turn on himself. His alliance with Turkey is a master stroke considering that they shot down a Russian plane a year ago and their Ambassador was shot and killed their a couple months ago. Trump has no clue he is being played and Putin is loving this anti-NATO talk. 

Fuck Republicans man, literally scum of the earth and Trump is no different.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it technically is your wedding but isn't the purpose of wedding food for the guests to eat-can you not have vegan food and traditional food ? I don't really see the harm but your mum has gone crazy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 15:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Captain John Smith (yes the one all Americans learn about in school) pretty interesting life and accomplished a lot. A shame he wasn't remembered fondly in his time  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 15:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of these things aren't actually real save that he was the king of Israel. So no it's all a legend ^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 15:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Winston Churchill surely!? Absolutely incredible life can hardly believe all the different things he did and how active he was. 

Eisenhower comes close as well.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The speech in Africa was my favourite bit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 23:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh well if you read it in Wikipedia you just be right despite me doing a history degree on colonial India...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 23:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finished it (aired in Europe last year) and really liked it. Lenny is a great character and the show has some beautiful moments  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How don't I explain it to me? Gandhi was killed by Godse, a Hindu nationalist-they exist look it up  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 14:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes faith helps people through suffering etc - don't agree with it but like an ideology of any kind it gives people something to hold onto  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 14:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah so welcoming African-American Civil Rights leaders to his home in India is racist 

I earlier acknowledge his racism when he was young in South Africa - which was a symptom of being in the British empire in the 1890's. yes racism is bad but you can't criticise it as harshly when your talking about the morality of 120 years ago and the fact he actually reverses this by his death is good enough for me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 12:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hindu is a much an ethnicity in India as it is a religion see Hindu nationalism  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 12:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you read his own writing ? Where he basically mixes the two together ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
