<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3901</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 15:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **[Definitely](https://i.imgur.com/dvynmPa.jpg)** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 15:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks a bit like **Kubo and the Two Strings** meets **[The Book of Life](https://i.imgur.com/dvynmPa.jpg)** to be honest.

I see **[flying particle flowery stuff while a dude plays guitar](https://youtu.be/8-fkmRaX0Wk?t=2m7s)**.
The only thing missing is a giant flaming bull made out of thousands of bull bones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 15:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't look that new to me after I've seen **[Book of Life](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NBw5YScs8iQ)** though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 15:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see **[flying particle flowery stuff while a dude plays guitar](https://i.imgur.com/dvynmPa.jpg)**.

The only thing missing is a giant flaming bull made out of thousands of bull bones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 11:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there *anything* that is 'universally accepted or supported'? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 11:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about Thich Nhat Hanh then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 11:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the other hand the Bhagavad Gita teaches:
"Consciousness is when we feel the suffering of every creature inside our own hearts."

Not sure what Eckart Tolle's quote says about empathy but to me it sounds rather *reductio ad absurdum* in a way that may be helpful to the individual in dealing with the suffering of others, but not so much helpful to a society. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 11:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, let me correct that - *in all the Buddhist philosophy I've come across*.

I've given specific examples elsewhere in this thread.

I also went on a ten day Vipassana retreat taught by S. N. Goenka and there was definitely a notion of "don't cultivate craving or aversion towards anything because it's impermanent anyway".

If the notion of not getting averse to an unpleasant sensation in the present because it's ultimately impermanent isn't future-oriented, I'm not sure what is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 11:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went on a ten day Vipassana retreat taught by S. N. Goenka and there was definitely a notion of "don't cultivate craving or aversion towards anything because it's impermanent anyway".

If the notion of not getting averse to an unpleasant sensation in the present because it's ultimately impermanent isn't future-oriented, I'm not sure what is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 10:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I linked to the context in the opening post - there it was about Eckart Tolle's "The Power of Now".

And I've heard similar ideas by Thich Nhat Hanh:
 
*"Mindfulness is to always arrive in the here and the now."*

and

*"The past is no longer there, the future is not yet there. There's only the present moment."*

are both quotes from Thich Nhat Hanh ([from this trailer](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ne7-wnnWqFY)). Not sure how 'orthodox' his teachings are, but that's a notion I seem to get quite a lot from secular western Buddhist teachers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 10:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *"Mindfulness is to always arrive in the here and the now."*

and

*"The past is no longer there, the future is not yet there. There's only the present moment."*

are both quotes from Thich Nhat Hanh ([from this trailer](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ne7-wnnWqFY)). Not sure how 'orthodox' his teachings are, but that's a notion I seem to get quite a lot from secular western Buddhist teachers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 10:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over in /r/Finanzen I was recommended **[this book](https://www.amazon.de/Souvern-investieren-Indexfonds-ETFs-Privatanleger/dp/3593504545)**. Maybe it can also be of interest to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Only the present moment is real" vs. "current suffering isn't real because it's impermanent, i.e. will be gone in the future" - a philosophical inconsistency? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 09:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I asked this question **[here](https://www.reddit.com/r/Meditation/comments/5zdvp5/quote_from_the_power_of_now_eckhart_tolle/deyamx5/?context=10000)** but would like to pose the question in /r/buddhism as well and maybe get an answer:

I can't exactly wrap my mind around how it makes sense to focus on **"the power of now"**, and in all Buddhist philosophy it's always about "the past is no longer there, the future is not yet there, there is only **now**"... yet the main tool to reduce suffering is to focus one's attention on the impermanence of current suffering, i.e. on the fact that at some point *in the future* it will no longer be there.

That's a bit of a contradiction, isn't it?

It seems a bit like picking and choosing what actually matters. If the present is pleasant but people cry about the past, or are anxious about the future, Buddhist philosophy tells them to focus on the *now*, and that neither of those other tenses are currently real.

If someone is feeling pain in the present moment, Buddhist philosophy tells them to focus on the awareness that *at some point in the future* that pain will be gone.

I do experience the benefits of meditation, and I appreciate Buddhist philosophy as far as I'm familiar with it - but I can't quite make sense of this seeming contradiction. It seems like Buddhism promotes being either present-oriented or future-oriented in one's consciousness depending on what's more convenient at the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 09:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the funny part about this kind of philosophical inconsistency... I can't exactly wrap my mind around how it makes sense to focus on **"the power of now"**, and in all Buddhist philosophy it's always about "the past is no longer there, the future is not yet there, there is only **now**" ... yet the main tool to reduce suffering is to focus one's attention on *Anicca* and the impermanence of current suffering, i.e. on the fact that at some point *in the future* it will no longer be there.

That's a bit of a contradiction, isn't it?

It seems a bit like picking and choosing what actually matters. If the present is pleasant but people cry about the past, or are anxious about the future, Buddhist philosophy tells them to focus on the *now*, and that neither of those other tenses are currently real.

If someone is feeling pain in the present moment, Buddhist philosophy tells them to focus on the awareness that *at some point in the future* that pain will be gone.

I do experience the benefits of meditation, and I appreciate Buddhist philosophy as far as I'm familiar with it - but I can't quite make sense of this seeming contradiction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bauer Unser - TRAILER </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 08:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 08:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was in German, French and English - depending on who was talking and what country the characters were in. The film takes place across France, Belgium and England, with the two main characters (Marx and Engels) as well as some other characters being German.

I saw it in Berlin where the French and English parts were subtitled in German. I expect the English release will have the German and French parts subtitled into English.

The film covers them writing *The Holy Family* but doesn't really pay attention to Stirner.

Reviews are mixed but I enjoyed watching it and recommend it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bauer Unser [2017] [Trailer] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 08:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 08:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By that logic you could however also dismiss any and all empathy for the suffering of people starving, getting slaughtered or raped as just being needlessly sentimental about *"a fraction of a dynamic process, a molecular dance"*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bauer Unser - TRAILER </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bauer Unser - TRAILER </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bauer Unser - TRAILER </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there any field that still makes money that doesn't change *at least* every few years?

My own (rather technical) industry changes every year, if not every few months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 22:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **[Relevant.](https://www.reddit.com/r/LateStageCapitalism/comments/5z7dgq/so_uber_asked_me_for_some_feedback_as_a_driver/)** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 22:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **[Trailer for "The Young Karl Marx"](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Dz-1BLjQlHo)** in case you didn't see it when I posted it here the other day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just got out of the cinema after watching "The Young Karl Marx". The director Raoul Peck also made this documentary: "I Am Not Your Negro" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 22:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 10:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bin gespannt auf das Buch - werde es lesen, sobald ich mit meiner momentanen Lektre fertig bin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 08:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. I used the word "expat" because "immigrant" has negative connotations for many, and most of my international friends (including many "brown people") refer to themselves as expats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thomas Straubhaar: Das Grundeinkommen ist nichts anderes als eine Steuerreform </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thomas Straubhaar: Das Grundeinkommen ist nichts anderes als eine Steuerreform </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  and you're even implying that ads must be inherently misleading which is definitely not true

Nowhere did I say that 'ads must be inherently misleading' - but advertising definitely fits the definition above about "*especially of a* **biased or** *misleading nature*". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good to know, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **[Indeed.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=S9X_gxD9YYg)** ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand that it may be easy for people to put me in the *crazy teenage edgelord* basket for voicing criticism against commercialisation but I think that's more than just a little reductive.

I want progress just as much as the next guy - but plastering every building with massive advertisements isn't *progress* in my eyes. On the contrary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And calling advertisements "corporate propaganda" sounds like satire to me, it's just over the tipping point of edginess to the point that I cannot take it seriously anymore.

They are *literally* that. Not figuratively "literally" but *literally* literally.

**propaganda**

 *prpand/*

 noun

information, especially of a biased or misleading nature, used to promote a political cause or point of view.

Check out the BBC documentary **[The Century of the Self](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DnPmg0R1M04)** (2002) to learn how around the mid-20th century, Edward Bernays changed the word *propaganda* because it had become negatively associated with war, and invented the term *public relations* for the advertising industry to use instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because once you're *grown up* you've stopped caring?

I don't know - I'm almost 30 and I'm still bothered by blatant advertising taking over more and more of previously much less commercialised neighbourhoods.

Maybe I should *grow up* and buy a Mercedes to calm me down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's a [false dilemma](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/False_dilemma). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is for every single person - man, woman, senior or child. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed - it's *"Schuld"*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm German and that still sounds utterly ridiculous to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 19:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **[How about some nice re-distribution of wealth? From the bottom to the top, of course.](https://twitter.com/ChrisOffner3D/status/841287956832931842)** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 19:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **[Edward Bernays happened.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DnPmg0R1M04)** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm happy to hear that, cheers for your comment. :)

Haven't been to the VFX Hangout in a long time... maybe I'll join one of the upcoming ones. The last Berlin CGI meet up I went to was probably Faux Images. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **[Pretty much, yeah.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cLJAXu5OD-c)** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Berlin, Germany.

Lots of advertising and signs are in English in Berlin. It's a fairly international city. Lots of expats here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perverse, isn't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They just want to provoke them so they see owning a Mercedes as a challenge to 'live up to'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, you help the world by helping yourself first. Many people will go to great lengths explaining what is wrong with the (external) world and what should be done to fix it but few will admit how their own practices and (internal) thought patterns contribute to larger problems. You have to be the change you want to see.

I agree in theory but how do you *not* contribute to the larger problems in a system like capitalism? The more I try to avoid engaging in and contributing to exploitative or environmentally destructive causes (through my work) the more precarious my living situation becomes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mercedes is plastering building facades in Berlin with the slogan of their new [campaign](http://www.adweek.com/brand-marketing/mercedes-benzs-most-ambitious-marketing-project-yet-is-all-about-what-it-means-to-grow-up/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only time I ever worked on a commercial was doing 3D graphics for the aforementioned video - and I despised it, and am still frustrated and ashamed that I indeed had to contribute to *attempting to influence the decisions of others for their own commercial gain*.

I felt shitty already back then about it, but at the time I absolutely could not afford to turn this job down.

You may call me a hypocrite for calling this corporate vandalism out but that doesn't make me wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of **[this quote by Banksy](https://i.imgur.com/m9wTMpS.jpg)**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of **[this quote by Banksy](https://i.imgur.com/m9wTMpS.jpg)**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of **[this quote by Banksy](https://i.imgur.com/m9wTMpS.jpg)**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ich wrde mir ja wnschen, dass sich mehr Berliner darber empren, wie solche Werbung ihre Stadt verunstaltet - und dann eventuell eine Initiative wie in **[So Paulo und anderen Stdten](https://www.theguardian.com/cities/2015/aug/11/can-cities-kick-ads-ban-urban-billboards)** angestoen werden knnte.

Durch Stillschweigen und Ignorieren kann man die fr politische Aktion ntige Stimmung gegen solche aufdingliche Auenwerbung kaum befrdern. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 13:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Verstehe ich. Kommentare wie *"Ach stell dich nicht so an, ist doch nicht in echt passiert", "war doch nur im Internet" etc.* wrde ich auch ablehnen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 13:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ich war vor ber zehn Jahren mal zwei Wochen lang in New York City und will dort nie wieder hin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 13:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ich glaube, das ist nicht ganz wortwrtlich zu nehmen.

Meine Interpretation ist metaphorisch - das Internet kann keine realen physischen Beziehungen *ersetzen*. Klar kannst Du Deine Oma via Facebook fragen, wie es ihr geht - aber es ist nicht dasselbe, als wenn Ihr persnlich beisammen wrt, Euch in die Augen sehen knntet, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 12:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would prefer it they went with *"Mercedes. It's time to go fuck yourself."*. Would take a bit more time and paint though I suppose.

But Friedrichshain isn't rebellious enough anymore I'm afraid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 12:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Verdammt! Jetzt hast Du mich aber erwischt. :D

Wiztigerweise steht genau vor dieser riesigen Mercedes-Werbung ein kleines Audi-Plakat. Kann man [hier](https://i.imgur.com/empxzBc.jpg) nur sehr klein rechts erkennen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 12:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your condescending bullshit aside: Unfortunately one does not get to decide whether one's environment is plastered with corporate propaganda like this or not - and neither does it matter whether one is in their 'target audience' or not.

I still have to walk past this shit every day on my way to work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 12:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I am genuinely pissed off about this and am not affiliated with Mercedes in any way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 12:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I worked one month on *[this one](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mgixGp8U0nI)* back in 2015 - that was the only time I did work for Mercedes.

I'm impressed you would stalk someone on an [external forum](https://community.foundry.com/discuss/post/1072325) to find this stuff after reading a Reddit comment critical of a corporation. Quite the investment, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 12:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fully agree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 12:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Du lieber Himmel.

Willkommen in /r/HailCorporate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 12:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fr Dich ist solche Werbung also eine "Aufwertung" des Stadtbildes?

Finde ich schon etwas pervers und zynisch, muss ich gestehen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 12:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gerne. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 11:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't think it's ugly and brazen as fuck to have a corporation vandalise your street (this is Warschauer Strae near Frankfurter Tor by the way, so not Potdamer Platz where one can *'expect'* such blatant advertising) telling you in giant letters to "[Grow up and buy a Mercedes!](http://www.adweek.com/brand-marketing/mercedes-benzs-most-ambitious-marketing-project-yet-is-all-about-what-it-means-to-grow-up/)"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 11:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Das war ein Zitat aus Louis CK's [Neujahreswunsch](http://uproxx.com/tv/louis-ck-new-years-app/):

I wish you all a Happy New Year. Meaning that I wish for your New Years Eve to be happy. Its hard to wish hundreds of thousands of people to have an entire happy year. Thats a lot. That feels greedy and hopeless and also some of you might not deserve a happy year. Everyone deserves a happy moment or day now and again but a whole happy year I would wish on maybe eight people and four of them are terminally ill children.

Also please remember that the turning over of one year to another is a mental construct that bears no more weight than the things that keep us apart and in competitive categories as human beings. Time is not moving. Youre not losing or gaining ground. Youre not separate from them anymore than youre separate from your own umbrella. Its now, were us and this is here. If youre in pain, this too shall pass. If youre in luxury, this too shall pass. Ask an old lady how shes doing. *The internet is not real.* Draw a picture on a napkin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
