<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3191</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: Reggie White and Lawrence Taylor were al ost team mates and I will never get over it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 23:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is the player your team passed on in the draft or free agency that you most regret? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 16:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giants: passed on Reggie fucking White in the 1984 Supplemental Draft. Reggie White/Lawrence Taylor/Harry Carson/Carl Banks on the same fucking defense and before free agency. 

Fuck you George Young. I know you helped us get 2 rings, but this is uforgiveable.Here is a video on it.

http://www.giants.com/news-and-blogs/article-1/How-Reggie-White-almost-became-a-Giant/38d78fd2-08e6-4c11-ac2b-354771eabf33
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump is delaying Winds of Winter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 03:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps victory is going to delay Winds of Winter another year... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 03:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prediction: Giants over the patriots in the Superbowl. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 01:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giants and 49ers met in the playoffs 5 times between 1981-1990. Any other teams have something like this happen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 00:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giants/49ers met 5 times between 1981-1990. Winner won the superbowl 4 of those times.

Following guys were in all the games
Players: Lawrence Taylor, Joe Montana, Ronnie Lott

Coaches: Bill Parcells, Bill Bellichek, George Seifert

Might be more assistants

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giants fan: we have a good scouting report thread up. You are welcome to chat with us there. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 23:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should Bowles get another year? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 14:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im not a fan of only giving a coach 2 years. Jets won 10 games last year. He has trash at QB. Revis has fallen apart. He seems to have lost the team with Richardon and Wilkerson skipping meetings. I dont know. 

This is supposed to be a terrble qb draft. So not alot of hope there. I see the jets making a run at Tony Romo. Alot of teams will even with his injury history.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is the gay bomb the greatest weapon to use against terrorism? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 04:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the gay bomb the ultimate weapon against terrorism? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 03:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should the US build the gay bomb? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 03:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should we build the Gay Bomb? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 03:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should we build the Gay Bomb and use it against ISIS? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 03:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Scotland votes to secede should the US hel our closest ally by showing them how we deal with traitors? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 03:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If it turns out you were a long lost heir to the UK crown and named King or Queen of the UK what would you do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 03:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Given how divisive the US election has been, lets have a reverse Revolution, bring back the Queen, and give her supreme power over the US. Then we can look at royal baby pics and be happy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 03:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How far removed from the Queen of the UK can you be and still be considered part of the royal family? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 03:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Queen had 4 kids. Are all of her grandchildren considered part of the royal family? What about her younger sisters grandchildren?

How far removed are you to be consider a noble/peer?

How far removed are you to get supported by the government?

How far removed from the queen are you before you lose tax exempt status and be allowed to vote? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where will Tony Romo be playing next year? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 15:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bet is on the Jets. Its a Jets thing to do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need a Trump supporter to service a group of Democrats on Election Night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 05:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need a Trump to service a group of Democrats on election day. MM4W </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 04:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pugh Sprained knee... And Cruz getting xrays on his foot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 20:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck. Pughs scares me. That could be a season ender. Anything with cruz scares me. All the giants have on offense is Eli and the 3 receivers

Update: cruz had an xray. Kept out, but no word on what was seen.

Update 2: cruz xray is negative. Has low ankle sprain. I think that is the less severe kind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does your country do better than the US? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 02:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giants Fan: How good are your injured D Tackles? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 20:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> short injury report:

Hiw big of a drop off is it to lose Allen Barbre.

DTs Taylor Hart and Bennie Logan are gametime decisions. Are they both starters? How good are they? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wish I could write a book people would want to burn. It is bulk sales and it keeps books off the resale market </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 03:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would off a book burners discount. Print books with scented pages so burning them is like burning incense, i would sell smores kits and have recipes on my website for roasting over the flames.

I would even have an app writte to burn kindle versions of my book , show the  flames, and permanently remove the book from kindle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How did the expansion of the universe overcome the force of gravity? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 00:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It is time for the Queen of England to step in and clean up the Brexit mess. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 13:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at where trusting the British people got her? Time for the Queen to knock some heads. Stick some people in the tower of Lindon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question for Raiders fans: Following a team that might leave? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 23:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a Giants fan. I forgot to check in on the Rams last year. What is it like to root for a team that might move? Will you follow them if they go? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People hit Comcast, etc... Data caps... What are you downloading? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 21:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Does space shrink when you travel close to the speed of light? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 14:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any word on Will Beatty? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 20:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Newhouse has been injured. Line is terrible, Beatty has had time to get in game shape. If he is healthy and can still plsy shouldnr he be out there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do people think about 3-4 bi weeks in the nfl? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 20:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To entertain us during the buy week tune into Redskins radio to hear the fans cry! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 18:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can get Sports talk 980 online. Redskins fans cry like bitches after games like this. Its alot of fun to listen to them call in and cry about it.

The gems are the old farts who talk a out how great they were in the 1980s... They are so old and bitter.

Lots of skins injuries too. They will cry about that too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does Donald Trump say to Melania after sex? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 14:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am just visiting my daughter. Ill be home soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump is so fat and ugly that a porn star was offended that he only offered her $10,000 and use of a private plane for sex. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 03:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which human is actually a robot? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 18:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is a likely plot twist. I have no idea who it might be. This plot twist was in Battlestar Galactica too. Who do you think it is?

I have no idea. I think it would be more interesting if its either someone who works at the park or the older guy dressed in black walking around with a scalp( cant remember thape character name) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for good genre blogs that skip the constant drama fights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 16:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very little to none political and drama fights. So nothing like Scalzis blog or Correias blog. Nothing that talks about politics or world view of certain books. I just want bligs that talk about the genre. I dont want a blog that declares itself a feminist SF blog or one that declares itself a "classic"( typically code word for conservative) blog.

Nothing like file770. Last few years its loaded with stupid drama fights.

Occassional posts about politics and such are ok. But most should be about genre stuff.

2 examples of stuff I like. Both of these give detailed discussions by people with all world views and just talk about the books.

Wertzone
Elitist Book Reviews </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why is it taking so long to fix the water issue in Flint? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 02:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is wrong with Nat Berhe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 23:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Concussion protocol should not take this long. Have the giants said anything about why he is still out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If the democrats take over the Senate who will be the majority leader? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 20:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harry Reid is retiring. Who is the likely leader?

Also Bernie Sanders would run the Budget committee. Who would run some of the other major committees? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How do American Tariffs work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 20:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My understanding is that NAFTA is a free trade union that eliminates most tariffs. My understanding is also that the TPP would do the same.

How do American tariffs work ? How high are they? My understanding is that states that have 'most favored trade status' have lower tariffs than those that dont. 

When people try to sell the TPP they state that tariffs are so low already signing this agreement will not have any negatives on us. We are gaining access to markets. If that was the case I do not see why other states would lower their tariffs on our goods in a free trade union. What do they get out if it? If out tariffs are already so low that it does not impact trade than there is nothing in it for them.  

What other trade restrictions other than tariffs would the TPP changed? 

This question is about more than the TPP. Its about how American tariffs work and hiw much they would be reduced with the TPP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do the colors that we see map to the wavelength the way they do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 06:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pacing on this ahow is really slow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 04:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big SFF fan. Having trouble paying attention. The pacing is slow. The big idea is robots start killing people and rise up. I hope they dont string it out for the entire season where at the end they still barely start wasting people.

Its kind of the big idea of the show. Hbo has had other SF style shows like the leftovers that were really slow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has the field in London improved? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 00:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last time I remember the Giants playing London it was a swamp. They barely got out of there with a 3-0 win over a terrible team. The Rams are a running team and the Giants are a throwing team. Bad field conditions favor the Rams. 


I know its a 6:30 AM game for the Rams. Just asking about field conditions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: What are the technical details of the Hybrid Cloud? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 01:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been a DBA for almost 20 years and I work for a hosting company that had started supporting the cloud. Basically the cloud offerings are VMs. They get deployed fast with software. User picks what they want on a web page. Pays. The software copies a VM that meets their needs and changrs some settings( such as memory, cpu, storage) are changed in the VM. VMs will have licensed software such as oracle, mysql dba, app servers, etc... They get what they paid for. All the servers are connected to SANs for storage( mainframe that just managers hard drives) .

For more advanced setups, the technical staff gets involved to customize stuff. 

I have seen references to google and Amazons "hybrid cloud". All I see on the web is dummed down bullshit that doesnt tell me anything useful. There is no real technical specification for cloud. Most companies use virtual machines. Can someone provide details on what is meant by "hybrid" that is technically detailed? 

This forum isnt for really technical posts. To keep the mods from deleting this please keep the first level response kind of readable to non techs. They can always followup wirh questions. Ill reply with more technical questions if I have them.

Looking for technical responses. Not the marketing garbage with silly acronyms that are all over the web. Its seriously difficult to find anything useful through the bullshit.

Any techs on here work on hybrid clouds?

Mods: this is a little more detailed than we normally get, but I asked that they not go too far down in the weeds in the top thread.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will Ted Cruz withdraw his endorsement of Donald Trump and if so when? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 08:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: If Mike Pence were to move to the top of the ticket, will Republicans have to get more signatures to change the ballot in each state? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 01:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wonder what other Trump comments NBC has on file from his years on the Apprentice.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 00:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does the UK keep the pound stronger than the US dollar? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 20:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this makes imports cheap, but it makes exports very expensive. Also the UK is very susceptible to offshoring knowledge work because eastern Europe is close to them in timezone and India is closer to them in timezone than the US. A pound that is very strong encourages encourages pushing inowledge work out of the US.

I have an mba in finance so please go into technical details. I work in IT. My company has a group in the UK. Some of the people there tell me the IT job market is weak because its so easy to move jobs to eastern Europe due to the timezone difference being so close.

Not looking for political fights. Please mod that out. If anyone can recommend a book on uk currency policy( i cant read a really academic book mba in finance is only moderately technical) or links to websites I would appreciate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How do you challenge the Chines exchange rate without the use of tariffs which most economists say will hurt the US economy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 19:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The US floats its currency. So the US basically accept ps the market exchange rate for the dollar. China does not float their currency. Its exchange rate is set by the Chinese government. The US appears to accept whatever rate the Chinese give. If I am wrong on this please advice. I have an MBA in finance and one thingwe learned is that China buys so many US treasury bonds because it needs to push the currency surplus with the US back into the US in order for their set exchange rate to work. 

Is it possible for the US to float the US currency against countries that float their currency and refuse to accept the exchange rate dictated by China? This would likely require congressional legislation right?

I do not think tariffs are a good idea. I think its too generic of an option and too broad of an option to work. I am wondering if there are subtler options.

I have an mba in finance, but I dont work in the finance profession. If someone can also recommend a books or a website too that would be helpful too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why does the UK keep the pound exchange rate so strong? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 19:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News hosts Hannity, Kelly trade testy exchanges over Trump interviews </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 18:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any scifi forums with less promo posts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 17:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the posts on this sub and /r/sciencefiction are promotional links. There really are not alot of discussions by fans. /r/fantasy is primarily diacussions by fans and alot of authors show up. Anyone know any good scifi forums that primarily discuss scifi? Not looking for gaming forums. Primarily for books and some movies, etc... Not looking for 1 universe or author.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Donald Trump is elected president what are some come to Jesus moments he will face? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 04:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the easiest way to get banned from a subreddit of your choice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 02:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Al Gore to Campaign for Hillary Clinton in an attempt to get Milenial Voters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 02:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How much does it cost news agencies in the US to conduct presidential polls and how big is the sample size? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 01:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would it take to get you to have sex with Donald Trump? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 20:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: With antibiotic resistant bacteria on the rise, how come the US government is not giving grants to research new antibiotics? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 02:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A recent Washington Post article cited a study saying thst 21% of CEOs are psychopaths, so which ones do you think are psychopaths? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 02:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was it like to live in Rome circa 550 AD after the population collapse? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 17:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it just the church officials and servants who were left? How did markets work with such a small population? Did the bulk of the population live in one small area? Also the old Roman ruins were not as ruined did people just move into some of the large buildings? I have had trouble finding information about why life and the economy was like in this period. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I flew into space and was not orbiting the earth, but just hovering would I still feel earths gravity? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 05:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Trump was president during the 2008 Financial crises how do you think he would have handled it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 02:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giant Injuries: lets keep it in one thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 20:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like always injuries are mounting.

IR: vereen 

Darian Thompson update: not as serious as giants worried. No ETA on return. On ipad so its hard to post links.

Robert Thomas: ill. They must like him. He has been sick since he got here without details. 

Any update on DRC or Eli Apple?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does the nfl have rules about how the 3rd qb and emergency qb can be used? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 00:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the emergency qb goes in my understanding is that the other qbs cant go in. I think if the 3rd qb goes in the other qbs cant go back in. 

Why? Also how did they handle this for the wildcat?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do teams split revenue for merchandising with players? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 23:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried googling it, but cant find it. I just read that Odell Beckham is giving $500k in Jersey revenue to charity to help people in Louisiana rebuilt football fields after the floods.

Curious how the cut works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How old was the Bloody Nine at the end of Red Country? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 04:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I finished the book I figured the new series would be about the Bloody Nine back home. Joe Abercrombie wrote in his blog that the new series would start 30 years in the future.

I read the books a while ago. I dont remember exact ages. I pictured Logan in his mid 30s in the trilogy. If I remember correctly there was a mention of Logan at his home for 10 years, but also mentions of how old he was. Given that he could still function physically, I imagine him late 40s.

That would put Logan near 80 in the new series if I am correct. I dont think he will be dead given the setup at the end of Red Country. This would pit Logan in the old folks home stabbing seniors for their pudding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How come the universe did not collapse into one giant black hole right after the big bang? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 03:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mykkele thompson put on IR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 23:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think its the second year in a row. He may be done. So two defensive backups on IR. Not huge now, but a little nerve wracking if guys ahead of them go down. As a giants fan , i gave learned to be paranoid about injuries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If an NFL head coach isnt calling plays, what does he do during the game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 03:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly dont know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neither the Seahawks nor the Rams have scored a TD this season. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 02:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marshall Newhouse was in a boot, Is Beatty Healthy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 23:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So Newhouse got hurt... was it Beatty who replaced him? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 23:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rashad Jennings is the leading rusher in the NFL over the last 5 weeks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 18:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have a web page links. It was on Giants 1st and Ten on Giants.com. He has gained 507 yards over the last 5 weeks. Ok its over 2 seasons. But he has averaged 100 yards a game. Its been a while since the Giants had much of a running game. Hopefully he can stay healthy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mods: Can we get a link back to the main NFL page? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 18:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see one. Its common to come here and also want to read the NFL page and then click on other teams pages.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best radio station shows for giants analysis? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 23:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not local to New York. Most radio stations let you download them off the internet.

Which shows are best? Are there certain days where the shows do more interesting analysis? 

I listened to so e WFAN stuff online recently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Permatreat says I owe another $50 on a treatment that they did t charge me for. Can this go to collections? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 01:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cant find my bill. I paid $500 to get my house spraid for termites. I just got a call from Permatrest saying I owe another $50.  The guy who did the work is not going to leabe and say I will bill later for the rest. The guy who called me could not figure out why I owed more and will get back to me. My next door neighbor arranged this for the two of us, she paid $500 too. We got the same service.

She has used them before and said we should straighten this out. So not real worried. However, could they send this to a collection agency and ruin my credit?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giants fan... Your hate of the Cowboys brings a tear to my eyes! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 18:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am humbled by fellow NFC East fans in their joining us in the Fuck Dallas Celebration! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 17:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fuck dallas posts in the main game threads from Eagles and Redskins fans bring joy to my eyes. We all bond in our hatred of the Cowboys and their fans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you are feeling Blue go to the Cowboys subreddit and enjoy the misery. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 02:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Retired professional athletes, what is it like when a new season starts and you are not out there? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 19:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to get every NFL game for free on the internet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 03:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: why are men far more likely to get prostate cancer ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 20:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lena Dunham on Angel Dust sporting a strap vs. Odell Beckham drugged Bill Cosby Style </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 05:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stupid question. How do I add a Giants flair? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 18:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did Will Beatty play last night? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 19:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any word on how he is doing in practice?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much gold to raise from 1500 - 1600 gold levels? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 19:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone know the base cost? or an estimate? Trying to figure out if I need to get more artifacts before i start aqcuiring units to raise my gold levels. I can get to 1500 and unlock the final quest. I am at around 1950 Enhancement levels. I am sure others know the game REALLY slows down at this point. I only get enough medals for 1.5 enhancement levels (though my runs are about 1 hour and 15 minutes, I can't revive 15 times/day). So the extra gold levels may help more than playing roulette with artifacts. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More Guild stuff released on the Korean server? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 19:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone in my guild was in discord and was told that more guild stuff has been released on the Korean server. Anyone have more information about what is being released? Have pets been released on the Korean server? What are they like?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When do Biters start attacking and biter evolution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 19:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have had the game for a while, but this is the first I spent much time on it. I don't know how many days in I am. I dont see a way to keep track. I have a mod that shows 'biter evolution and its at 11%. Does this mean when biters get stronger? This is based on pollution? So at 100% they get stronger? 

When do biters start attacking? I think its related to pollution. I have a mod for monitoring that. 

I have 1 radar running and I dont see any biter bases on my map. I used 'regular' for biter bases. I think in .12 I would get biters nearby, but now I don't see any. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mining slow and inserters missing items on the belt when they go to grab them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 01:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I turned off my mods and its still happening. I am using an electric mine. The mining appears to be much slower than in youtube videos. I tried using this console command (default appears to be 1000 from the wiki) to increase mining speed. 

/c game.player.force.manual_mining_speed_modifier=2000

Nothing happened. 

Also, my inserters are not able to grab things off the belt unless the belt is backed up. They move too slow and they literally miss the items on the belt. 

This is in the latest .13. I had a bunch of mods running and I just disabled them all. I have not played in a while ,but I don't recall this happening in .12. 

Has this happened to anyone else? 

I just loaded another game up that I had saved from .12 and the game seems to be running normally.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Sean Murray crazy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 03:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does the game hang for anyone else? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 23:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont have a low end PC. The game isn't totally hanging. I can't move. It looks like the game is still running, but I can't move for a couple of seconds. Its happening more and more often. Does this happen to anyone else? IS it a setting a I can lower? I have some mods installed. I dont have any overhaul mods. 

I do have some mods that collect data. Not sure if that is it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you upgrade Mining Drills? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 00:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw this on the tips when you log in. You can fast rebuild. How do you upgrade a coal based mining drill to an electric drill?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> issues using cfan with Factorio .13+ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 15:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have not played since .12. I uninstalled .12 in steam and added the experimental branch for the latest release per the instructions on Steam. 

I got the newest cfan.exe

https://github.com/trakos/CFAN/releases

cfan is showing a bunch of mods installed from when I was using .12. These mods are NOT in my mod directory. 

Inside cfan I do File - Factorio Directory: 
C:\Users\RYAN_SSD1\AppData\Roaming\Factorio

I look in the /mods directory. Nothing there. Yet I see a bunch of 'check marks' next to mods. I try to uncheck them then apply to remove them. Cfan shows they were removed. I then try to check and install. Says they install. I dont see any mods in the /mod directory. I remove them again from cfan.

Close cfan and reload. It shows the same mods installed with a checkbox. I have deleted and redownloaded cfan. 

I can't figure out what cfan is reading to make it think these mods from .12 are installed and I can't figure out where its copying files to. The json in my mod directory does not show any mods installed either. 

Next test I did was use the in game mod installer to install mods  (its a pain compared to cfan) and installed a couple of mods that were not in my .12 version. Installed fine. Shows installed in game. Exit game. Launch cfan. Does not recognize these mods as installed and still shows the old mods installed. 

CFAN must be looking in the wrong directory. I can't figure out where or how to change it. If I can figure out where I can use a shortcut to redirect CFAN. 

any suggestions?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A patriotic satanist could say God Damn the USA and mean it as a compliment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 16:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Reddit existed during the life of Jesus what would it be like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 04:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stupid 4th Down Call in the Billls Game. Reminds me of Old Eli </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 22:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3rd and short. Go long. Incomplete punt. This used to happen all the time under the old offense and it made me pull my hair of my head. 

4th and 3. Go long. Incomplete. The cornerback on beckum was lined up deep on him. It was obvious. Eli should have audibled to a quick pass to Beckum. He takes 2 steps. Eli hits him. 

I absolutely hate this go deep crap on 3rd and 4th and short. It used to happen all the time and almost never worked. Occasionally it work, but most of the time it wouldn't.

Yeah I know preseason, but its such a stupid idea and its frustrating to see this again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we add a link to a Tower of Trials critical unit post to the FAQ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 20:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many more medals do you now get above Stage 4000? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 20:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shikatsu seems to have changed his build. I think he used to use alot of Faeries for support so was going for build. His new build appears to be for attack power. This may be in response to the new Lich Unit and the increase in medals above stage 4000. He may also have 12 senior dark archers ,so he can afford to lose the speed bonus from faeries/priests/drummers, etc... 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rank 608 (676 m Medals) and going up. Looking for Guild that attacks 2x a day and people fight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 20:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: Talked in Guild chat. We have 5 active members. One is the co-leader. We all attack twice/day. Medals are between 93m - 676m (I am the highest). However, we all attack alot. 

Anyone want to take on 5 people who attack twice/day? You can boot inactives. 

One of my guild leaders vanished. So we only have one. He can't be on every 12 hours to get us 2 attacks a day. We only have 5 guys that attack regularly. Its not getting better. This is costing me alot of Guild Coins. 


1. I fight in all wars
2. I gift 5x/day. 
3. I buy perm double every week. I have premium shop bought out. I am pretty active. 
4. I have spend a few gems on Guild Wars so there should always be people for me to beat. 

Looking for:
1. Send Guild Name and RANK. so I can look you up. I won't join a new guild. I need to see that you have attacked twice/day for a while. I can tell from wins. 

2. Dont care if you lose alot when attacked. This is good. Encourages people to attack us which means more guild coins. 

3. Dont message me with a new and/or inactive clan. I wont join. Leaders must attack 2x/day. 

4. I dont care what level people are. This doesn't matter at this point. I am going up fast, but all that really matters is that I am active.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> how to call hoverbike for the second time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 15:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used a hoverbike on one planet to test it out. I left it and kept exploring. I figured since I had the controller I could call it again from another planet. I put the controller in a slot and use it. Nothing happens. I dont get a message saying the hoverbike is broken. 

Do I have to actually remember where I left the hoverbike and go back to it to repair it? I dont get a message saying the hoverbike is broken.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone understand the new trans unit in timeshop change? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 14:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like 6 star units that are trans in time shop give 5% medal buff. The update also says 

"If every unit is also in the timeshop you can also get additional medal buff. "

I dont get this. 

They use 6 star as an example. You get half the medals for others. I just added a t2 battle knight and saw thst it gives 5% medal buff per level. So is this half in the timeshop? 

So looks like 
You get no medal buff for senior and trans t1


You get smaller buffs by senioring and then trans tier 2-4 units and it gets cut in half in timeshop. 

i dont know which tier is best to t1 for medals in terms of cost.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Are people an invasive species? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 03:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> why do i keep dropping my gun? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 23:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weaposn dont get destroyted. but i have lost 2 guns and a flashlight. I found one on the ground. I am doing something to force it to drop without realizing it. I have it in a quick slot . since they cant get destroyted. where do they go?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> good inventory management mods? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 17:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inventory is a pain just like in terraria. It would be nice if we could craft with items nearby in chests. picking up items and moving them is a pain. I have an inventory mod where i can rename chests. Is there anything else? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have an epp breating unit equipped, can I breath without air? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 17:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I looked at some starbound videos and when you can breath without air, you have an O2 symbol in your inventory screen. I have my epp breahing unit equipped but I dont see it. Some of the videos were older, b ut they show the O2 on your ship and air is present. I dont want to test this and die. can i breath without air or should i have the O2 symbol in my inventory? if so what am I missing?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has Anyone the main plot and gone to the center of the universe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 03:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some people like the game. Those that do.... Have you followed the main plot and gone to the center of the universe? Is it interesting? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> is there a minimap mod? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 19:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am playing on steam. I did not see any in the steam workshop. Not having a minimap is pretty annoying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to change ship teleport locations? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 18:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I googled it. How do i set a marker for teleporting back to my current location? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the rewards for levels 32-34 of tower? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 19:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wo en of reddit... If women were physically stronger than men what would you do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 16:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are all of the new artifacts in the artifact shop? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 13:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought 5 of them. 2 of them have not come up. Trying clear out before using honor coins again.

Has anyone found these 2 in the artifact shop?

No 125 secret book 2
No 123 assassins boots </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Enhancement request: please change guild war to 2 attacks a day instead of every 12 hours and let others declare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 17:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guild leader is inactive. The coleader has to live and cant come on exactly at 12 hours to attack. This is really tedious and leads to burnout. Couple of simple changes

1. 2 attacks in a day. Just reset when dungeons change. 

2. Let other positions in the guild declare war. People come and go. People go in vacation. There isnt any harm in guild war. Its to your benefit to be attacked alot. The leader can always demote people who do stupid wars. Just keep a log of who declared. 



Make it less tedious for guild leaders. I dont know if the developers read this. If you agree please send an inquiry in game to elkhor. If many people make the same request, it increases the liklihood of a change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do knights work in work in tower of trial? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 17:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Says 20% in battles. Tower is in battle tab? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: how much would the metal in Michael Phelps Olympic medals be worth is they were melted down? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 01:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best combo of support to max speed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 18:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know artifacts matter too. I have a griffin rider and a druid.

5 senior priests
3 senior drummers
2 senior faeries

2 dark archers to swap in. You obviously want 10 eventually.

Max elf skill so with faeries i have a 40% chance to skip a stage.
When i hit for 5x i typically do 70 stages in 2 minutes. Noticed a big increase when i picked up one of the new artifacts that improves human engaging time.

I am now topping off about 3270 and its about a 2 hour run. Time varies based on guild battles, dungeons, etc... 

I dont care about strength. Anyone done any spreadsheet work on calculating speed? What mix of support units are best. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone get to 1500 gold levels? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 17:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have 7 6 star artifacts and the rest 5 star. All my 5 star are maxxed. When i max my 6 star wirh open gold the final quest will still cost 50s which I will never reach in a run. 

My core 2 tops about 1355 in a run. I can go a little higher if i want to focus but its not worth it. My runs last under two hours. 

Does anyone have enough 6 star artifacts where they get the final quest open and top off gold levels at 1500? I now go up only 8 enhance per run. So i go up stages rather slow. Without more gold levels this may drop to 1-2.

It takes a long time to aquire honor coins unless you buy all the packages each month and even its a total gamble. 

Anyone get to 1400 gold levels? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any word on pc modding support? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 16:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on the reviews it looks like they created an interesting engine, but the game is lacking in UI and depth. This is something that modders can really enhance. I am sure people will mod the game, but more support means more and better mods.

Any words on whether they will open up the API like bethesda does? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for Youtube Hard Science Fiction/Futurism channels </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 02:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not looking for channels that discuss books and movies, but channels that discuss science elements in them. I found one that is terrific called 'Isaac Arthur'.

https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCZFipeZtQM5CKUjx6grh54g

There are a number of these for fantasy such as Metratron, Lindybeige, KnightErrant, and more. Does anyone know of others like this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> game runs much faster on newer devices </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 18:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ipad 2: Would take me 8 hours with double bought to get to stage 3000.

got the game running on a new iphone. its down to 2 hours 15 minutes. 

Damn. ewverything runs faster. I think some of us who ran out of time in tower of trials and others couldnt understand why may be because game is running on slower devices.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When to molpy down the first time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 18:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading the wiki, it looks like you dont get good bonuses until you have a bag of holding right? This seems pretty far into the game for your first run. Should I wait for that and then molpy down as soon as I get it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you get more diamonds for besting higher level enemies in guild war? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 18:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tower of trial critical units </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 17:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am stuck on floor 31 of round 42. This is the farthest I have gotten. I dont have the diamonds to senior the units I see people say you need to get passed this level. 

This isnt for right now. But I am looking for advertising ce going forward on what to prioritize. What are the most critical units to senior and tier for Tower of trial.


I have a t1 skeleton warrior. I see a t3 is critical. What other senior and trans units do you use alot? These are longer term goals for me.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Enhancement request to guilds: show how many members and make it easy to declare war on the same guold again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 16:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a lower tier guild... Frustrating when guild leader declares war and there are only 2 members. You cant tell how many members. You have to participate to get rewards. 

Also keep a list of who you fought and how you did do its easy to declare war on the same again.

If you like these ideas please send an inquiry and recommend them.
 
Please attack my guils Midgard. Rank 388 with 30 members. Level 6 through 33. Easy target </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If the US Presidential Election is tied 269 to 269 in the electoral vote, the House of Representatives can pick anyone they want including someone who is not running for president. So who do you think would be president? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 01:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trumps older kids remind me of Uday and Kusay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 20:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you received a wish from a Genie for some sort of wealth what would it be and how do you receive it in a way that the police don't come after you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 02:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why will the universe eventually go dark in galaxies and galaxy clusters are under gravitational attraction and the expansion of the universe does not affect them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 18:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Midgard recruiting anyone who can attack every day. Also we are weak. Low level. Please attack us. Easy win. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 19:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to stay in the S battle group? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 18:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I finished in the top 50% of the S battle group and dropped to the C group. I received 600 honor coins and diamonds which is the reward for top 50% in the S battle group. Per in game help you are supposed to drop it only if you fall below top 50%. What happened? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Griffin rider vs. unicorn knight in core 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 18:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> T2 druid. Dont have gold to get him to 1400. Tops around 1350-1360.
T1 unicorn knight.
Senior griffin rider. Have units to t1 him.

How much better is a griffin rider vs. a unicorn knight assumimg artifact, etc... Bonuses are the same. One of the units i need to trans griffin, i need for transing unicorn knight.

Another consideration is that i need a big foot to get mu uk to t2. When i used my only big foot to tier my druid this lead me to not get very far in the tower of trouble. Big foots magic resistance is critical in many rounds. So one considerstion would be in not tiering my uk until i get 2 bigfoot so i can go up farther in tower of trouble. Honor coins are slow to come by. Not sure if this is the best strategy. Been playing a month and only got 1 big foot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please attack my guild Midgard. We are weak. Easy for you. We get coins for losing. So good for all of us. Currently ranked 152 and level 3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 17:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do high level players transcend battle drummers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 16:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made it to the S battle group. I noticed a bunch of players with transcended drummers. When you senior a unit it the skills get better. But i thought when you trans its the stats that get better and you get a 10% bonus to medals. Drummer is a support unit. I noticed many trans drummers without medals in them.

Do they trans them for the medal bonus?

Also how do you get battle drummers? I hVe never seen it in the buy units. Been at this 3 weeks. I looked in the data sheet, but i dont see a list of things you only get from roulette or vouchers?  I see succubus mentioned in a post that says only available in roulette. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best build to quickly get medals? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 19:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not best for pvp or dungeons. I have only played for 3 weeks. I would appreciate it if people with more experience would evaluate.
I think its some combo of the following. I dont have the units to test, basically the fastest way to climb stages.

I typed this on an ipad. Likely has typos. Its hard to post from an ipad. I apologize. I will edit from my PC tonight. Please forgive typos and grammar for now.

Get the skill to level 5 that lets you skip stages. This means you skip 30% of stages.

1. Core 2: 1 magic and 1 weapon 5 star. See tier post in faq for recently recommended units.

Do not put medals into support units so you can freely swap them out for dark archers just before you revive.

2. 10 senior dark archers without any medals.Each one lets you start at 5% of your revived stages. So if you get to stage 3000 and revive with one senior dark archer you start at 3000 * .05 = 150 stage. With 10 senior dark archers you start at 50% or stage 1500.

Since you will skip 30% of the stages on average you need to do 1500/1.3 stages or 1153 stages to get back to stage 3000.

3. Remove them and swap for some mix of senior priest and senior fairy.

Senior priest: 5% chance that every 10 levels you get 2 minutes of 5x speed. So if you have 10 that is a 50% chance so on average you get it every 20 stages.

With the skill that lets you skip stages 30% of the time on aberage you need 20/1.3 = 15.38 stages. 

With 5x speed i tend to do 21-24 stages in 2 minutes. So on a average i should akways be at 5x speed.

I dont know if artifact and unit bonus that make you faster at double time are more effective at 5x time.

4. If you have 10 seniors faeries each allows you to skip 5% of stages. So with 10 its 50%. If you have the skill thst lets you skip 50% of stages you will skip 80% of the time.

So 1500/1.8 = 833.33 stages. So on average you have to do 833 stages instead of 1153 stages.

Assume the person has permanent double either bought or from videos.

Not sure what combo of priests/faeries is best. Will depend on whether your speed bonuses from artifacts and units scales to 5x.

I have only played about 3 weeks. Can somwone with more experience let me know of any errors? Or a better build to do stages faster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guild points </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 19:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any use for these yet? I see we can use guild coins in the shop.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In game VIP message working for anyone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 18:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enter my email. It never sends an email. It also permanently shows as an unread message. Is this eorking for anyone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tower of trouble, best units? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 17:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Various questions from someone at stage 2420 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 20:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you do dungeons with a core 2? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 17:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think if you do a core 2 that means only transcend 2 units right? It doesnt mean eventually put medals in them and senior others right? With a core 2 you will have dungeons without a unit to hit troops or boss. So you will cap out lower.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do Eiropeans have white skin? Doesnt dark skin protect you better from the sun? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 07:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> some protesters at next weeks republican national convention may be just be people hunting pokemon go. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 03:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are you required to stop if protestors move to block a highway like they did in Oakland? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 18:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do people value signatures? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 17:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skill vs. an Upgrade ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 18:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which items are skills and which are upgrades?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Screen cut off on right on ipad 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 16:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Game forces the screen to be longside. On the right on workshop screen it appears cut off. I think the cost to buy stuff is on the right because i cant see the prived </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What ammendment would you add to the US constitution? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 04:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for good sff blogs that focus on the genre and avoid politics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 17:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know about file770 which is basically a news agrigator and wertzone which has outstanding contact. Elitist book reviews is m favorite fantasy review site. Pats fantasy hotlist is good too.

I prefer blogs that do more than book reviews like the wertzone. For example wertzone has a hige series of posts about the history of epic fantasy that are very good.

I want to avoid sites like whatever.scalzi.com which is loaded with tons of political content. These types of posts tend to inevitibly get posts with recommndations that have tons of political content. Please dont. It looks like most author blogs have tons of political content so I prefer if they are not mentioned. I dont care if the person who runs it is known to support certain political views, but the blog should focus on the books and the genre. For example the guy who runs file770 is clearly a lefty and the guy who runs Elitist Book Reviews used to work for Larry Correia. Both sites focus on content(yes I know posts on file770 lean left). 

I dont want sites that just talk about left leaning or right leaning books or talk about perceived injustices on all sides. Just about content. Elitist book reviews has positive and negative reviews of books by people who are known to be righties and lefties.

Authors do not send me IMs pimping your blog or your book...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
