<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2947</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 09:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol some of the mods on the subrebbit will remove anything controversial just because they dont like it, its ridiculous, Majority are nice   do their job, but theres a couple mods here who rwt/ involve themselves with fishy characters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 04:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgot about amulet of the damned buff for each barrows items. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Only 5 Balance changes since 2015??? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 04:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weapon balancing that we currently need -

Dragon longsword - Damage buff

Ballista - Damage Nerf

Armadyl crossbows (special attack) - Damage buff

Dragon mace - Accuracy Buff

Abyssal blugeon (special attack) - Maybe Poisons other players?

We've had about 5 balance changes since 2015 most of them barely affecting the weapon - 

Crystal halberd buff

abyssal dagger buff

blowpipe nerf

Abyssal blugeon buff

Heavy Ballista Nerf - You can 1 tick now   still stack all the damage, It needs a damage nerf.

- I know 07 has a small team, But pvp is dying, noone can deny that.

Maybe if the current meta was changed, More people would start pking more? just a thought, post your thoughts.





 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 03:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow you put in a lot of work into this, sorry for being skeptical at first, cant be too careful from all the scamming ads r2007 reddit will get sometimes.

( was literally one a couple weeks ago asking for your runescape username - email   current address,(website also grabs your ip) to win something.)

Anyways you might have better luck Reaching out to streamers on twitch to promote this. Goodluck with the site :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 02:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems sketchy, Will try it out aslong as i dont have to download anything nor Enter my login details. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 15:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google : "insert time zone here" Time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
