<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2257</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 07:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> extraterrestrial titties </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 06:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I mean, I think she wanted to get you between soft pillows if you know what I mean </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 04:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean a girl looked me in the eyes once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 04:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you wait long enough, you'll see some fireworks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 22:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *hears I LOVE MONSTER FUCKS yelled at top of lungs* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 20:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is why I said very limited contact, not no contact </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 20:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> please tell me it wasn't a duck porn montage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 19:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jello with rice
Mac'n cheese with rice
Nutella with rice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 17:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL that at one point, a perfect scenario was described as being 5/7, and not 10/10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 08:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> USA! USA! USA! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 00:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a rather complex criteria, but it is for the long term survival of the human race:

100 million will contain the highest IQ's on earth
100 million will score the highest on some arbitrary fitness test
100 million will be selected as a result of superior genes and their the fact hat they aren't prone to anything
100 million will be the highest rated on some arbitrary beauty scale.
100 million will be just good wholesome people, filled with kindness and compassion, used to balance out the egos of the first for categories of people.

AUTOMATIC EXCEPTIONS: 

No one with chronic conditions 
No one with STDs
No smokers
No other addictions
Anyone over the age of 60
The entire state of Mississippi. Fuck those guys.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 23:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American life expectancy is definitely more like 80... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 23:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well we know he's not dead yet because he did run for president this year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 20:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that all these memes are compiled into one place is fantastic. 5/7 would totally recommend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 17:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The computer has grown too powerful and is now picking its own leader instead of following the algorithm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 17:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A long, pointless existence filled with suffering and a vain search for meaning. Eat Arby's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 13:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is a Reddit historian an actual thing? If so, we're employing you, and you start on Monday doing research at precisely 9:00 AM. Don't be late. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 03:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is Obama a prime example while trump wouldn't be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 01:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No but you can become president as a result of idiots </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 00:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely a 269.69 point boost in IQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 22:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was more looking at it as a contrast between European ideals and how it shapes their policy ideals and the Americans respective ideals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 22:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to think the original comment was a European(given the pounds) and this comment was an American. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 21:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump has no idea what in the hell he is doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 17:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Raging bonerz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 17:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hello sir. Do you have time to talk about the teachings of Jehovah's Witnesses?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 17:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This especially applies if you live in Moscow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] You were on the ISS when the Yellowstone supervolcano exploded. After 9 months of very limited contact, it's time for you to come home. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 05:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You were on the ISS when the Yellowstone supervolcano exploded. You arrive back to Earth 9 months later to find a very changed America. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 05:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If there was one moment in your life that you could just erase, what would it be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ACDC- Shake a Crab Leg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coloring Book by Chance the Rapper- innovative cross between gospel and an uppity rap style </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely the orgasm. Can anyone else imagine joyless sex like those fucking cows have </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how dare you make such a shitty pun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's with the half? Did the mailman have to wipe his ass or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Looks like I picked the wrong week to quit sniffing glue." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bro he just said he wanted to upvote your sister. Don't take that shit from him, beat him up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 21:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's funny how it shifts, because in 2012, all the Royals had to do was win but now I guess a World Series warrants the caveat that they must score 5 runs and win now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 07:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obligatory explanation that this was my dad, but one of his coworkers got convicted of embezzlement, went to prison,  and is now fittingly the finance manager at a car dealership. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 00:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like you were being rather *dramatic* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 00:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Clark! Your jizzers full!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 00:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every one of us enjoying a final shredded animal sandwich from Arby's as we die a lonely, painful death, fading into the unalienable blackness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 00:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even better, a naked portrait of Melania Trump makes it into the Louvre </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 19:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, more like Fidead Castro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 18:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Astird </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 08:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or the state, but that suggestion is coming from one of those 3 million people who live on farms dispersed throughout the state, waiting for a tornado to come terrorize us </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 08:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Raul, what is this Black Friday the Americans celebrate?" Fidel asks as he looks through the newspaper

"Well it's a special day Americans have just to buy things."

*dies from capitalism overdose* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 00:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know you've probably lived a dirty lifestyle when your pornstar ex-gf is pissed off that you didn't tell her that you had AIDS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 00:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anthony Weiner, and, well, his weiner </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors who weigh themselves before and after a Thanksgiving feast, what is the single greatest weight gain in a day you have ever recorded? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 08:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 23:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Depends where you are. Depending on which college town you are in, places just glance at your ID(almost always fake) and let you buy it or let you into the bar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 23:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that leads into another thing, is that there are select laws that so many people ignore and even the police begin to ignore, like the drinking age in certain aspects </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With their song Black Beatles at #1 on the charts and their extremely topical song Up Like Trump, sign my petition to get Rae Sremmurd to perform at the Presidential Inauguration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 07:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 21:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> give candy to young children </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 23:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an immense appreciation for this after binge watching Brickleberry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 17:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hello Santa, I'm here to claim my eternal place in hell, and I am willing to sell my soul to do it."

*Jesus Christ what are they putting in these kids cereals today*

Hoping I had misheard him, I told him to repeat what he said and tell me what he wanted for Christmas.

"I already told you Santa, I want to claim my place in hell for eternity, and you are the man to do it.

*Wow, this kid's really not kidding. I'm getting too old for this shit.*

For the previous 28 years, I had been the Santa at Oak Ridge mall, exploiting my plumpness and my unnaturally white beard for good. Besides, ever since the accident, I had to find some way to keep busy.

This year was like any other, with suburban bratty kids pouring in, unabridged by any parental control, set to ask for absolutely whatever their little heats desired. I had gotten some weird requests in the past, highlighted by a kid in 1997 asking for Kurt Cobain's shotgun, but no one had ever asked for an eternal place in hell.

"Ho, Ho, Ho, you seem awful young for that little boy. How about a nice football?"

"No Santa, this is important. I read online that as soon as possible, I needed to offer myself to Santa if I am to be one of Hell's dark earthly overlords when Kingdom of Hell consumes the world in a few short weeks."

*Wow, this kid is straight up wacky.*

"And where did you find all of this information?"

"At my favorite website, www.SantaIsLord.net!"

"Are you thinking of Satan little boy?"

"Oh my Satan! You're right! This all makes so much more sense! Thank you! And yes, I will take that football now! Thanks Santa!"

--------------

Let me know what you think! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 21:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Shit, dude, be careful with that turn," I told the tow truck driver as he backed into the gates of hell, which were surprisingly very narrow.

"Bud, I know you sold your soul to the devil and all, and that makes you think you're hot shit, but trust me, I've done this before," Jesse said.

It was true, Jesse had done this before, and he was the best available. 20 years earlier, he had start his own soul repossession company, and within five years, he was the best in the game. He was a trail blazer in the industry, as prior to that soul repossession was considered a dark art, and because of this many individuals were left on their own to repossess their souls from the devil, who as a matter of fact has very bad credit. So up until 20 years ago, whoever ventured to repossess their soul ultimately failed due to lack of information. The biggest problem, for example, was the size of the soul, as each souls would be stored In a storage container in Satan's exorbitantly priced storage center. In order to repossess you need to tow it out of hell, and this is why I needed Jesse so badly.

"So tell me about your childhood. Were you vey religious?" Jesse asked

"Yes, I was a devout Catholic, and just this once I gave in to serious temptation," I answered semi-truthfully.

"Did you do much voluntary community service?"

"Yes, almost 250 hours per year. I won he presidential service award from when I was in fifth grade all the way until I finished high school."

"Shit, dude, you were a good kid. Usually these souls fit into an 8' by 10' container, but just because of your good  background, it's looking like yours might be a 10' by 20' container. That's pushing the bounds of this truck, but ice got faith that old Bessie'll get the job done again," Jesse said. "So how'd you sell your soul to the devil again?"

"I am an avid musician," I answered. "Although I'm originally from New York, a product of Juliard, I was touring with my symphony throughout the south, and we stopped in Atlanta, Georgia. A dark, shady man came up to me and offered me a gold fiddle for my soul, and considering it was a gold *Stradivarius* fiddle, I complied, figuring this man was an incompetent hobo with a ridiculously expensive family heirloom. Turns out it was Satan himself," I explained. "To top it off, I only got the bow with the guarantee of receiving the rest of the fiddle on a monthly basis, but now that it has been six months without payment or contact, it's time to take back what's mine."

"Say isn't here a song that goes something like that?" Jesse asked.

"Not that I know of, but I am a classical musician so I am rather unfamiliar with the musings of modern society."

"Alright, enough of that mampy-pampy classical bullshit,  were almost here," Jesse declared.

I looked out the window, and to my surprise, instead of seeing endless fire and suffering, I just saw a storage facility next to an abound ones trailer park.

"What the hell is this trailer park for?" I asked.

"No time for that, Satan sees us and he's not happy."

And at that moment, a 20 ft tall demon-man came charging at us, screaming and ranting.

"What the fuck? I made my payment yesterday! You can't take his storage locker! This is my shit! Get out of here! This is my stuff!" Satan screamed.

"I'm sorry Satan, but you have fallen behind in your payments again. We have to repossess your stuff. You know, as always, I don't enjoy doing this stuff, it's just business, man," Jesse replied with an annoyed indifference.

"No, no, no, no! This can't be happening! This is the worst week of my life! If you take this in going to kill myself," Satan screamed as he rolled around in a fit of hysteria while the storage container was loaded onto the truck.

"Look Satan, I know this hurts but quit bullshitting me. The week Jesus rose again was definitely worse than this, and we all know that you can't kill yourself because you're the eternal ruler of hell. Anyway, have a nice day and make sure you keep up on your payments next time," Jesse said.

With that, the storage container was on the truck, so we bolted in down, loaded up and headed out, leaving Satan sobbing on the ground. 

"Wow, I don't know Satan could get like that," I told Jesse while still trying to recover front that situation.

"Yeah it's all in a day's work. You never know how these guys are going to respond. These guys are desperate, and I start to feel bad for them, but I remember that these people have billions suffering down here in their trailer parks of hell," Jesse answered, looking off into the distance. 

With that, we came over the hill, out of the gates of hell, and into the world once again, where Jesse dropped my soul in my driveway, bid me farewell, and left me there. As soon as he left, I got in my car and drove to the church, because I had a hell of a lot of stuff to confess.

--------

Let me know what you think!



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On Jose Fernadez's Impact throughout society, especially after this election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 19:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 18:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bombs, Burgers. Sounds like we could make an animated comedy on FOX. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 18:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, if we're discussing the reverse gender gap, the porn industry also has an extremely high pay gap  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 23:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well hey, Canada might not be home but it's still a great place so I wish you the best man. Thanks for your comments </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 23:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, it's much appreciated. I'm actually from Kansas, I just used some leftover high school Spanish to assist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 22:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew it was a bad side of town, but it had the best bread, so I went there anyway. It was usually a once a week occurrence for me, and after going for a year I had gotten to know the area pretty well. However, today, I learned that there was another part to this side of town.

Per my usual Monday routine, I was satisfying my sweet tooth for the week, picking up a pack of cinnamon rolls. After that, I shifted to sliced bread, which compared to Wonder bread and all of the other processed crap, was incredibly fresh and delicious. That brought my journey to the front of the store, where I picked up a cookie to give to my son when he got home from school.

As I approached the register, the old Venezuelan baker asked in his old, kind voice "Hello Mr. Bush, how is you today?"

His English wasn't perfect, but almost everything else about him was, as he was the kindest person I had ever met. Everyday when I walked in to the store, he would greet me by name with a smile, when I would check out, he would ask about my son, and knowing the cookie was for him, would almost always give me the cookie for free. It was just his family that ran the bakery,  and it had been that way ever since the day that Mauricio Perez left Venezuela and arrived in our city, almost 50 years prior.

"I've been good Mr. Perez, how's your day going?"

"Ah, it's going," he responded with a smile.

"How's your son Mr. Bu-" He was unable to finish the question he had asked so many times, because at the moment a brick came flying through the window above the register, shattering it and the subsequently shattering the glass on the check out counter.

"WHO DARE PLAY THE MULIZZANI FAMILY?"  The voice was booming, and it was approaching. Two large Italian men then burst through the front door. 

"Alright Perez, it's been time. For long enough we've let you slip through our grasp because you're such a nice guy and a staple in the community, but it's about time you paid up. Our services ain't free you know, you bastard."

"I'm sorry, my amigos. I don't have money. Business no been good lately, and I no have much money," Mauricio stammered. He was an old man, and it was pretty clear he hadn't seen a time like this in a while.

"I have $40, here take my money," I spoke up, defending my friend. " I can have more money quickly, I just need time."

"And who are you, you primped up little shit?"

"I'm just a friend," I nervously responded.

"I couldn't care less about what you are, just shut up!" He yelled as the brass on his fists split my face open. Needless to say, I fell to the ground, rolling in pain.

"Ay por favor, por favor, necesito mas tiempo. Need more time, please, please," Mauricio said as he started to panic.

"No, bud, see I need the money right now. And if I don't get money right now, then you and you're friend down there are going to both pay in a different sense."

I was on the ground, approaching unconsciousness at this point, simply hoping a miracle would deliver me from the grasps of these beasts. I needed to see my son. I didn't want to die.

"Ay, I have $100 in safe under counter. If I give, can I have more time? A week and you get all money you want. Please sir, I want to live," Mauricio pleaded.

"Sure give me the money, and I'll let you go for a little while longer. Just don't play me again."

So as I laid there on the ground, bleeding profusely, Mauricio bent over to get in the safe, and a hail of bullets rained through the front door, ripping into the bodies of the Italians, sending them on an express ticket to hell.

"Viva Venezuela!" a voiced yelled from outside.

"Viva Venezuela!" Mauricio called back. 

Immediately, Mauricio was by my side, tending to my wounds.

"In my country, they have a saying: 'No vas a lograr nada sin familia.' The men outside, they are my familia. Now, you need to get to hospital. Here take your stuff and go get help. There is hospital down block. I want to take you, but I need to get rid of these two. Ados mi amigo, buen suerte."

With that, Mauricio picked me up and the old man practically carried me out of the door, hailed a cab, and sent it to the hospital he described. It wasn't until I got in the car when I looked through the good I had originally tried to purchase, everything was still fine, except for that one cookie was covered in blood.

-------------

Let me know what you all think! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 21:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Dear God, why does everyone smile so much?*

I sat there, in the first day of high school, simply scrolling through Twitter. Of course, I had been told by my parents that I was too young for Twitter, but as the organics in the world dwindled, I felt it necessary to connect with them to avoid the inevitable alienation of being consistently submerged in the normals.

It wasn't just the alienation though, it was more that all of the normals were just so *boring.* Because of the desirability of both intelligence and athleticism, the human gene pool was now flooded with kids of those two traits. So me, an organic who just likes playing old school video games, am left by myself, because video games we no longer viewed as 'efficient' and therefore 'normal.'

*This is just awesome. I hate it here.*

I sat there, as everyone filed in, looking at me like an alien, per the usual. I was the ugly one in a sea of genetically perfected faces, I was the dumb one in a sea of genetically perfected brains, I was the weird one in a sea of refined social structures, one that filtered out sarcasm and irony from communication due to their inefficiencies. So there I was, sitting in my new high school class, ironically considering the sense of irony in my life.

"Hello class," my new teacher said with a perfect (but still creepy and hollow) smile. "On this first day back from winter break, we have two new students, Charles and Jeb. Please give them a warm welcome."

With that, everyone in class, in perfect unison, clapped three times, per the usual for any mildly joyous event.

"Alright, Charles will you come up and introduce yourself?" The teacher known as Ms. Smith kindly asked. "Will you tell us some of the sports that you play, where you plan on going to college next year, where you moved from, and the lab that you're from?"

*Oh, God, not this shit with the labs again.*

So as I sat uncomfortably in my seat pondering how I would handle the backlash to not being from a lab, Charles, a perfect human specimen, confidently walked to the front of the class.

"Hello everyone, my name is Charles," he said with a smug grin. " I play football, basketball, baseball, lacrosse, field hockey, and ultimate frisbee, I will be attending Yale next year, I moved from New York City, and I was from Steiner labs in New York."

With the mention of Steiner labs, everyone simultaneously gasped. We were in the presence of a celebrity, a product of the most revered lab in the world. It was no wonder he played 6 sports and is going to Yale next year, that was the kind of product Steiner ensured. With that however, it was my turn to speak, so I uncomfortably got up and shuffled to he front of the class.

"Well I don't know exactly how to follow that one up," I said in an effort to lighten the mood, only to forget that these people didn't recognize sarcasm, so there I was left under the scrutiny of 30 pairs of eyes, all judging me for my unconventional social standards. "My name is Jeb Tree, I play a little golf, I moved from Birmingham, Alabama, and I am an organic."

With that last little bombshell, everyone gasped, but in a much different way than that of earlier. Even the teacher had her mouth gaping open, at which I told her "Shut your mouth honey or you'll catch a fly."

Of course at that point, everyone was confused as hell, both by the joking demeanor and the concept of a fly, as they had been eliminated 20 years earlier by the federal government. To be fair, I didn't know what it was either, I just knew it was a figure of speech my parents used.

So there I sat, a victim of incredible uncomfort, waiting for someone to save me. After 15 seconds, a girl, predictably very beautiful raised her hand from the back of the class, and asked "Is everyone in your family an organic?"

I decided to answer truthfully.

"No, I actually slipped through the cracks. My older brother, George W. Tree, was also designed in the Steiner labs, but there was something my parents felt the missed in him, so they decided to try me out as an organic baby."

With that, the class once again fell silent, and I quickly shuffled to my seat, longing to relinquish myself from the limelight. Class flew by after that, as I had essentially retracted into a box of self-loathing, allowing myself to block all surroundings. The bell rang to signify the end of class, and everyone filled out, but I still sat there, continuing to shut myself up in my box of self-loathing.

"I'm an organic too."

I looked up immediately, startled. It was that beautiful girl who had asked the question earlier, offering that she too wasn't perfect. 

"I really loved your jokes. I'm sorry, you probably thought I was a normal, I've been told I'm very very pretty for an organic. But I'm sorry I had to tell you that, now I sound all conceited and stuff. I just wanted to let you know that I think we should hang out sometime, because there really isn't very many of us."

I don't know if it was her sense of humility that convinced me that she wasn't a normal, or the sole hope that I could finally make a friend that made me believe she was telling the truth. Nonetheless, I packed my stuff up and headed out, talking to the first true friend I had ever made.


-------


Let me know if this is worth writing a second part for! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 15:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The crazy part is that these attitudes stayed pretty much identical until 1975, and then they started shifting but because of the AIDS epidemic attitudes really didn't get better until the 90's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 05:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Fuhrer, it is the time! The white nationalists shall rise again! It is the Aryans' time!"

"What is this white nationalism you speak of? I do not recollect anything of this sort, regarding Aryans or nationalism.  Also what do you do in these parts about a headache, the side of my head hurts quite badly. It feels like someone put a bullet in my head," Adolf responded, wiping 70 years of deep sleep out of his eyes.

"That's because someone did shoot you."

"Oh really?"

"*You shot yourself Adolf*"

"Under what circumstances, I must ask?"

"In the defense of the Aryan race."

"I do not seem to remember anything along these lines. Fetch me a history."

Excited to please my supreme leader, I quickly scrambled over to the bookshelf.  However, all of the history books approached nearly 300 pages, far too long for a man who failed to get in to even art school.  Instead, I opted for the greatest of all of man's inventions, Wikipedia.

"Here Fuhrer.  Disregard this computing box, simply read the screen. You can use this thing called a mouse to scroll through and read more.  This is a complete history of your life. Hopefully this will jar your memory and help you to remember when Germany was great."

After setting a man that had been dead for 70 years lose on Wikipedia, I quickly jumped on my laptop.  
 
*Oh what a time it is to be alive. Now who shall I contact first, my fellow nationalists of Stormfront to tell them I have revived their hero, or the medical community to let them know I had successfully revived a long dead man.*

As soon as I had determined that the medical community wouldn't have appreciated the revival of a man who killed millions of people, I heard my leader exclaim "It's beautiful!"

"Oh it really is isn't it, Fuhrer. We shall rise again!" I exclaimed as I ran to his monitor, full of the excitement that the future held.  Instead, I reached his station only to find he had somehow found his way to the surrealism page on Wikipedia, where he eagerly grinned and scrolled through.

"It's beautiful! It's all so beautiful! This destruction, these symbols of death, it creates such harmony!"

"Fuhrer?"

"Oh I simply love this style.  Who is this Salvador Dali fellow?"

"Why he is a non-pure foreigner."

"Nonsense! Any artist is pure! From here on I will adhere to the styles of Dali! Quick servant fetch me a palette, I must get started as soon as possible!"



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 04:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that's where I, the OP, was coming from. That and I wrote this entirely during my Calc III class so I was slightly distracted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 03:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever we would do rhetorical analysis in high school English, I would always wonder if the writer actually meant to put that much meaning behind he word he chose. After being on the other side, I realize, no, there's a good chance that that word just happened to be the first word that came to mind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] You get placed into a universe entirely based on the lyrics of a song. After realizing you don't like your life there, you switch genres until you find your home. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 21:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You find yourself in an alternate universe that </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 21:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 21:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I opened my eyes again, something felt different. I might have dozed off, I might have just blinked, but nonetheless I found myself sitting in the warm, sleep-inducing sun. Rubbing the sleepiness out of my eyes, I glanced at my hand, noticing a significant amount of wrinkles, some that I had never noticed before, but I guess it was just another daily reminder that I wasn't going to be 30 forever.

"Honey," I called out for my wife, suddenly realizing my hunger, "What are we doing for dinner?"

There she came, the woman I had started a life and a family with, but she wasn't the same person. Her face was more hollow, more hidden by makeup. Her fashion had changed, now similar to a suburban soccer mom instead of the fashionista I married. It must have been the scoff and look of deliberate confusion that set her off and made her ask

"What's wrong honey?"

"I... Uh...," I stammered. "Uhhh, what happened to you?"

"What? What do you mean?" She asked with a sense of hurt perplexion.

"You, uh, look older."

'Oh you idiot,' I immediately thought to myself.
'Why would you ever call your wife old?'

She was very clearly hurt, began welling up, and went off to cry in the master bedroom. In any other circumstance, I would have immediately apologized and tried to make up to her, but I was far too confused to process why had just happened. Instead, I decided to go see my purpose in life, my daughter, just to check up on her and see if she had miraculously changed either. 

As I transcended the stairs, going up to my daughters room, a soccer ball came rolling down out of nowhere, followed by the obnoxious rumbling of an 11 year old boy, who quickly said 'Hey dad! Are you coming to my game later?"

Confused as hell, I could only mumble an uncomfortable 'sure' as he barreled on past me and out the front door into the front yard.

'I don't have a son,' I thought confused to myself. 'Do I have dementia? Did I get hit in the head?'

The panic in my heart was slowly rising I burst grow my daughters door, the white door that I had just painted pink two weeks ago, to find a beautiful young woman packing her clothes into boxes.

"Emily?" I asked, with tears starting to well into my eyes.

"Yes dad?" She answered. She was still looking at her clothes when she answered, but at that moment she turned her head, and as I looked into her eyes, I saw the dazzling eyes of my wife, and the heart-warming smile of my mother. It was apparent that she was my daughter, and at that moment, devoid of the previous 13 years of memories, I started crying.

"Oh dad it's okay," she told me. "I know I'm your princess, but we all have to go to college someday. Don't worry, I can survive. You've taught me well."

My legs gave out. My heart collapsed. I was now sobbing. My prized possession, the girl I had on my shoulders just yesterday, was now off to college, leaving me without 13 years of seeing my favorite person in the world grow and develop into the most amazing person I had ever seen. I simply laid there, sobbing like a 5 year old who just got their favorite possession stolen from them, as I simply wished to go back 13 years in time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> *obama gets up to speak to nation* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OBAMA: "It's okay everyone, this country is going to be alt-right now."
COUNTRY: "Oh thank God, finally some good news."
OBAMA: "Thats a great attitude. I've gotta tell you, if I was getting this news, I don't know that I'd take it so well."
COUNTRY: "But you said it was going to be alright."
OBAMA: "No, Trump hired Steve Bannon, so its going to be alt-right."
COUNTRY: "YOU SON OF A BITCH!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 00:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fast times at Ridgemont high. Classic humor followed by the plot twist of teen pregnancy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 22:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just like Gary Johnson  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A haiku </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 21:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIP this thread
Our Gary Johnson dream's dead
Death awaits us all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 09:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try telling someone in 2012
-the Cleveland Cavaliers are the NBA champs
-The Royals and the Cubs are back-to-back World Series Champions
-Donald Trump is president
-The UK dropped out of the EU
-thousands of people wrote-in the name of a dead gorilla as their presidential vote

It's been a wacky year bro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 03:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could've said that you dressed up as young thug and I totally would've bought it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 22:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm new to this science thing but from what I understand it will prob be difficult to produce a nuclear bomb a thousand times more massive than the earth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 21:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If that thing was wearing a bow tie I would have already shit my pants </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 20:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This makes a lot of sense, because why would a stunningly beautiful coworker go for a guy who didn't get married until his mid-thirties </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 16:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one thing I noticed in her acting was that she reacted to quickly to them telling her husband was dead. Normal people wouldn't start bawling and screaming half a second after they received news that shocking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 16:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean Internet reviews should be taken with a grain of salt. A lot of my friends and I worked at the same frozen yogurt store, and we had one of our other friends write a glowing review that even name dropped one of us, and lo and behold our boss pulled this kid aside, told him great job, and ended up giving him a raise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 01:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ironically half the reason we do this stuff is out of national pride from kicking the Nazi's ass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 01:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ironically half the reason we do this stuff is out of national pride from kicking the Nazi's ass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 01:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear the Europeans get pretty weirded out but the quasi-nationalism on the fourth, but to Americans, this is the United States of fucking America so let's go blow some shit up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is Donald Trump facing only a civil suit in his child rape accusations? Why is there no coinciding criminal investigation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 21:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 18:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Airplane, a three hour movie about a flight that goes perfectly well and lands with no comedic or romantic implications  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 03:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like he definitely harbors the thoughts that 'flying airplanes is for pussies' and 'space travel is for the real men' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 02:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never said communists invented killing dissidents, but praising a dictator who continues to do so on the scale of 10,000 throughout his regime is just irresponsible IMO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 02:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://cubaarchive.org/home/images/stories/1.25.2012_update.pdf these political killings exactly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 20:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just ridiculous that there are two top voted comments on this thread that had explicit examples of family members being murdered by the Castro regime, and I state an extension on those comments and get down-voted and shit on in the comments in order to protect the name of the perpetrator  of these crimes. Smh there's a reason Jose Fernandez tried to escape four times before he succeeded: it's a shitty place to live. The GDP per capita is between Namibia and Ukraine, and it's littered with human rights abuses. Just because the US government may be shit, the enemy of your enemy isn't necessarily your friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 09:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> internationally unlawful then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 09:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's one thing to support communism, it's another thing to distrust a major government, but it's another thing to support a government that presides over a country that is literally crumbling, in housing and in any infrastructure, and then to justify mass political killings and suppression of human rights. GTFO  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 09:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how Fidel Castro was able to come over early to be the 'charming man' she described him as. He must've finished early with the 'unlawful jailing of journalists' or 'repression of human rights' parts of his schedule. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 00:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So how exactly do you plan to eradicate systemic racism, something that has existed since the dawn of civilization, in four years, while your party has not one seat in the house or the senate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 21:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah and it was only once, it's just more the concept of being spanked by a pixie stick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] With the latest Hillary investigation, Donald Trump is propelled to victory, but he changes the country in a way no one foresaw. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 21:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 21:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For what it's worth by Buffalo Springfield is an incredibly well-written yet melodically simple song, which is what provokes that emotional reaction for me. American Pie by Don McLean with the honorable mention.

Edit: I forgot about his originally, but Runaway by Kanye West also gets the feels going.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 20:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> missouri drivers are worthless cock guzzlers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 20:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fairly certain my physics teach just flat out told me 'You were a mistake' one time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 20:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once hit my brother with a pixie stick, so I ended up getting spanked with that same 2 foot long pixie stick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 20:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm afraid I just blue myself" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 23:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The president has been shot. I repeat, the president has been shot"

Don Lemon was usually a fairly calm person, but it was apparent that this was simply too much for him. He took a moment, paused, and looked into the camera, but was still unable to hide the tears that were steaming down his face. He continued to read the bulletin.

"The president -- has been shot despite the extra security detail that was assigned yesterday, due to the assassination of the Vice President. The condition of President Obama is unknown,  but Paul Ryan has been sworn in. 

As if the election wasn't a bad omen enough, the signs of the rapture were becoming all the more apparent. Hillary Clinton had been shot, an attempt on Tim Kaine had already taken place, but luckily he was spared. The violence had started just 36 hours ago, the morning of November 1st at roughly 8:00 AM.

I remember that moment so clearly, so vividly, and am I positive it will stick with me until the day I die. I was driving to work listening to the radio, and the DJ had finally relented to my unending demands for "Born in the USA" by Bruce Springsteen. The song wasn't even finished before it was interrupted with the bulletin "A double assassination has been attempted on presidential candidate Hillary Clinton and her VP Tim Kaine. Clinton is currently in critical condition after  sustaining two gunshot wounds to the abdomen; Kaine made it out unscathed. The suspects are still at large, but witnesses state the assassins employed military style positioning and movement."

Fast-forward to now, 8:00 PM on Wednesday, November 2nd. The assassinations continued throughout the day yesterday, and now into today. What has changed though is the rise to prominence of the right wing militia group, Army for a New American Lifestyle (ANAL), as they had claimed all of the assassinations, saying that a war was going to be raged for the protection of the white nationalist movement. 

I can only hope this is the apocalypse as described in Revelations. For the first time since the Civil War, America lives in constant peril, fighting against its own citizens. All I can say is that if this is indeed the apocalypse, I can only hope that as the rapture separates the repented and the unrepentant, the person who called in this rebellion has a special spot in hell specifically for them.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 21:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know what they say, she's a pistol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EU] You descend into Dante's version of hell only to find that every American hero is there. The catch is, the more glorified the hero is, the deeper they are in hell. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 19:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 19:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any car with the windows tinted so dark that you can't see in the back seat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 18:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well a good chunk of abolitionists simply objected with the idea of slavery but still supported the idea of African-Americans being an inferior race, so the amount of social progress could very well anger them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You descend into Dante's version of hell, and you're surprised to find every American hero there. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 18:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 18:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You tiny fingered, cheeto-faced, ferret wearing shitgibbon" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What has been the craziest thing you have ever woken up to? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 18:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 18:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first one I remember well was madden 07. Mike Vick was the shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 18:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> probably one with a skull and crossbones on it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 18:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Why the fuck is a woman running for president if she can't even vote?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 18:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever I catch people using the wrong form of your </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 18:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure and I have a feeling many others on this Reddit would know, so I would redirect you to /r/askscience. I feel like they're gonna be much more of a help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 18:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who is the best candidate for president? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 04:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit I actually deleted Scottish, had Irish typed, and then was like nah I'll go with scottish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 22:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he seems to be the only thing in America that liked Conan  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 22:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL;DR anal, so much so that they have to adopt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 22:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well I mean the concept is no different than making out its someone soooooooooo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 21:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope your Scottish because under read this in a Scottish accent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 18:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was wondering if this was an exaggeration but there is no way that was not taken from gob </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think we all missed a huge opportunity when no one asked Donald Trump at the presidential town hall on whether his wall was going to be 'triple-reinforced' and 'Mexican-proof' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 15:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kanye has given very clear shoutouts to Derrick Rose and Bill Cosby. Perhaps he should give shoutouts to people other than rapists. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 02:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 22:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget about his constant intimidation tactics in regards to the press </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
