<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2923</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 20:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thread is down vote central. Wha' happened? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 20:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might want to play shittier gear if you want people to give you money... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 20:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read that it was a yamaha e1010. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 05:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a darwin fish also. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 01:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! Done! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 02:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I got lucky. It's rare, but sometimes happens. I got my Analog Man ARDX20 delay from guitar center in perfect condition for $200 a little while back... certainly not the steal of the century, but a pretty decent deal nonetheless (plus you can return it if you don't end up liking/using it). Just gotta keep those eyes peeled... and check in multiple times a month like a weirdo who only comes into the store for about 90 seconds, stares at the used case and then leaves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 02:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you hook up two of them (I already had one), you can use one as a stop/tap tempo/clear phrase button, and the other to scroll up and down through the different loops and select the next one while you're playing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 08:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had the same dilemma today actually. Ended up getting the boss because I got it at a good price and I've read a lot of horror stories about digitech's software when it comes to loading tracks onto the looper from a computer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NPD] Boss RC-3 Looping Pedal - got used it in pristine condition from Sam Ash for $100. Prettttaaay, prettttaaaay, pretttaayy good. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 05:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 21:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God, I hope so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 03:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're just talking about a multitap delay. I believe there are settings for multitap on a lot of different digital delays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 21:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should get a vox pathfinder 15r. They sound so good at bedroom volumes and can get much louder. The tremolo is really nice sounding and they are super cheap. I like them so much that I have 3 of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 22:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The digiverb is super underrated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 22:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, the ardx20 and diamond tremolo do just what I want. Everything else I kind of sub in and out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 21:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahahahaha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why has no one made a horror/christmas movie called Monster Claus? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 22:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 08:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have that same color scheme! Love the tilt eq. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 08:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, I've had my eye on that skreddy echo for a while now. I'm assuming you're happy with it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 07:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's more the purview of the semantics police. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 07:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. I won't be doing that again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 07:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Context: I asked my girlfriend if she meant to say she "listened" to two books on tape last month when she said she "read" two books last month. Arguing ensued. She is pretty upset. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you think it's ok to say you read a book when you actually listened to it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 07:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 20:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Diamond Tremolo is definitely worth checking out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 20:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was really excited to get a black fountain, and was super underwhelmed after I got it. The one setting that I really liked (vintage), I wasn't able to blend properly. The volume would jump really fast from not being there at all to being too loud. Also, the modulation was nothing special. I think I was just expecting too much. They just look so cool and those knobs videos make me want to buy every pedal they demo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 23:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, everybody(close friends, family and girlfriend who I live with) responded in a caring and supportive way when I told them. It was a relief to know what the problem was and helped explain my odd bathroom schedule. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 23:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got diagnosed in January. My case was severe, but besides being on prednisone twice the main thing that has helped me has been good probiotics (vsl #3) and apriso. I mostly stopped eating junk food, spicy food, and food from taco trucks and stopped drinking soda. I also avoid liquor for the most part. Don't be too freaked out and listen to your doctor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 05:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Analogman ardx20. Ohhhh weee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 20:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Mac Demarco uses a Yamaha E1010. It's not a pedal, but it's what I've heard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wonder if 50 year old me will think I'm as much of a dumbass as 30 year old me thinks 20 year old me was. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 20:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 01:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like an ehx micro pog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 00:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems to be overlooked a lot, but I actually like the Digitech Digiverb. It does a lot of fun stuff... I belive it goes 100% wet too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-06 01:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to do that! Sold it and got a JHS emperor... which I honestly didn't like all that much... and then sold.

Anyway, that tone knob on the ce5 is great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WHAT THE FU - - - oh nevermind </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-05 19:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WHAT THE FU - - - oh nevermind </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-05 19:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Truly He is the Nap King </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 00:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 19:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Headroom and dynamics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Look at This Crazy Beast </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 05:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
