<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2797</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 04:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> gotten advice from people looked up strategies and done a few puzzles not too many  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 04:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks. I play just regular.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I literally do not get any fucking better at ALL.... EVER whats the fucking deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 03:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stay in the 800s on lichess. chess is fucking impossible its like I have a chess learning disorder mother of fuck how long does it take to get even remotely somewhere with this frustrating fucking game. its not fun at all right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> whats the deal with potting soil substrate? would you recommend it for my avic avic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 20:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sometimes I have trouble maintaining humidity without constantly spraying  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 19:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 19:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not at all probably the majority if I had to guess  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> my dream is to be a physicist/mathematician but the world is telling me no </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 19:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there is nothing else I could ever imagine doing bu I keep failing essential classes and all of my friends are graduating. lifes a bitch  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 19:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel the complete and exact opposite. I feel like nobody else has any problems in their life and everything runs smoothly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 17:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> also I just said strategy, there has got to be some sort of basic strategy. but thanks ill check the source  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 17:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dude its just that im losing horribly against level 0 computers on like 11x11 boards   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> jumping spiders are 13% of all spiders families. what makes their anatomy/physiology so advantageous? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 00:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the hydraulic system they use to move? their eyesight? both? just food for thought  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 17:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> honestly I think it all boils down to lack of good algebra. but im ok with trig i feel, also I never said anything about the theory of diff eq calm down  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 16:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow I can appreciate the effort you put into that  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 16:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just don't understand how I can be comfortable with abstraction, graph theory, set theory, some amount of 1st and 2nd order diff equations but calc 1 is impossible except for integration  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> is it possible to get a global warming debate going between Bill Nye and Freeman Dyson? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 16:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> do avic avics eat beetles? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 08:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is it natural for them to eat beetles in their natural habitat? mine got a hold of one  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 18:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only came here hoping to see some examples damn...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 18:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was a terrible student in high school and took the minimum amount of math </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 18:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> for some reason I just cant perform on tests. I can swear I understand the material. its so annoying  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> could use advice from mathematicians who may be able to relate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 18:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have always loved mathematics and have recently decided I would like to try to pursue math and physics. the problem is I am finding it impossible to make it through calc 1. It feels like a huge block at this point and Im starting to conclude that maybe I should just bite the bullet and move on to another thing. has anyone ever had this experience...?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 17:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> geometry and some topology. the maths more or less yeah I guess Im not sure where to go for the physics. thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> trying to get into understanding yang-mills </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 22:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> anyone have useful advice on a good starting point?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> what does everyone do with their molts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 15:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I currently have owned my first tarantula (avic avic) for about 7 months and he just had his first molt. I am not sure what people tend to do with them afterwards? I definitely do not intend to throw it out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 15:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks for the replies  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 21:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> putting my avic in his aquarium out in the sunlight? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 20:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't tried it because I want to know if it is ok first. seems to me like it would be a natural heat and light source. thoughts/experiences? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> having difficulty with double stroke rolls in traditional grip </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 01:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my fastest (clean) double stroke roll with traditional grip is significantly slower than it is with match grip.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 05:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you know you could have likely given a helpful or interesting answer or at least nothing at all yet you instead decided to be a pretentious fuck who wants to jack off some jizz in your mouth like "oh there is single and multi variable calc and advanced calc is an arbitrary term" but you decided instead to be a dick. fuck you and everyone who looks like you   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 00:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> says the person conversing with random people on the internet who probably does so daily... fucking idiot. youre clearly not a mathematician with that lack of consistent logic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> difference between advanced calc and calc 1-3 ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 14:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what is different about advanced that isnt covered in single and multi vairable at undergrad level? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 14:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> perfect thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> does the poincare conjecture use contracting rings to imply contracting spheres? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 21:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is it correct to interpret that it is stating that since ANY ring contained within the 3 manifold is capable of contracting to a point, it follows that the collection of contractable rings in 3d space can be represented as contracting spheres?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 23:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am already well into being a chemistry major. so I plan to get a BS in chem but may go to grad school for something more rooted in math and I want to know how to become skilled at maths </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> want to be a mathematician... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 02:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to be a much better mathematician and study some graduate level mathematics in the future. I currently know calc 1, 2. some calc 3 and a small amount of set theory. I am interested in topology. any advice on where to go from here? thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The movie Whiplash </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 00:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so I really enjoyed the type of jazz in this movie and would love some suggestions as to what to listen to which is very similar to this style of fast tempo jazz. Thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> considering going to grad school for physics... but Im not a physics major. thoughts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 00:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a chemistry major falling in love with math and physics. But still love chemistry equally.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> can someone help explain the Nambu-Goto action? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 13:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> especially in regards to how it is derived? thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 05:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can you explain how to derive V(t)= t+ t^3 -t^4 for a trefoil? I just want to understand the basics of applying it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> new to topology. is this thread still active? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 21:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I study chemistry as an undergrad and recently am becoming interested in topology. will take any advice on getting into it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> anyone have a way to help explain the Jones Polynomial? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 21:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> having a bit of difficulty understanding it, today is my first day getting into it. links to videos etc are encouraged </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
