<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3788</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Networking, how do you do it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 16:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Other than traditional networking opportunities such as local bar functions, how do you network? Specifically, has anyone become part of  BNI Group? Do you network with more attorneys vs other professions?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 16:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What type of company is it? There will be a difference between a LLC and Corporation. A corporation will entail more digging based on: the bylaws, stock certificates, shareholders/agreements, any property (personal, real, or intellectual) owned, account receivables, current contracts, licenses, etc. Your school's library should have a form book with sample schedules in it; from there just brainstorm on everything you will need. Everything should check out favorably for the acquiring client, and if it doesn't the due diligence period is the time to disclose it in order to determine the value of the company to be acquired.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 15:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on what your acquiring; land will differ greatly from a business.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 13:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice, I would do the same also. Good luck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 16:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would suggest taking these questions to your school's PR professor. I took the July Bar and still have not received my character clearance, and scores came out last Friday.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 18:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Offering a concentration gives the school a projection of what classes must be offered. Also, schools offer them to give their students another line on their resumes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 20:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't you just post photos without showing your face? I mean no disrespect, but if [this](https://www.facebook.com/sarah.medlin.5) is you, then you need to learn how to cover your identify a little better if your going to go through with it. If that isn't you, then so be it, but all I did was type your name in google followed by "law school."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 17:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, were now talking about two totally different things. I'm not talking about non-wifi related injuries. There is a clear line between injuries relating to the condition of the real property and those occurring in a virtual realm. Again, you can wear more then one hat. Yes they are a business invitee, but you cannot deny, they are also a licensee. I agree with you that a court would not interpret a release based on a wifi TOS agreement for non-wifi related injuries. All I was saying is that I would argue, in relation to the use of the wifi, that the user is a licensee and absent a TOS agreement the owner of the network owes the user some type of duty as to the use of the network.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 16:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know definitively, but I would argue it does. By accepting the terms and conditions you agree to release the owner of the wifi connection of any damages that result from use thereof. Now if you don't agree to release them, and you computer is hacked by way of their network and damages result, I would argue they do have a duty. It may not result in a traditional premise liability negligence claim; but, absent acceptance of a release of liability, I would argue the owner has a duty to everyone on their network. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 12:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely! I was just trying to illustrate on a multiple choice exam that every element must be found within the fact pattern. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 12:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see what your saying, but I still think it is relevant. You don't have be on the physical property to be connected to their wifi. Accepting the terms and conditions gives you the license to use their virtual property. It really would depend on the facts involved, but you can absolutely have more than one title. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 02:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I ask why three states? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 02:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What specifics are you looking for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 02:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Stand up and say "Objection Professor...relevenace?" Haha this was done and it did work. It helped greatly that the professor was tired of the students questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 20:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would go with NJ first based on your living and working status. There is no sense of creating more stress about getting to PA testing site, living, working, etc...even if your on the border of PA. Keep it as simple as possible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really depends on the context of your argument and the facts involved. I see where you are coming from, but you have to keep the titles separate;an individual may have more than one. So the person going to Starbucks will be a business Invitee whether they are going there strictly for the coffee or wifi. The environment Starbucks has created to invite people to come in, sit, relax, and spend some money gives anyone who goes there a title of business invitee. Now, when the person accepts the Terms and Conditions and uses the wifi provided by Starbucks...Starbucks has given them a freely and revocable license to do so; also, giving them a title of licensee per se as to the internet use. Similarly, board games at some locations is another example of a license given to an invitee. Also, like I stated before the person could also be a trespasser if they go beyond what they have been invited to or have a license to do; so, potentially you could have all three titles held by one person. For example, I went to Starbucks for a coffee...logged onto their internet to write this post on my laptop...and then went into their backroom thinking it was the restroom, even though it was clearly marked "employees only." I suggest reading the terms and conditions next time you log onto a wifi connection at your local hot spot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 16:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it is Crim Law just know the theft crimes, murder, and accomplice liability...those are the big ones. Also, remember what JDX your in because accomplice liability and some defenses change based on the JDX. Idn the format of your exam either, but if it's MC, make sure you check off each element...otherwise they can't be charged with the crime (again, duh, I know). PM if you have any questions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 15:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both Crim Law/Pro were no notes exams for us. I had a boss for a proff and his thing was knowing the material inside and out. I only had three exams where I could use notes: (1) Energy Law (2) Secured Transactions (3) Sales...when I took those exams I had my book. I had done a lot of memorizing for both Secured and Sales and did not refer to the book that much, only to double check stuff. I had a buddy who didn't do much studying and relied on his book/notes and he just ran out of time because he didn't know where to look and omitted key analysis. On my Energy Law exam I memorized the facts of the cases and just went to the case in the book based on the questions facts. That could work for you too with Crim Law/Pro since every case gives your something specific.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 15:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crim Law know the elements inside and out. The Defendant MUST meet every element, otherwise they can't be charged (duh, I know). I would memorize as much as you can and then have checklists for whatever crimes you have gone over; then same thing for defenses also. Keep any open book/crib sheet simple don't try and write everything you can...you will get overwhelmed and lost.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 15:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good shit on the MBE. I live in St.Clair County and the mail always seems to take an extra day or two.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 15:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The person going to Starbucks is first a business invitee, on the property for commercial purposes. When the person logs onto Starbucks's WiFi and they accept the Terms and Conditions for it's use they have a license to use their WiFi. The license is freely revocable at any time. If Starbucks wishes they could ask the person to leave, at which time they would be a trespasser if they don't leave. Or, if the Invitee/Person goes beyond their invitation they become a trespasser (similar to Crim Law concept).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 15:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pass is a pass, haha. What was your overall score (just curious). I haven't received my results in the mail yet...still waiting. I'm kinda excited to see what ones I did well on. I know I tanked that Con Law essay. It's funny how Themis labeled cruel and unusual punishment as a Crim Pro topic and literally only had two sentences in the outline for it; nothing in the Con Law outline.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 15:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For really anything you want to keep your grades up as best you can; especially for biglaw. I wish I had gone and done something at a local municipality earlier on. If you want to go that road your going to want to do Moot Court, and even if it doesn't appeal to you, law review is a huge plus. I would try and get as much practical experience as you can; just create a dope resume.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 00:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do Moot Court and Law review if you can (this is key; practice, practice, practice!). Also, keep your grades as high as you can and see if you can get a Federal Internship.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 00:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would suggest taking Sales the term before you take the Bar. I did and skipped studying Sales entirely. Article 3 and 4 of the UCC are rather easy concepts, and you also get a nice refresh of Contracts all together. It was nice not having to worry about what a Holder and Due Course is or whether the the negotiable instrument was properly negotiated.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 00:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do. 

1. No-Fault 
2. Agency Law
3. Civ Pro/Evidence
4. Contract Law
5. Professional Responsibility
6. Evidence Law
7. Domestic Relations
8. Sales 
9. Equity Law
10. Personal Property Law
11. Wills Law
12. Real Property Law
13. Criminal Procedure
14. Constitutional Law
15. Criminal Law

Congrats on the pass; I passed as well! PM me if you want specifics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 00:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, actually that is low. I can't find the specific statistics, but normally it is right around 70-75% from my understanding. That is actually a low number across all the states, I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 19:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Passed MI...very very thankful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 19:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right around 65% from what I hear.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 01:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you front the cost of litigation, look to the client for the costs, or just front and then deduct on the back end once everything is said and done? I agree with "Screw Avvo and Yelp." I talked to an Attorney who had an intake form that had a clause in it saying if the client had not posted a review within 30 days from termination of representation, the Attorney had authority to post on the client's behalf (obviously favorably); I thought that was interesting. Other than repeats and word of mouth, where does your $300/mo go? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 01:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doing the math your signing roughly $16,000/week; that is interesting. I don't do or plan to practice PI, but I know it is a very intensive market. Do you use Avvo as advertisement, or something locally? Also, are you getting most of your money upfront or are you signing these clients on a contingency basis? Congrats on the average too, great job.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 01:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your probably looking at who has what rights between shareholders and board of directors. Voting rights, notice rights, types of shares, etc. Possibly the different types of business entities and their scale of liability. We also covered Agency Law in my Corps class- so know all four of those as well. I had a midterm like this and it had some fill in the blank; I don't know it was kind of juvenile imo. I would assume you have yet gotten to preemptive rights, Board of Director fiduciary duties, Business Judgement Rule, shareholders right for claims (against the corp or on it's behalf), and mergers/acquisitions. If you have any questions shoot me a PM.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 00:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is smart; you are their agent. I completely agree. The client is coming to you in order to solve their problem. I can't even imagine not going for lost use or lost value, if they don't wouldn't that be malpractice? I certainly agree and can see how that would impact the client's portrayal of you as an Attorney, and as an individual. Edit: So, do you see the repercussions of going that extra mile for your clients? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 22:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like what? Oil changes, tire rotations? Haha just kidding. I could see where you set them up with a car rental or maybe an uber ride; which actually wouldn't be a bad idea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 22:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't agree with you more, great analogy. I am waiting on my bar results and have been advocating that I will be opening my own firm since I was a 2L. I live in a smaller but up and coming rural market. I want to build a law firm that is nothing like anything else; I personally think the traditional law firm concept is drawn out. With businesses like Legal Zoom, the traditional law firm concept is being attacked and I think it's time to re-invent the wheel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a Solo, how do you set yourself apart from your competition? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 17:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just curious as to how some of you set yourself apart from other law firms in your area. Other than excellent customer service, do you offer reviewing documents for free to get someone in the door, extra services like going to the customer, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 17:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you attribute you growth to? What type of area do you practice? What type of law? Congrats on the climb.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 17:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is important to keep track of what happens and in what order. Watch the chain of events in your fact pattern closely. Also, remember that the Plaintiff must show BOTH Actual and Proximate causation, but only AFTER establishing the Defendant owed a duty and breach their duty owed to the Plaintiff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 13:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It freaked me out at first, but I have grown to accept it. I would just be upset if they released the names and I hadn't received it yet. Regardless, I know this is a waiting game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 17:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, no not yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 17:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MI

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 17:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, your suggesting my background is both not cleared and cleared? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How long did you wait for C+F? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 15:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am still waiting for my CF clearance and results for July's Bar Exam could come out at any time. How long did you wait for your clearance?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 18:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep second guessing myself...I am trying to have faith in what I did, but the wait is slowly shaving my faith away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 17:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't find employment and waiting on these results are beginning to kill me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 15:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have not, but that is an interesting topic. I think the drive would still be "operating" under the influence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 12:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> B all day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 15:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear you in MI as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 15:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I worked at a firm that had a client intake form that was filled out when the client entered the firm; almost like a doctor's office. Once the client completed the form, their information was transferred to the filing system; both electronically and on paper. Both forms had their own system and was updated at the same time if anything changed. The paper file was for finalized documents and the electronic file was for drafts and scanned-in documents. The electronic organization is  key and what many people have problems with. I separated all my files in the following cascading order: year; type of law/issue; client name (last, first)...then in each client file you have drafts; downloads/scans; finalized/filed..etc. This way you know EXACTLY where to go and you don't have to waste time searching for a specific file. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 01:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PM if you need help, remedies was my thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 01:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Index is key, yo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 01:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is your health, seriously? Your heart? Taking so much isn't the best idea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 00:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, you know that part in the shake law video where they rapidly scroll through all that text....that is what your buying, and NOT the signature line. Here is an idea--just get a blank piece of paper, draw a big "?" and a signature line, then sign and date it. SAME THING. Attorney's may cost money, but they are a tool in your tool belt, USE THEM! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 00:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should also consult an Energy Law Attorney near you. Among other things, there are many restrictions that come with wing energy. For example, is the area inhabited or used by some migratory bird under protection? Wind turbines are much different than PV; there is aesthetic qualities some communities have used their police powers to zone against. Also, the lease (contract) should also be reviewed, for your protection, before you lease your land. I would consult an attorney before taking any more steps, honestly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 00:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speak with a local business attorney. Some attorneys will give you free initial advice; if you are forming a new business you may qualify for some tax deductions, but again speak with an attorney.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 22:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you suggest reaching out to the processor? Did it help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 22:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Themis for the win.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 18:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea write a paper about this, lets see if he can research and write a paper we don't want to do...then never call him back. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 18:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would roll with it and see what happens; if anything you have an interesting story and took one for the team to give us the scoop on whats up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 17:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't we just create one here and just post reviews of the professors we had and others can join in....?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 17:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WOW! Have you thought about that before, shit son.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 17:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's funny. I don't think they have a meal plan, nope, they don't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 17:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anytime man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 17:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jeez I think we scared this person away from being an Attorney all together; they deleted their post and account! HAHA Welcome to the deep end.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 16:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude I would be pissed regardless; they have no professional courtesy. You give the professional the benefit of the doubt; they are trying to get it just as much as you are with all types of other life-shit going on. It goes a long way, they have burned their bridge for your help in the future; try not to let it get to you. Others only mock when they are insensitive of their own imperfections.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 12:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jeez...duress yes...but what a project. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 19:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends, a quick and simple google search will yield ample explanation. [Read this] (https://www.reddit.com/r/LawSchool/comments/54llz0/please_take_care_of_your_mental_health/) Maybe that will give you an idea of what you may encounter on your journey.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 18:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hit the pavement"...."Pound the ground"...I would say it is an old salesman's motto used to motivate the salesmen before they went out and sold their merchandise. It applies to you because you yourself are the"merchandise." You, as a law student and ultimately an attorney, are what you will be selling and nothing else. You are what will bring your clients in,and keep them coming back.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 17:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. Still waiting on my results. I have an open mind about opening my own practice in a region with a small amount of practicing attorneys. I also was going down the law enforcement route, but graduated with my BA in 2009 when the economy was shit. I turned down a position from DHS to go to LS, and have never looked back. I could easily go to a local PD if nothing pans out, but again, I am optimistic I will be successful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 17:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, your a 2L...pound the ground. I didn't because I had to work full time, and I wish I had. Dip your feet in anything you can so when you do "get your foot in the door," your coming in wet with experience! Anything is better than nothing so it doesn't hurt to have a broad range of experiences.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 17:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clinics, volunteer positions, the like. Ask some professors you are close with if they have/know of anything. Try and get as much practical experience as you can.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 16:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who decides right and wrong?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Houston Shooter was a Lawyer with Law Firm Troubles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 16:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 16:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Completely agree. Stop asking for a handout and go get your own shit straight. Every one of these answers should have been "IT DEPENDS!" You know every JDX is different. I like your last paragraph...or sentence...your going to get laughed out of every court room and conversation dude, come on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 16:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Waste? TRO? Prelim Injunction? Ugh bar review is still in my head! I have so many follow up questions! haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 16:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't you appeal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 17:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahah! It really is a great book to read. I can see you point though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 16:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *The Winning Brief* Garner...you will get mad respect. If you don't have it go buy it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 16:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dealt with it. I made sure I had everything on point before I went to class. After 10 straight weeks of answering her questions exactly how she wanted them, she dropped the barrage, but would always randomly point to me and ask me to chime in. She gave me mad respect the last class. Contracts 1 + 2... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 15:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mouth and my brain. No disrespect, but you have to put yourself out there. I had zero contacts in the legal environment pre-graduation. I have inserted some language into every conversation I have had post bar to mention that I am awaiting my results and will prospectively be an Attorney soon. You can go to your local courthouse for motion call and watch how your area works. You can contact a judge's secretary before heading down just for S G's; "hey I'm X. I just sat for the bar awaiting my results. I will be in Courthouse X checking out motion call. If the judge is not overly busy I would like to introduce myself to him." Also, you can do the same thing with other SOLOs in your area. I went through the Yellow Pages and found 24 law firms in the area that practice what I will offer, I called them to introduce myself and ask them a few boilerplate questions; just to get the juices flowing. 

With the business plan, it is something I am keeping closer to myself; its your playbook, this is the time to be creative. The internet is full of ideas on how to run a law firm, and you just have to tailor what will work for you; build on your strengths and stray from your weaknesses. With any business, there will be time for adjustment if something isn't working. Start with the basics of forming a business; I am going into business law so I know what type of entity and tax elections I am going to make, things like that. PM if you want to talk further.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 02:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want your job...holy crap! Amazing work, simply amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JD ROI...has it paid off? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 01:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will make this short and sweet. I am petrified I will be strapped financially forever. I am still awaiting my bar results and my loans are about to come due. I have a few jobs lined up contingent on a passing score, and would like to open my own law firm, but I know that anything can happen. 

Has your JD paid off? Has it become profitable? If you could change how you tackled your loan, what would you do different? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 00:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am also planning to go SOLO straight out of law school in MI. I have made contacts and will continue to do so; but, I have focused on designing a business plan to set myself apart from other attorneys in my local. Be creative.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 16:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea that's all we can do. I'm find living off $30-$40...but sadly that's the medium salary for starting salaries, unless you go biglaw. I'm right there with you on the first time and I don't/can't afford it to take it another time. Fingers crossed as well, good luck to you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 01:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your investing in your future, regardless of how you look at it. Your friends, family, and sig. others will not understand your choices; and neither will you until it becomes second nature. You got this shit...dig deep and focus before you loose sight of the path you have started on my friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 01:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Other than "it depends," What is the ROI of a JD? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 01:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MI waiting still too...this is insanity, my loans are coming due! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 16:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Agreed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 16:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, the job market for Attorneys, in general, is over-saturated. However, I live in a growing rural portion of Michigan. There is little to no Attorneys in my practice area so there is the potential to buy in now and watch it grow around me. I agree with this being a significant portion in time. I personally think a JD will open just about any prospective employment door given your specific background; it just depends on you as an individual. I worked for an Attorney who has ran his solo-practice since he was sworn in, that was 42 years ago; being an Attorney, you sit at a desk and use your brain. You can potentially do it until the day you die if you are competent, instead of having a job where your body gets tired and breaks down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 16:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was shocked to see the median salary, but the amount is understandable with the number of available degree holders willing to work for less. Do you think more JDs should go solo after obtaining licensing to compete with big law?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 15:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, but let me play devil's advocate: How would you purpose the industry change? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 15:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem. I am curious to see what kind of reform comes with this new president, but I am not holding my breath. It is important for younger Americans to learn how to save because at the rate we are going were not going to have state-funded retirement programs when we reach 65.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 15:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, that 6% nation wide does not seem to be that high of a jump. I don't have the time to research it, but I wonder how that has increased and decreased over the past 10 years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 15:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just graduated from law school and 9cr hours was part time; part time may depend on the institution, but I don't know. If it works for you I am not going to knock it, I myself have thought of going back for additional degrees as well. I have a law degree and any degree I get from here on out will only increase my income and reputation in the legal community. I would like to practice intellectual property law and have pondered going back to get an electrical and mechanical engineering degree. I understand they are completely different disciplines within the engineering realm, but when a school offers both degrees, with the exception of four different classes, why not take the mirrored class requirements for both. I guess it just depends on how much you owe in student loans already. I would not mind going to get a few bachelors degrees that diversify my educational portfolio for $40k each, but when I have a law degree and a bachelors that cost me close to $200k, I'm already in the deep end of the pool.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 16:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to make a choice that is best for YOU. When you attend law school, you are going to learn a ridiculous amount of information that you can apply to any job. There are so many more "lessons" then just the law. It is a much better investment than going to school and learning about under-water basket weaving, for example.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 14:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a problem with this data though. I am curious as to what "Legal Occupations" includes. Does this include Law Enforcement positions, Paralegals, Attorneys, etc? I think it is a little overboard, and would be curious to see the break down of specific disciplines.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Legal Occupations" set to rise 5.1% from 2014-2024; Is that significant enough to justify obtaining a J.D? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 13:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 12:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right! Like come on man. Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 01:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, but I think the reporter is acting professional as well. In Michigan (Metro Detroit Area) we have this reporter named Rob Wolchek who basically goes about the city calling people out who are blatantly breaking the law; he calls it the "HALLLL OF SHAME!" I think this reporter is on par with Rob's stories and sometimes people need to be a little aggressive. Regardless, both the reporter and group are bringing light to a genuine issue. IMO the legal assistant should have refrained from saying what he did when they were leaving the office.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 18:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They will cover both Prop 1 and Prop 2 topics. You could just buy them and then put aside the Prop 2 cards until you need them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 13:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. That PO was so scared and confused! I was laughing the entire time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 13:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This just sounds stupid. If it takes you 20 years to get a degree, most schools have a 5 year matriculation requirements. Therefore, every 5 years your classes will be useless. Also, 1 grad school class does NOT classify you as a part-time student. Even if you did embark on this journey, who is to say legislation couldn't change this in the future? How would you argue past legislation/rules/laws apply to you? I mean absolute no offense, but it is NOT smart to just continue to go to school in order to avoid payment. I would LOVE to continue to go to school, honestly, but this current system is extremely flawed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 13:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, I understand all regions are different-but why are we all settling for $50-65k right out of law school? Is this why more and more baby lawyers are jumping the big-law ship and opening a solo? I just went through my student loan info and $50-65, even with my wife's income, has us plotted for full satisfaction in 7-10yrs; that is with NO life events happening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
