<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2482</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 20:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd never even considered doing something like this, it bleu my mind! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 17:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I make separate meals for me and my kids...because I don't think my kids would like to eat Keto Chow every night for dinner.  Haha.  (Nor could I afford them to!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 22:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best post in the thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 22:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I certainly wouldn't call 9 net carbs per serving Low-Carb!

I guess some might though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 20:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, the .5g sugar labeling can be used against us too.

Biggest perpetrator?  Tic tacs!
A tic tac is basically pure sugar.  A single tic tac is .5g - .49g of which is sugar.  
So the [standard] container of 40 servings (each tic tac is 1 serving) lists it as having 0 sugar...when in fact, there is 19.6 grams of sugar in the whole package!  Very deceptive.

You have to be wary of things with very small serving sizes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 20:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> KCKO! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 19:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  In the end, the best diet isn't really a diet at all. It's a way of eating you can stick to that will boost your overall health.

This so much!  The whole article tries to get summed up by saying keto is a diet that is just like any other diet, but is restrictive.

To ME, it's a diet (way of life) that is easy, takes very little thought, and gives me more time to do other things in life because I'm not constantly thinking about food or how hungry I am.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 16:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds great, and very affordable!  I wish I had one of those nearby me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 16:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a minor breakthrough the other day when I realized at the end of the day...I'd not reached my caloric goals yet, but I wasn't hungry at all!  I actually had to force myself to eat some stuff in order to make my calorie/macro goals.  It kind of helped me realize how wonderful keto is for controlling cravings/hunger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 16:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my opinion, that's an awful lot of carbs for a little food. =( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 03:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think many people that "try" keto but that didn't research it enough don't understand how easy it is to go over the carb limit and not be in ketosis.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 20:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And what meal is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 22:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the yeps.  Muttering No No No No No No No No frantically while trying to do anything possible to get your mind off the train of thought of oblivion.  

Madness lies beyond these gates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 17:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should talk to a doctor about this.

Dysgeusia is a form of abnormal taste sensation, and (very rarely) is a symptom of some forms of cancer.

https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC2077685/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 02:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't work for me when I go running...because I desperately want to be back where I started, and not running. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 02:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Your parents did it wrong. 

Your parents weren't affluent enough to be able to afford to stay home and teach you themselves.

There, fixed for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 02:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It is not just that they lack opportunity, attend poor schools, or are plagued by poverty. They are barred by law from doing so.

WTAF is this about?  Who the hell is barred by law from "moving up"?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 21:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  or when im just trying to skake it up.

I see what you did there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 19:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just like Jedi stated.  I (personally) am doing keto not because it's the road to weight lose....CICO is what weight loss is all about...but because keto lets me not be hungry all day long!  And not being hungry means it's SUPER easy to meet my CICO goals.  

The fact that I get to eat liberal amounts of bacon, eggs and steak is just icing on the cake for me.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 19:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The comments in imgur comments always crack me up, when people talk about it not being healthy with all the butter, fat etc.  Don't listen to them (obviously) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 19:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [speaking strictly keto] If you're not worried about your budget....

Two hard boiled eggs, and an entire 8 oz package of sliced roast beef.  It clocks in at close to 400 calories, with zero carbs.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [FP] Wendy's Baconator with no Bun or Sauce </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 01:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coworker was going out to get food earlier today for lunch, and I asked her to stop by Wendy's and get one for me, not knowing what to expect.  

The price was a little more than I expected, but Mmmmmm, was SO GOOD.

http://imgur.com/gallery/3r8CM
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 17:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me know what you think?!  My mouth has been watering thinking about having it again ever since I wrote that, haha.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 14:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (On a lark) I bought a tin of Bumblebee Smoked Trout (boneless/skinless), to see what that was about.  
Oh.my.God.  

That was one of the most delicious things I've had in a LONG time.  It was like gourmet Tuna.  So tasty it felt like it was melting in my mouth...and it was drenched in the oils we need.  

It's a little bit pricey, but do yourself a favor and try it once.  It was simply amazing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 14:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure they were making a sarcastic joke. =)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 14:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My point exactly.  To us, a cow dying to make a burger means nothing.  To "them", us dying to make room for an intergalactic rest stop might mean nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 05:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't buy that at all.  I just smooshed an ant crawling on my desk, and I didn't give one thought to the idea that I was deleting a consciousness.  
Same with the burger I ate for dinner.  A consciousness was obliterated so I could raise my cholesterol level.  
Meh.

We're not special snowflakes.  We can expect no special treatment from another "intelligent" being. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 21:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa, it just clicked due to your reply, thank you!

I totally get it.  You subtract the fiber carbs from the total carbs, because they don't count at all due to non-digestion, not because they are "cancelling out" other carbs.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Science] Question about Net Carbs (Negative Carbs?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 20:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all, brand new to the scene, and started my keto journey only about a week ago.  Going fantastic already, it's almost...too easy...at how this is working.  

Anyhow, I see that the "formula" to calculate how many carbs you are counting is the total carbs minus the carbs from fiber.

My question is, if you eat something with...say, 5 carbs of Fiber, and no other carbs...would/could that be considered negative 5 carbs?  i.e.  That 5 carbs of fiber could negate something else I ate with 5 carbs of sugar....

Just a thought that came into my head while browsing the forums...I look forward to reading how my thought process is wrong, haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 21:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL: Drug Dealers take checks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 21:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Metaphors are, by their very definition, not a direct correlation.  Take your straw man elsewhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 20:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This *fact* has never really impressed me much at all.  If anything, it makes the moon feel super close to us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 21:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saying that the heat death of the universe is going to be in trillions and trillions of years....is akin to saying that your human lifetime will last femtoseconds and femtoseconds long.

Technically true, but the scale you're using is way too small.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 00:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL:DR - Clowns are scary.  We'll discipline your kids if they "invite" clowns to terrorize us via social media.  

.

The hell you will.  As long as my kids aren't breaking any laws or doing something I disapprove of on social media, you can stay out of their business, thank you very much.
If my kids want to "invite" zombie hordes, the Kraken, Dracula, or Godzilla to come legally walk around near the school and be creepy, they have every right.

This is media paranoia run amok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Letter my kid's school sent home today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 00:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 20:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I hope you're right.  

His dedication to the book currently, seems to be...not very high...so we'll see if a 70+ year old man (when it's time to write the last book) in not the best of health still thinks that spending another half decade writing something that he seemingly has no passion for really happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 20:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I imagine you also tell people that are abused, or hurt, that they could have avoided the brunt of their injuries if they just backed down and didn't stand up for themselves.  

The law is that the merging vehicle has to give the right of way.  He very obviously broke the law by taking the right of way.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 20:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The officer took the statement from him first, yes, and then he came over to me and once I said I have footage of it, he seemed really happy.  He watched the footage three times, asked if I had anything to add...I said no, the footage is my statement, and that was all there was.  His Insurance Company later asked for a copy of the footage also when I filed through them citing the police report, they had no problem reimbursing me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 20:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All animals/insects with a CNS have a period of dormancy/inactivity that can be considered sleep.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 22:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I see ya at the bar, I owe ya a beer. ;)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 22:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah.  We should definitely just go by his convictions and what he has said in interviews.  After all, he said in interviews we'd have WoW by now.

/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 22:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About a year ago, I had a very aggressive driver trying to get into the mainline highway from an entry ramp, but traffic was at a crawl.  The mainline was letting people from the entry zipper into the flow no problem, but this guy was making it very clear that he wanted to get in front of me even though I was making it very clear that I already let someone in, and he could merge in behind me.  

He inched closer, and closer and closer to my front, trying to make me get off the butt of the car in front of me, so he could fit in, but I wouldn't slow down.  

Sure enough, he must have said "f it", and he just turned right into my front quarter.  

He tried to tell the police that I accelerated into him (not that he just turned into me while we were doing 2 mph).  

If he was smart, he would have noticed I have a dash cam and it caught the entire thing as he swerved into me.  The police report was written not in his favor once I showed them the video, and the insurance determined 100% his fault.  

I was late, but it was almost worth it.

*TL:DR - Get a Dash Cam.  If everyone had one, less people would be jerks on the road. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 21:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why you keep a handful of pennies in your dash somewhere.  

Toss into the air behind you out the window....it's like ninja smoke, but for cars.  

*LPT: don't do this, you'll go to jail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 21:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  motorway driving. 

The 70's called, they want their Vehicular Travel Path name back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 20:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My biggest worry by far is that when he finally gets WoW published...he says something along the lines of "The HBO show did a great job at finishing the story...that's how the story was going to end, I will not be writing the final book."   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 20:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good correction on your part about my leaving in the decimal, but it would be a 555 followed by 34 zeros, not 36. (as you no doubt know, the two fives count as two of the 36) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 19:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I disagree with the way you said it, I agree with what you said.  Have an up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 18:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He/she said almost exactly that in the notes below that graphic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 18:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You get my upvote for referencing JATO rockets in a food story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 17:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The scale on the (second to) last info graph is horribly skewed.  It makes it look like we're halfway to the end of the Universe.

You want to put Time in Perspective?  Do it right!

If all 13.8 Billion years of the Universe's existence was represented by ONLY 1 MILLIMETER on the left side of a line chart, and the right side was the future of time going up to where only black holes exists (10^76 years)....the chart would look like this.

1 millimeter (on the left side) -  7.66 x 10^46 LIGHT YEARS (on the right side)

Lets put that into further perspective.  Light has had 13.8 Billion years to travel.  So.  Our little infographic line chart would have the current age of the Universe as 1 millimeter on the left...and the right side would be the distance light has traveled since the birth of the Universe TIMES 5.55 x 10^36.  That's a 5.55 followed by 34 zeros...times the distance light has traveled since the universe was born.  Compared to 1 millimeter.  

Our minds can't even grasp a ratio that incomprehensible. 

And, that's only until there are only black holes left.  For the actual heat death of the universe, add 44 or so more zeros up there.  

*edit Wording

*Second edit.  I did in fact miss it saying 10^10^76 ...so, my numbers I have above are brain melting-ly small compared to the actual numbers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 22:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^^
This so much.  

When I was in, we ALWAYS had heritage and tradition brought to our attention, and were hammered with how important it was   is.  Ask any Navy Chief what heritage and tradition means to them.  It's not just important, it's literally the culture our Navy is built on and thrives on.  

This is such a horrible idea.  

And YES on HuMAN....MANkind...it doesn't exclude women, it includes them.  Hell, if they had their way, they'd get rid of the word WoMAN.  

I watched the live-stream of the CNO speaking to an auditorium of random Sailors in Norfolk about this new policy.  A Sailor asked why they kept the term "Seaman" and got rid of the other terms because of gender equality....the CNO and the MCPON had the nerve to say "For Tradition".  FFFFFUUUUUU CNO.  
Also very telling, a female Sailor asked a question and made a sort of joke about not being able to call her Boats anymore (nickname for a Boatswain's Mate) because she isn't a BM anymore...and the entire crowd erupted into applause at her concern at that.  That just showed that pretty much 100% of the Sailors in the audience thought it was a stupid idea as well to take this path. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 22:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't agree with your opinion that it's the employees brunt to bear.  He's the Chief, he takes the responsibility, even if it was the employee's fault.  That's just the way things work.

However, I do agree with you that it probably happens all the time in the industry.  Wells Fargo just was unlucky enough to be caught first.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 22:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice try Russia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 21:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just scrolled though hundreds upon hundreds of comments on this, and there was literally only one response that was for this change.  

Public opinion is definitely against it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 20:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Name checks out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 19:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is pretty crazy.  If you read the actual NAVADMIN that went out to the entire Navy today, the title changes are in effect immediately.  As in, even though everyone still has their ratings they've always had, now you have to awkwardly say "Hey, Petty Officer First Class, take a look at this."  Instead of "Hey MM1, take a look at this."

You can apparently still just call them Petty Officer.  But, you know who calls someone "Petty Officer Smith"?  Someone that's trying to be a dick, that's who.

*edit*
For those not in the know for Navy culture...calling someone Petty Officer Smith, instead of MM1.....is the equivalent of instead of calling Bob Smith by his first name when you talked to him [Good morning Bob, What's for lunch Bob]....you called him Mr. Smith ONLY, all the time [Good morning Mr. Smith, What's for lunch Mr. Smith] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 18:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh oh, /r/The_Donald has developed a leak and someone's gotten loose.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 18:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  116 mph on the autobahn felt like 80 mph in Texas.

Since 116 kph is a bit over 72 mph...maybe you were looking at the wrong gauge. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 18:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beauty School Dropout, no graduation for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 23:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God dammit Dee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 22:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Contard is much more fun to say than libtard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 17:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We Humans think this is a great idea, don't we, fellow Humans?  It's a good thing that the Human in charge of pulling the switch is a fellow Human!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
