<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3318</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the one thing a Christian would like to ask a Muslim? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 00:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 20:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 03:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IF it is a liquid is to place oil on places that are hard to reach (small motor bearings etc)  If it is a grey powder it is graphite for the same purpose </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 03:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its to help fat people get closer to the mirror when they are shaving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are the Roman Catholic and Russian Orthodox church separate in the first place? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 22:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why didn't the leaders get together to talk earlier?  One thousand years is a long time to wait. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 02:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember, the grass is always greener on the other side until you get there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 13:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Getting back on topic - a little bit Ironic.  My last drinking binge was a case of 19 Crimes wine.  I hit rock bottom on that stuff.  Been just short of 30 days that I am dry.  I feel great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 03:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the early 80's there were quite a few of English artists on the charts like The Smiths, Adam and the Ants, Culture Club, Spandau Ballet, The Cure and Duran Duran.  I enjoy them all. 
I looked up the term "POM", does it still mean something derogatory or it "just a name"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 01:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am an American. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 17:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sorry....pom???? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A song dedicated to my stopdrinking family. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 03:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VjEq-r2agqc

From me to all of you.  Enjoy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 03:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my opinion the health benefits of not drinking out weigh the garbage food you are eating.   Things will settle down, give it time.  Your body has no idea what is going on.  Sooner or later you will be more aware of the food you are eating and harness the cravings.   Hang in there!  This is probably the best gift you have ever given yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 13:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why don't we hear about people dying of cancer in the past, but cancer takes so many lives now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 19:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is cancer something that has taking  hold of us in the past few centuries because of our health choices?  Perhaps in the past they did not know what cancer was or how to diagnose and it was just as prevalent?  Perhaps because we have longer life spans? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 06:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are they in Flint, Michigan? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 06:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the last thing on your mind?  What is the first thing on your mind.

Today, Facebook is the last thing on my mind - I just erased my account.  Right now, hoping my kids are safe is the first thing on my mind.  I think I'll call them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the last thing on your mind? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 06:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 20:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see a lot of young folks asking advice from elders.   What advice would a young person want to offer me about life.   What do you know that I am missing because I am set in my ways or I have on the "blinders".  

If you are older than fifty years old, what advice do you wish someone gave you when you turned 50.  What is it not too late to do at 50, but it is too late for you?

Edit - spelling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
