<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3428</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pricing of Nintendo games </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 01:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nintendo games have always been more expensive than games on other consoles. Take for example the prices of Skyrim($5) and Skyward Sword($35) or Ocarina of Time 3DS($42) and Uncharted 3($5) on Amazon. Do you guys think that Nintendo is charging to much for their games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 00:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But how much better reviewed. Are you talking like a 1/10 to a 10/10 or are you talking about a 9.5/10 to a 10/10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 23:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just used Skyrim as a point because it was a game held in high regard. Plenty of others were released around the same time with similar reviews. I guess you don't see it like I do, so we can agree to disagree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 21:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is because Nintendo rarely drops the prices of new games and they don't print very many games to make the used prices more expensive. They are more expensive because Nintendo keeps the prices high and if you own a Nintendo console you have to buy Nintendo games(monopoly) because if you don't you will have nothing to play, which was OPs original point, that the games are more expensive than games on other consoles. You may think skyrim wasn't as good as Nintendo games(subjective) but the reviews and Game of the Year awards speak differently(objective). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 21:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again completely subjective. If you like Nintendo games as well as highly rated games on other consoles, Nintendo games are almost always more expensive even when compared to Game of the year winning games. Check out the prices of zelda, pikmin, donkey kong, mario and compare them to non Nintendo highly rated games and you will see the huge disparity(compare gears of war 1, oblivion, and twilight princess all released in 2006). OP was making the point that Nintendo games have bad prices compared with other games of equal quality. Your original comment was asking a question to the OP, hopefully you can see his(and my) point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 07:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually Skyrim won more Game of the Year awards than Skyward Sword or OOT 3DS, and it is a much bigger game than either of those.  The point OP was trying to make is that $20 isn't that great of a price for such old games. Check out this site for how long it normally takes to complete Skyrim, OOT, and Skyward Sword. [http://howlongtobeat.com/](http://howlongtobeat.com/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 04:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Completely subjective. If I like both Skyrim and OOT I am not going to wait 5 years for the price to drop to $20. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 02:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is the point OP made. If you like Nintendo games and other games(xbox, ps, pc) then this doesn't seem like much of a deal when these type of people wait 1-2 years to get good games 60-80% off while games like OOT after 5 years are only 50% off the original price. He is saying that these games cost much more than games of equal(if not better) quality that came out the same year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 01:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But almost all good games(excluding Nintendo games) drop in price fairly quickly(1-2 years under $20) while Nintendo games(such as Skyward Sword) stay at a high price for many years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 23:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the Original Post was talking about good games going cheaper than $20, and saying that these prices aren't good for games
 released 5-10 years ago

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 23:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You said,

 Nintendo should drop their prices lower just because bad third party PS3 games have dropped to $10 or less?

And I showed that their were very good games released the same year that costed $60 on release(OOT 3ds costed $40). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 18:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those don't seem like bad third party games to me, and they have been cheaper than $20. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 18:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But, Dark Souls, Arkham City, Portal 2, and Skyrim were released the same year that OOT 3ds came out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 18:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, because any game that is not a Nintendo game is automatically bad. All of those cheap Sony Game of the Years.^/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 18:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fanwank is strong with this one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 21:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Triggered </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 05:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What game is this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 17:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is there a picture of Pete's Dragon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 07:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 22:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya, Goku is becoming a parody of himself.  He is acting more like a dumb child who only cares about fighting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 21:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goku is on Beerus' team, which means if Goku wins Earth will be destroyed.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 19:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goku is so stupid in Dragon Ball Super, he can't even count to 12.   In the latest episode Beerus said he would wish for the annihilation of the earth if his team won the tournament, and Goku said he didn't care.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 23:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People(me) take this stuff very seriously on [WhoWouldWin](https://www.reddit.com/r/whowouldwin/).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 23:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know right. All of these people think just because a punch is really fast it is somehow weaker than a normal punch. SMH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 23:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man people don't understand how much damage Barry could do with a single punch. Force= acceleration x mass  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 23:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never heard of plot armor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 23:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cory is in the FlavorTown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 08:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [https://i.ytimg.com/vi/6svqjrR4bFA/maxresdefault.jpg](https://i.ytimg.com/vi/6svqjrR4bFA/maxresdefault.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 08:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FlavorTown </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 00:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks man just changed it to public. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] All winter cards but #11 [W] Any regular trading cards. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 22:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Send trade offer here- [https://steamcommunity.com/tradeoffer/new/?partner=86979356 token=OzqIGbYi](https://steamcommunity.com/tradeoffer/new/?partner=86979356 token=OzqIGbYi)

I can't use the Steam market for another 20 days so I would like cards that don't expire. Can be almost any value. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 11:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ended up not getting the expansion, could use the dollar to get the Witcher or another cheap good game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 05:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 04:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it worth the extra $1 or should I put that towards a different game on sale? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 03:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Chivalry worth $2.50, and if so what about the Deadliest Warrior expansion do people still play it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 03:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do people still play the expansion? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 02:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you thinks it is worth the extra $1 for the Deadliest Warrior expansion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WSIB] Chivalry: Medieval Warfare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 01:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have $12.79 left from buying a $20 steam card and I was wondering if you guys think the game is worth [$2.50](http://store.steampowered.com/app/219640/) or if I should save the money for a different game.  Do people still play it, is it worth [$1](http://store.steampowered.com/sub/30564/) more for the expansion, and does it have good replay value. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 05:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude Superman can shoot ice out of his mouth because of the sun. :I </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 23:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So unrealistic, unlike when Superman breaks all physics because of the "SunForce". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
