<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2777</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 10:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved Born of the Gods because when it released it cost me only like $5 for Bile Blights and Drown in Sorrows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 11:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got 5 and 1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 23:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are the rules for tagging in and out?

Oh I'm being attacked, let me tag my partner, now you're attacking him, NEW DAY! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 12:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to Goatbots Calculator, the EV of a friendly league is -2.44 with a 58% win rate, so . . . in a way you're ahead? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 12:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Favorite Thought Hemorrhage story, from ALA-ZEN Standard:

It's my turn. I have no board and my opponent has lethal next turn, but they're also at 4 life. It's been a grindy game and they have no hand, while the Thought Hemorrhage has been rotting in mine. I draw for the turn, it's Sign in Blood. After weighing my options, I decide to cast SIB on them, putting them to 2, then try to guess what they drew and kill 'em with Hemorrhage. "Kazandu Blademaster"--they lost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 00:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I play Braid of Fire in my Red Akroma EDH deck. Works great with Morph and Firebreathing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 00:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Axe Land? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 00:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a Daze with "Harm's Way" written on the back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 00:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I just broke Modern:

4 Lost in the Woods

56 Unhinged Forests

These sleeves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 13:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 11:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't pay too much attention to the Conspiracy sets, so I've never seen Enraged Revolutionary before. It seems like a solid creature--has anyone tried it out before? Do you find it gets in a good amount of damage, or does it just die to Doom Blade? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 10:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the Horcrux stuff but I don't think it technically works.  I believe  Creature and Tribal are the only card types that are allowed to share subtypes. So if Horcrux is an Artifact subtype, Harry and Nagini can't have it, and if it's a Creature subtype the rest can't have it.  I think you'd need to either:

1) Leave Horcrux as an Artifact subtype and turn Harry and Nagini into Legendary Artifact Creatures.

or

2) Turn Horcrux into a Creature subtype and make the Ring, Diadem, Cup, etc. into Legendary Tribal Artifacts.

I'd go with option 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 19:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blue Island

Land--Island

Blue Island is Blue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 08:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe a keyword/mechanic that severly nerfs the effect if you already have a copy of the card in your graveyard or exile.

Path to Dispatch W

Instant

Exile target creature.

Diminishing Returns--if there is card named Path to Dispatch in your graveyard or exile zone, instead tap that creature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 07:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "No rest, no mercy, mo matter what"

And

"The Specimen seems to be broken"

From Akroma and Deep Analysis, respectively.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 12:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough.  Funnily, they have slightly different ratings on Gatherer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 11:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you decide that BFM would take up only one slot? My inclination would be for both halves to have be seperate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 10:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a Sakashima EDH deck that over the years has to devolved to a state where the win condition is just having three Ulamog in play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 21:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time I see this black circle I think it's Damnation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 12:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Limitless Power? Not enough to beat my little snake friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 21:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always wished I could mash the instant effect of Abbot of Keral keep with the mana-independent effect of Dark Confidant. And then there's Silvergil Adept, but she's pretty deck-restrictive:

Abbob

1 b/r

Human Wizard

Kicker 3 or Reveal a Merfolk from your hand.

Prowess

When this ETB, reveal the top card of your deck, put it in your hand and take damage equal to its cmc. If you paid the kicker this ability triggers twice.

2/1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 17:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as the red one gets a random card. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 02:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does that make them binique? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 20:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (number of relevant 4-card hands that get you your 3 remaining types) divided by (total number of 4-card hands)

So figure out each combination that gets you Delirium (such as Creature-Sorcery-Sorcery-Land) and figure out how many ways there are to get that combination of types. (So 13*5*4*23 assuming all those cards are in your deck). Add those all up, and divide the sum by how many possibilities there are.

I only have a rudimentary knowledge of programming but here's my pseudo code If anyone want to type it up. I think the logic is sound but wouldn't mind being double-checked. Sorry if my notation is wonky.

~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~

%Program: Odds of getting Delirium after a Vessel of Nascency.

% T is a vector whose entries are ({list of types}, # cards in deck with exactly those types)

% C for creature, A for artifact, S for sorcery, etc

% You can change these numbers based on the game state.

T=[ ({C}, 13), ({A,C},3), ({S},5), ({I},8), ({E}, 4), ({P},4), ({L},23) ]

%G is the set of card types known to be in the graveyard after Vessel resolves.

% It starts with E because of the Vessel. If there's other types already you can add them in here.

G={E}

%D is the number of cards in the deck

D=Sum_{i=1}^{length(T)} T[i][2]

%Q is the number of possible four-card hands

Q= D choose 4

%R is the number of relevant four-card hands that would grant Delirium.

% ie the number of hands with three or more non-enchantment card types.

% Starts at zero. We will modify.

R=0

% The following loop looks at all the possible combinations of types from four cards.

% H is a combination of card types from four cards.

% P is the number of ways to make the combination out of cards in the deck.

% If the combination and graveyard don't give Delirium we replace P with 0; it's irrelevant.

% S replaces T while calculating P to account for repeated types in a combination.

% To find the final value of R we add up all the relevant P values.

**For i from 1 to length(T)**

S=T

H=S[i][1]

P=S[i][2]

S[i][2]=S[i][2]-1

**For j=i to length(T)**

H=H union S[j][1]

P=P*S[j][2]

S[j][2]=S[j][2]-1

**For k=j to length(T)**

H=H union S[k][1]

P=P*S[k][2]

S[k][2]=S[k][2]-1

**For l=j to length(T)**

H=H union S[l][1]

P=P*S[l][2]

if |H union G| 4, then P =0

if P0, then P=0

R=R+P

%End Loop

% Solution

Output R/Q </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 12:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conscripts vs Lark hurts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 23:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, thanks. Definitely didn't "develop" it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 20:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poor Craw Wurm. It's like the doctor telling you you have six months to live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 10:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought cards with an Overload cost cheaper than their mana cost would be neat:

Desperate Times 5G

Instant

Target player gains 10 life

Overload G (Instead, each player gains 10 life). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 00:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find I can never have enough perfect fit sleeves. Maybe 60ish packs of those? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 00:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've got two years to learn! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 22:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Monarch cards? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 22:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, it excludes LEGOs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 11:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Respect for the main deck Destructive Revelry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 11:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I get the Oracle text for that child's picture? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 08:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let us know how it goes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 08:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oracle Update:
Zur's Weirding 3U
Enchantment
Players play with their hands revealed.

Explanation: This is a funtional change. It was done to bring the card in line with its' online counterpart. Now players can enjoy a uniform experience in both paper and online play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 21:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't Dredge and Burn both play Stomping Ground? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 21:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree UR=Purple. But you know that UR Thing in the Ice deck that's been picking up popularity in Modern? Using this association:

Thing in the Ice = TITI = titty = nipple = nurple,

I call that deck Purple Nurple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 11:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Combo" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 11:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh the humanity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 15:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love me a Bolas-Ugin Team up, but this takes the cake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 05:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use an oversleeve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
