<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3859</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-28 10:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for answering btw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-28 10:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was playing backyard football and collided with someone full speed, his knee went into my leg as it was planted, worse pain ever. Saw a blinding flash of light  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What can help a broken bone heal faster?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-28 04:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys I broke my fibula a few days ago, anyone know what can help with the repair? What can I eat? Drink a lot of milk?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-24 02:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just saw this on facebook!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-23 23:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have the power to downvote....so if shit like this gets to the front page, its the communitys fault as a whole. And anyone can put up pics of hot girls wtf, I can Google  shit like this all day, karma doesn't even mean anything in real life, stop ruining the damn subreddit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-22 09:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happens to me every night....happening right now HOW DO I MAKE THIS STOP AHHHHHH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-22 04:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks, it's not finished, I will be in a few days though, I'll get you a high quality shot too, this is a quick snapshot by my phone, it loses the color in the grass and the colors in the background :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-22 02:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel the same, except I'm a guy -_- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-22 01:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be sweet have a nice break , god knows we all need it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-21 22:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-21 18:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you its 4 feet tall in oil paint, I have much more work to do on the face, like to go back and add rock texture to the face. The giant face represents excess thoughts,worries, anything that can keep the mind running in times of meditation. I will have the light from the monk more on the big face to show the strenght of calmness and peace. I will repost once finished. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-21 08:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks Its 4 feet tall, was so hard to do the face, did it like ten times over and I still need to go back and make it look like volcanic rock
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am painting what it means to find inner peace, WIP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-21 08:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey guys, I am painting the struggle(volcanic face) to find inner peace(monk), thought you might like it.WIP  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-21 08:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am painting the struggle to Finding Inner peace, work in progress </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-21 08:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-20 08:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's the first thing that came to my mind when i read this
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-17 07:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fuckin awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-13 20:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-13 07:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, you too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-13 06:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dang, alright guess i'll just have to pay it,i just sold two paintings as commissions today and got 120, and its going to that ticket haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-13 06:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah thanks, you too, get those a's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-13 06:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he was a calm dude,but in my dream it was serious, this is my friend who got shot in the head a couple months ago. A few days after he died he showin in my dream and im trying to paint it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Had the worst luck today  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-13 04:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-12 18:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha thanks for the suggestion, ill lighten up on parts. I can tell the outline looks very....outlined Haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-12 18:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah my professor is sick with it, he can make photo-referenced paintings look like real life, of course it took him like 30 years to build the skill, glad you can appreciate it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-12 18:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I will. Just the eye sockets and cheek bones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-12 18:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah we were supposed to leave it simple compared to the rest  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-12 10:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I havent put up much of my class work I finished this semester yet, all the drawings still need to be put up. After I finish with finals I will update </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-12 10:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is my blog,     www.noodos.blogspot.com
there is a lot of art on there, if you get to the bottom, click "older posts"

and thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-12 10:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you, poured a lot of time into it, just wanted to show reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Final for my drawing class, ahhhh finally its over, time to ice the wrist  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-12 09:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-11 06:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Work in progress of my friend

http://lh3.ggpht.com/-48eX4K9x8gc/Ts0IoDM1LgI/AAAAAAAAARA/k6WlQVC0xJA/IMAG0502-1.jpg

sweet idea btw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did this all day today at a [7] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-06 09:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IDAP of Visualizing hypercubes  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-06 06:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-05 22:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I didn't mean double I meant the same from chin to eyes , would be eyes to top of the head, its kinda hard to explain in text but basically eyes are always gonna come to be around the middle of the head, if you made a line horizontally in the middle of the head, eyes would be there, of course the angle of head changes that considerably, changes the angle and placement of the ear also. With the ear I usually figure it out by finding the angle of the eyebrows first, and then finding the angle from the brows to the top of the ear, and I find the bottom by lookin at what its lining up with on the face, usually is the bottom of the nose of top of lips.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-05 08:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dude that looks sick,anatomy seems right, but your line work can be improved for some parts, it gets real fuzzy around the head.. makes you look unsure about the size of his head, and ear might be a bit small....and for me man, the top of the head, its usually double the distance of chin to eyes. Of course, its your style an I don't see the picture so take it if can help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-03 20:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I wasn't really saying that its doom and gloom. It's just that I always think about my parents and even when I feel alone from other people, they are always there, so I can't say I feel your pain, not yet, but the way you talked about being alone in the universe described exactly how I think it will to lose them. And my dad is exactly like that too, he will never say how much he cares, but I can recognize it in little things he does. It really is a good comment, sometimes we forget how much our parents really mean and sometimes its too late, reading your comment made me call them. I'm sure I'm not the only one who will take your words to heart,its easy to be pessimistic about op's situation, but  you found the right and optimistic words, thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-03 20:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think anyone could have said it any better, thanks for the wisdom and the tears </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-03 09:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha you just made me geek, this just happened as I read it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-01 07:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh, yeah I feel you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-01 07:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's sad, great movie, you are missing out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grave of the Fireflies, check it out guys,made this a while ago. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-01 04:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-01 01:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I walk around campus, they say "who let the hobo in?" 

[Imgur](http://i.imgur.com/kmRxX)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-30 03:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Art is life  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-30 00:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh SHIT I JUST REalized Hahahahahaha that's hilariious  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-30 00:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh didn't know I had to deal with them signing in other people too. Thanks, I don't think I can handle dealing with that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-30 00:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha yeah it was made a couple years ago, sorry if its wasting your time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey guys I made this a while ago, a pretty trippy combo, thought someone might enjoy it. Butterfly effect. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-30 00:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-29 23:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost brought a tear to my eye. Thank you for sharing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-29 21:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's a +1?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-29 08:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Art major Here, deadlines raping my soul right now, 40 drawings due at 1 pm and here I am on Reddit....well I have 4 done so its not so bad... Reddit has been distracting as fuck but what can ya do. Semester has flown by man, kinda tired of endless work, break was just to catch up on work, redo assignments an crap. All nighters all the time make the mind numb, and I rarely procrastinate, atleast we don't have final exams Haha, just final projects...which take weeks 0_0. I'm not bitchin, I love my major, it just gets tough sometimes, I'm sure everyone is going through this feeling now that finals are here, just try an keep your heads up and punish em.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-29 05:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha sorry about being so vague, it was a commission to a song by linkin park. that's the lead singer, chester bennington and it's themed to "My December". I uploaded in a hurry so I didn't bother with details, my bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-23 18:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woah deviantART has upgraded since I was on there a few years ago, will check out th work and am considering updating my DA also. Find me. subject3859 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-23 15:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here you go,  www.noodos.blogspot.com , I don't update as much as I should but theres still a lot of work on there and I just did this  leg drawing yesterday and showed some process work to help people out. Be sure to hit "older posts" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-23 00:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have wrote more but wanted to finish the drawing. Still need to fix it a bit an then will write out what I did, glad it helped someone out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-22 10:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Www.noodos.blogspot.com , doing legs at the moment check it out, its the process. Updating as I work. Thanks
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-22 09:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> true words, skill and hardwork will always outdo talent alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-22 08:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The relaxed shocker really, couldn't keep my hand flexed for too long, haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-22 08:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-22 06:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since a lot of people were asking about the process or method, I'm doing another drawing at the moment and will show process as I draw on my blog, www.noodos.blogspot.com   Thanks reddit, much love </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-22 06:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have this anatomy book and just drew all the bones in the body and all the muscles, legs, arms, all seperate and learned the proportions that way and when I draw people now I can see the muscles and bones. it's basically obtaining x-ray vision. I have been also drawing a lot from life, my own arm, doing legs at the moment, it helps knowing the figure, and also have a drawing class, nude models. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-22 06:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> heres some process work for what Im working on at the moment

http://noodos.blogspot.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-22 06:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://noodos.blogspot.com/   I just put up the first few updates check em out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-22 05:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, Yeah fingers,  very deceiving, I did this correctly by finding the phalanx of each finger and makin simple circles for where they were, and the contour lines came in after.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-22 04:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't see the second half of your question but I will come back to your question, drawing legs right now and will explain the process, method when finished. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-22 04:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the process pictures I took for this arm aren't very useful to a beginner, I'm actually about to pull an all nighter doing another drawing, of legs. I will take better process pics and explain how a drawing like this comes about, so it will be up on my blog by tomorrow.. usually spend around 10 hours on something like this.  I can still give you some tips regardless, don't get caught up in details, just start out with a light pencil, I used 2H for the whole thing, any pencil will do but, you don't want dark lines til you know where everything is going to be. Start out with basic shapes representing what your drawing, and your going to build up to the details, details come last. Whatever your focal point is going to be, that is what should have the most detail and work. I am not considering shading right now, so think about line quality too, the darker the line, the more attention is brought to it, use line to lead the eye around the work.  Once you have the basic shapes down, start building up the form of things, adding more shapes.  It will be better if i just show you, so if you don't understand completely, just wait til I finish my current drawing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-22 04:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> actually yeah, that was actually what I meant by 3 months of practice. I have been studying anatomy from this book: "Artistic Anatomy" by Dr. Paul Richer and have a figure studies class twice a week where we have nude models come in. From the book I basically redrew the whole body, both bones and muscles on torso, arms, legs, everything. Now when I draw, there is little guesswork because I know how everything is supposed to look in comparison. Semesters almost over but I've learned a ton.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-22 01:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah actually I can upload some of the process to this drawing to help, I'm not home but I will later, and here is my blog. www.Noodos.blogspot.com.  and yeah I can help you out, just gimme some time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-21 23:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, it's all line work, haven't really learned to model(shade) yet. Will post more when I start shading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-21 23:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks, its my own arm, hehe, try to draw from life as much as possible, you'll learn a lot and will be able to see much more then in a photo. good luck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Never thought I could draw so technically, this is a result after 3 months of practice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-21 23:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-19 20:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry to hear that if this really happened </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-19 00:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope you feel better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-18 00:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.msxbox-world.com/xbox360/guides/141/tekken-6/851/character-tiers-list.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-08 23:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What bullshit, fuck them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-07 23:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much do you get paid? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-03 05:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahaha why destroy it? keep it all, start a blog or something,  you don't even have to show anyone. Or atleast take pictures before destroying it, it's great to look back on it all. I'm in art school so I blaze all the time and pull out assignments for my classes, not a painting major though, will minor in it soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-03 05:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks, just glad to share em, I had one more, "The pursuit of happiness" but cannot find it at the time, it really is great toking and painting music. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-03 05:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's to "cudi zone"   

here is "do it alone"- http://3.bp.blogspot.com/_h4hhmnDCogY/TUJbTi0M85I/AAAAAAAAAIs/kdEJf19LgCQ/s1600/Do_it_alone_by_subject3859.jpg

both by Kid cudi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey guys, first time posting here, thought I would share some paintings I did while listening to music at reasonable [9] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-03 05:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-02 06:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't really know the exact time for my 2011  5.0 gt/cs, but I've always read its around 4.5-4.8, basically the same thing..., they would probably have it around 4.2-4.3 with better tires. Its odd how 470 horsepower is gettin the same time against 412... But Maybe 0-60s don't mean that much when it comes to muscle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-02 03:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are not faster then either the camaro or stang.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-30 17:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Retuuuuurn the slaaaaab </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-28 21:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 0_0 oh man, mouth watering* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-26 20:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://joni-chng.suite101.com/evaluating-and-buying-art-for-absolute-beginners-a161097

Some basics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-12 23:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope I'm not reposting this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-11 06:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this subreddit, its hilarious seeing posts about somethin you walk by everyday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-02 22:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would but I don't have a picture of that...and live nowhere near. Wanna find a specific pic you would like?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-01 09:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also DAP of her

http://4.bp.blogspot.com/_h4hhmnDCogY/TUJUt2Afw9I/AAAAAAAAADA/nrueDxC0g_Y/s1600/Abandoned_Gold_by_subject3859.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-01 03:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow I'm in art school, those have been concerns of mine in the past, beautiful and inspiring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-30 07:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuckin awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-27 15:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad you think so, thanks, charcoal btw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey reddit, check out my first creative piece with perspective </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-27 08:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-26 08:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be sweet, art! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-23 00:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I REALLY doubt that everyone can do that...the guy playing probably has an insane arcade stick, and is good as hell. Even without the switches he can pull off EWGFs like 5 times. I haven't seen anyone other videos where the player is that fast and good at timing it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good god! Mishima combo exhibition </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-22 22:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-22 01:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright man, I don't know what came over me to diss your work like that, but I'm gonna try an help you out a little. ok when doing faces man, starting out is fuckin hard, cuz u have no sound method to getting all the proportions right..and without proportions it doesnt matter how good everything else looks..... the painting is gonna be crap.  take a look at this, just did it

http://lh4.ggpht.com/-j-vP20acGLs/TnpqqQmgZYI/AAAAAAAAAO4/uZmDUk1E7p8/IMAG0026.jpg

Ive been painting for a couple years, and have taught a few to paint also.

you know that first layer when its all wet, using gamsol or turpenoid? the thin layer..... you wanna have a good underpainting.... Try choosing a dark color and basically drawing out where the imporant parts are gonna be....you know, getting everything right, eyes in comparison to head,etc.   you can start out with the basic shape of the head like i did....and then a line right down the middle of the face(between the eyes, middle of nose) and then from there you can put lines going across, for eyes, for the bottom of the nose,,,and another one for lips...and then LOOK and COMPARE where the eyes are gonna be....and then using ANGLES from the edge of the eyes....to the edge of the nose, pinpoint the nose...same for lips....I can't help you much online besides that, try an get basic shapes to fill in the face, see the drawing?? the circles in the cheeks?? helps me see how full they are and where the nose,etc would be. I'm not saying I'm such a good artist that you suck and i have to show u everything...Im just trying to provide more feedback then my last shitty comment. sorry again for being a fuckin DOUCHE. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-22 00:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Afo by any chance?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I drew a vicious bird attack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-21 22:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-19 05:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RABBLE RABBLE, RABBLE RABBLE? rabble </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's really good? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-15 08:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-15 04:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> actually it's Dr. Paul Richer's Artistic Anatomy book, edited by Robert Hale. I don't think angles can be tweaked later...they can be erased later, but starting out, it feels as if they help put everything in the right place. its nice having reference points and then finding angles from those to pinpoint exact location of limbs, etc. I mean for the human body, it seems like a must, until I master it, maybe that's when I won't need them, I guess that's what you were referring to. Being good enough not to need them. I'm not yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-15 00:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Starting out:   http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-70bI0pdu0J8/Tm1_YjjmADI/AAAAAAAAAOc/OQHWLu_6_oI/s320/321136_10150301976404001_662494000_8029015_1936787100_n.jpg


FINAL: http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-AUOzYUwsWsU/Tm1_ZiCe-LI/AAAAAAAAAOo/19AGSA72Y_E/s1600/299112_10150302136504001_662494000_8029943_1789173647_n.jpg



crit would be nice, if anyone gets the time to look at em.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I learned the importance of angles BEFORE you start the contour lines </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-15 00:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-06 07:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah I noticed the shabbyness of some of the lines..and yeah I will work on the obliques...it was done fairly quickly, and the bigger one will be very precise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-06 07:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some crit would be nice, the shoulders look off because of the interference with reference points I started out with. It's just practice for a bigger piece starting tomorrow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IDAP of a Juicy Human </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-06 07:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-31 21:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wtf I live in springfield and never heard of it either
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-27 06:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this all tablet? any oils? and this might be a stupid question but do you have to pay to have a blog like that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-24 21:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah its adora, I came from India a couple days ago and saw peacocks there so I kinda just incorporated the animal , making the hat an stuff, thanks, oils, brush and palette knife </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A father's request </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-24 09:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A father's request </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-24 09:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-12 17:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Punjab, back to the roots, the village. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-12 00:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-11 23:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha thank you, Indians aren't really into art so when I was starting out with just the outlines, my aunts were like , your ruining the wall and said they would wipe it off when I left. But when I finished they loved it and the 6th girl is the oldest and has gone away to a different village for school. I have done many self portraits and was kind of sick of seeing my face Hehe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
