<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3364</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 13:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Different language </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 13:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a different language I meant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 12:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surely you're talking about Boku no Pico? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 12:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved Poppo as well! Though Menma was my fave D:

Also, coincidentally just downloaded Kokoro today so I will check it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Summarize your favorite anime in five words or less. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 12:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ALSO, please write down the name of the anime in your answer.

I'll start us off.


Anohana - Will inevitably cry for Menma.

Fairy Tail - Erza Scarlet = waifu

Haikyuu - Made me love volleyball. HYPE.

Noragami - Best OP ever

Toradora - Feels for Minori </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which anime character angered/annoyed you the most? (Possible Spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 12:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did their actions/attitude anger you?

I just finished watching AnoHana and I loved it and have sympathies for the MC 'Jintan.' However, his cold attitude at times was so annoying. For example when Anaru was crying to him and he brushed her off, that sucked.    :(  

Still a 10/10 anime though.

Edit: Also, Yukiatsu from Anohana was a douchenozzle the entire series. Jesus christ. Give Jintan a break you knob. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Besides religious views, what is a belief you have that is contrary to what is commonly held? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 10:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 10:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. AnoHana
2. Toradora
3. Haikyuu
4. Fairy Tail
5. Noragami </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 08:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NORAGAMI!!!!!! The OP alone will make you love it :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 08:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen it already. I really liked it though and am waiting for more eps (don't know if more will come out). Also the OP was so catchy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 07:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking just for any good anime. Preferably with a bit of comedy in it. And a school setting would be nice. I watched Toradora and it was brilliant. Just finished AnoHana and I loved it. Clannad wasn't for me (though I only watched 2 eps so I might pick it up again later).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 07:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your description of Shokugeki no Soma exactly matches my thoughts on Haikyuu so check it out if you havn't seen it. You won't regret it!  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 05:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The reveal is at 4:38 if you want to skip ahead. But the build up will give context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Host loses it at friend's reaction to prank </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 05:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most NSFW event that happened at your school? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 12:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Swearing on air prank. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 12:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 11:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want to skip to the reveal it is at 4:28. The build up is still amazing though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Host loses it at friend's reaction to prank </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 11:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the smoothest thing you've ever done? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 13:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If your favorite subreddit (please state it) was a real person, what would they be like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 13:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If your favorite subreddit was a real person, what would they be like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 13:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 12:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lukaku out for Gray/Negredo. Maybe bring in Kyle Walker to improve that defence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 12:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd personally swap out Lukaku for Gray or maybe Negredo, then use that cash to keep or improve the squad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 12:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm assuming you're playing 3 at the back? Then you should swap out either stones or morgan to free up some cash in the bank. Amat from Swansea may be a good shout. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 12:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You obviously haven't visited 'The Sun' recently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brilliant response to Arsene Wenger's claims on Arsenal employees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 12:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 01:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In front of that Brazilian crowd? He would have to have a death wish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 01:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine the scenes if he missed it though. Good win Neymar! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 14:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Klopp in the background. What a man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reus and Lewandoski bittersweet moment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 14:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which movie/tv show was unexpectedly scary? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 09:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something to look forward to in the future? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 04:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most disgusting thing you have had in your mouth? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 13:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 13:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leave. Now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 13:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have heard about this one, but I've no idea what it really is and I don't plan on finding out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the stupidest thing that has gone viral? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 13:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 13:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 18 year old. Male. Single. Australian accent. PM me if you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Noob question on wildcards </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 10:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 10:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What have you started on this thread Starship_Nemesis and liquor_for_breakfast??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Penalty Kick takers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 13:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can anyone list the guaranteed penalty kick takers or players who take the majority of their team's kicks? Would be really helpful for choosing players. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fantasy Premier League Tips? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 11:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 13:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's actually telling the truth you kno-   Oh... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most ridiculous misconception you or other close to you have had? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 11:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 03:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christ. Phelps doesnt look like he has aged at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When has a situation 'escalated quickly' and how did it occur? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 14:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 14:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Not like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 14:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who can't mind their own business. I'm not talking about people joining in conversations, I'm fine with that. I am talking about people who feel the need to criticize what I am doing even though it has nothing to do with them and they are saying nothing helpful at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 14:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  nobody is looking at your dick

That's what you think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 14:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well cya then. Bye. (Both walk in the same direction) Oh, we're going the same way? Yea, haha. Heh. (Continue in silence while thinking of things to say) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 14:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbf, you had to give a standing ovation for 'Inception'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something that is considered normal/acceptable in society, but you find weird or annoying? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 14:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 23:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kyle Chalmers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 23:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted in this in r/videos 12 hours ago and it got nothing whilst this has 8000 karma.  :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 13:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man City will not finish in the top four. Their poor defence will let them down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kyle Chalmer's grandparents heartwarming reaction to his Olympics win. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 11:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which anime has the best 'wallpaper worthy' scenes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 11:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leave links if possible please. I just started watching Log Horizon and  the animation is amazing. The dawn scene in episode 3 (I think) was awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 23:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Without context, this would look like a traitorous Madrid fan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In your opinion, which national anthem sounds the best? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 11:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 23:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We'll be on suicide watch
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by accepting a drink from a friend. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 14:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 03:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Username checks out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most uncomfortable situation you've found yourself in? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 02:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Classic Movie Discussion: Jurassic Park (1993) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 14:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 13:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'd go with Kuroo from Haikyuu as the most handsome though.

But..but Tanaka!!!!

http://i.imgur.com/1kisvFB.gifv </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 12:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet mother of god... How have I not seen this?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which character, in your opinion, looks the best? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 12:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't have to just be who looks the most beautiful/handsome. Think about the best character designs in anime. IMO Ichigo Kurosaki from Bleach looks amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 12:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you liked Haikyuu check out Kuroku no Basket. Similiar concept but for basketball. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite anime opening? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 12:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine is 'Goya no Machiawase' from Noragami. 'Masayume Chasing' from Fairy Tail is really good as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 12:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should have specified. Ozil will get POTY if Arsenal get a better striker who won't let him down. Will fix it now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 12:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know. I'm really hoping he changes this year though. That goal against Lens and against the other team today (forgot their name) have gotten my hopes up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 11:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to fix it. So frustrated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> English Premier League 2016-17 Predictions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 11:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A new, exciting season is brewing. Several, huge managers have joined the fray. And class players like Ibrahimovic, Gundogan, Mkhitaryan, Kante and Guzan have signed on. With these predictions, I tried to remain as unbiased as possible. Let me know what you think in the comments. Considered opinions would be preferable over mindless abuse.



**STANDINGS**

Manchester City

Man City has arguably the most talented squad in the PL. The addition of a fine manager in Pep Guardiola will push them to the top along with signings like Nolito and Gundogan. Kevin De Bruyne is also a player to watch out for. And Aguero is undoubtedly world class.
*Team MVP - Kun Aguero*

Manchester United

As my friend has reminded me gleefully for the past month, United have Ibrahimovic. Though he is nearing the end of his career, Ibra is still playing amazing football. The uber talented Mkhitaryan may take some time to adapt to the PL, but he is sure to rack up many assists with Ibra leading the line. At the opposite end of the field, Smalling and De Gea will be relied on with defence. A certain transfer target could also push United to first place. This will be a huge improvement on United's apPAULling previous season ;)
*Team MVP - David De Gea*

Arsenal

The urgent cries for a striker have grown louder as other teams make serious moves. Though Giroud may be talented, he will not be able to carry Arsenal to the peak. Granit Xhaka is an amazing signing who will solidify the midfield. Mertesacker's unfortunate injury will mean that Arsene Wenger will definitely be signing a new defender. Yet again, Sanchez and Ozil will be the main stars in this squad. The addition of a better striker would mean even more assists for the world class CAM.
*Team MVP - Mesut Ozil*

Chelsea

Though some may see 4th as a failure, I see this as a huge improvement. The team came 10th and forced my mate into hiding last season. Though the squad has obvious talent, and additions like Kante and Batshuayi, I think it will take some time for Chelsea to shake off the poor form of last season. Ivanovic and Matic will have to step up. Courtouis has been dissapointing. Fortunately, Hazard was very good in the Euros. Fans will hope he can carry this form into the new season, Chelsea's season relies on him.
Team MVP - Eden Hazard

Liverpool

I love Klopp. LOVE him. He is a manager who is charismatic and who can lead the team successfully. Though Liverpool will not break into the top 4 they will come close. Matip and Sakho will be lead a solid defence, and the addition of Mane will definitely be beneficial. Coutinho is an exciting, young CAM who is capable of taking control of the game. Karius is a young proven goalkeeper with WC potential who may take the starting spot when returns from injury this season if Mignolet underperforms.
*Team MVP - Phillipe Coutinho*

Tottenham

The Spurs were impressive last season, until the final few games which would have given fans sleepless nights. Their defence will again be led by Alderwield, who was one of the stars of last season. Lloris is a WC goalkeeper who is sometimes overlooked. Wanyama and Janssen are new signings who will be valuable additions. The attack will be led by Eriksen and Harry Kane. Though Kane was disappointing in the Euros, he will bounce back in the PL and be one of the top goalscorers.
*Team MVP - Harry Kane*

Leicester City

*Team MVP - Riyad Mahrez (Vardy if Mahrez leaves)

West Ham

*Team MVP - Dimitri Payet*

Southampton

*Team MVP - Virgil Van Djik*

Everton

*Team MVP - Romelu Lukaku (Ross Barkley if Lukaku leaves)

Stoke

*Team MVP - Xherdan Shaqiri

Crystal Palace

*Team MVP - Steven Mandanda

Swansea

*Team MVP - Ashley Williams*

Watford

*Team MVP - Troy Deeney*

Middlesborough

*Team MVP - Victor Valdes

Bournemouth

*Team MVP - Jordan Ibe*

West Brom

* Team MVP - Jose Rondon*

Sunderland

*Team MVP - Jermain Defoe*

Hull City

*Team MVP - Abel Hernandez*

Burnley

*Team MVP - Andre Gray*


**TEAM OF THE SEASON**


GK - David De Gea (MU)

RB - Hector Bellerin (ARS)

CB - Chris Smalling (MU)

CB - Toby Alderwield (TOT)

LB - Luke Shaw (MU)

CDM - Granit Xhaka (ARS)

RM - Riyad Mahrez (LEI)

CAM - Mesut Ozil (ARS) + Player of the Season IF Arsenal get better striker

LM - Eden Hazard (CHE)

ST - Zlatan Ibrahimovic (MU)

ST - Kun Aguero (MC)


RESERVES


Kevin De Bruyne (MC)

Laurent Koscielny (ARS)

Petr Cech (ARS)

Dimitri Payet (WH)

Alexis Sanchez (ARS)

N'golo Kante (CHE)

Moussa Dembele (TOT)

Virgil Van Djik (SOU)

Phillipe Coutinho (LIV)


**Biggest Improvement**

1. Alex Oxlade Chamberlain - Very impressive in preseason. Did you see that goal against the mexican team??!? If he can carry that form into the new season he could be instrumental to Arsenal's success

2. Eden Hazard - Will return to form after the fiasco that happened last season

3. Kelechi Iheanacho - Will continue to develop into a huge player for Man City

4. Jordan Ibe - More game time at Bournemouth. He still has potential to develop into a star.



**Leading Goalscorers**


1. Kun Aguero

2. Zlatan Ibrahimovic

3. Harry Kane 

4. Alexis Sanchez

5. Eden Hazard


**Leading Assists**


1. Mesut Ozil

2. Kevin De Bruyne

3. Christain Eriksen (TOT)

4. Eden Hazard

5. Dusan Tadic (SOU) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 13:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. Starting XI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 13:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Koscielny is a beast :) and would be a huge upgrade. Schneiderlin for Kante is debateable though. I actually rate Schneid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 13:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who would you be trading out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could take any player from your league who would you take, BUT they'll be traded with your own team's player in that position. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 13:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RULES

-Can only be players from your team's league

-Can't switch a player from their main position. (Eg. Alaba can play at CB but he mainly plays at LB, so you can only trade with your own LB.)

-Only players in the team's starting XI (edited in)

My choice would be Aguero for Giroud. I have great respect for him, and he's been consistently great (though injuries are an issue). Second choice would be Smalling for Mertesacker. I like Merts as a person but not as a player. Smalling is much faster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 12:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but Gray and Erza were the first of the original four (five if you include Happy) to be together. And I love their dynamic when they're by themselves.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 12:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stupid, sexy Flanders! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 12:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same thing for me with Walter White - Breaking Bad. I can't hate him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 12:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I like men now." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 12:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kent: 'Could Homer Simpson be a communist? His father spoke out on his behalf.'


Abe: 'Homer is not a communist. He may be a pig, a liar, an idiot, a communist, but he is NOT a PORNSTAR.'  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 12:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just started it! I hate him. But my friend said he was one of his favorite characters so maybe if I continue the show I will see a different side to him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 12:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not really a quote nor is it funny, but the episode where Homer gets the job at the nuclear plant to support his family (Maggie especially), was really touching. The 'Do it for her' poster was so heartwarming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which person (fictional or non fictional) do you love to hate and/or hate to love? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 12:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 11:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only one who'd rather have Erza x Gray over Erza and Jellal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 10:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Real shame. Wanted to see him vs Pepe again :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 10:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guess this means no Diego Costa to Atletico move  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favorite video that is 30 seconds or less? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 07:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 14:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HAHA! Huh? ew. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 14:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'baby in the corner' - Fall Out Boy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 14:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it from Malcom in the Middle? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
