<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject398</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 13:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the tips. I speak a very small amount of Spanish I learned for my 2 week look see to Costa Rica in 2010. I have been told my annunciation is very good and fell back on more Spanglish so people would understand I'm trying but if I started with Spanish they would  take off speaking and ... well... let me tell you... there is a whole lot of difference between speaking a small amount of a language and understanding it when it is spoken. But you are right, it made for a better connection when I used it. 
There are places I have lived and visited in the U.S. that the tips on how to handle money and keep it safe were necessary.
I'm still trying to figure out my travel plans as to where to start and how long to stay and such but your 3 countries you visited seem to be the logical places for me to land at first. Again, Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 03:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Central valley Costa Rica </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 19:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't drink much so the drunk creepy old guy shouldn't be a problem for me. I'll just have to fight my natural instincts to not become sober creepy old guy. Thanks for the reply. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 19:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, thanks for taking the time to reply in such depth. It is appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 19:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you leave out a couple "nots" in your post.... errrr... thanks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 19:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks u/guy_guyerson for the info. This is more the long term travel I'm looking at doing. Great info for me. Your blog will be helpful also. Maybe someday we will cross paths. Good traveling to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey Youngins, help an white haired old fart out here. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 15:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Solo, 62 yr old male getting ready to escape USA for at least the 2014 winter or longer in Central America. What are your suggestions for travel and stays? Any suggestions will be appreciated to avoid falling into the "creepy old dude trolling" category. I just don't want to set around waiting on my turn in a nursing home.

Edit#1, Thanks for the replies and good info, folks. This is a little scary for an old guy who has never traveled like this and your input is helping.

Edit #2, Wow, nice! You folks real are good people. Maybe a little more info about my situation may make this even more helpful for someone else like me just starting out on this sort of adventure/quest. So, I just started receiving Social Security of $1008 a month, that is all I have to live on for the rest of my time if I stop working and a big part on my travel is I figure I can have a better quality of life for that amount somewhere other that the USA. I am a member of workaway and plan on doing a good bit with those folks. So along with taking my time in different places I will be looking for a new place to plant this new me eventually.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 02:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frank "Tookie" DeLeo, cut his hair for a few years, became friends.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 02:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just posting to follow this. I believe this might get good.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 14:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are 7 listings for Antwerp on workaway.org </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 02:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> udemy.com
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 04:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was also called Goose Liver in my family. I though everyone called it that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 03:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> slowly and alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 02:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Travel often, play often, don't worry about establishing yourself to soon, it will happen. Be kind. An asshole be not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 02:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bleeding Madras. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 02:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whhhyyy do you build me up Buttercup... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 01:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stimulating the scalp causes increased blood flow to the head. Increased blood flow to the head means increased blood flow to the sinuses. Increased blood flow to the sinuses means enlarged blood vessels stimulate the nerves of said sinuses. Stimulated nerves in a sensitive person's sinuses is cause for a few good sneezes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 01:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are no naturally gray hairs. There are colored hairs and there are white hairs that are translucent. The colored hairs showing through the white hairs giving the over all look of gray. The whitening of hair is a sign of a lack of nutritional absorption. As we age most of us lose the ability to absorb certain vitamins and other nutrients. When our bodies are in short supply because of age or sickness of these it takes from the hair causing it to loose color. This is why I started graying at 17 and others never gray. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I start this affiliate business? I have an "in". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 16:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an "in" with a company that has a nice size niche where I can get a 10% affiliate percentage. The company up to now only pays a 3% affiliate commission and does have a few affiliates willing to work for that through the in-house program. Would you think it possible for me to go on some affiliate sites and offer a 5% commission with a 2.5% second tier and make a nice little passive income? What would be some pit falls I should watch for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 13:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good God I wouldn't want to live your life or even have you anywhere near me or my loved ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 19:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Highly charismatic.
Highly insightful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 14:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ANNND there you are... so simple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 14:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is an excellent idea. Wish I had time to do it. I'm leaving the USA for Central America this fall for a very extended period of time. But keep an eye on the site, if I use your idea you are very welcome to your 10%.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 14:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks I'll check them out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
