<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1563</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 17:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is exactly why I love stand up comedy. It's my own little safe space away from PC culture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 17:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's a strawman if I've ever seen one. How is not baking a cake for a gay wedding comparable to the murder of human beings?

And actually there are a lot of discrimination laws in place and currently lots of businesses have gotten in a lot of trouble for not serving certain kinds of people.

Are you saying that if someone starts up a private business, they should be forced to serve customers and should not be able to decide that they don't want to serve somebody? We're not talking about emergency medical care here. We're talking about baking a cake for somebody. Why should you have to serve somebody you don't want to? It's not like they wait for the person to pay and then don't give them service. They just decide that they aren't going to take that person's money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 17:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hipster is just shorthand for "anything I don't understand and don't like." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 17:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta get that le 90's kid cred!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 17:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please tell me what advantages being fat has in modern living? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 17:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you live in an area where every fucking business around is horribly bigoted and won't serve certain kinds of people, I don't think it's ridiculous to say that maybe you should move. I'm a straight white man and no way in hell would I live in an area that banned gays or banned Muslims or banned anyone on the basis of race, religion, gender etc. from using their business. I am also pretty sure this town would have absolutely no economy at all and it would be widely publicized as one of the worst places in America.  

Edit: I'm saying yes, it's awful for businesses to discriminate like this and they shouldn't do it. However, I don't think any business should be legally required to serve anybody. Name one business that has openly discriminated against certain kinds of people and didn't lose business because if it. By nature, these kinds of places will suffer economically from discriminating. You decide as a business you won't serve gay people? They're just gonna go to your competitor then. And if you happen to live in a fictional part of America where your kind of people are not taken well at all and businesses everywhere don't wanna serve you, I don't see why you would want to stay there anyways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 16:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then you chose the wrong area to live in. Move. Or bake your own cake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 19:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol yep heard that line about 20 times. Watched him plummet to his death off the cliff by the graveyard. So satisfying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 17:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the biggest lesson learned from dark souls is that actions have consequences. You entered a boss fight before preparing? Say goodbye to all the humanity and souls you just acquired. Attacked an NPC? Have fun getting killed over and over again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 17:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm not trying to be morally superior, we're all enjoying a life of comfort and easy modern living.  Wasn't even really trying to make a statement this just came to mind when I read the comment and I found it ironic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 15:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shilling with an awfully written meme with multiple misspelled words and it has over 6000 upvotes. Fuck you, Reddit. Fuck you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 15:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Props to anyone who tries no death runs. I would never even attempt it for any game, ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 15:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, [everyone](https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Er1kTF3smOE/hqdefault.jpg) should eat that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 14:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, Reddit has a weird affinity for Islam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 14:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dark Souls. Bought it on steam on a sale, never played it until now. It starts out kinda clunky and my first thought was that it seems outdated, but I was totally wrong. I'm loving it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 19:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel you there. I love Rick and Morty, love Archer and love Bob's burgers, but I never bring it up to people because most of the time I hate the people who talk about those shows. It's like they think watching those shows makes them interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 19:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went from being a communication major to computer science and holy shit what a different crowd.

 Communication was totally wrong for me and was a stupid major, but I do miss being around people with social skills, even if some of them are as dumb as bricks. 

If only there could be more mathematically inclined and computer literate people who could actually socialize. There's only a handful of people in my major that actually speak during class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 19:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A scorpion. Absolutely deadly but with a pair of boots and good timing I could crush it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 19:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean it's hard to say that he got the joker totally wrong because there are multiple jokers. He obviously was chaotic and there were definitely a few humorous moments, but clearly he was a deranged and dark joker. I just think of Ledger as a different take on the joker, I wouldn't say a bad joker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 19:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean any good villain is relatable. Just because you can see where he's coming from, or he seems to have justification for what he does, doesn't mean he's evil. When a character's morality boils down to the ends justify the means, they're pretty much always evil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 13:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am straight white male. Don't want to eradicate minorities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 21:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just commented that! Listen to it every day on my commute to and from school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 21:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Waking up with Sam Harris. The latest ones he's been discussing AI a lot and his guests have been awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 17:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess /r/explainsomethingtomeinawaythaticanunderstandbutdoesntgrosslyoversimplifyit  just wasn't a catchy subreddit name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 16:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't remember the last time someone said "thank God" and then blew up a bunch of innocent people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 16:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then you'd probably have a handful of dollars... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 19:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually impossible to not be yourself. No matter what you do, it's you doing it. If I decide to spastically start murdering everyone in sight, though it's not usual for me to do that, I'm still being me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 19:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes always and it takes up a lot of time when I'm taking tests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 03:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would have been cool. I think though it would be cool and not even that complicated to open up a dialog option which lets you either be merciful and let them flee, take all their shit or just kill them anyways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 18:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If that's true, why the fuck haven't they patched it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 15:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't remember the last time I got a genuine compliment, usually they're backhanded compliments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 03:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to have one buy my cousin broke it unfortunately. Unless you buy the expensive ones they aren't too sturdy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 01:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean I can imagine the longer you're in a relationship the less desire you have for sex with your SO. Seems pretty natural. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 16:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll have to try doing that. My other problem now is that I'm too weak to one hand zweihander so it's nice to be able to have a shield and a weapon, which is another advantage of using halberd right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 16:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Noob at this game, is it stupid to be upgrading two different weapons? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 17:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been using zweihander +5 for the most part but I'm finding in confined spaces it doesn't do too well because it keeps hitting walls so for that I use halberd +5 with a shield in my left arm. Is it a waste to do this? I'm trying to do a strength build. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 17:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you get that many souls/aren't you afraid to be running around with that much to lose? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 17:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, it's a video game. No actual harm is being done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 17:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not gonna lie, I got absolutely destroyed by it probably the first few times I fought it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 17:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just bought the game a couple weeks ago and this is the kind of stuff happened to me a couple times. Honestly just see it as a learning experience. Yeah it sucks that you lost all those souls, but now you'll be smarter next time and make sure to get to a bonfire when carrying that many souls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 17:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "When you play the game of thrones you either win or you die. There is no middle ground." - Cersei Lannister </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 19:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is how gayness happens /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 04:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think twice before entering an area you haven't gone to yet. Humanity and a massive amount of souls can quickly go down the drain. Also, try not to die in an area you can't get back to fairly easily if you do die.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 04:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My hilarious friend is disabled you cunt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 15:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally unplayable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 14:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean yeah of course I'll agree with you that Rick isn't such a good guy either. He's always had the attitude of shoot first, think second. The difference is that Rick doesn't seem to enjoy the killing. If Rick were to decide someone had to die, he'd shoot them. He wouldn't bash someone's brains in with a bat and smile the whole time doing it. He also wouldn't burn half of someone's face in front of everyone...and he sure as hell wouldn't force every woman he wants to be one of his wives and taunt the men they were with.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 05:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's psychologically manipulating people. The only seemingly good things Negan does is really for manipulation purposes. He just wants to continue doing whatever the hell he feels like and that means not being cruel all of the time. Negan obviously enjoys toying with people, harming them and killing them. Clearly a psychopath, but he's not an idiot. He knows he's gotta throw people a bone here and there to keep them happy.

Yes Negan is doing a lot of these awful things to maintain authority and to keep things going smoothly, but I don't see how he isn't a bad guy. What does he use his power for? He fucks all the women he wants, he humiliates people and he brutalizes and/or kills anyone who misbehaves. He hasn't shown that he's doing what he does to make the world a better place. You're falling for an obvious villain trope.

http://tvtropes.org/pmwiki/pmwiki.php/Main/NotEvilJustMisunderstood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 04:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> piece of pizza

Bruh... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 00:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what you mean about that second part, almost makes takes away from immersion when you're trying to be a certain type of character. However, it makes sense that you couldn't be strong enough alone. 

Edit: also forgot to say that yes absolutely the Miraak fight was so badass. 

[ "So the first Dragonborn meets the last Dragonborn at the summit of Apocrypha. No doubt as Hermaeus Mora intended."](/spoiler) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 00:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess you're right. I just felt a lot more stressed and overwhelmed in the Oblivion final battle, and really felt immersed with all the Daedra attacking the imperial city. I felt more like I was trying to save the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 17:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You didn't think the whole scheme to get into Camoran's Paradise was cool? And then fighting off hordes and hordes of Daedra in the imperial city and having Martin turn into the avatar of akatosh was cool? No you didn't get to fight Dagon one-on-one, but clearly he'd obliterate you with no effort. I guarantee you if you remade the final part of the game on Skyrim's engine, it would absolutely demolish Skyrim's ending. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 16:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. I wanted to rp a character that had a strong curiosity about the world and cared about truth and understanding above all else. The blades are the total antithesis to that, so it was frustrating to have to work with them so much. I just wanted to hang out in High Hrothgar and talk philosophy with Paarthurnax  and pretty much become a Greybeard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 16:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alduin was just a harder dragon fight, and when you spend the entire game killing dragons it's really a disappointment. After playing and beating Oblivion, which has such an epic final battle, Skyrim's ending was just lackluster. There wasn't really anything special about the Alduin fight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 16:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that was kind of weird...who does that stuff?

*spends an hour putting buckets on guards' heads* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 15:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ESO isn't canon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 17:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try and lure him by an edge somewhere, I think there should be some stairs down by the graveyard. Just time a good hit and make him fall to his death. I am new to the game and made the same mistake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 19:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just checked. Confirmed true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 19:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disagree at all on /r/feminism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 15:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The "true solution" is one that works.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 14:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's because he's charismatic and because he's a liberal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 13:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The libertarian in me says prostitution should be legal, but I personally hate the idea of prostitution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 03:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This game is absolutely unreal with the glitches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 03:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would hope so as someone who is voting third party, but the establishment would never want a third party in there. Whoever took Clinton's place would be a weak candidate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 02:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A private business should have the right to discriminate. If I am setting up a shop somewhere, I alone should get to choose who I hire and who I serve. In practice, I wouldn't want to discriminate because 1)I'm not an asshole and 2) it's idiotic from a business standpoint.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 02:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DAE Islam and Christianity aren't so different??????????? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 02:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Morrowind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 02:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it reads more like, "bitch u won't, 1v1 me faget." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 02:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah and they'd lose.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 00:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An amulet of Mara. You're looking for marriage, then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 22:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Trump supporters would be the most vocal. Bernie Supporters would shit themselves because that means Trump wins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 22:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guy here. Honestly I'd love someone to ask me to come do calculus tbh. Shits hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 22:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know. Others already explained. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 20:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I responded to someone else already. I understand it in that context, it's when I hear it uses in other ways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 15:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assuming platform doesn't matter


Skyrim

Majora's Mask HD remake

Mortal Kombat X


I normally don't like mortal Kombat that much but that's because I'm too impatient to learn all the combos and special moves for each character. With three months, maybe I'd become pretty good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 15:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely don't have the body type for that  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 05:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard it said as in, "that guy's an asshole, innit?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 05:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "innit" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 00:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 00:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Generally they're annoying and get in the way, but on certain quests they can help. Earlier on with the character I'm using now, I'd get absolutely destroyed by any type of magic so having a companion to distract mages and different kinds of magical creatures helped me to not get rekt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 00:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's a decent costume for a guy for $15 and minimal effort? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 00:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "straight" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 22:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd argue that abortions are more of a gray area. You're talking about killing a developing fetus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 22:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ITT: Games I'd rate 9/11 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 20:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aenel Bede. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 19:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No because running Skyrim on the highest settings now drops my frame rate a lot. I'd love to if I could. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 19:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't either </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 19:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's fun to do sometimes, but I could never do a whole playthrough without fast travel. It's just too inconvenient. Great for immersion though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 15:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that was a lot weirder than I thought it would be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 15:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good episode, phenomenal acting by the characters, but I have to say that I still don't think the cliffhanger was worth it and I'm annoyed at how they didn't show right away who it was. My fears that this is just going to continue to drag on the plot, leave us at cliffhangers and barely deliver are not alleviated. I'm not gonna lie, I was downright angry at the show when it was Abraham who was picked. If Glenn didn't go too, I would have stopped watching.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 15:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally no one is stopping you. If you're too self conscious to do what you want to do, you have no one to blame but yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 15:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Believing that Jesus was God in the flesh, that he performed miracles and that he rose from the dead and saved us all from sin with absolutely no evidence is seen as a respectable belief, but believing Bigfoot exists makes you insane. I'm not trying to be edgy, but I'm really baffled as to why we give religious beliefs special treatment even though they are no more plausible than belief in Bigfoot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 06:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just don't think about it all the time. There's no really dealing with it. Never do I fully just accept that I'm going to die. It's inconceivable. The only thing that is comforting is that I'm not the only one. Literally everyone dies, so I guess that's just how it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 06:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew that I would only hurt her by pursuing anything further, since I just got cancer from reading this post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 05:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ben Shapiro said it best that when Trump and Hillary attack eachother, they're both telling the truth. When they're defending themselves, they're lying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 05:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about no. It's not the job of anyone to prove that they aren't racist by pandering to nutjobs like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 04:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like Trump  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most ridiculous supervillain you can come up with? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 02:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 02:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I could still fap to her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 02:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not about your character, your accomplishments or your ideas, it's who you choose to fuck and how you feel about your gender that makes you an interesting person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 02:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slam poetry is an awful mix between poetry and rap, combining the worst elements of both and not rhyming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 02:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted a comment but I would love one set during the time where Dwemer dominated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 02:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An Elder Scrolls game set during the height of Dwemer civilization. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 16:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I haven't gone full archer but I made a heavy armor character with sword and shield, using a bow as a secondary weapon. Killing dragons is pretty damn hard without it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
