<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2469</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Survivor Part 2, Digital Painting, 200MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 11:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 12:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here are the options that I think you could take:

1) You keep your current channel even if you change content: 200views per videos is not that bad, many people would love to have that, let's forget about the subscriber count for now...maybe you could start off building your new content audience from there. You might expect people to leave but you know if you start from zero, it will take a lot more time...

2) You make a new channel but actively advertise it on your old channel. Perhaps some people would like to follow you to your new channel and maybe later all of the inactive people will notice you. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Black Neko,Digital Painting, 300MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 09:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 06:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I can see that my subs viewership is poor, but it's not miserable so I haven't lost hope yet. It might still happen, but even if it doesn't happen, I'll just have to continue working harder then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 15:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it is OK to use smudge tool to blend, but I'm using Clip studio paint pro so there is a variety of blending tools...I think smudge tool is equivalent to "blend".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 14:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Survivor, Digital Painting, 200MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 13:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 07:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started to post videos in July 2015 ... I did a lot of promotions paid and unpaid and now I'm at 1K. Currently waiting for some snowball effects :-/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 05:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  thank you, I really like that method :3
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Demon hunter part 2 [Digital Paiting] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 17:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Demon hunter (final process), Digital Painting, 200MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 08:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy curl, Digital painting, 7MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 10:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 09:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no...no..nono....nope. Nope. No problem :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 22:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you need to your parts of that video and not all of it...if you use too much...on the other hand if you are not monetising, I think it could be alright. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 20:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My video for this month https://youtu.be/5-v1-ekrHRU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 20:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 12:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, it also happened to me, but it was fixed after one day...just give it some time it's probably just a delay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WIP: "Happy curl" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 11:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy curl (work in progress) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 19:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Halloween Candies, Digital Painting, 200MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 14:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 08:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd advice to be as organic as possible, and focus more on healthy and/or organic makeups. Health is the most important and where I live for example, people are more and more fond of organic stuff. Maybe you could do some research about the pros and cons of a particular product and discuss the risk associated...but of course you'll also have to demonstrate a strong knowledge on how to use makeups ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 15:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> of course it's nice to get more subscriber, everyone would like that :D ... but I'm only talking about what should be in priority (which is to enjoy yourself), otherwise it wouldn't make sense anymore to post videos :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 09:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say that I really wish I had this 10% viewership ... mine is much lower...and yes as the others said, being subscribed to a channel doesn't mean one is gonna watch every single videos :) ... the only thing to do is try hard to make more and more interesting/appealing content. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 08:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is really pleasing to look at 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 08:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the most important thing is to enjoy yourself and to make something you really really like...the result is often good when you do it with your heart...simply because you will not feel all your efforts and aim to improve your videos more and more, no matter what ... especially if you are  new youtuber who will surely not get much views at the beginning :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Demon Hunter, Digital Painting, 200MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 20:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 18:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you should just be yourself, because if you try to pretend older than you are, you may give the impression that you're fake. I see a lot of young youtubers that do just fine :) ... have fun :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 18:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you didn't stop posting new videos regularly...I guess now it's spring and it will be summer soon...I'd suspect that people spend less time on youtube and on the internet because they would go out and enjoy the sun :) ... hopefully you'll get back to your regular views count when it's cooler... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thumbs up final, Digital Painting, 200MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 09:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thumbsup, Digital Painting, 200MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 16:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 00:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 10:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's a good start but as a general advise and from my personal experience, keep videos less than 10min long or as short as possible ... and yes you already pointed out the lack of liveliness, I'd advice to do a little bit of stretching and warming up even if you just woke up...make sure your body is fully awake before recording :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 17:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think your idea is a bit ambitious, it is hard enough to get an audience on youtube and the first reason people goes to youtube is because they mostly want quality stuff for free...however, if you manage to get 1million subscribers then I guess it could work...On the other hand I'd like to comment on: "My goal is to produce a profit so we can start paying our actors and crew for their valuable time, and eventually make this a full time gig for everyone involved."... I'm sorry to say that if this is a business plan, you have to invest and pay your crew yourself to produce quality content, unless you are surrounded with people who do not mind working for free for years or you have some of those overly-talented people that would make your audience jump in the blink of an eye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My colourful sketch for a challenge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 17:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 12:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the second episode of my art diary series, I made a surprise challenge with another artist youtuber https://youtu.be/mXM2Nv5gjMw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The hero meets his destiny Part 2, Digital Painting, 200MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 17:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 09:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds really fun idea, I agree with the others don't tell them to share...hope you'll get there ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 13:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for sharing, sounds really useful :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The hero and his destiny, Digital Painting, 200MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 13:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 09:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 09:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roses (My first speed painting video), Digital Painting, 500MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 07:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 06:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you :D ...I'll consider your advice in my next videos  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Review Video] Art talk: Skills and Creativity + drawing cute cats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 11:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the first video of a new series I am making. https://youtu.be/AeklXexxDSQ
Self review: According to the advices I had here last time I posted narrated video, I got myself a microphone and increased the volume of my voice. I feel like I could improve more on the script because I realise now that there was some stuff that I repeated twice. I also still need to get more comfortable while talking, it's really hard to talk alone in one's room.
Reviews:
https://www.reddit.com/r/youtubers/comments/4eilef/review_video_how_to_make_money_as_an_artist/
https://www.reddit.com/r/youtubers/comments/4eknkv/review_video_response_to_1159_arrow_s04e18/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 10:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think its a nice video, the lightening fits right. But I feel like you could improve a bit on the narrating a be a bit more energetic especially since you are sitting. You could also add closed caption to the video to make easier to follow your chatting, and it's recommended as well for youtube creators to help improve search results. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 10:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the other said the music is a bit loud and it's a bit distracting, I think you are talking really good, fluid and natural. How many time did you record? if I may ask? ...thank you very much for the nice review, I find it really useful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some Art talk while drawing cute cats, Digital painting, 200MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 07:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 10:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you ^^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 10:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're welome ^_^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 07:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally do not like to hear too much swearing...for some people it even sounds like a disease when the put "f*ck" in every single sentence they say ... no offence but I don't find that funny... I personally use these languages only when I'm really angry ...though sometimes people can sound really funny while swearing, but that really depends on the person, it doesn't add anything more to the content the person is already making...I think it's better to just be yourself, swearing or not swearing, just be true to yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Dreamy Cyclops part 3, Digital Painting, 300MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 07:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 17:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh My God, I love this so much  so I posted it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Blacklight, webang111, Digital Painting, 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 17:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 15:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes you're right...shushushu...go away temptation!!!! lol ... I'll keep praying and making some incantations to keep focused w </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Come with me, part 1, Digital Painting, 300MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 21:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 20:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it was nice to watch...for the ending, perhaps you could try out a zoom in or zoom out on the drawing...maybe scan it and attach to the ending of the video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 20:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you meant "lots of Youtubers have SIMILAR video" and not "EXACT same video" ... I know you didn't mean the latest because it would be funny since it sounds like you uploaded someone else's content on your channel. As for the take down part, I guess it should have something to do with how much length of the video did you watch on the camera? if you watched the video till the end that means you have 100% of someone else's content on your video so I think the take down could come from there....Though I might be also wrong, I haven't yet faced that issue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lotus Elf </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 13:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 18:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I drew Einstein, hope you enjoy, thanks for watching :D </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 17:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 15:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an artwork inspired from one of my favourite artist...thought it's totally different from the one he/she made in both concept and quality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mermaid in the moonlight Part 1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 15:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 14:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> either these video got viral or the channel owner paid for those views or have a huge social media following that are not subscribers. I've recently been tempted to make some random cat videos on my channel to get exposure o.O, which is totally off my topic...but it's hard to fight the temptation.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Swan, Digital Painting, 300MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 18:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Cyclops part 2, Digital Painting, 300MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 21:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 09:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly do not like any channels that lack channel info...and I become reluctant to check channels that have hidden subs....In fact I look at the subs number, the date of creation of the channel the channel info and then check out some videos....but once I can't do one of those, I become lazy to do the others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 09:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the right question to ask is: "Will Disney allow you to film their parks?", only Disney can flag Disney related stuff ... if yes then the next question is would you monetise the content or not...If you don't monetise your content then, Disney has no reason to flag your content...If you do monetise but don't get any considerable amount from it, I think Disney will leave you alone...the trigger for flagging you is alway how much money you make...for example I read somewhere that Disney would claim any disney related content that reaches over 1 million views...and I guess it's the same for any big companies...So you can have as much fun as you want as long as money is out of the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch me draw a mermaid, subscribe for more art and occasional tutorials/narration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 11:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Cyclops, Digital Painting, 500MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 10:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A dreamy cyclops </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 10:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Foreign Disciple part 2, Digital Painting, 500MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 16:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 10:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you :D, my watch time increased when I put the final product first...I also do that because some people may not be so much interested in the process so they can leave whenever they want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 10:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you for the feedback, I'll think about them :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 07:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you for checking out...in fact I did that in the beginning and the watch time was worst. Latte,r when I have more subscribers, I can try again, but for now I don't want to change what's working. I'll be thinking about the outro  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 19:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you for the review and the advice, I'll do so ^_^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 19:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you for the review, I'll probably work on some commentary later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A foreign disciple, Digital Painting, 500MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 14:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 12:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with the others, getting commissioned is one of the best way, but you'll also need to have outstanding skills, people wants to get what's worth their money unless you find people that are just super fan of your work and just want to support you no matter what the quality. You can also take a look at patreon.com or tapastic.com but it really depends on your audience and fan-base...Hope this helps and good luck :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Review Video]Speedpainting: I'd like some opinion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 10:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello all,

This is my latest speedpainting video https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_8h5eR4BN8c

Self review: I feel like I speed it up a bit too much, I tried to combine the speed with the rhythm of the music but let me know if it makes you feel dizzy or anything else that might be a problem. Thank you 

Two reviews:
https://www.reddit.com/r/youtubers/comments/4bnns3/review_video_sketch_channel/
https://www.reddit.com/r/youtubers/comments/4bqmwd/review_video_newest_photoshop_video_on_my_channel/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 09:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> colourful chicken ... however, I think you could find a better representation of your title, the only thing you do is really just replacing the eggs by the chicken. The title is interesting so I think you should keep trying to build better content around it ^_^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rei Ayanami by webang111 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 20:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 20:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is it just me or the video is moving back and forth, it made me a bit dizzy...the sound is really low, maybe your mic is not good...and lastly, I would suggest to use closed captions (cc) to help the viewer follow better...good luck with your channel and work hard ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
