<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3240</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 02:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cockroaches. I had vivid dreams (still do) so when I had nightmares, they were awful for me. I had one that my mom turned into this giant cockroach and ate our house. I was pretty young (maybe like 4?) so as silly as it sounds, I was terrified. 

Fast forward a few years and while I don't like them, I can breathe normally even if they're in the same room. Mom decides to break me of this phobia at the State Fair by forcing me to hold a Madagascar Hissing Roach. Thankfully, I screamed right before it touched me and everyone was staring at this mother holding her kid by the arm as she's having a panic attack. We got out of there quick. Ever since I get panicky just seeing pictures of them. The more I see on sidewalks at night, the more nervous I get. If I get too close to one, I'll start freaking out. Can take an hour for me to calm down and stop checking every corner, sock, etc. for them.

It's gotten a little better (my boyfriend has helped a lot since instead of getting irritated with me like my mom, he just reassures me everything is okay) but I doubt it'll ever go away completely. Makes night time walks really difficult.

TL;DR Irrational phobia of cockroaches causes me to have hour-long anxiety episodes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 01:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This reply is late but wanted to say that I've seen the cow eye disection at that museum before (I also live in AZ) and good lord, we left an egg out after Easter once by accident and even in the spring, the heat just destroys everything. We found it simply on smell alone. Praying for your poor nose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 01:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always been pretty good at getting away with shit, but I do remember when my sister was about 4 (I'm older so I would have been 7) wrote all over the walls with marker, wrote "jane did this" (my name) and then tried to blame me for it. The problem with this was that 4 year old handwriting and spelling is very, very different from 7 year old handwriting and spelling.

She was pretty upset while scrubbing the walls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 17:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have a coffee shop here called Bikini Bean and while I'm sure that says enough, all the girls that work there wear bikinis. The coffee is pretty good, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 19:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100% Wisconsin Cheese Curds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 19:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every gemini I've met (including myself) talks a lot. But we have the best stories! ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 19:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People from Arizona are actually all super pale (not tan like people think) because none of us go outside (when it is 115 F, hell no) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
