<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2997</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 08:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meanwhile Barry wears a suit that looks like ice cream </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 08:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arya's a good assassin but she couldn't take anyone in this field in a straight-up fight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 08:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright let's do this (I mean it can hardly do worse than my actual brackets tend to do):

**Jon's Region**

1 Jon Snow defeats 8 Kovarro

4 Bronn defeats 5 Syrio Forell

3 Daario Naharis defeats 6 Ramsay Snow/Bolton

2 The Hound defeats 7 Qhorin Halfhand

4 Bronn defeats 1 Jon Snow 

2 The Hound defeats 3 Daario Naharis

4 Bronn defeats 2 The Hound

**The Mountain's Region**

1 The Mountain defeats 8 Meryn Trant

4 Robb Stark defeats 5 Karl Tanner

3 Barristan Selmy defeats 3 Beric Dondarrion

2 Robert Baratheon defeats 7 Ygritte

1 The Mountain defeats 4 Robb Stark

3 Barristan Selmy defeats 2 Robert Baratheon

1 The Mountain defeats 3 Barristan Selmy

**Jaime's Region**

1 Jaime Lannister defeats 8 Janos Slynt

5 Grey Worm defeats 4 Brynden Tully

6 Stannis Baratheon defeats 3 Loras Tyrell

2 Ned Stark defeats 7 Alliser Thorne

1 Jaime Lannister defeats 5 Grey Worm

6 Stannis Baratheon defeats 2 Ned Stark

1 Jaime Lannister defeats 6 Stannis Baratheon

**Drogo's Region**

1 Khal Drogo defeats 8 Rodrick Cassel

4 Tormond Giantsbane defeats 5 Areo Hotah

3 Brienne of Tarth defeats 6 Yara Greyjoy

2 Oberyn Martell defeats 7 Benjen Stark

1 Khal Drogo defeats 4 Tormond Giantsbane

2 Oberyn Martell defeats 3 Brienne of Tarth

2 Oberyn Martell defeats 1 Khal Drogo 

**Final Four**

1 The Mountain defeats 4 Bronn

2 Oberyn Martell defeats 1 Jaime Lannister

2 Oberyn Martell defeats 1 The Mountain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 07:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because he's wrong. Finals are pretty much always left vs right on the bracket, not top vs bottom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 07:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it hasn't.

[Here](http://www.ncaa.com/march-madness-live/bracket) is the current official NCAA bracket. In the semifinals the East Region's champion will play with West Region's champion and the Midwest Region's champion will play with South Region's champion, since the the number one overall seed (Villanova) was in the East and the number four overall seed (Gonzaga) is in the West. Left vs Right, not Top vs Bottom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 04:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 04:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By that logic everyone who buys gasoline refined from Saudi oil is literally supporting human rights abuses and terrorism.

The show isn't donating to Sorbo's political fund, they're paying him to do a job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HBO has always shown promos for their own programming. They don't interrupt the show you're watching, they're just at the beginning (on cable they're between shows). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 01:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Americans isn't FX's worst-rated show; this season it's 8th out of 15 in viewers and 10th out of 15 in the 18-49 demo (FX's current lowest-rated show is Sex Drugs Rock Roll, which they cancelled). Also FX is a cable network so it's business model is significantly different from that of a broadcast network like NBC.

 NBC just loves cancelling well-made shows and replacing them with shit.

NBC loves cancelling shows with shit ratings and replacing them with shows they hope won't have shit ratings. But they renewed Hannibal twice despite its shit ratings, and for that you should be thankful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 01:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing as ratings translate directly into revenue for the network and the network is a business, yeah, renewing their worst-rated show was arguably rather generous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hannibal was NBC's worst-rated show in its second season and they renewed it anyway, which is far more generous than networks usually are. You should be thankful that you got even 3 seasons of Hannibal given how bad its viewership was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're mad about Hannibal getting cancelled blame all the people who didn't watch it, not NBC who gave it a third season in spite of its abysmal ratings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The relationship itself is kind of the usual cw standard and has been done before.

This has been my feeling regarding Alex/Maggie the entire time. It's a stereotypical CW relationship and as such I don't care much about it. Also it's pretty clear that Maggie's purpose was to be Alex's love interest first and her own character second, which adds to my disinterest in the relationship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And basically, what OP is describing is Yield on Cost (YoC)

So back to my original question: how is Yield on Cost a useful metric? Using YoC to make investment decisions just seems like classic anchoring bias. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obligatory reminder that TBBT is one of the top shows in the 18-34 demo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it's one of the most-watched shows on TV </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 05:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blucifer already killed the guy who build it, just imagine what it could have done if it were this size... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 05:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  it has the picture of Maedhros (I think?) throwing a Silmaril into the ocean.

That'd be Maglor. Maedhros threw himself and his Silmaril into a fiery chasm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 03:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think ratings only get reported publicly because they're measured by a third party (and even then, the Nielsen data that gets released publicly is but a small fraction of the data networks get from them). In-house data like streaming numbers are hardly ever released by anyone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 03:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are lots of fiscally irresponsible people, and dealing with a big lump-sum income isn't something most people are really prepared for. Most lottery winners go broke within a few years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 03:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not at all surprised that people are still willing to do it; plenty of people would probably have been willing to do it for less than 1 million originally, but $1 million made for a nicer round number. $1 million is still a huge sum for most people, and it's only a 30% decrease in real terms compared to 17 years ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 03:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arrow S2 is also generally considered a bit better than S1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 22:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is true but not really relevant to /u/I_Have_3_Legs's question. Filming for Prison Break didn't conflict with filming for LoT, Dominic Purcell did both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 21:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure that's a bright side </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 21:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> However the post-Flashpoint reboot was due to Doctor Manhattan screwing with things, not Flashpoint itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But Knights weren't common soldiers, they were a rank of nobility. Men who would become Knights generally did start training as children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or you know, knock and ask if the room is occupied. But usually if the door is closed and the light on inside you can just assume the room is occupied. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 08:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 08:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrestling was a very important skill for a knight. Fighting in full plate armor would often involved wresting moves because of how much the armor limited the effectiveness of most weapons (for instance armored longsword fencing was arguably closer to 'wresting with swords' than to modern fencing). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 08:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Does the Knight's rigorous adherence to his battle etiquette get in the way of his being able to preform if the Marine decides to play dirty?

The knights' "rigorous adherence to his battle etiquette" wasn't really a thing. Knights fought to win and had no problem with fighting dirty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh people interpret ratings stupidly all the time on this sub (and elsewhere); that doesn't mean the statistic itself is useless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as ratings translate directly into money for the network they're not irrelevant; a producer joking about them doesn't change that. Sure first-run ad sales not the only way WB/CBS makes money on the CW shows, and it presumably makes up a lower percentage of total revenue for CW shows compared to shows on the big 4 networks, but it's still significant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was 2015-2016, not 2016-2017. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 03:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Why don't people use the search function?](https://www.reddit.com/r/FlashTV/search?q=what+happened+to+gideon restrict_sr=on) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 02:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt cutting the episode counts would improve the writing as much as many people seem to think. 

But more importantly, cutting the episode counts would decrease the amount of money the CW would make on the shows, so it's unlikely to happen (premium channels have a very different business model from broadcast networks). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 02:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm going to wait to believe this until I see it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 01:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Has there been any news on when it's starting?

No, because it hasn't even been ordered to series yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 22:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  What if you can't tell if someone's in there or not? 

Then knock and/or ask if there's anyone in there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bathrooms often have locks but it's pretty common to not bother to use them. Generally people just follow common courtesy and don't go into the bathroom when it's already occupied.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 18:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But why use the price at which you bought a stock as the denominator in the yield calculation rather than the current value? That's not the way yield is typically calculated, and doesn't really do anything aside from conflating price appreciation and actual dividend yield. Saying that different people simultaneously get different yields on the same stock simply because the purchased it at different times makes little sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 17:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Now, you have $0.75/share dividend, which when compared to your initial $10 purchase price yields 7.5%. 

How is (current dividend)/(price from years ago) a useful metric? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 17:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At long last we have the identity of the hacker known as 4Chan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 07:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well in a sense Fifty Shades *is* Twilight, seeing as it originated as Twilight fanfiction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 05:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You don't fight with honor!"

"No. He did..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 21:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [No they've been dropping,](http://tvseriesfinale.com/tv-show/arrow-tv-show-cw-season-five-ratings/) although not too massively. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I mean Oliver Queen lost his company and then when Felicity Smoak stopped being the CEO of Palmer tech

By any semblance of logic Oliver and Felicity (and possibly Thea) should still collectively own most if not all of Palmer Tech. Granted the show ignores this, but then it also ignores the matter of how Team Arrow is financed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 08:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We should get this. But we won't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 07:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well Wyoming *could* do this but it would be pretty damn pointless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 06:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it's pretty bad; OP didn't seem to realize that a convertible bond is not the same thing as a warrant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 06:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP's math assumes Tesla is selling warrants, but they're actually selling convertible bonds. So OP effectively forgot to account for things like interest payments and repayment of principal; the analysis is worthless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kreisberg wasn't a creator of Fringe and was only with the show for a short time, he's only credited as a producer in seven episodes, six in the the second half of S1 and one in S2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More odd than an army of superintelligent telepathic gorillas invading from a parallel universe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Means people named Bruce, Hal, and Diana exist in that universe. Does not mean Batman, Wonder Woman, Green Lantern, or any dort of Justice League exist in that universe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean it's free, so yeah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The CW app only ever has the last 5 episodes of a show </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was just an easter egg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 23:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But those shows use laughter from a live studio audience, instead of simple canned laughter!

As does TBBT, but many people seem to ignore that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 22:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sub is for discussion without circlejerking, shitposting, or overly antagonistic behavior. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 21:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Not quite through the roof, but quite solid for FX.](http://tvseriesfinale.com/tv-show/fx-tv-show-ratings-33426/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You say that like Legion had poor viewership, which isn't that case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, many of the Marvel Netflix shows drag heavily at times, meanwhile AoS does 22 episode seasons with much faster pacing and little filler. Fewer episodes can help but mostly it just comes down to quality; the reason the Berlanti DC shows have stupid unnecessary drama is mostly that they're poorly written, not that they have too many episodes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plenty of older millennials watch it, just not necessarily your personal acquaintances. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christine Baranski plays Leonard's mom. Laurie Metcalf plays Sheldon's mom in TBBT; her daughter Zoe Perry will play Sheldon's mom in this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When WB buys out CBS's stake in the network </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  All together DC/WB/CW made over a billion dollars on just the CW/DC Universe

The DC shows (not just the CW ones, Gotham is big here) accounted for $1 billion in revenue, not profit.

 In five years, their entire superhero lineup could be generating more revenue than Disney is making on film and at a fraction of the cost.

Yeah, no. A single Avengers movie pulls over a billion at the box office. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a trailer for season 1, not the animated series, so I don't see how there would be anything misleading about it as far as the animated series goes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Constantine is getting continued as an animated series on CW Seed (like Vixen), no live-action plans at the moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  but I will mention that the CW writers have been really hamfisted with the Mon-El arc, compared with how the CBS writers handled the relationships in Season 1.

Just to be clear, WB produces the show and the writers are mostly same from season 1 to season 2. But I don't doubt that the network change has resulted in different instructions being given to the writers.

Otherwise I agree with everything in your comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [tvseriesfinale](http://tvseriesfinale.com) is a good source for ratings.

This season of TWD is averaging a 5.5 in the 18-49 demo (Live+SD), with its most recent episode getting a 4.7. That's the best on AMC by a huge amount ([source](http://tvseriesfinale.com/tv-show/amc-network-tv-show-ratings-33643/)) and easily better than any other current cable show (Game of Thrones will likely be close once its its next season comes out as it averaged a [3.85](http://tvseriesfinale.com/tv-show/hbo-tv-show-ratings-33447/) last season). It's also better than any show on the major broadcast networks ([ABC](http://tvseriesfinale.com/tv-show/abc-tv-show-2016-2017-season-ratings/), [CBS](http://tvseriesfinale.com/tv-show/cbs-tv-show-2016-2017-season-ratings/), [Fox](http://tvseriesfinale.com/tv-show/fox-tv-show-2016-2017-season-ratings/), [NBC](http://tvseriesfinale.com/tv-show/nbc-tv-show-2016-2017-season-ratings/)). If you looks at the ratings for other networks you'll see that nothing tops TWD and very few shows are even close.

It terms of overall viewership it's also top on cable by quite a bit, but there are a few broadcast shows that beat it in that metric.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 08:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the Kara/Lena relationship (and it's easily more compelling that Kara/Mon-El or Alex/Maggie) but I feel like the interesting aspects of it would be ruined by making it romantic. In the hands of better writers perhaps it could work, but not Berlanti's crew. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 07:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Savitar is Jaqen H'ghar confirmed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 07:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe doing that would be what is known as "playing one's self". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 07:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I wonder what the ratings point AMC execs have in their mind where they'll go "Okay okay we can stop doing 3 cast members per episode and actually try to advance multiple plots in a single episode."

At a bare minimum probably not until TWD is no longer the top-rated scripted show on TV (which it currently still is by a wide margin), and likely far longer than that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 07:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're trying to sort by date then YYYY/MM/DD (or an equivalent such as YYYY-MM-DD) is the best format to use, by far. It puts the most significant digit on the left and the lest significant on the right, just as with numbers. YYYY-MM-DD is the format typically used in computing currently.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 04:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He usually does the Tour de Romandie and Volta a Catalunya as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're going to shit on Lance at least don't be completely ignorant about it (it's not like there aren't plenty of legitimate reasons to shit on him).

Lance was not a nobody prior to 1997. He wasn't a star youth cyclist because he didn't switch to cycling until he was 20; prior to that he was a two-time national champion triathlete. In his second year as a pro cyclist he won the world championships; from 1992 to 1996 he also won the Fleche Wallone, two stages of the TDF, San Sebastin, and had second-place finishes in LigeBastogneLige (twice), Paris-Nice, and San Sebastin. Oh and he finished the 1995 TDF in 36th place. 

As far as doping goes I don't see how comparing Lance to Pantani means anything; Pantani was doping just as hard as Lance (multiple retroactive positive tests for EPO from the 1998 Tour, got thrown out of the 1999 Giro for having 50% hemocrit, etc). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this point I just expect that from Sagan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Not quite](http://tvseriesfinale.com/tv-show/abc-tv-show-2016-2017-season-ratings/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 01:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Have the shows restructured since last year?

Nope, if anything they're more formulaic and repetitive than ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like fewer romantic relationships, period; none of them are particularly interesting currently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably not. And I doubt it would be nearly as successful as you think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I am in this demographic, and don't know anyone who enjoys it.

Okay. That doesn't change the fact that lots of people in that demographic *do* watch it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They wouldn't know those exists.

However they do know about cold guns and how those can be effective against speedsters, yet they don't bother to use one of those against Savitar... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a single-cam so it won't have live audience laughter like TBBT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obligatory reminder that TBBT is one of the top shows in the 18-34 demo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Money </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay but they're still separate issues, and only the one that isn't the subject of this thread would actually accomplish anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My point is that sending people to another Earth is effectively no different from sending them to another city, since they're dealing with an adversary who can easily travel between Earths. So I really don't see the point in focusing on sending people to different Earths. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's the show that defined those tropes.

Smallville, One Tree Hill, Gossip Girl, 90210, etc., all fit those tropes and predate TVD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Supergirl et al could just as easily come to Earth-1; bringing in additional forces to fight Savitar is a separate matter from taking Iris to another Earth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone attacking Savitar is a good idea, but what difference does the first part actually make? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He didn't age very well.

Let's be fair, dude still looks pretty good for 50. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Monitoring Team Flash's actions, torturing one of them for the information, he's got options. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *They send Iris to Earth-X.*

*Savitar goes to Earth-X, grabs Iris, brings her back to Earth-1 and kills her.*

Yeah I'm not seeing how that accomplishes anything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has (because we've had over a week to process this information). What is your point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't new information.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the "I'm Cyborg Superman!" is similarly organic to the "I'm [used to be] Ra's al Ghul!". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But even then, TVD is hardly the first CW show fitting those criteria. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This whole "change things so the future is different" plot is so dumb! 

It really is. It's like, instead of coming up with ways to actually stop Savitar, let's just try to make arbitrary changes to the future and assume that will somehow prevent Savitar from killing Iris. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 08:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The final (8th) season will have only 6 episodes, while the penultimate (7th) season will have 7. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 08:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Big Bang Theory (despite how much reddit loves to hate it). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 05:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's about the budget of the whole Lord of the Rings trilogy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 02:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  its a different model, from both the distributor and the network.

Oh definitely. OP's scenario where ad revenue is simply replaced by additional subscription fees is purely hypothetical, it wouldn't actually be feasible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 02:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Him making promises that may not been delivered upon doesn't mean he's the one responsible for how the Dominators looked. Guggenheim is only involved with 2 of the 4 shows involved with the crossover, so it's unlikely he had the final say in the design of the Dominators; that would presumably be Berlanti. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 02:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You'd have to pass off at least half of your network's revenue onto consumer costs, probably more than that actually.

Subscription fees already account for roughly two thirds of revenue for major cable networks (at least based on the revenue numbers I could find, including those for ESPN, TNT, TBS, AMC) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
