<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2840</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoyed a daughter of smoke and bone, the author did a great job with the imagery and the added fantasy was pretty cool. The only thing that annoying is the whole "the worlds are in danger because of your relationship" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YOLO comes with a pinch of salt. Sure if you can get on a plane to Costa Rica for cheap, go for it. If you've been offered heroien for free, decline. Try to pack your life with the most awesome experiences, and try to have as many of those as possible. That's what YOLO means.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea this is so true. The books are a mess if they're full of big words, I always use simple words or use big words with loads of space in between </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The hospital maybe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably al3ren </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tinder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kil 3m wa antum bi5air </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Overpriced  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem with having a collection in Bahrain is that no one sells what you want. The majority of my collection is from abroad that I've gotten from travelling. My advise is that you should look into buying the rocks from online.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a good dental hospital in Saar, American mission. It's a bit overpriced but the quality is excellent  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually just learned this a few months ago. I thought my country was in the Red Sea. I'm 15 and have been taking geography classes since 4th grade Turns out Bahrain is in the straight of Hormuz lol, I'm just glad that i didn't tell anyone about this fuck up. God bless you google maps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was just thinking about this today, the world isn't set in stone. By world I mean the maps and the rulers. Ex: Russian annexation of Crimea. Fall of Ghadfi. Revolts are still happening, new countries will form and some will come together. Back before WWI, Europe was pretty happy that there were no more wars they said that now peace has come and war is long gone. Then WWI. Then they said it was the war to end all wars. Then WWII, and they said the same thing. 

In a hundred years, they'll talk about that time that America was a republic. Or when Austria and Hungary spilt. The cycle will never end, all empires collapse under their own weight eventually. Play it smart, see who the (probable) winner is, and stick to them. This is the only part of the world which hasn't changed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get what you mean, mind giving me an example?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 13:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happened a few minutes ago, and inspired my question. 

Last day in turkey, we bought more than our bags can take. My dad went out and bought 2 huge ass bags to carry our stuff. The bags were full. He bought some stuff to fill up the bags. I had to keep my mouth shut out of respect but mannnnn I was about to explode all over him lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was something that was just so impossibly inefficient that you've ever witnessed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 12:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 11:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since you don't "want" anything, I highly suggest that you occupy your time rather than waste it. Become a senator or governor. Increase your knowledge, learn a new language. Travel the world. You don't want to do any of those things though, that's the problem. My advice is set for yourself a goal, any goal. Ex: visit ever EU nation. Find a way to accomplish it. Search around online for something that'll occupy you for a good while, and just do it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 10:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you whip it hard enough? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 10:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 15 [M4A] heyo looking for someone to talk to, my snapchat is subject2840 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 10:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Intrests:

Reading
Tv
Traveling
Playing cards
Rubik's cube
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 09:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> subject2840 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Keeping a bike upright while riding, but when it's stationary, you can never keep it still </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 17:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stay in Bahrain. Honestly, I don't think my country has any real significance in war. They might bomb us a bit, but I don't think anyone would take the resources to bomb a random tiny middle eastern country when they could be bombing Russia or Germany.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I collect cards. A lot of cards. I might have 30 decks as of right now, from 3 different continents. I've learned a bunch of cool tricks and shuffles that looking fucking epic. Kinda annoys me when I show someone a trick or shuffle that's taken me fucking months to learn and then they're like "I can do that! Pass it over!" And then my cards are all over the floor lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
