<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1875</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 08:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's black ?

But seriously, what can you do? The older generation does not have a valid reason for not accepting , its just because. 

Actually tell them that they are the ones making the choice , not you. Social stigma in the country and culture you no longer live in, or their daughter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not EMT/ Or Paramedic. Worked as a security enforcer In the main trainstation of my country. 

In scandinavia its not unusual that the stations and trains are secured by private security, wich means that we are usualy the first responders on emergency situations and trained to deal with the most common first aid and "triage" estimations

Because its to do with trains so a lot of suicide by train = mince meat

Friend had to assist on moving the biggest pieces of the track cause the closest meat wagon was to far away (fire marshalls orders) ain nobody got time fo dat!

Me and my partner responded to a run over ( Person hit by train) when we arrived EMT/FDP alredy working on the situation so we isolate the area so they can work in peace. Lo and behold she's alive, just lost her leg, the last i heard before they got her in the ambulance " make sure you have my bag!" No screaming of pain or depresion of loosing the leg mind you

Second that haunts me most is not the worst ive seen but how i reacted to the whole thing

Im shift supervisor and i get a call that there is a drunk/junkie sleeping in a stairwell. I order ST-2 ( radio call) to check it out. I start to go to get lunch and he calls me on the radio and tells me the person is uncontient/non responding *just fucking perfect* ST-2 Do you need a Deffibrilator on the scene?
I...i..i think so, 
Turn back, grab the d-fibb and run to the sceene open the door and look down on the patient.. And i look back on my clearly shaken up guy, look down on the patient again " are you serious?, what am i gonna do with this( shaking the d-fibb), I couldn't get this guy even lukewarm, nevermind save him! he looks confused at me

The "patient" had clearly been dead for days, face is retracted to a grin, gums are black, face is green, swolen black stomach and the syringe is still stuck in his arm. Cops determinded hes been dead for a weak. 

Im still disturbed that i found it amusing that my guy wanted the d-fib to try and save the corpse, and that i started to fuck with him when i saw that it was hopless

In fairnes we didnt have any suport system: 
See a dead body? Get punched? : nobody takes sick leave, if you do, you are not cut for this unit.  



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Northen Europe seem to share the mindset : they are gonna fuck anyway so for gods lets try and sake make it safe  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
