<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2069</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL I know right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah... a horror game where the enemies are actually horrible people with horrible views and vices. How shocking. This review imo completely misses the point of the horror genre. Its not meant to be PC and nice, especially the enemies and villains. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eurogamer reviewer completely misses the point of horror games </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I couldnt even finish it. And i enjoy all the others, even as a shitty guilty pleasure sense. But this was so bad from the first half hour or so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its still my game of the year. Its a shame capcom overestimates its sales targets. 4 million is a tough figure to get unless youre brain dead fodder for the masses it seems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 12:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats whats the true travesty here. Alien Isolation absoloutely craps on ghost recon wildlands and the latest fifas and madden yet cant make half the sales. I dont get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 06:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im not sure id miss ubisoft these days tbh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would it be worse?

UBI already shove microtransactions into single player games and try their best to insert online drm into games. Id welcome a take over at this point, i could hardly see them getting worse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats what I dont get. How much did they expect to sell?

I think over a million months after launch was great considering it was coming off colonial marines which nearly buried the brand for good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 12:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absoloutely gutted. What a shitty fake rumor to start. I really hoped for a sequel in the vein of aliens this time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL Not everyone here has no idea how to fight of throw a punch dude, if thats what you think i guarentee you are speaking only for yourself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wild Lands for sure. Such a disappointment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speak for yourself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It put both guys over really well. I like both guys and was satisfied  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha you havent seen her fight im guessing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its not gay if its in a three way, with a honey in the middle theres some leeway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 12:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mma wasnt really marinas thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate the souls games. Find them tedious. So hopefully this is a trend that will stop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like kalisto </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to see their take on a colonial marines style game. I hope this is actually happening and not baseless guess work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a shit game. But hey im sure if you like generic ubisoft busy work games, more power to you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im not shocked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im on the fence. I kinda expected a horror.  Would you say its worth it anyway? I enjoyed rapture a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you know what they say about a fool and their money </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Resident Evil 7 in VR convinced me That the platform is custom built for horror </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So is this a horror game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess you just got unlucky </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its not your fault your taste is shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im ashamed you all have shit taste </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait has this game got lovecraftian vibes?

Im still not sure about it. It doesnt seem like a horror game which i was hoping for </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im from the UK and thoroughly ashamed of my fellow gamers for this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow really??? Its not very good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man that trailer was sad to watch. I hope she is finally at peace </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He got tea bagged because his friend is a shit stirrer lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a cunt, other guy didnt even seem to want to fight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why because some people cant use common sense? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sadly wont make a difference. Seems no one has balls to stop him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah wtf? He must have seen his friend get sucker punched and take a beating so he drags off the skinny one lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Classless piece of shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Much respect to camera dude first fight. Made sure guys glasses didnt get smashed and called out his buddy trying to use keys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Charisma? Cena? LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got destroyed lol

You dont even know basic words. Get yourself an education bitchcakes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should have said "your education has failed you", or "go back to school" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your use of it was wrong LOL idiot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God your english is shit

Do schooling lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you dont care  why he does it? LOL . Great, so shameless self publicity is as legitimate to you as someone who does it purely as a selfless act.

My family has always fought for the downtrodden. My great great great grandfather was a well respected politician who did a lot for the poor of london and sick and helped out many families in need. 

What do you do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many people has miz got fired? Like where he had a problem with someone so they are gone?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For pro wrestling, derp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont really care </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Dolph never had momentum LOL


And he got alex riley and mickie james fired. What a great guy right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Its not the best. Wwe is. Mundo couldnt cut it in wwe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe he needs to roid up like cena </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL of course they werent gonna be much after cena was thru with them.

And did miz beat down ziggler week after week after week, in handicap matches where he was winning two on ones with ease? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Say it again so it makes sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AAA is no wwe and never will be. Not even close </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL because he gets free publicity for it. And id wager my family has done more for those in need than you or any of your generations ever will.


And yes lets talk about wwes wonderful be a star promotion. Hey JBL is on the payroll for bullying a mentlaly ill person! Totally legitimate charity not at all done out of publicity despite being hypocrites, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> English? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention Rusev, he tried to Bury Miz, and a lot of characters whos careers nearly died after he destroyed them all  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i mean the whole group he buried. Maybe you forgot he destroyed them all week after week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? Its not legitimate fighting, you know that right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL Mundo isnt in the big leagues because hes not a total package. Hes a decent flippy guy with the charisma of a wet blanket.

Miz was just in a high profile wrestlemania match after the excellent bella skits. Miz won that battle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And pretty much all of the nexus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So underrated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MizMorrison. I think thats proven at this point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cena buried others careers when he made it too. Dudes a selfish piece of shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well he doesnt look like your prototypical wwe star. Cena looks like he eats roids for breakfast lunch and dinner </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bad! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well she is hot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realised i was talking to someone with shit taste </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found Cenas reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know what really pissed me off? The concept for infinite warfare zombies was so cool. It had a great cast in paxton , malkovich and berthnal. I really wanted to see the whole story. But the easter egg bullshit was so convolouted and hard that it made sure i couldnt ever get thru it. Sucks. Same with the others but IF seemed to have a more interesting story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Miz has come so far from the original Tough enough </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was rewatching the TE wrestling with wregret and it had clips of pre wwe miz. Hes so much like so many of us. Dude just loved wwe. Had lots of merchandise and wwe stuff in his room. You could tell the guy had so much passion for wwe.

Its a travesty the fans voted for pruder over miz. But it worked out for the best in the end.

The miz just seems like he would be an awesome dude to be friends with.

For every cena who was born with a lot and was physically athletically gifted and gets the hot chick, i much prefer guys like miz, who transcended his limitations physically with just charisma, passion and never giving up.

And although a tiny part of me is jelly maryse is so gorgeous, a bigger part of me is so happy for them both. They are so in love. You can feel it. That recent tarantoola clip melted even my black heart. 

Just so happy to see the guy succeed.

Once again fuck JBl and Benoit for making the guys life hell. Im glad he came out on top </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just said you liked jrpgs though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure if your taste is shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasnt bullshit, that money should go to the NHS and our struggling systems than the Masters in Brussells </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He said it SHOULD go to NHS. Which it really should.

Thats not a guarentee  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to see a walking dead game from a better studio to be honest.

not counting the tell tale game, which i enjoy but want a more traditional experience </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL NO JRPG can come close to witcher3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theres a reason it always tops these lists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love pugs! Adorable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 15:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually find that quite moving </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 15:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was still shit though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 15:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok so whos the " one of the greatest" you are referring to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whatever happened to overkills walking dead game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 14:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im not a huge fan of overkill. Not only do i not find payday particularly good, but they seem super shady how they deal with dlc and customers.

That said, I was intrigued by the prospect of another fps walking dead game. For all its flaws. I actually did enjoy survival instinct. 

But theres been nothing on this in a long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 14:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As much as I do really enjoy their walking dead and other games, I really would prefer a more traditional walking dead game now. And a guardians game would have been brilliant as a co op third person game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 14:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Overall though, the Miz is better. For me a wrestler has to have it all. And i find the Miz more compelling to watch and entertaining.  His promos truly invest you in whatever he does.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 14:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Witcher 3 deserves it. By far and away the best RPG ever. Not only that, one of the best games ever period.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 06:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoyed their recent efforts, but as the other dude says, they need to try something new. Like a game of thrones game should feel nothing like guardians or walking dead. As much as I do enjoy them, its very close to being played out. And theres no excuse for major bugs and hick ups on a comparatively simple game engine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 06:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they are trying to beat your ass and steal your stuff? Gets same treatment as any thief </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ughh no. Miz is better overall.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck benoit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing. I hope they wont hurt her when they grow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dear god. Hes too adorable. It shouldnt be legal to be so cute </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 23:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hate the over complicated easter egg style.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL i cant even be jelly miz has a hot wife. What a great couple. Im so happy miz didnt let the miserable fucktard antics of jbl ruin him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 17:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hes (magnus) still a twat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 17:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 17:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really didnt like it.  Felt like a shoddy version of ultimate alliance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 17:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was a great game. I took it as saying that sometimes, someones time is up no matter what you do. The alternative timeline chloe "lived", but was so miserable she wanted to die. And even if you saved her in the end, it caused so much death and misery and from what we have learned she will end up dying anyway, probably. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone actually have proof though? Size matters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> =*o( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, im saying i dont really believe it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It makes it hard to believe is what i mean. She doesnt look like she would be capable of it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She didnt even look tough or threatening though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is one sad story, moolah was a piece of shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is no one getting this lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its meant to be </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big fan of Ken. i would love to see him come back. And good for Ken standing up for others.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit. I always saw her as some sweet old lady </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive met him in person. Twat. Hes crap but he thinks hes the dogs bollocks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wnt to school with john cena. His seat was always empty and no one could figure it out. All makes sense now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Magnus is a twat. Hes nowhere near as talented as he is in his own mind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happened in it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happened in the ama? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
