<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3415</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buddhism comes in the same shit flavor ALL religions come in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 14:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And there is some random crucified dude at the end...holy shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 14:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So over night at a animal hospital they left not only the kennel unlocked by the front door? Sure. 

Totally real video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She didn't drop hints like that. You clearly didn't even read the article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like you're suggesting we should just move on now...why? It's good all this shit is being dug up they are a terrible company and deserve to be publicly humiliated for their fuck ups as any company should. 

It's good that Reddit is blowing up about it. The attention from us gets it out into the mainstream quicker, soon everyone learns how shitty United is, and hopefully something is done about either by United themselves or a third party with authority to come down on United. 

Either way if you're tired of it go read something else. There is a reason this is news and there are reasons people are digging up United dirt. We want this company down and if the most we can do is share shit about it then that is what we will do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Special needs and entitled is entirely different. Go on, go live with someone who has full blown autism and see why they were so antsy to get her hot food.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How were both sides shitty?  The woman made a reasonable request that could be carried out quite easily and they still refused. 

From a pure customer service perspective just give them a damn hot food for fuck sake. It's not hard, doesn't come out of anyone's pocket, and would of kept this whole mess from happening in the first place.

Is a diversion and the embarassment of a family as well as the waste of resources by calling both medics and police officers in addition to holding up EVERYONE ELSE ON THE PLANE worth not just giving the woman some fucking hot food?

Anyone who would argue against the family in this case is mental. I really think you just want to play devil's advocate so bad you'll say anything to fit the role.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you didn't understand my analogy. 


I'll just be blunt because we've come to a point of disagreement.

If you weren't playing when the cosmetic was only available for current players as a reward you don't deserve it because you weren't dedicating your time to the game at the time. The point of my analogy has nothing to do with the color of the ribbon...you don't even deserve one because you weren't there! 

The exclusive cosmetics are just as desirable to those who dedicate A LOT more time than a casual to moderate player. There should be high end level rewards that you can't get unless you were there. 

Do you think everyone should get party hats in Runecape? They wouldn't be rare and special then. Think of how older players feel when the new players get the same rewards by paying for them that they worked so hard to earn in game. 

Bottom line: If you weren't playing when it was an exclusive then you don't deserve it. It's a status symbol to show a players dedication to the game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't the point of an exclusive to reward players who where there at the time/showed the dedication to get these cards?

If you miss out you miss out. It's just a cosmetic. Some of you are arguing as if these developers are locking you out of core game content when in reality you're complaining about missing out on a few cosmetics. 

Not to be insulting but it just comes across as a really weak argument. 

In analogy you're mad that you just signed up for a baseball team and didn't get last seasons participation ribbon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are you being punished as a new player by not being able to receive the rewards from previous seasons that you didn't play?

You're not locked out of any of the content except for the seasonal transmogs and cosmetics. If you don't play the season you don't get the transmog...that isn't a punishment that is just how it works. 

You're basically asking for a trophy just for signing up to the team...it don't work like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the game should cater to new players by forcing long time players to go without rewards?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was unaware, due to all the posting about it I thought it was still relevant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breeding is not the same as farming, breeding is an aspect of farming but the comparison is pretty loose.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> one shot non-lethal weapons to prevent it turning into a bloodbath.

So maybe we just shoot each other with rubber bullets? Sounds fun, like extreme one shot paint ball. 

While I can see there are rules written do you think the modern average person would give any regards to these?

If this were a thing it'd have to be government sanctioned and come with a waiting period, six months maybe. If you still hate someone after six months then duel it out.

I disagree with the whole idea and think it is moronic but should it ever come to pass I hope there would be so much litigation around it setting up a duel would be a paperwork nightmare and a huge headache to discourage people from going through with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://plusblog.org/2012/06/18/congratulations-to-michael-flint-hole-in-one-winner-at-se-chapter-golf-outing/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You aren't one to say they can't but your logic and general care for the health of society sure as hell can. 

I think it's really sick so many people in this thread are seriously asking why this can't be a thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> basically meant you were in the wrong, or worse, a coward.

No American would want to be called this things, we'd be killing each other left and right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could provide an outlet for unhinged, violent people who want to mow down a crowd with a rental truck or shoot up a movie theater audience.

This wouldn't make it a bigger problem?

I used to joke we should have death row inmates fight it out but there would be a lot of legal issues and general moral fucked upness to legalizing sanctioned death bouts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why should they?

Imagine the legal problems this could cause. Two people alone, one murders the other and claims they were dueling so it's justified.

You know how many hot headed people will duel it out because it's legal? 

What stops some crazy person from bringing an automatic to a duel?

We don't let people just off and kill each other for many reasons, consent or no consent. Too many complications just to allow some people's egos flare up to an unnecessary degree.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The community made them into a big deal, Valve just introduced the idea to the main stream on one of it's most played games.

You can't blame the company for the product when the consumers are eating it up left and right like hat craving ravenous piranhas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DLC for free is was a good idea. 

It kept people from abandoning Titanfall 2 like they did the first one. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because crusading for any rightful cause on the internet is usually met by hundreds of nay sayers playing devil's advocate for fun. 

You're not allowed to tell the whole truth in internet reporting, only the exciting and interesting bits. So whichever ones contain violence, sex, or money keep but if it contains truth, thought, or change don't show that shit it won't sell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't farm tigers for anything. Without a real reason to do so you don't. 

If people believed Tiger fang could cure infertility it wouldn't give you a good reason to set up legal tiger fang trade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why should a government legalized the entrapment of Rhino's to harvest them for horn shavings to make some idiots homeo-therapy nuts happy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with this. I think if the video is big enough or relevant enough to spark a needed discussions the rules should be put by the way side for a special exception.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 04:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had one really good one and he did play with me a lot but that was when we had PS2's and the such. Back in the day I played NES/N64 mostly by myself. 

I've never played Goldeneye 007 MP Slaps only on an N64 because  of this. Makes me a little sad. 

Sorry, tangent. I just had trouble socializing at a young age and still kind of do so it's hard for me to make friends with most people because trust and things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 02:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All gear should just dropped as perfect rolled ancients. 

Only Royal Squares should drop. 

All goblins should be blood goblins. 

How much more does Diablo 3 need to hold our hands as players?  I thought maybe increasing the legendary drop rate would be enough for the player base but each season seems to bring more and more easy farming changes. 

If we keep headed this direction we might as well have rifts be zombie only, you start level 70, etc. 

Maybe a bit of a slippery slope but these hand holding changes irritate me. No challenge left in the game except how long you can be bored.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 02:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What game do you know of OP that locks necessary content behind a paywall? 

In this example the game is charging you to play 90% of the rest of the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 01:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or until you run out of energy to be derived from said salad and bread sticks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 01:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My family nor friends liked playing video games when I grew up...I still would plug in the second controller and zoom around the map. It was never the same though. Shame I can remember the same nostalgic things as everyone else but didn't get to share in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is your point here?

He's not feeding them the duck, the money he makes from the ducks goes to charity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's insulting because no one but little kids like Super Roman. He's boring, can't hold his own on the mic, and looks like he's has shit under his lip. 

There are plenty of people on that roster who could hold their own against the Undertaker. 

Kayfabe don't mean nothing when the star in question is poo poo all around.  Roman was great in the Shield...now...ugh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is tradition but it's not always true.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Randy Orton during his Legend Killer era. 

If only Randy had been more behaved backstage we could of witnessed the birth of a mega heel in Orton as the Legend Killer. 

Undertaker has even said in interviews that he wanted Randy to end the Streak but Randy didn't want to out of respect. 

The Streak should of never been a prize, you either have to give it off to the perfect person OR keep it intact. 

WWE did neither. They killed the Streak with the Broccoli Laser and then had a few lame matches between ending with The Undertaker jobbing out to Roman Reigns. 

If my entire life revolved around wrestling I'd probably kill myself WWE is so bad. Like...it's really really bad. Have you watched it lately? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roman was way over when he was the enforcer for the Shield. 

Now he's just an annoying "big dog" who gets mega-pushes like there is no tomorrow.

Him wrestling in the last match against the Undertaker may be a death bell for his career. I hope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
