<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2423</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 05:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got a little bit of woman on your boobs there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 05:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #**COCK** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 05:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WTF is Batman doing? He can't fly like Superman or sometimes Wonder Woman, and he's not running as fast as Flash. So is he just awkwardly in mid horizontal fall? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 04:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rights to the character are constantly in flux. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 07:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These DC movies typically go through 3 directors before one sticks, so once Reeves drops out due to creative differences, we'll get the one that conforms to the studio's shitty vision. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 01:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you get banned from /r/gaming you're doing something right.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 00:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why'd you tape up the stand? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 00:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better pick these up while the heat is low, cuz the movie is  testing VERY well. http://www.hollywoodreporter.com/heat-vision/guardians-galaxy-vol-2-scores-extremely-rare-100-test-screening-974277 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 2' Scores Extremely Rare 100 in Test Screening (Exclusive) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 00:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 2' Scores Extremely Rare 100 in Test Screening (Exclusive) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 00:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 22:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shallow-throating Donny's micro-dick? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 22:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm amazed this is up on the front page. I posted a clip from last weeks show and I was instantly brigaded by some of the Trumptards on this sub. They really hate "Nasty Woman" Sam Bee around these parts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 18:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's probably just a nod by the Marvel Legends team, and also a marketing tactic, because Iron Man is "different" now, so parents won't be able to say their kid already has that Iron Man and Spider-Man from the Civil War Multipack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 18:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It just looks like a repaint of the Mark 46. I don't believe Marvel would do a new armor for  a movie where they won't be able to take full advantage of the design in all merchandise, since they won't be able to sell it without a Spider-Man due to the deal they made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guys, this is photoshopped. It's based off a Hasbro Repaint. It won't be in the movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 06:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazon. Never gotten a dud from them. Paint apps have always been good. None have ever broken on me either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 04:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did say we were panicking. You were warned! It's not my fault the place has devolved into a fucking train wreck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 04:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> best thing he'd written.

Not a high bar to clear, lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 03:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here, but hopefully being a critical darling from the mastermind behind Fargo saves it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 03:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Be sure to come panic with us about the ratings for the show at [r/LegionFX](https://www.google.com/url?sa=t rct=j q= esrc=s source=web cd=1 cad=rja uact=8 ved=0ahUKEwiW1bvt1IPSAhXhxlQKHVyZA2kQ3ywIHjAA url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DdQw4w9WgXcQ usg=AFQjCNEPGa2VKuL0GefK_nkQoh9csTD8OA sig2=16mZDnbw4UgP5t5KESTsAg)!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 01:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #**SEE YOU IN COURT! THE SECURITY OF OUR COUNTRY IS IN TRUMP STEAK! EASY D!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 01:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Be sure to discuss the show at [r/LegionFX](https://www.google.com/url?sa=t rct=j q= esrc=s source=web cd=1 cad=rja uact=8 ved=0ahUKEwiW1bvt1IPSAhXhxlQKHVyZA2kQ3ywIHjAA url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DdQw4w9WgXcQ usg=AFQjCNEPGa2VKuL0GefK_nkQoh9csTD8OA sig2=16mZDnbw4UgP5t5KESTsAg)!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 01:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, X-Men have typically represented minorities metaphorically in the past...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 01:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could always just buy them if you really want to watch them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woah, how do you get a disco batman? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for this. Looks like nothing major. I'll go see the movie when the heat dies down then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 19:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Be sure to discuss the show at [r/LegionFX](https://www.google.com/url?sa=t rct=j q= esrc=s source=web cd=1 cad=rja uact=8 ved=0ahUKEwiW1bvt1IPSAhXhxlQKHVyZA2kQ3ywIHjAA url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DdQw4w9WgXcQ usg=AFQjCNEPGa2VKuL0GefK_nkQoh9csTD8OA sig2=16mZDnbw4UgP5t5KESTsAg)!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 19:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like you've got some bootLegos.

Also the T-800 from T2 is hero, damn it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god, the paint apps don't fucking blow. They actually look really close to the prototypes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 07:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man you motherfuckers really fucking love hearing fuck, faggot, cunt, nigger, and weenies don't you?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 02:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same with WSJ. I do transcription work and one of there shows always crops up, and I have to transcribe their bullshit down if I wanna sustain my hobby. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 23:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And those Easy Ds too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 23:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He must be looking to get re-elected as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 22:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well now you know to keep it off your list then, ha ha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 22:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Green Arrow wants to feel like he can do things on his own and he's not just a morose guy in green filtered leather. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 21:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think so. These characters were annoying, non stop. It's like they were modeled after r/funny or something. It was also too easy to do things without getting into a big thing. You were basically a walking god mode considering no other characters besides the annoying fat hacker lady were hackers. It also has an issue of the open world not feeling alive. I frequently found myself in sparsely populated areas, or people and cars randomly disappearing.

I often wondered why these characters were doing what they were doing beyond their "Wake up sheeple!" mentality. Aiden Pearce was bland, but at least he had a better motive for doing things and wasn't annoying.

I think this game is where I get off the Watch Dogs train. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 03:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I put "have sex" in the final question. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 01:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw this video in my French class in college. So cool seeing it here years later!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 07:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was the idea! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 07:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grant Gustin is not much of a voice actor, or he's not being given good direction. Both of the things I've heard him voice act in, (this and the Vixen shorts) he's given out some dull line readings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 04:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't really mix and match figures from different lines with Icons figures. The scale will be off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 03:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Careful with Batman. His biceps can easily tear off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 03:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I love about this is that the blue on the walls and his suit reflects the way his balls are feeling, and that's why he decides to make the hanky-panky with a sex hotline. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 03:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the app called? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Video] The ONLY REAL game-breaking bug left in LBP3. The other guys don't have all the REAL info. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 02:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 22:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kara and Her Ambiguously Gay Dads coming soon to CBS!


And Season 2 on The CW! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 21:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't know the half of it, OP forgot to mention that the game routinely spazzes out and starts playing Hey Ya! by Outkast on a loop, until you restart the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only one of those games I'm interested in is Horizon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing could have saved this movie besides a good script. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Wick Chapter 2 is Wicked Awesome! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Wick Chapter 2 is Wicked Awesome </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently painted my tv white, but now I'm having difficulty seeing what I'm playing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like they're filming something from the very beginning of the 2013 game, if that airplane wing is anything to go by. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 18:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard it was because the show had too many people watching it. Other shows were complaining, saying,"It's ratings are so good," and that they weren't being watched so Fox mercy cancelled it for the other shows happiness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So they help create a culture with their douche and turd "both sides are bad" (cuz emails are just as bad as sexual assault), and now they're unwilling to even attempt at satirizing Trump, claiming it's too hard, when other people are doing it just fine, SNL doing it with the same amount of prep time that they give themselves.

With last season being mostly a dud, and reddit beating the shit out of  every single South Park joke as episodes premiere, I think I'm finally ready to let go of this show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 07:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well take a look at who we have for President, and the people he surrounds himself with. 

People who make up fake terrorist attacks like the Bowling Green Massacre. These people could see this and say it's a documentary, and people that follow them blindly will treat it as gospel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 07:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like it's time to buy the movie, series box set, and Lost Missions on Blu-Ray. I wonder if I can get Disney Movie Rewards Points on all of that?

Just saw the prices for the blu-ray of the movie, so maybe my DVD of the movie will do just fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 06:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given what's happening in the real world, some of the stuff in the show just doesn't sit well with me. 

I was in high school when I watched the original series so a lot of the stuff that was in it flew right over my head, until I learned more about it afterwards. This though, I understand as I watch, and it's bugging me, because the POTUS could watch this and use it as a weapon that will strike fear in the uneducated people in this country.

All that said, I did enjoy the episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 06:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought they were a lot *cooler*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 06:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #**DON'T FIGHT IT.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #**DUSTY OLD BONES, FULL OF GREEN DUST!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell of a performance. 

People will be making gifs of her jumping off the stage at the end there for ages... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we are all built-in gps on this blessed day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 01:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never watched it to begin with, lol. The premise just sounds boring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 22:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "He was a traitor, and we need to pray for Arnold tonight, people. u/GovSchwarzenegger needs the ratings, like I need ~~Ivanka~~ Melania." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 22:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice cleavage  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 22:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, I wish they'd stop calling his resort there the winter white house. It's not. 

George Bapalopolas called it that on his show this morning and it made me angry in front of my pancakes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 21:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #**GO PAPERLESS, DON'T STRESS GIRL, I GOT YOUR DISCOUNTS FOR PEE** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 20:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they need to cut their losses and reboot the universe with new actors, new everything if Wonder Woman and Justice League are cinematic shit too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there going to be any exclusive minifigures or polybags given away in theaters for The Lego Batman Movie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 03:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Look at Marvel Legends 2 Packs for Dr. Strange, and GOTG </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Samantha Bee Tears Into Trump's "Not A Muslim Ban" on 'Full Frontal' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 06:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I wont mention that this refugee ban is immoral, embarrassing and inhuman, Ill just point out that it is the act of a giant pussy." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 05:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> '24: Legacy': TV Review </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 17:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was the Burger King 5 for $4 meal discontinued? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 03:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Patrick Stewart to Voice Poop Emoji in 'Emoji Movie' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 21:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Byrne and St. Vincent - Love this Giant NPR Concert [Alternative] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 01:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Talking Heads (David Byrne and St. Vincent) - Burning Down the House [AWESOMESAUCE] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 01:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know what happened to SNL reruns on cable? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 19:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Comedy Central and Logo both stopped airing them on New Year's and I can find nothing online about what happened or why. No one else seems to be airing them either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK Marvel Legends Collectors! Warlock X-Men wave available for Pre-Order Now! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 20:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch Dogs 2 $30 at Amazon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 17:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> '24: Legacy' Review: '24' Is Back And Hasn't Changed A Bit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 22:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stone Cold Steve Austin stuns Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 05:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stone Cold Steve Austin stuns Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 02:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mute (2017) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 19:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Logan (2017) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 07:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't Breathe (2016) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 04:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince (2009) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 04:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Dark Knight Rises (2012) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 04:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marvel's The Avengers (2012) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 03:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inception (2010) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 03:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mark Hamill's Carrie Fisher Tribute: "Making Her Laugh Was a Badge of Honor" (Guest Column) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 17:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mark Hamill's Carrie Fisher Tribute: "Making Her Laugh Was a Badge of Honor" (Guest Column) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 17:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How long does it take to get a refund on a returned item? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 04:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I returned two items at the same time, got a refund for one about 3 days after dropping them off at an amazon drop off location, and it's been 10 days since I dropped it off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Emoji Movie - Official Teaser Trailer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 22:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spongebob Squarepants - Goofy Goober Rock [Rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 17:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TV Networks, Studios Shifting Program Strategies in the Trump Age: "Are We Telling the Right Stories?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 18:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More S.H. Figuarts AOTC Anakin Skywalker Photos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 04:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More S.H. Figuarts AOTC Anakin Skywalker Photos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 04:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Andrew Garfield Says Missed Opportunities With Spider-Man Were "Absolutely Devastating" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 01:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Just Keep Checking) ML Sandman Wave up on Amazon! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 23:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Spider-Man](https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B01D11DYRK/)

[Green Goblin](https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B01D11DVPA/)

[Ms. Marvel](https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B01D11DVOQ/)

[Spider-UK](https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01D11DWPE/)

[Shocker](https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01D11DWO0/)

[Jackal](https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01D11DW1I/)

[Spider-Man 2099](https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01D11DWS6/)

They're coming in and out of stock, just keep checking, and you should be good. 

Good luck guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (POPS UP SPORADICALLY) Marvel Spider-Man 6-inch Legends Series Symbiote Spider-Man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 08:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SPOILERS] It's time for Gimple to step down as show runner. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 03:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Not Mine) New Spider-Man ML Wave found at a TRU in South Carolina </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 18:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'The Walking Dead' Is Exactly the Show We Don't Need Right Now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 05:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I fucking hate country music, and all 50 of it's god damn awards shows. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 05:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like, how many times does this shitty genre need the spotlight on it, and how many times do these shitty artists need to partake in these masturbatory award shows? god damn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So is the Middle Class Scholarship being distributed or what? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 00:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They said they'd have it out by mid October, and mid October has come and gone. Anyone gotten their's yet?

EDIT: The FA Office told me that they're going to be disbursing them out over this week and next week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SNL is... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 05:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a wonderful skit show! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kevin Hart is Santa Claus now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 02:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harry Potter and the Professor Who Broke Bad (Complete) | Robot Chicken | Adult Swim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 03:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hot Toys Deadpool available for Pre-Order again! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 06:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ML Venom in stock for MSRP @Amazon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 04:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ML Deadpool up for Pre-Order @Amazon! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 06:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Billy Bush Negotiating Exit From NBC's 'Today' Show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 23:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I just watched the season premiere of Supergirl... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 06:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...And I already love this low-budget show's interpretation of Superman more than the Snyderverse Superman.

Supergirl nails the characterization of Superman in less than half an hour of screen time, than the latest films have.

And I'm not even surprised by it, considering the folks who make these CW superhero shows have shown more love for the source material than the folks that put out Man of Steel, BvS, and Suicide Skwad.

For me, Superman has returned.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just watched the Supergirl season premiere... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 06:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Late Night with Seth Myers- The Trump Tape and Debate Fallout: A Closer Look </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 03:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] THE LEGEND OF KORRA Goes on a Toy Bender! | Nerdist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 03:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Legend of Korra Action Figure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 20:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Marvel's Luke Cage': TV Review </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 04:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
