<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3297</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 05:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once again, i'd be remiss not to voice my opinion that "The Wolverine" and it's Unrated extended cut had just as much lunch as Logan with violence and is so brilliant as a Kurosawa-esque family drama in a superhero film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 05:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, the big action scenes in movies like days of future past, the wolverine, and first class or centered around either character or a motion with the great technical proficiency and showcasing the fights. X-Men: Apocalypse it's just An absolute bundling failure. Fox has a half-and-half track record with the X-Men franchise, so I have absolutely no clue if they'll learn the right lessons from their two R-rated movies, Or if they just think the critical praise and fanboy hope comes from the fact that the R-rated movies say "fuck" a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 05:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The R-rated "Unrated extended edition" version of "The Wolverine" is FANTASTIC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 01:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked him a lot in the role.

"JUICE!!!!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 23:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's it. We've reached humanity's highest achievement. Everyone go home.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 23:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "There wasn't even an awning or anything." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 19:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The V for Vendetta film adaptation is a romanticized look of freedom vs. fascism, and isn't really like the movie, but I think it's DAMN brilliant and I think it's better than the source material. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 19:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pitch Black. Everyone is out for their own survival. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 18:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inglourious Basterds

 Well, if this is it, old boy, I hope you don't mind if I go out speaking the King's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 18:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No way! "Are You Afraid of the Dark" for life! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 18:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Yeah, I don't think that outfit was age appropriate." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 08:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Jade Empire

* Crimson Skies: High Road to Revenge

* DmC: Devil May Cry

* Remember Me

* Back to the Future: The Game

* Goldeneye: 007 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 08:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In terms of what? Gameplay? Story? Genre? Atmosphere? Writing?

I'd suggest the first two Dead Space games, Gears of War 1/Ultimate edition, Gears of War 4. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 07:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Force Unleashed in some scenes. KOTOR has their old analogs for a star Destroyers, and they destroy an entire surface of a planet  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 07:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my opinion, it's the best thing Tarantino ever worked on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 07:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well not a belligerently racist one that spoke on the company's behalf and wasn't ever reprimanded for his behavior. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 03:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was that Johnny Powell's voice actor from The Darkness 2 at around 0:50? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 03:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have conflicting thoughts getting the game after Manveer Heir's racist tirades. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 17:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad to hear the music from The Wolverine getting some usage here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 17:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DRIVE THE SARACENS FROM THE HOLY LAND! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what she is

She's here to do

Whatever she can </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now, now, let's not bring the mothers into this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is why I personally see him more as an entertainer than a critic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 06:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, I do. Especially since the "EWW" video has spawned a whole new genre of lazily written 'film criticism/poorly written jokes' and with some of the laziest video productions known to Youtube.

It's no less or more of a "dialog" than CinemaSins has been doing with their videos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 06:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not? The CinemaSins guys have their livelihood with criticizing other people's work. Why wouldn't a criticism of their own work not count, especially in the exact same format that the CinemaSins guys use? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 05:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy birthday to her!!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 04:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Road to Perdition
* Drive
* Inglourious Basterds
* True Romance
* Sicario
* The Drop
* House of Games
* The Usual Suspects </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 03:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he's clearly mentally unstable in some form or another. Mostly, he's all there in the head. But those moments of extreme tension or emotion, he does get a bit nuts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 03:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't "need" to see the others, but the extended unrated cut of "The Wolverine" is FANTASTIC.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 03:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Question out of curiosity, why? I know, for money and it's Hollywood. What I mean is what's the point of adapting sleeping dogs into a film? All you can do is inhibit the running time and content. I bet more than anything they'll make a PG-13 movie out of it, which is not at all what the video game was about, especially the moral ambiguity of Wei Shen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 02:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ip Man was great but I'd be remiss not to mention how disconcerting the xenophobia was.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 02:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He did land that plane after all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 02:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "What?! No, you dern fools! The sheriff is a n-- (DONG!)" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 02:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You dangerous mute lunatic." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 02:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best anime </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 02:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "See you, Space Cowboy." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 02:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big socks!!!!....wait, I did that wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 23:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why so mad? Even the Cinemasins guys welcome criticism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 23:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh, you forgot to mention the two best shows on G4 - Judgment Day (aka "Reviews on the Run" with [one of the best reviews I've ever seen](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VnvCGfbiO3M)) as well as G4TV.com the show (with my first celebrity crush, [Laura Foy](http://img5.bdbphotos.com/images/orig/f/v/fvwfime2khqlwviq.jpg?djet1p5k) ).

I miss old school G4. Sure, they had the production budget of a High School play, but there was SOO much heart behind it all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 02:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why the Hell should we care what the Academy thinks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 02:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who the Hell cares? The Oscars haven't been about concerning themselves in terms of recognizing the best in quality filmmaking for years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 02:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't it more "body-swap" movie than "gender-bender"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 01:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're gosh dang right! DAMN that's a good game!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 00:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too, but I agree that after cancelling Phantom Dust, Scalebound, AND Fable Legends, Microsoft needs to get more video games in development.

Still love games like Halo: MCC, Quantum Break,Halo 5, Ori and the Blind Forest, etc. but I want to see more experimentation and games, GOSH DANG IT!!!!

Also, I'm probably going to get ReCore when I get my next paycheck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 00:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely. And it sucks since we were scheduled to get Scalebound, Phantom Dust, and Fable Legends this year until they got cancelled. 

I'm loving my Xbox One for the console and "full" exclusives, like Halo 5, Halo: MCC, Ori and the Blind Forest, Quantum Break (didn't get enough love, IMHO), Rare Replay, Gears of War 4, etc. but if Microsoft wants to keep me as a customer, they GOT to get more games going.

Looking forward to Cuphead and Sea of Thieves, though. 

I'm jealous of all my SONY bretherin who get to enjoy Horizon and will get to play Death Stranding. This is a very weird industry where the art is separated by particular hardware moreso than any other medium.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, some people might view an unsatisfying narrative as a detriment big enough to drag down the rest of the movie while ALSO mentioning the good performances and cinematography. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once again, I'm not saying he isn't a troll or has opinions on film that are against majority consensus, or even that some of his opinions don't make sense.

I'm just commenting hat not liking the aforementioned films before don't immediately make a person a troll. Put into a wider context with Armond'a viewpoint is fair to make the judgment that he's not exactly being consistent with criticism, but the previously mentioned three films aren't a holistic indicator of a person's film criticisms or intentions as a critic.

Post-edit: Why am I being downvoted for saying that not liking three films inherently makes you a troll? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Driver </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I, Robot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snatch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gangster Squad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True Romance

Go

Snatch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doctor Strange </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Count of Monte Cristo (2002 adaptation) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Usual Suspects </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, you can also not like those films and not be a troll.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Tron Legacy, and I hope that they get to make a third film </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. For some reason I thought "Andrew" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 00:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a complicated issue, because what constitutes a "Christian film"? Lord of the Rings is inspired by Christian ideology and beliefs, but it isn't ABOUT those ideas directly. No, Christians (including myself as a Christian) don't win people over by vilifying people with different beliefs. Look at the TV show Firefly and the following movie, Serenity; Joss Whedon is an atheist, but Shepard Book is perhaps the biggest moral center in the entire show. Book is hinted to have an even darker past than anyone else on the show, but he's never turned into a cliche or a cardboard cutout that insults everything Christians are about. Even Joss Whedon in The Avengers where Cap directly says "there's only one God, Ma'am, and I don't think he dresses like that." It's important to see that these are people first and not merely mouth-pieces for ideologies. 

I think to be a truly "Christian" film, it should confront the issues held by Christians. Examining them that includes the "why" and "how", as well as its impact. 

Outside of the list of recommendations already mentioned, I'd suggest two unorthodox films - "The Book of Eli" and the 2002 film adaptation of "The Count of Monte Cristo". The first deals with a violent man in a post-apocalyptic landscape pressing forward with faith and belief, but using extreme violence to do so, and struggles with his understanding of what his belief is about to justify it. "Monte Cristo" (just as a refresher) is about a wrongfully imprisoned man who loses his faith in God and instead dedicates his life to the vengeance he craves for the wrongs done upon him, but can't seem to shake God from his life. The similarity between these two stories is that they're both about protagonists who contend with their faith, what it means to them, and how they go about 'embracing' that faith. They're not merely conforming to the beliefs of strict Christians and are rewarded for it. They wrestle with these issues and try to find meaning, especially when neither of these men experience a "simple life" that easily conforms to a Christian life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 23:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is how do you define what a Christian movie is? The Lord of the rings is very much in spired by Christian doctrine, but it's not a direct Christian movie. Does that count? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 23:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think a lot of times passions can get inflamed in terms of what people believe, or don't believe, and that can lead to hostilities. While I do think it's important to have an honest dialogue, I do agree with you that it is important for people to keep things in context and with a tempered attitude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 23:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For myself, I was raised Catholic and questioned my views when I went into college. Especially with the allegations and scandals that arose from the child molestation stories surrounding the Catholic Church, I started to drift from the flock, so to speak. For myself, I turned to knowledge concerning the religion. Christian apologetics from intelligent people like John Lennox , Books like the case for Christ, looking over the historocity of the Bible and how it matches archaeological discoveries made afterwords, and the list of intelligent dissections of historical evidence (like third party sources citing Christ' existence) has made me a complete believer from the evidence presented. 

Also, it's important to challenge those believes rather than maintain comfort in the early excepting them. Listen to debates. Ask questions. Never settle for merely accepting what you've been taught. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 23:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bible said we needed to love our God with all of our mind, so that means loving science. John Lennox made a great distinction between God and science by comparing it to The creation of the model T. Who built the car? Mechanical engineering, or henry ford? Just because Science exists doesn't disapprove the agent that created the method. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 23:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm very happy that you didn't go through with it. There are always difficult times in our lives, and enduring it together is what a good community is all about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 23:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's very nice to do! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it possible to learn this power? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A reference to the Spectacular Spider-man series? My man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 15:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know I may be the odd one out here, but I like holden and the actor they chose for him. Especially as a self-sacrificing 'good' man struggling with responsibility rather than a morally compromised leader.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 20:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Starring Idris Elbear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 19:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's always Pitch Black. LOVE that film </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A gaggle of floofs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm nawt a cawp!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 15:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  meat tank

Oh, Channing Tatum's in this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 15:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Hillbilly

You can't use that word! That's *our* word! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say that assassins creed should still feel like epic historical sci-fi, as weird as that sounds. I still believe that black flag was the best of the bunch and nail down everything so perfectly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 03:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, American Sniper showcased how the American military utilizes civilians for their own gain, had a main character who was obsessed with fighting war and was demonstrated to be unhealthy, and underscored the absolutely messed up nature of war in the Middle East  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 03:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A New Hope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 03:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know there was this much sand in the whole galaxy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm responding to Hickspy's comment about the costumes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Top: When you get into the office at 9 am with a cup of coffee.

Bottom: When you finally leave at 5 pm back home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THIS IS THE MAKEUP ARTIST! HE'S GOT MY BACK! I SUGGEST NOT GETTING TRAPPED IN THE MAKEUP CHAIR! HIS MAKEUP TEAM CAN CAPTURE YOUR SOUL FOR OVER 5 HOURS APPLYING MAKEUP! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, doesn't everyone remember when Harley Quinn dressed like a cheap Detroit prostitute in her comic debut?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SMOKIN!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 04:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm asking what his basis of something be considered alive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 02:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As others have pointed out, the story's focus on revenge absolutely betrays the nature of the actual books which views vengeance as a self-destructive poison. I certainly hope that they rectify the situation, or at least address it in some manner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 00:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I have no idea the mental gymnastics it must take to think that being absolutely anti-abortion yet fine with the state killing or castrating people is somehow consistent.

Because I believe in punishing people responsible of grave crimes, especially against the innocent. 

 I appreciate your honesty but your views are so incredibly callous and appalling that I can't continue this. I hope you change your mind someday.

I appreciate your honesty, but your views are disgusting in supporting killing innocent babies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  that positions seems to be fairly consistent but a moral monstrosity by completely erasing the bodily rights and desires of the woman. 

I wouldn't say that it's a moral monstrosity at all. I believe that it is a life, and I side with Ben Shapiro on the issue and in terms of when the baby is considered "alive" and the lack of clarity in terms of defining WHEN it's alive:

 "How about week 15, when the baby has an adults taste buds?" he asked. "How about weeks nine and ten when the babys teeth are already beginning to form? Its fingernails are already beginning to develop. Were talking about two months old, right? The baby can turn its head and frown. The baby can hiccup. Is that okay to kill?" How about day 22? The hearts already beating with the childs blood, which may be of a different blood type than the mother," stated Shapiro."

I don't believe in infringing upon someone's individual rights UNLESS that freedom endangers someone else's very life, and I consider that baby alive. In my point of view, it's not self-contradictory but a consistent basis for freedom and rights for a human being. 

Yeah, it sucks if someone gets pregnant and they didn't want to get pregnant (which is the majority of abortions). I personally believe that those pregnancies should be carried to term, with government financially helping the woman in question, and then given up for adoption if the mother doesn't want the child. For the issue of rape, as horrifying as it is, it's still a life that you're ending if you choose aborting that fetus. I would instead have the rapists either killed or chemically castrated if found guilty to deter rape in the society.

I find a more abhorrent defense of abortion being that someone's individual liberties are more important than ending a life. You probably don't share that opinion, but that's how I genuinely feel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You claim religion to be horrendous and vile, yet you don't seem to understand history in that organizations and governments pushing state atheism/secularism have led to some of the worst atrocities in human history. It would be intellectually dishonest if I said that the worst of people who believe in atheism are inherently the same as the best of people who believe in atheism. 

Ideologies of every shade and shape (not just involving spirituality or religion) have been abused and contorted for evil ends. Ideologies do not make people do horrendous things, that would be the people themselves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Try, difficult it may be for you, to seperate people from religion

Try, though probably impossible for someone like you, to understand that religion doesn't inherently make a person worse or better than the next person.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So if a fetus were declared a person in the legal sense (they're not currently persons according to https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Personhood#United_States), it would be granted some rights (but not duties, since we can't really ask it to do them), such as perhaps the right to not be aborted. 

On that note, is a 15 year old "less" of a person because they don't get the same rights as a 30 year old? This isn't to provoke an argument, just a thought process I'm having.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, does a baby need to be able to survive outside a womb to be a person? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Imagine being at church and hearing that shit. I bet every single person in there thought they were crazy instead of "oh it's a miracle!"

As a Christian who researched this, even Jesus' resurrection as accounted in the Bible was met with  people saying "yeah, right".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it's directly supporting an ideology the company heads don't want to support because of their religious convictions and don't want to encourage. Not to mention that the people who work for these companies aren't entitled to making the company cover whatever they want. It's a contract, an agreement between employee and employer and if you want contraception, then don't work for a place that doesn't offer coverage for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Or try to criminalize abortion. Odd.

Yes, it's as if some people view the death of the fetus as ending a life and want laws against.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention that many advances and developments of hospitals were supported by the Catholic church and other Christian organizations. Like...dude....your religion WANTS you to use science! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Well, I don't see any radical Atheists starving their children to death.

Well, radical atheists were in charge of the Soviet Union and sent god knows how many religious peoples into gulags to be tortured and killed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I will not roll over and allow something so horrendous and vile as religion to survive just because something else equally horrible may rise in its place.

Well, that's the attitude Pol Pot, Mao Zedong, and Joseph Stalin had and they had killed millions of people and destroyed any religious people/groups they could find.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I will never allow religion to flourish in my presence. 

Well, that's absolutely bigoted and close-minded, especially when most laws and morals concerning universal and inalienable human rights are from the Bible.

Also, question out of curiosity are all religions the same, and just as dangerous? What about Buddhists? Are they all a pack of deplorables? Are all Christians dangerous? Are peace-loving quakers the same thing as a Protestant? Are all Jews a bad influence on society? Are the Catholic churches investment in science and education a bad thing for the development of the Western world? 

Why is it the religion itself being a danger, and not the people who commit those actions?

The only one blindly subscribing to an ideology seems to be you, buddy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh....well, actually, here's some readings against slavery in the Bible, [example](http://christianapologeticsalliance.com/2012/10/20/you-say-the-bible-advocates-slavery/), [other example](https://carm.org/slavery), [last example](http://apologeticspress.org/apcontent.aspx?category=6 article=1587).

Not to mention "antebellum slavery" was not the same as concept as "Greek slavery".

And for stoning, a lot of philosophers and historians side more with the idea that the law was meant to discourage acts that were found to be sinful: [example](http://www.equip.org/article/stoning-adulterers/)

Also, blaming bad morals from the Bible is like blaming the Gulags of Joseph Stalin and the USSR with Pol Pot and Mao Zedong's genocide against the religious as a direct influence of state atheism/secularism. It's ludicrous for thinking a particular brand of ideas make people bad, and not the people themselves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Cells don't have rights. If it cannot exist outside of the womb, it is not a person.

Is a person only a person when it's born? What about at 8 1/2 months? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Religion shouldn't be the basis upon which we create our laws.

Well, then there goes "inalienable human rights":

 Does the denial of God have any entailments? Yes, it does: take just one examplethe concept of human rights. Modern human rights theory is based on the Judeo-Christian idea that human beings are of tremendous value and worth, because they are made in the image of God. Reject God and suddenly you have to start again, explaining why one particular creature, thrown up by the forces of time, chance and natural selection mixing and chopping atoms and chemicals for several billion years possesses inalienable rights, whereas amoeba, aardvarks and eggplants do not. Many philosophers and thinkers recognise the problem and are honest enough to admit if you dismiss God, you lose many other things, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  but saying that religion doesn't have much to do with it is being willfully ignorant. 

That's just intellectually dishonest. There are people who are not religious who believe that a life begins at conception, or even far earlier than some groups would like to advocate for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We dont have to wonder about when to apply human rights. They already protect the mother from having her womb not belong to her for 9 months.

The argument is that you are killing a human being in the womb, and that people don't have the right to end another's life if it's not endangering them. It's a far more complex issue than that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the difference between an archetype and a stereotype? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 03:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of my favorite openings to any story across the spectrum of all media (games, movies, TV, etc.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 06:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should we stick with the same brand of video camera? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello everyone. My company is thinking about acquiring another video camera to record professional events. Currently, we have a Canon VIXIA HF G10, and I'm researching the Canon XA10 in terms of camera quality that is "similar" to the G10 (as we want to have the visual fidelity of both cameras to be as close to the same as possible as we want a consistent visual look for our footage, so "better" cameras might be out of the question). 

We're trying to find a camera to fill that role, but we were also wondering if we should stick with a Canon camera, or try and branch out to another brand. Are there any added benefits of sticking with the same brand of camera? 

Thank you for taking the time to read this thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is God Great? Christopher Hitchens vs. Professor John Lennox (an intellectual stimulating debate that personally strengthened my own beliefs). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 05:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you consider to be a "Horror movie"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 18:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey everyone,

I was rewatching "Aliens" over the weekend, then decided to watch "Jurassic Park" after that, and it got me wondering. What is a "horror film"? Are both of these movies horror related? If not, why not? Do horror films need to have certain staplemarks? Does it just need to be scary some of the time, or most of the time? Can a "true horror film" be PG-13? Can it be a genre mash-up, or does it need to stand as the primary defining feature of the movie?

I wanted to see what you all thought and give your opinions and insight into how you define a "horror film." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was anyone else surprised with how fast the editing was in Shin Godzilla? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 15:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not that I'm complaining because they used it to great effect, but I was watching the film last night and I was noticing just how quick the editing was with so many different cuts.

It reminded me a lot of Dark City they cut so frequently (once again, I don't have an inherent problem with it as I ALSO loved that movie).

Did anyone else feel this way when watching it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The Darkness 2" has some of the best collectible descriptions of any game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 05:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jesus, the Wasps and Banshees ruined Warzone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 05:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Between not having enough ammo to take down the flying aircraft, and having the aircraft being so maneuverable it doesn't matter what weapon you have, aircraft have ruined Warzone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Don't Have Faith to be an Atheist - John Lennox, PhD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 02:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Favorite line from a bad film? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 20:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, everyone.

We all have our favorite lines from great movies, but what about great lines from bad films? I know we all have different definitions of what "bad" could be, but, in my eyes, these would be examples of pieces of great writing in an otherwise unremarkable or downright awful film that for whatever reason managed to have a great piece of dialog.

For myself, I'm going to have to go with Street Fighter:

"For you, the day Bison graced your village was the most important day of your life. But for me, it was Tuesday." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
