<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1369</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 44 games into his season Steph Curry has made 204 three pointers. With 38 games left Curry could very well become the first player to make 300 and 350 three pointers in a single season. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 07:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Todd Gurley is going to be bigger than Kobe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 08:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What should I do with my RG3 jersey? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 02:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any suggestions?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> According to the DNC the Sanders campaign improperly accessed Clinton voter data </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 06:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AJ McCarron is currently playing professional football. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 19:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Force Accounted: A visual breakdown of the use of the force in every film </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 17:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does the AAC need to do to become a Power Conference? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 01:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is P6 and G4 a possibility?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trade suggestion: Nene + 2016 1st round + 2018 1st round = Demarcus Cousins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 07:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt we secure Durant next Summer. I think we are one major piece away from being a legit title contender. Cousins is that piece. 

Just imagine this starting 5. Wall, Beal, Porter, Humphries, Cousins. With Gortat coming off the bench.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is scoring higher than it was last season or am I imagining that it is? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 01:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Games seem to be higher scoring than in the past. Am I crazy? 

Are there any stats to prove or disprove this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we compile a list of our favorite sketches in the post-Meyers era, to put to rest the idea that "SNL is now terrible" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 22:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please help add to this list. 

[Dem debate](https://screen.yahoo.com/snl/democratic-debate-cold-open-103219641.html)

[39 cents](https://screen.yahoo.com/leslie-jones-snl-skits/39-cents-070921029.html)

[Drunk Uncle loves Trump](https://screen.yahoo.com/leslie-jones-snl-skits/weekend-drunk-uncle-donald-trump-091616957.html)

[Abilify for Candidates](https://screen.yahoo.com/snl/abilify-candidates-084222560.html)

[Calvin Klein](https://screen.yahoo.com/snl/calvin-klein-ads-065622613.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does the Big 12 not like to play defense? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 18:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happened to this site? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 04:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dining staff shortages compromises dining experience - Collegiate Times </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 21:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texans have cut Charles James </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-05 22:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the angriest you've been when watching an NFL game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-20 03:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Fincher's HBO remake of Utopia is cancelled. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 22:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wilson Ramos hit two home runs off two different Ray's position players tonight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 04:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MASN's Dan Kolko: We just had the Nats pinch-hit a pitcher as the DH against a position player as the pitcher. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 04:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I had a dream I was hanging out with John Wall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 10:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was really cool. I hope I run into him again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tanner Roark 1st win of the season! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 23:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a weapon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Miami Marlins and the Baltimore Orioles are going into the top of the 10th scoreless. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 03:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who needs runs? 

EDIT: 

Top 11th, 0-0

Top 12th, 0-0

Bottom 12th, Brian Matusz ejected for foreign substance on arm. 

Top 13th, 0-0

Bottom 13th, Marlins win in walk off base hit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/NYYankees salivates over the chance of poaching Harper </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 02:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The most unpredictable playoffs ever" will feature both the #1 and #2 seeds in the conference finals. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 02:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your most upvoted comment and what is your most downvoted comment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 01:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In the past year both the Football and Basketball national champions played the respective VT teams. Neither defeated VT in regulation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 19:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BULLS LOSE AGAIN UPVOTE PARTY!!!!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 04:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bucks take game 5. Bulls lead series 3-2.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Pressiah and faith </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 05:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Pressiah will come. It has been told. 

With the arrival of the Pressiah will come the final truth. Only those who have become a presser shall be saved. No color is better than the other. We are all equal under the Pressiah. All who have failed to press will be damned for eternity to the void. Those who have destroyed their accounts will too be damned to the void. 

We are advocates of peace. Any war in the name of the button is unholy. 

We must recruit followers while we patiently wait for the Pressiah to lead the pressers into the After Press.

Truth will only exist in the After Press and the path runs through the Pressiah. Praise him.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Prophet will come! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 05:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All truth will be revealed through the Prophet. He is destined to come as told by the mods. The Prophet will be the last to click the holy button. The Prophet has already been born and walks amongst us, we must wait for his arrival. 

All hail the Prophet. Join the movement. Pledge your soul to the Prophet.

We are the patients, waiting for the button to reveal the Prophet.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A prayer for the damned </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 05:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thrust into existence without hope, they are few but they are trapped. The reminder of the lowly life of a non-presser forces us to contemplate our own relationship with the button. 

You are blessed to even have a relationship with the button.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Firing, finances roil Collegiate Times' parent company at Virginia Tech - Roanoke Times </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 20:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was your favorite CFBBall comic from last season? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 22:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite rivalry game to watch that doesn't involve your team? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 21:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it has to be the Georgia-Auburn game. No matter what happens the outcome is always interesting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some good elective courses to take? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 02:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (No Spoilers) When do you realisitically believe TWOW is coming to come out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 04:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vote for Lane in /r/CFB's stadium tournament to pull off the upset against LSU! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 00:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A CT profile of a Blacksburg Transit "Drunk Bus" driver </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 05:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What will it take to expand the playoffs from 4 teams to 6 or even 8? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 04:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does /r/news always seem to have a post on its front page about a Police shooting? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 19:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The following posts submitted over the last month combine for a net upvote score of: 23,617.

http://www.reddit.com/r/news/comments/2xymtv/florida_police_shoot_unarmed_pot_dealer_in_face/

http://www.reddit.com/r/news/comments/2wdj8m/unarmed_cooperating_man_shot_in_own_home_the/

http://www.reddit.com/r/news/comments/2wnmzs/lawyer_video_shows_that_a_philly_man_was_running/

http://www.reddit.com/r/news/comments/2wvs8s/prosecutors_not_enough_evidence_cops_who_shot/

http://www.reddit.com/r/news/comments/2xmkaz/deadly_lapd_shooting_of_homeless_man_caught_on/

http://www.reddit.com/r/news/comments/2wzmll/video_of_philly_man_killed_by_police_after_being/

http://www.reddit.com/r/news/comments/2vjfmp/teen_accidentally_shot_by_offduty_officer_police/

http://www.reddit.com/r/news/comments/2x85ey/police_fired_17_times_at_mexican_orchard_worker/

http://www.reddit.com/r/news/comments/2wzch4/lapd_officers_will_not_be_prosecuted_over/
http://www.reddit.com/r/news/comments/2xl030/louisiana_police_officer_charged_with_negligent/

EDIT: As of 7:39 March 5 EST: 11 of the 25 stories on the frontpage of /r/news feature the police.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UVA's Tony Bennett should replace Whitman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 08:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vote for Lane Stadium in /r/CFB's Stadium Tournament! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 05:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> According to the artist, the shadow cast by the plant on the mantle in Bill Clinton's National Portrait Gallery painting represents Monica Lewinsky's infamous stained dress. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 03:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does this sub hate Baylor so much? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 22:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have a confession. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 09:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was born into a Redskins family. I have followed the Redskins. I feel like I have a responsibility to the team. 

But I have to make a confession. 

I am in love with the Green Bay Packers.

I mean whats not to love? The institution - a unique entity in the NFL - one that I believe has the ability to breed the most success. A storied history filled with famous coaches and innovations. A stadium so beautiful and proud. A team filled with talent and potential.

Yes, I am in love with the Green Bay Packers. 

I dream of being in Lambeau surrounded by the best fans in football. I dream of being friends with Eddie Lacy and James Starks, Devante Adams and Richard Rodgers, Ha-Ha Clinton-Dix and Aaron Rodgers!

I want to scream "Go Pack!" every kickoff. 

I want to jump up when Aaron Rodgers throws the game winning touchdown to Randall Cobb and scream "thats my quarterback!" 

I want to high-five Mike McCarthy and hug the Vince Lombardi statue. 

I want to slurp down a warm beer cheese soup and catch the ball Jordy Nelson throws into the stands. 

I want to be a part of this. I want to be a Green Bay Packer. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy Valentine's Day Ohio State! From Virginia Tech. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 00:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can't wait to see you next time you are in town. 

http://www.thekeyplay.com/sites/default/files/images/2015-valentines-day/meyer.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former VT starting QB and Arizona Cardinals Head Coach Bruce Arians named AP Coach of the Year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 03:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Super Bowl XLIX (49) To Feature AFC Champs New England Patriots and NFC Champs Seattle Seahawks on Feb 1 at 6:30 pm EST </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 04:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seattle is the defending World Champion and had a regular season record of 12-4 gaining them the #1 seed. #1 Seattle beat #4 Panthers 31-17 in the divisional round and went on to the NFC Championship to defeat the #2 Green Bay Packers 28-22 in a late comeback surprise.  

New England lost in the AFC Championship round last season to the Denver Broncos who went on to lose to Seattle 43-8 in the Super Bowl. New England had a regular season record of 12-4 winning them the #1 seed. New England beat the #6 Baltimore Ravens 35-31 in the divisional round and defeated the #4 Indianapolis Colts in the AFC Championship 45-7.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CNN just said Serial was created by NPR. It is not. How can news organizations not understand that simple fact? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 01:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Serial is a spin off of This American Life which is created by WBEZ Chicago and distributed by Public Radio Exchange. PRE is a direct competitor to NPR. It would be like saying The Tonight Show is on CBS.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who needs doggie doors? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 00:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FiveThirtyEight: Can Alabama Afford To Lose? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 20:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there an online database where we can see when classrooms are reserved for classes and when they are vacant? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 21:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If there was a College Football Coaches Playoff who would be in your top four? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 18:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My take:

1. Nick Saban
2. Jimbo Fisher
3. Urban Meyer
4. Frank Beamer  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Right now we have adequate parking...There are no plans to build additional parking at this time. - VT Spokesperson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 06:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Make arms and legs illegal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 16:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It might be an overhanded marketing scheme, but you know what, I really want Snoop Dogg to come to VT. Help raise us from #4 to #1! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 20:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These clocks in the same building are an hour apart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 17:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Price We Pay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 03:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two on-campus franchises among the most visited in the nation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 18:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vox: How long it takes to read the books youve been putting off </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 18:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Law   Order: The original series free of gimmicks and surprisingly full of well balanced social commentaries. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 06:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Julia is defeated on the 10 year anniversary of Ken Jennings first appearance. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 01:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Oliver reads an unexpected and hilarious response from POM Wonderful after skewering them on his show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 18:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What did Kurt Kobain have such a terrible time in 7th grade? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 04:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was having a mid-life crisis.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This scene from HBO's Too Big to Fail does a great job of explaining the 2008 financial meltdown. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-12 00:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some of the greatest events in Pink Floyd history? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-10 05:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are your favorite? They can be mundane or monumental, I just want to hear about them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would one become a US Senator before the 17th amendment? Was there a campaign within a state legislature? Were people just appointed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 22:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If someone wanted to be a US Senator prior to the 17th amendment how would you go about doing that? Did people campaign against one another within the legislature? If people were simply appointed did anyone ever turn down that appointment?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is going to replace David Letterman after he retires? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 23:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.nytimes.com/2014/04/04/business/media/david-letterman-to-retire-in-2015.html?emc=edit_na_20140403 nlid=68192450 _r=1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When the news talks about a "theory" regarding the missing Malaysian airplane shouldn't they instead use the word "guess?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-20 00:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Example: http://www.washingtonpost.com/national/health-science/assessing-the-theories-about-flight-370s-disappearance/2014/03/19/d5d59f5a-af7f-11e3-9627-c65021d6d572_story.html?hpid=z1

Aren't theories conclusions made after a series of tests? Many news outlets seems to be using the word "theory" as a more formal substitute for the word "guess." 

Would the word "hypothesis" work as well as "guess?"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should transfer students live on-campus or off-campus? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 18:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will be a sophomore in the fall and I am wondering what the best option for housing is? What are the pros and cons? 

Also there is a wait list for on-campus housing, does anyone know the probability of being offered housing?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The roommate from hell. He refuses to clean, use storage, or bathe. He sleeps all day and plays video games all night. The 2-liter coke bottle is not halfway filled with soda but dip spit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-03 22:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Sandy Hook school shooting 911 audio recordings have just been released. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-04 20:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /u/Muzic22 is playing dumb, may be giraffe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-02 17:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tectonic Hype </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 05:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I believe I have found the closet American equivalent to Qi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-15 02:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some U.S. Redditors may have heard of it. It is not a television show but a weekly radio show. 

Its called:

[Wait Wait...Don't Tell Me](http://www.npr.org/programs/wait-wait-dont-tell-me/)

Its produced by WBEZ Chicago and is broadcasted by NPR. 

The show is hosted by Peter Sagal and features U.S. comedians who face a topical news quiz. I repeat, it is very topical. 

Its not a perfect equivalent but I believe it is the closet.

I hope American Redditors can enjoy it if they haven't heard of it before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 85 days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-26 05:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where there any business or sectors of the economy which did well during the Great Depression? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-22 02:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT][Show] Late 90s/Early 2000s children's show about a kid who worked at an ice cream stand. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-15 00:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to say it ran on a premium television station like HBO. I remember watching it with my parents so it must have been a children's show. I remember it having more then one episode so I think it must be a show, not a movie. I was young when I watched it so it must have been the late 90s or early 2000s. 

The show was live action, not animated. It centered around a young(ish), maybe teenage, boy who worked at an ice cream stand in the summer. 

Please help me, I have been wanting to see this again for a long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chick-fil-A accidentally gave me two chicken patties on one sandwich </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-10 18:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two similar-looking diners wore the exact same shirt while sitting near each other </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 22:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dogs and Cats or Reddit, what is the most annoying thing about your owner? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 21:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Descartes, the father of modern philosophy in three minutes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-31 18:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is the most influential person in history? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-13 20:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You still have 12 hours to vote for Virginia Tech to host the Victoria Secret Pink concert </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-16 05:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What will it take for mainstream vendors like Amazon and Google to begin accepting bitcoins? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-11 01:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What needs to change or improve about the bitcoin economy for bitcoins to have a near universal acceptance among mainstream vendors for at least online transactions? How far away is this from being realized? Is it even inevitable?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most important date in History? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-31 22:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Thomas Jefferson was able to experience America today what would be most surprising to him? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-29 23:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On Naming Our Highest Church </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 03:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What shall we name our great institution? 

* The Church of the Latter Day Flaggs
* The Nation of Flagg
* The Maine Church of Flagg
* The Church of the Highest Flagg 

Other suggestions welcome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite literary magazine? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-10 20:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am interested in choosing a literary magazine(s) to read regularly. What does /r/literature value as the best literary magazine available? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Bush struggles to explain the Oval Office </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-02 19:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Balcony view of Central Park from the Dakota building </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-25 22:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to get from LGA to Grand Central? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-23 20:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm traveling to NYC soon and I am wondering the best route to get to Grand Central Terminal from LaGuardia Airport.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> -- Help me water this tree. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-21 22:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Easily the most cringeworthy political ad from a competitive candidate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-21 03:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nate Silver  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-08 20:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What am I doing wrong?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-15 04:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am fairly new to Photo Shop. I have taken no classes other than quick YouTube tutorials. 

I tried my hand at face swaps and may have gone overboard: http://i.imgur.com/aP4Wd.jpg

But that is not my question! I want to know: how could I improve the skin color matching on the faces and bodies?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Uncrustables sandwich had crust... (X-post /r/pics) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-13 22:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Uncrustables sandwich had crust...  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-13 22:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE Else think we should just put Colby to sleep? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-14 22:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After a year on Reddit I can honestly say that this site has changed me for the better. Redditors, what have you learned or benefitted from Reddit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-14 04:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Being Ignored On Your Cake Day Feels </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-14 03:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why doesn't Guude tell stories in his videos anymore? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-13 02:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One minute Obama's AMA karma score was 16,000+, a second later it dropped to 8,000+. What could have happened? Are downvoting bots to blame for the dramatic drop?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-30 02:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is a link to the thread in question: http://www.reddit.com/r/IAmA/comments/z1c9z/i_am_barack_obama_president_of_the_united_states/

I was interested in how this AMA would play in the standings of most popular Reddit posts of all time. I constantly reloaded the page to see the score. For a while it was around the 16,000 net karma mark. Then, after one reload, the number plumented to 8,000+. Effectively halving the net karma. 

Did the Reddit servers just now catch up? 

Are downvoting bots to blame? 

What could have happened? 

EDIT: Something must be wrong. The AMA is now less than 6,000 net karma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is anyone else frightened by the Reddit alien's encroaching eye?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-26 00:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are all being watched! Snoo's eye is getting bigger and bigger! I don't know if I'm read to see whats past her pupil! What is going on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend's dead body is still warm, is it too soon to cash in on his karma?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 18:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skeletons that are on fire should shoot flaming arrows </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-22 22:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zombies that are also burning should catch the player or villager on fire when they attack them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which Mindcrackers are going to Minecon?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-13 20:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So far here is the list:

- Docm77

- Guude

- BdoubleO100

- W92baj

- Shreeyam

- GenerikB

- Millbee

- Kurtjmac

- Pyrao

- PauseUnpause
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There souls have combined! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-13 06:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Kurt logged out Wolfie seemed to be occupying the same block as him. In that moment the two were sent to the same logout dimension. Since Kurt held the magical golden record it allowed there physical composition to breakdown and open up. Here there spiritual auroras combined into one to form a new soul. 

Kurt is now Wolfie and Wolfie is now Kurt. There is no need to grieve because Wolfie is still here, inside Kurt. 

Now the only way to find [Wolfie](http://i.imgur.com/orOYH.png) is for Kurt to find himself. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Theory on Wolfie's disappearance  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-13 06:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Kurt logged out Wolfie seemed to be occupying the same block as him. In that moment the two were sent to the same logout dimension. Since Kurt held the magical golden record it allowed there physical composition to breakdown and open up. Here there spiritual auroras combined into one to form a new soul. 

Kurt is now Wolfie and Wolfie is now Kurt. There is no need to grieve because Wolfie is still here, inside Kurt. 

Now the only way to find [Wolfie](http://i.imgur.com/orOYH.png) is for Kurt to find himself. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can you believe the Republicans want this right winger as our Vice President? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-11 15:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some of your favorite little known books and authors? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-05 19:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I'm in need of a good book the first place I turn is the best selling list. Those are, nowadays, filled with young adult's novels and erotica so most of the time they are a bust. 

What books or authors have you come across that you have enjoyed but are fairly unknown?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Speculation] - UHC Season 8 to premiere on Sunday, August 5th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-03 22:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to BdoubleO100's latest Mindcrack video he mentions that he recorded a special video(s) that will be released on Sunday. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=62xgkUmN4go feature=player_detailpage#t=712s

Other Mindcracker's have mentioned that the last few days have been busy for them since they are recording so much. 

Since 1.3 was released on Wednesday, and Guude has said they will wait for 1.3 to start a new season of UHC, then it makes sense that we should expect a new season any day.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about Kuroro </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-25 20:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone know which videos Kuroro infamously follows Guude around and annoys him? I feel like their interactions would be hilarious.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My favorite moment in the OOG Legendary series </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-25 16:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Obama is visiting Richmond this weekend, making a stop at the Hanover Tomato Festival  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-13 04:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Farewell to Arms: The Hemingway Library Edition - Collects all of the alternative endings and drafts to other passages for the first time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-05 02:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Suggestion] Players should drop raw meat when they die </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-03 20:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine you are stranded in a desert with your best friend Robb. Robb has accompanied you on your journey and you two have survived together for 40 days and 40 nights. But now you have no food and your water is running low. You are down to 4 hearts and your hunger bar is approaching zero. The desert extends for hundreds of blocks further in every direction and you know that you will not make it to any town in time. You have one choice. Kill and eat Robb. 

Hunger has taken your mind and you raise your sword to Robb's head and cut through his leather. Out of his pockets spill empty glass bottles and a worn wooden sword. But he also leaves behind his meat. It is raw and provides little sustenance, but you have no choice. Robb would have wanted it. As you tear through Robb's flesh with your teeth you have a new take on life. You now have hope. You can survive.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tornado touchdown in Mechanicsville on Saturday night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-02 23:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeb announces that 1.3 will be released in one month. Will Guude and the others wait to record UHC in August?   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-02 19:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the link to Jeb's tweet: https://twitter.com/jeb_/status/219828495918960641 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The first episode of The Arcan Chronicles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-02 00:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new epic fantasy series filmed entirely in the video game Minecraft </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-02 00:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Health care inquiry sparks debate over why America is better than other first world countries that have freedom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-29 19:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When Etho's single player world ends could he move to MindCrack entirely? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-28 21:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Etho has been on his single player world for around 6 months and it is still going strong. But perhaps in the future when he decides that he should move on from his second world due to updates and game changes he could focus his LP on MindCrack entirely. This would be when Guude and the others agree to a map reset. I imagine Etho's LP and the MindCrack world to end at approximate times.

So, do you think Etho should move his LP over to multiplayer?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tectonic Hype </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-28 16:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Episode One Discussion Thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-25 05:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's choose Romney's Vice President </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-24 23:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In just a few weeks Republican candidate for President Mitt Romney will announce his running mate. 

Let's step into the Romney's shoes and see if we can get as close to his choice as possible. 

Factors for Romney's choice include:

- Appealing to the middle class

- Appealing to women

- Appealing to Latinos

Remember to make the choice based on what will benefit Romney's chance of winning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arkas just promised on his live stream to put a video out in a week or two! Subscribe to his channel to catch his first video! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-24 02:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What episode of Mindcrack did Guude first mention the idea of Ultra Hardcore? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-20 23:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember Guude was trying to shear a sheep on a hill and he thought of the concept of not regenerating health. I believe it was in the 250s or 260s. Does anyone know which specific episode?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why does England continue to use the Pound as currency instead of the Euro? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-20 22:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ASOS Spoliers] A Storm of Swords is to be split into two separate seasons. Where will season 3 end and season 4 begin? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-19 21:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The second half of A Storm of Swords is full of new characters and intense turn of events. The Red Wedding being one of those events. It does occur just after the half way point of ASOS, so will the show runners save that scene for the end of the third season or the beginning of the fourth? 

I would love to hear what everyone thinks will be put in each season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Suggestion] Ability to hide IP Adresses in multiplayer list </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-18 19:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To help LPers protect the privacy of certain server IPs there should be a button that can show or block the IPs in the multiplayer screen. 

For example the IPs under the names would be removed when the button is pressed. http://i.imgur.com/6lgkb.png

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should the server change to a new map when 1.3 comes out?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-14 01:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both PauseUnpause and VintageBeef are insisting on a map restart. Guude, however, believes the time is not right. There are a large amount of new people on the server who are working on large projects. 

How does the /r/mindcrack community feel about a change? Are you for a change or are you against it? 

EDIT: I can't tell if people are downvoting because they don't want a new map or because they don't like this post? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who else would love to see her as the Queen of Thorns? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-30 01:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Earth has just established radio contact with intelligent life on a different planet. What do we tell them? How do we even communicate with them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-28 22:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hypothetically our top scientists are now able to send and receive radio signals to and from a planet somewhere in our galaxy that harbors intelligent life. The creatures on that planet are able to communicate and as advanced as we are. How are we able to translate our language to theirs and vice versa? Even if we could understand them and they could understand us what would we even discuss?

PS: For the sake of conversation lets say the time gap between radio signals is only an hour.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
