<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1497</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 09:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And don't offer water to people who've just come around after being knocked out. They don't need fucking water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 09:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks man! I knew there would be some kind of form. There's always a fucking form. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 09:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noice pooter, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 09:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds likely. No one offered to let me pay duty, the shit just never arrived and I eventually gave up trying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 08:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, it looks like you are trying to enjoy a tobacco product. Would you like me to try and ruin it for you, in the pettiest of ways? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 08:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you go about organising it? I tried importing the odd cigar in the past but they were confiscated (I just never received them, so I guess Customs took them) with no letter sent or anything. Just nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 07:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She actually runs a hardware store - 5 cents a screw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 07:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get it real bad when I take amphetamines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can you order tobacco products from overseas if you are willing to pay the duty/tax/excise? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 07:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like if I want a cigar I can't get here. Can I get it from America and be billed for the relevant fees? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 07:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the music rooms at high school we had these big Casio synthesisers that played the most obnoxious, annoying demo track anyone had ever heard. Truly appalling. I can still remember it now. 

It wasn't long before anyone who hit that demo button was sent the fuck outside. Depending on the mood of the teacher, it could be for quite a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 07:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who cares? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 07:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yesterday people were saying it reached 190 km altitude or something like that. Now, it blew up after 4 or 5 seconds. Which is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 07:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. I'll give it a go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 07:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers mate. Never knew about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to watch a youtube video that is blocked in my area dues to "copyright restrictions". Can't find it anywhere else. What do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 04:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's called "The coming War On China" and was showed on a local TV station last night. Now I get this copyright bullshit when I try and see it on youtube. I can't find the full length show anywhere else. 

What can I do? I'm not signing up to the dodgy site you get forwarded to from youtube. Fuck that. How do I get around youtube's restrictions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 04:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you not see the bit where I said I can't remember? Again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 15:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to know a bloke who smoked at least 100 cigarettes a day. That's about one smoke every 7 minutes, if you sleep 50% of the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wonder what happens when a security guard won't let another security guard into the nightclub? They both know all the moves... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 15:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 15:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surely, you can find another way to justify removing posts and comments... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 14:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it still true that all sturgeons caught in English waters are property of the monarch? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 14:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shoulda been charged extra, whiny cunts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 14:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was extremely surprised no one else thought of it first. I mean c'mon, it was there for the taking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 14:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pfft. Like I'm gonna listen to someone who underwent years of schooling before they ever even saw a real patient. I know what's best for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 14:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cold pizza is best pizza. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 14:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can believe that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 14:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ask the cab drivers if they have room for a case of beer and a pizza on Friday nights. They always say yeah. And when I go, "bllllluuuuuuuuuuuugh!" and put it in the back seat, they get all pissy. You were the one who said you had room, cunt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 13:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks mate. I'll look into that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 11:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He shoots, he scores...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 10:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the help. Cheers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 10:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks mate. I'll give that a go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 10:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank fuck for that. I was hoping wouldn't be another one of their lame FWD offerings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 10:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that's what you get for "cracking down" on every fucking single drug people like taking, for decades on end. Oh, no - you couldn't leave people the fuck alone to do the less harmful drugs. You had to screw that up and drive people to the very worst types. Reap what you sow, you fucking idiot lawmakers and law enforcers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 09:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you read properly? Obviously, I'm not talking about this one, moron. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 09:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RWD? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 09:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vegetation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My PC died, but I managed to salvage what was on the hard drive. Does anyone know where I'll find my FireFox bookmarks and if I can get them working again? [Win 8.1] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 09:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surely it's possible? I just have no idea where to look. I did manage to save the contents of the entire HDD and now I've reinstalled FF, I would really like my bookmarks back.

Anyone have any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 09:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not surprised, with the amount of fucking reddit detectives who go through your history in some lame attempt to get the upper hand in an online argument. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 09:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that's where I get my BBQ bottles... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Witcher 3] Why does the information displayed in the corner of the screen keep disappearing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 09:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want the info that tells you which buttons you have assigned to food/drink/potions etc., to remain there all the time. It started out displaying it like that (as far as I can remember). But it seems to come and go. Playing with the settings doesn't seem to fix it. I want what R, F, Y, T do displayed ALL the time, if possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 08:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted that fucking Game Boy so bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 08:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most 2-strokes do not have a dedicated oil lubricating system (although some use auto-lube systems). So you mix the oil with the fuel and then use the fact that the crankcase pressurises the oil/fuel mixture to provide lubrication (in small ones, that is). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 08:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Phenergan, perhaps? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 08:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want to ask any Aussies here if you ever won anything (other than a free one) in the Paddle Pop lick-a-prize competitions? Every time it was on, our school would go through untold amounts of those fucking things. People were buying more than they could eat and just scraping off the ice cream to try and get something good. And no one got a fucking thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 08:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paleo diets are a joke, just like any other fad diet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 08:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And two were already dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 06:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Superhero movies. And unrealistic movies in general. They're fucking shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 06:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? I asked one for a book on suicide - and all she said was "fuck off, you won't bring it back". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 05:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Governments can basically use their sovereign rights to do whatever they want. Companies be damned, if they decide so. I don't like it but that's the way it is. 

Blame the inhabitants of these countries for supporting such draconian measures - like the whiny cunt in the street who thinks his health is being damaged because he gets a whiff of tobacco smoke once in a while. 

The researchers who already know smoking is bad but still apply for (and are granted) funds to demonise it even further. 

The main culprits are the public, plain and simple. They were told to heap scorn and faux concern on smokers and they diligently followed those instructions to the last letter. Trust me, I know - I live in Australia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 04:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a joke. STOP trying to control what people say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 04:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was once banned from /r/worldnews for having an ''offensive username''. There was absolutely no rule in place for that, but rules changed a few days later. Absolutely fucking pathetic. I can't remember what is was but it wasn't even that bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 04:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but like... paleo diets, man. We've been doing it wrong all these years. Trust me, I saw it on TV. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 04:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is relevant to my interests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that why we're talking about it in this very thread, then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, you can find chop-chop if you want it - but it's not very good. Few people have the skill to cure it properly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 15:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American ''chocolate'' LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 15:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No need. I hear this head gasket crap all the time. Seems to be way overblown. I don't believe a word of it. Treat the car properly and it will be fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 15:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its worth more, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 14:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, pulled meat. Another culinary fashion I'll be glad to see the back of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 14:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I keep seeing people using the words "douche", "ass", "sofa" and "sidewalk" on this very subreddit. I call it out every time and I'm usually downvoted for it. So, yeah it would seem that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 14:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Streamable fucking sucks. Although not as much as instagram. That really sucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 14:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just can't imagine how pathetic celebrities must regard people who are obsessed with them. I once saw a post on reddit where someone left work and risked their job to go and attempt to meet some lame-o celebrity at a local bar. It got thousands of upvotes and comments. Fuck's sake. 

Why would whoever it was want to stop and talk to some loser who quite literally idolises them? At what point do you risk your job to meet someone who doesn't even know you exist and won't remember you 10 seconds after you leave? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 14:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flush it down the shitter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 14:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't give me ideas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 14:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. The pressure would kill you very quickly. That fucking thing is deep. Being quickly submerged in a very tall column of turbulent water would end you in a speedy fashion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 14:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a nice anus! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 14:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good. Safety first, please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 14:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> British cars, eh? You dug your own grave. Although I do admit I am mired in German sports car madness - with no end in sight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 13:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do not understand why people care about celebrities so much. I just don't get it. They are not your friend. You don't know them. Nothing you do will make you be like them. Can't people watch a fucking movie without literally worshipping these "stars". It really is pathetic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 13:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NONE. Sick of celebrity garbage impacting on every single aspect of life. It is not necessary. Why do people insist on living vocariously through the comings and goings of fucking famous persons they don't even know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 13:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally too many to list. The Australian government is doing everything in its power to kill off as many brands and forms of tobacco as possible, while simultaneously driving prices into the fucking stratosphere. You have no idea how expensive and annoying being a smoker in Australia has become. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 13:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because we can put tribal and cultural differences aside for the sake of making money? That led to making money by improving quality of life. Everyone wins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 13:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did he ever not try way too hard? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 13:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If that's what he thinks of the movies, I agree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 13:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my cars is a 3 Litre Outback. It's got 240,000 km on the clock and the worst thing that's happened was that I had to replace the cat converters. Bought the parts for 600 bucks and did it myself. Piece of piss. Almost too easy. They are a very good car, all things considered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 13:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Banned in Australia, FFS. we can't have anything without the Fun Police taking it away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 13:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are they mushy peas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 12:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dig a giant ring around it to a depth that is sufficient to cut off what is already burning from where it could potentially burn. Send down temperature probes to work out where the ring should be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 12:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go buy some loose filters, some paper and learn to roll them properly - with your fingers. It's not hard after a few goes and you won't need that fucking monstrosity ever again.

If you must, use something like these:

https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/41JQrFtrSCL._SX300_.jpg

http://s0.merchdirect.com/images/7894/v600_10169-22885.jpg

Extremely simple to use. Guaranteed consistent results and you can take it with you if you want.

But yeah, I strongly advise learning how to do it with your fingers. It will seem impossible at first but you will very quickly work it out. Do yourself a favour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 12:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get someone else to do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 12:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need that in my life. I wouldn't do anything with it but I need it just the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 12:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Completely depends on the rest of the exhaust system. It will definitely sound different but the type and especially the condition of the rest of the exhaust tract is the main factor. Some cars will be very loud, some won't and most will be in between.

Is yours fuel injected or not? Many cars will have a fit if the cat is removed and the CEL will come on straight away. But depends on how new/old/complex the engine management system actually is.

The cat converter is there to convert (hence the name) harmful things like nitrogen oxides into less harmful species. They also can get rid of CO and unburnt fuel to some extent.

The device needs to reach a high temperature to function correctly. In most applications, by the time it is hot enough to work the engine has stopped producing most of what the cat was designed to get rid of. Modern engines usually place the cat as close to the engine as possible so that it heats up quickly.

And finally, over time the cat will be 'poisoned' - it will lose effectiveness until it does nothing at all. Some engine management systems will detect this and some won't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 12:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. When you buy a cat-back system, the maker assumes the cat remains in the same place. So you just bolt it straight on. Still a waste of time, though for most vehicles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 12:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's just thankful it's not him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 12:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can hold on for the first hundred yards... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 12:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, Telstra have driven me to drugs before. And they'll probably do it again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 12:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't say common. Not at all. That one is a 75, I believe. Total production from '99 to '05 was 211,000. We didn't get many Rovers of any type. 
Rover are known for their 3.5 L V8 (the 75 did not have that engine), that can apparently be tickled quite a bit to get some pretty respectable power. But I don't think many people would bother here. It's too small. 

I couldn't find any sales figures for Australia but I'm pretty into my cars and I've seen about five in my life. They weren't good. They weren't bad. They won a few awards. They're just classic British, if you like that sort of thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 11:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks mate, I'll give that a go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 09:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Muslims are the reason this is happening. It does not fucking matter what the history is or isn't. Muslims are the ones rounding them up. Muslims are the ones torturing and killing them. Muslims are the ones who claim they don't even exist. Pull your head out of your arse and stop pretending this is due to any other reason.

What is it with people like you? You will do anything to take the heat off the real culprits. Why, I will never know. Muslims are muslims - wherever they are from or going to. Whether their history is one way or another. STOP apologising for them. No, the Russians did not make them religious zealots who will literally kill to protect their religion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Having a problem starting the latest NMM. Files are missing and I don't like the look of the .exe file it suggests I download and run to fix it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 09:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks quite dodgy, actually. I don't trust this. I installed the NMM and when I try and run it, I am presented with a message that says something to the effect of:

.NET framework version 4.5.2 missing. Do you want to install now?

When I click yes, it takes me to some site called:

dotnetsocial.cloudapp.net 

and wants me to download and install some file called: 

NDP462-KB3151802-Web.exe

What the fuck is that? I've never had to do that with NMM before. Should I trust this? Why isn't the NMM install working like it always did before?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 09:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, the Russians gave the muslims their islamic scriptures and teachings. I never knew that. Thanks for the tip. 

The Russians are the ones forcing the Chechens to be separatists, on account of those teachings. Again, I never realised. 

They only became hardline muslims after the Russians dealt with them and their demands for their own country (so it could be a proper muslim nation), huh? Muslims never go hardline all by themselves, of course. They never start this separatist shit up as soon as they have the numbers. No, they wouldn't do that.

What the fuck are you even on about? You are somehow trying to twist the immediate situation such that these Chechens who are capturing and torturing (presumably with a view to kill them) all these homosexuals, who their own leader refuses to even acknowledge the existence of, are doing it because of the Russians. 

Is that what you're trying to do? Because it sounds like it. Stop apologising for muslims. They are doing this because their scriptures tell them to. If Russia gave them their own country tomorrow, they would still be doing this. You know this. Don't pretend it's anything but the will of their tiny little islamic brains. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 09:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ended up working it out. I was so eager to keep playing I ended up putting them on instead of off.

Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 09:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I thought they were off but they were actually on. Dunno how I fucked that up. Thanks for the mouse control tip. I didn't notice it the first time (too eager to play). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Been playing for a few hours and it's making me sick. It's too blurry and the camera swivels around too fast. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 08:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a good game but I can't deal with the sensitivity of the camera and the extreme blur every single time you look around. Can anything be done about this? It's just too much. No other game has ever had this effect on me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Been playing for a few hours and it's making me sick. It's too blurry and the camera swivels around too fast. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 08:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a good game but I can't deal with the sensitivity of the camera and the extreme blur every single time you look around. Can anything be done about this? It's just too much. No other game has ever had this effect on me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 08:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I'm saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 07:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a bad idea. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 07:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plutonium has 7 allotropes. Super easy stuff to work with... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 07:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What measures does the US have to counter the latest generation of Russian ICBMs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 07:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If people want to racially segregate themselves (i.e. no one else wants anything to do with them because of their behavior) than they can have it their way, for all I care. It actually works quite well. You know exactly which places to avoid in just about every town. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 07:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone know a good way of getting rid of the residual stench that kind of filth leaves behind? I helped a mate clean up his house last month and the fridge was appalling. His parents died and he lost the plot and just stopped cleaning up after himself. I'm trying to help him get back on track but it's an uphill battle. 

The fridge wasn't quite as bad as this pic but it's still pretty bad - everything is 'clean' but the smell remains. And it is horrendous. It's not the rotting flesh smell, but something else almost as nasty. Nearly makes you heave when you open the fucker and some foods/packaging are still absorbing the foul odour. I'm pretty sure he's not gonna fork out for a new fridge, so I need to make the best of what I'm working with.

Suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed. If this shop were near me, I'd go buy something right now. I hope the community fully supports him. The same community that probably didn't ask for an influx of a certain type of people from a war ravaged shithole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm okay with it. There you go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And? This guy needs to protect his business, not the feelings of a small group of people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too bad. He needs to protect his shop, not their feelings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Berk! Feed meeeee... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They completely and utterly prevent that particular person from reoffending, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, they're wasting their time and money installing these huge systems? Yes, it can increase power and efficiency. Two seconds of googling will tell you that:

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Turbine_inlet_air_cooling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just shut the fuck up. Why do you seem to need the last word after you started the whole thing? FUCK. OFF. What part of that don't you get? You carry on like a fag and you get all indignant when someone calls you one. 

What argument? You just started the thread being a fucking unhelpful smartarse. You think you won an argument or something? Do me a fucking favour.

You didn't start this conversation to help anyone, you started it because you wanted to sound superior. Everyone else here, except you, managed to resist the urge to be a fucking smartarse and a know it all. Everyone except you. And now you're still trying to save face by questioning the language I use.

Fuck off and die, faggot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. You can look up wiki for a definition.

https://www.defensetech.org/2010/04/12/gates-says-u-s-has-conventionally-armed-icbms/

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Prompt_Global_Strike

https://www.wired.com/2011/03/air-force-waffles-on-nutty-icbms-vs-terrorists-plan/

You don't know if they have them or how many and neither do I. Neither does wiki. It's not like it's impossible or can't happen . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. It's the fault of muslims living there. Plain and simple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a while it could be a sticker but or course the Fun Police put and end to that. So now, if you get (what was) a really nice cigar box or metal tin for tobacco, the warnings are printed on, ruining the whole thing. For a while you could get cases with your brand at tobacconists but again, the Fun Police couldn't tolerate it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it's a slur here in Australia, too. My go to word for those idiots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
