<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3504</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-03 03:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My pals and I were hanging out one day in Los Angeles. My friends are in a relationship and they were going to stay in a hotel that night. Hours later, it's time for me to leave and we drive to the hotel so i could say goodbye to them. It's freezing outside. At the door this conversation ensues:
Pal:"im walking you to the door its cold!"

Me:"fuck you guys haha im gonna be going fucking outside!"

Pal:"haha we'll be fucking inside!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-02 00:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they are a bully </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 23:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't say I freaked about knowing, it was more about how to let my family know. I hate them not knowing because they really have been my support through other hard things ive had to deal with, and I just feel if i tell them this they will break. But of course i wont know for sure till i tell them... To be honest i dont want to go to a therapist, but maybe a counselor. Therapist tend to make you more confused in my opinion. 

But I will breathe and take MANY MANY deep breaths ( : </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 23:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea im 18 and regardless of my age I never like living in lies or concealing things so im trying to understand, comprehend, then make the best decision. Telling people is hard for me but I know I need too so Im working on who to trust.

The person I like is a friend of mine who is bi as well, and she knows about me AND how I feel about her. I only told her that i MAY like her but little did i know i like her very much. I don't want to like her and don't know how to push it away. Crushes are easy to stop but i believe this isn't a crush so its really hard. 

But all said, Im going to follow any advice I can get because I know that i don't know what the hell to do or exactly what i want.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 11:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ENJOY MUSIC BEFORE..WELL YOU KNOW .. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I know I'm BI, no one knows, help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 10:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I just realized, put the pieces together and became aware that im bi. Im just nervous and scared about people knowing, not only friends but family mostly. They mean everything to me but they are also judging people when it comes to this. And the other half of this is that I really like someone but I want to quit liking and maybe even loving them because its too much to have to carry with me. Its hard enough accepting these changes that Im not use to AT all, let alone execute them, when i have no idea how too. I dont wanna lose their friendship but dont know what to do. I constantly feel paranoid that im going to out myself before im mentally prepared too. I just need guidance and most of all comfort.

Edit: I let a pal use this to get help. I forgot to tell her to mention that.
This is her question.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 01:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see. I guess i was referring to the Disney happy go lucky versions. My apologies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 00:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, I mean it's like Spongebob suddenly being a Karate hero fighting a druglord and his henchmen. Kinda off. I understand your point though. The "childrens" stories were dark but still aimed at children. Right in the childhood.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what are your thoughts on the new children gone warrior movies? Ex:Snow White and the Huntsman and now Hansel and Gretel. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 00:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-24 02:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thatsphuked.com may have a different spelling but it scarred me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-21 06:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found my cat in the tree like that today. She was stuck when we got home, we had to get her out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-21 06:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OUR LIFE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 22:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone think of the Sistine chapel?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-17 19:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the night knows  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-17 11:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is your actual name?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-14 18:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can crawl around like a cat or spider around the house without making any noise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-14 05:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL Americas first African-American president was actually half white.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-14 02:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a sec I thought the title was sarcasm reading the beginning. But hey congrats girl! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-12 20:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone see bubble boy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-12 19:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow the end molestation fucked me up, but that fucking *pile..* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-12 02:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's her fingers plus the reflection if her fingers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-10 09:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Swagger, sagging, looking like an idiot overall </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-10 09:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YES I THOUGHT THEY DIE-oh they just blew over </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-08 07:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mr. Burns dog... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-06 08:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey snoop my aunt said she saw you once before your stardom. You hit on her and she turned you down..sorry about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-29 17:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not butch, but I use these because they are fucking convenient.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-28 21:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same as OP. Stay inside mostly because i live in Los Angeles. So anything could happen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-26 23:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cleaning up. Like I never put shit where it belonged. Didn't care really, tried to remember to no avail. Now. When im over my pals house and see pants on the floor or on the desk im like seriously dude PUT THEM AWAY.

Also I hate when people don't use coasters. ..dat ring... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-26 22:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoops. I read playing with himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-26 22:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put myself and my friends through college. Give money to family. Buy a car, then set up an account for when I buy a house later, then set up a college fund for my future children.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-24 05:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My cat as well..
http://www.imgur.com/WDWlv.jpeg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-23 07:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That kinda scared me O.o </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-22 11:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kits wife pregnant?

Alien baby?

Wut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-22 11:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The show makes it seem waaaaay shorter..days even. But five months? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-22 00:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Things people do in secret then wonder if anyone else is as strange as they are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-21 09:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kermit and marbles! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-19 05:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shes cute :)

I like how there's one downvote like there is one pissy bitch xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-17 23:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jenna

Alex

Siobhan  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-16 22:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Mom I have some news..."

"What is it?"

"Im gay..."

"Oh that's totally cool!  Let's celebrate and tell our accepting church and family!"

"Thanks mom! I have a tattoo as well!"

"GET THE FUCK OUT."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-15 18:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Middle School: girl caught sucking dick in a stall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-15 17:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I taught my little cousins (aged 7 4) to love everyone. And being nice to a person even if a boy kissed a boy, a girl kissed a girl and a boy kissed a girl. Everyone is special.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-15 02:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Laughed too hard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-15 02:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL;DR if you date online your are going to have a crazy time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-15 02:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry but i have no clue what im lookin at :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-13 21:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over here we call it "ghetto padding" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-13 06:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im a woman reading these for fun, and so far between laughs I noticed the top three subjects here:
1) Dick 
2) penis
3) more dick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-11 03:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow that summed up my whole life lmao. As a black woman who enjoys just about everything, its awkward when people are like "you like Cold War Kids? Waaa?"

"What the fuck? You like August Burns Red? But your black..."

"Oh you like Drake? Me too."

Like the fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-10 02:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Front row to a soccer or football game.

Sneak into a Svenhards factory and eat all of the danishes.

Go into a comicon and make people think their powers are real.

Eat a shitload of greek food.

If there is a midnight showing of a movie to my liking,  go see it. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-09 05:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OCD my friend  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-07 18:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was at a play last night and during an intermission, spotted a lesbian couple. I asked them if they knew the results.

(Not many people knew because it was announced during the play. No cells phones..yadda yadda)

I asked of they wanted to know. I'll never forget the look of fear on one of the girl's face. Romney literally scared this woman, and she didn't even know if he won/lost! I told the results and the relief! You could cut it with a knife.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-07 18:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Elvis * </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-07 18:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> California-beaches and hipsters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-04 22:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you watch infomercials and they show their product being used in color being all awesome. Then they show the derpy ass way of using a similar product in grey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-04 08:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was about 11 years old when my biological mother's boyfriend decides that getting drunk and shooting his gun would be a good idea.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tonight I told my girlfriend that I loved her for the first time. What are the unique ways you told your significant  other you loved them for the first time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-04 06:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We were at at party for my friends father and there was a jumper there, (friends father has friends with kids) so we decided to go in when it was empty. We talked for a bit and even jumped a little. Then it was time to tell her. I was scared shitless. So i used pop culture to help ease me along. 

Me: "Have you heard the song 143 by Ray J?"
Her: "noo.."
Me: "well do you know what 143 means?"
Her: "No, what is it?
Me: "143 means I Love You....And i do. I do love you."

TL;DR too scared to tell girlfriend 'i love you' normally so I used a pop song as help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-03 05:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Erykah Badu

"If we are made in God's image then call us by our names." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't do it personally, but my roomate's mom may have a problem with it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-02 00:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-01 21:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grandpa? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-29 09:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hummus, wheat and white pita bread, baklava. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-29 09:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-29 09:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dont hate me....but....chocolate :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-28 04:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds enhance for me. Like an air conditioner suddenly sounds like WW2. Once i was halluciating when an episode came on and a friend was laying in front of me on her laltop. When  felt it coming on she was suddenly sitting up staring at me it was so weird then my breathing was the loudest shit id ever heard! when it was over I blinked she was laying down again. I asked her about if she heard my breathing and if she moved. She heard nothing and DIDNT MOVE AT ALL. Pretty creeped out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-28 04:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit I clicked on this post just to say that. Fuck it, upvote for understanding how that shit can be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-28 03:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> already posted, this but whatever. Not lately, but in the 2nd grade I had to pee really bad. I raised my hand like a good child, and the teacher(bitch) was standing in fron of the class talking so she says to stand next to her till ahes done, then I can go. I was fiddling with my dress straps(im a girl), and by some fucking asshole magic my dress fell to my ankles. Remember i was standing in front of the class. Ive never moved that fast in school since. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-24 09:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend nicknamed me Figaro like the cat from Disney.
Im into astrology, and Neptune is my ruling planet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-24 08:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Styrofoam  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-24 00:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely forgot about that shit. Plus claytons shadow..I remember feeling scared because i just watched a man accidentally hamg himself plus dead bodies. Thanks Disney. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-23 15:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snow white: loving, nurturing.....warrior? 


NO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-23 15:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually just held my fucking breath. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chefs/cooks of Reddit, does it offend or hurt your feelings when a costumer doesn't finish all or most of the food you made? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-19 10:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work at a restaurant and I was bussing tables and I noticed one of the plates had most of the food still on it. Its like the person just took a few bites. Seemed pretty wasteful to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-07 03:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Candy man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-07 03:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pasadena here. Loves DAT ranch.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-07 03:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eagle Rock music festival </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My miniature poodle Teddy He was waiting for me like this on the patio. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-07 00:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-06 04:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tells me I'm not, so far I'm good. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-05 20:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vanilla sky </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-05 19:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slutty telletubby </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-05 19:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My grandmother was a foster parent. She got three siblings. It was nice because I was usually alone when I went to visit her. They never left her and she eventually adopted them. They are wonderful additions to our family :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-05 19:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-05 10:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope not sophiathedictator </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
