<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2894</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She wasn't drunk I was. I'm guessing you didn't understand what you tried to read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It happened to me and I didn't do anything. It really didn't bother me other than she was my best friends supposed girl at the time and he caught her luckily. He was with me all night and knew I went to crash and I was wasted and what he caught her trying to do made it obvious I wasn't able to stop her. He's a nice dude even took her home but that was the last I heard about her other than over some beers later to say wtf was that and laugh about it. Good question though. Still doesn't bother me years later. I guess it's different for males when a female is the aggressor and maybe it has to do with the type of aggression and state of mind if the victim.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I compromised in saying we could go in the morning and skip fishing. He could have countered with cash or something but took the first deal. So you may be right I guess... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Back in the day before Reddit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was at my friends camp in Delaware I think near the Indian river. We were staying in his grandparents camp. 4 dudes in a trailer shape house but I think it was an actual house they called a camp. We got there at night and I slept on the way down. We were in college at the time. Me and my roommate stayed in one room with two twin beds that were on opposite sides of the room. We all went to bed around 1. We were getting up in the morning for some fishing. 

This is where it gets odd. We were both in our bed with the lights off. I was laying with my eyes open and I started to see a gray smokey like figure above my roommates bed. I didn't say a word and really didn't think much of it until my roommate said "hey *my name* quit f'n around. I remained silent. I stared to get a bit scared. He said my name in a more panicked way and I said "I'm over here dude". He then said "turn on the lights" I said "no way I'm not moving" he then said our friends name and said get the f out of here. This whole time it looked like the smokey figure was kicking at him that was in front of the bed and one was floating above the bed. He jumped out bed and turned on all the lights in the building. He tried to get me to leave right then but I was to tired. We left at 6 am and he didn't enter that room again. I believe he sat in the recliner in the living room all night. I drove home.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My quick ghost story </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was at my friends camp in Delaware I think near the Indian river. We were staying in his grandparents camp. 4 dudes in a trailer shape house but I think it was an actual house they called a camp. We got there at night and I slept on the way down. We were in college at the time. Me and my roommate stayed in one room with two twin beds that were on opposite sides of the room. We all went to bed around 1. We were getting up in the morning for some fishing. 

This is where it gets odd. We were both in our bed with the lights off. I was laying with my eyes open and I started to see a gray smokey like figure above my roommates bed. I didn't say a word and really didn't think much of it until my roommate said "hey *my name* quit f'n around. I remained silent. I stared to get a bit scared. He said my name in a more panicked way and I said "I'm over here dude". He then said "turn on the lights" I said "no way I'm not moving" he then said our friends name and said get the f out of here. This whole time it looked like the smokey figure was kicking at him that was in front of the bed and one was floating above the bed. He jumped out bed and turned on all the lights in the building. He tried to get me to leave right then but I was to tired. We left at 6 am and he didn't enter that room again. I believe he sat in the recliner in the living room all night. I drove home. 

Typed this up for another Reddit post and thought I'd drop it here for you all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No man I was 19 and worried about partying and girls. no one believed us not even our Friend who's camp it was. My buddy and I still bring it up every couple years. We're 34 now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. They weren't after me. I left the lights on though and covered my head. I never got out of the bed to my recollection. I was pretty scared  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was at my friends camp in Delaware I think near the Indian river. We were staying in his grandparents camp. 4 dudes in a trailer shape house but I think it was an actual house they called a camp. We got there at night and I slept on the way down. We were in college at the time. Me and my roommate stayed in one room with two twin beds that were on opposite sides of the room. We all went to bed around 1. We were getting up in the morning for some fishing. 

This is where it gets odd. We were both in our bed with the lights off. I was laying with my eyes open and I started to see a gray smokey like figure above my roommates bed. I didn't say a word and really didn't think much of it until my roommate said "hey *my name* quit f'n around. I remained silent. I stared to get a bit scared. He said my name in a more panicked way and I said "I'm over here dude". He then said "turn on the lights" I said "no way I'm not moving" he then said our friends name and said get the f out of here. This whole time it looked like the smokey figure was kicking at him that was in front of the bed and one was floating above the bed. He jumped out bed and turned on all the lights in the building. He tried to get me to leave right then but I was to tired. We left at 6 am and he didn't enter that room again. I believe he sat in the recliner in the living room all night. I drove home.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was at my friends camp in Delaware I think near the Indian river. We were staying in his grandparents camp. 4 dudes in a trailer shape house but I think it was an actual house they called a camp. We got there at night and I slept on the way down. We were in college at the time. Me and my roommate stayed in one room with two twin beds that were on opposite sides of the room. We all went to bed around 1. We were getting up in the morning for some fishing. 

This is where it gets odd. We were both in our bed with the lights off. I was laying with my eyes open and I started to see a gray smokey like figure above my roommates bed. I didn't say a word and really didn't think much of it until my roommate said "hey *my name* quit f'n around. I remained silent. I stared to get a bit scared. He said my name in a more panicked way and I said "I'm over here dude". He then said "turn on the lights" I said "no way I'm not moving" he then said our friends name and said get the f out of here. This whole time it looked like the smokey figure was kicking at him that was in front of the bed and one was floating above the bed. He jumped out bed and turned on all the lights in the building. He tried to get me to leave right then but I was to tired. We left at 6 am and he didn't enter that room again. I believe he sat in the recliner in the living room all night. I drove home.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Np good luck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't have a suit go get one from the good will or hustle someone who loves you to hook you up until you can get them back and find a deal somewhere. Darker Gray seems to be the safe color. Where a tie, blue or red but if you are looking in something a bit more trendy purple seems to get some attention. White shirt. Clean dress shoes. Make sure it's all pressed. You can probably hustle all this for cheap. I know I can. Make sure you are cleaned up on your face and hair. Even if you are a trendy person just suck it up and do it. Be yourself after you proof yourself. 

Try to line up some interviews now with companies you can see yourself enjoying the work at. Send your resume and specific cover letter identifying your interest and a few reasons why you are a good fit. Research the company a bit so if you do get an interview you can speak intelligently about their business. If you don't get anything lined up b4 you get there. Make a list of targets and plan to get the first when when they open in the morning. Ask to speak to the HR. If they are available sell yourself. If they are not thank whoever you talked to hand them your cover letter and resume and move on to the next one. 

If you get an offer and you still have more interviews or targets I'd say tell each offer that you are grateful for the offer and you must do due diligence and sleep on it. They should be ok with that and if they are not move on. Keep repeating until you figure a way to sell yourself to a organization that needs something you can offer. 

Good luck 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriends cousins are missing from DC area. Can you get the names and description out to your audience please? Sania   Liara Harris. 15 years old, 5-2 or 5-3 tall, 120-130 lbs brown skin, Sania has a birth mark on her right cheek 

IMG_3251.PNG </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 14:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Obama and the left are more 1984 with their "Daddy State". Trump is like something we haven't experienced b4 in the US.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone should build these palm oil guys a breathable exoskeleton suit with an electric charge to zap that big ass snake when it wraps around you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well done. I couldn't agree more. 1.8 HS GPA here and the whole time I knew I was wasting my time. I had one teacher that agreed and she made a deal with a group us really disruptive guys that she would make us brownies on Friday's if we worked on getting some Microsoft certs. I ended up getting a few certs and ended up in IT and now I've got a 4 word title and CEO's actually call me for advise. Shit still blows my mind when I think about how HS made me feel like I was the dumb failure and now I'm the youngest person I know at my level.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 06:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just my opinion, I think it's the level of intrigue he displays when he says it that could rub some one the wrong way...the big black cock is attached to the scary black man. Not saying Joe is at all a racist or bigot but I hear what this post is about. People can be sensitive about that I'm certain it turns off a portion of the audience but Joe doesn't seem to be looking for mass market appeal so probably the right thing to do is not listen if you don't like it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
