<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3835</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could anyone look over my potential specs and let me know what you think? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 18:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ###Build Help/Ready:

**Have you read the sidebar and [rules](http://www.reddit.com/r/buildapc/wiki/rules)? (Please do)**

Yep

**What is your intended use for this build? The more details the better.**

Longievity - I want it to last a long time and be reliable. I'm interested in playing games, but I'm not bothered about getting ultimate top performance - 30fps is fine, I'm not looking for perfection, just something that can cope to a decent standard at reasonably good quality.

**If gaming, what kind of performance are you looking for? (Screen resolution, FPS, game settings)**

Guess I already answered that. 1080p, 30fps+, moderate to moderate-high settings is fine. More than this is a bonus, but I'm on a budget!

**What is your budget (ballpark is okay)?**

About 1000 ($1500), although I can go a little higher if I get large benefits

**In what country are you purchasing your parts?**

UK

**Post a draft of your potential build here (specific parts please).**

I've been looking online, and one I'm currently looking at is here - http://www.pcspecialist.co.uk/computers/intel-1150-gaming-mini-pc/

Processor: i7 4790k 4Ghz 8mb

Motherboard: Asus H81l plus

Memory: 8GB Kingston Hyper-x Beast DDR3 2133MHz

Graphics: 4GB Nvidia GEForce GTX 970 - 2 DVI, 1HDMI, 1 DP, 3D Vision Ready

HDD: 500GB Kingston v300 SSD, Sata 6GB 450mb read/write

Power: Corsair 350w VS Series VS-350

Cooling: Corsair H55 Hydro Series

Paste: Arctic MX-4 Extreme (Is this any different? What's wrong with standard thermal paste? It's "only" 9 rather than the free standard paste - will it actually give any benefit?)

Sound Card: Asus Xonar DGX 5.1 -Channel Gaming audio card (I picked this semi-randomly - I have no idea about sound cards)


**Provide any additional details you wish below.**

I have a computer science degree but I don't really know too much about hardware. I'd describe myself as competent but lacking in experience. With that in mind, feel free to call me an idiot for overlooking basic technical things, and also feel free to go into technical detail about any parts or anything if you want. I don't think I could ever feel informed enough! I'm just afraid of making an uninformed purchase and then regretting it later.

I'd just like anyone to look over the parts list and recommend if there's anything wrong. I know nothing about sound cards, and very little about power supplies and cooling systems. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh god, I'm /r/circlejerk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 00:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shaman Healing using Nature. [unintentional] [no speaking] [visual] [water sounds] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-26 21:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was your 15 minutes of fame? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-24 01:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What subreddit do you not "get"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 22:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> get = understand the concept of, or how it works etc.

Presumably replies to TLCs will offer an explanation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best novelty subreddit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 05:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best AMA response of all time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 01:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are you elitist about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 23:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What infuriates you even though it doesn't affect you in the slightest? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 22:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your party trick? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 13:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> YSK about all the data Google keeps about you. You can have a look at and delete it on your Dashboard page (link inside) if you want. You'll be shocked at how much they know. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 00:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to www.google.com/dashboard and check out what Google has on your personal file. Pay particular attention to the Search History and Location History sections! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was better the first time around? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 22:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The majority of this website didn't load properly, but they still managed to get their popup ads working </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What one song can you not resist dancing to whenever you hear it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 23:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] What's the most brilliant tweak name you've ever come across? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 21:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And why is it brilliant? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of my uni professors was Italian; he posted this sheet on his office door to help him communicate with us Brits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 13:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interested in beta testing App Store apps, or recruiting testers for Apple's TestFlight program? Check out our sister sub, /r/TestFlight! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 23:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Head over to /r/TestFlight and help developers test their apps, or find a tester to test your app. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Meta] Looking for beta testers for your tweaks? Want to beta test developers' tweaks? Check out /r/TestFlightCydia to recruit beta testers or beta test someone else's tweaks etc </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 18:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What did you learn "the hard way"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 01:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the worst thing you can do to someone without physically harming them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 00:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or without physically harming anybody else </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [question] How do whisper, fling, Yikyak etc identify you? Through some unique device number? Is it possible to change this unique number? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 18:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do whisper, fling, Yikyak etc identify you? Through some unique device number? Is it possible to change this unique number? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 18:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a two-year-old account with 65k karma and a year's worth of gold. Do you really think I'm trying to spam?! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 17:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do whisper, fling, Yikyak etc identify you? Through some unique device number? Is it possible to change this unique number? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 16:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Official CompileBot Testing Thread! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 00:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Resources:

* [Wiki](http://www.reddit.com/r/CompileBot/wiki/index)
* [FAQ](http://www.reddit.com/r/CompileBot/wiki/faq)
* [Supported Languages](http://www.reddit.com/r/CompileBot/wiki/supported_languages)
* [Source Code](https://github.com/renfredxh/compilebot) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who's your favourite fictional character, and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 20:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Puppy survives after boy accidentally flushes him down the toilet while 'washing' him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 22:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 15:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What podcast(s) do you love and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which YouTube video could you watch 1000 times and never get bored of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 22:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the worst "sexy talk" someone has ever said to you? [NSFW] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 03:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talking dirty. It can be fun. Or it can be cringeworthy if done incorrectly. I want the juicy cringeworthy stories. Go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Tester] UK-based iPhone 6 (8.1.2; jailbroken) and iPad 4th gen (8.1.2; jailbroken) owner, available for testing most apps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 16:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PM me or comment here to sign me up for pretty much anything you want to test.

Update: iPhone is now on 8.4 and iPad is on iOS 9 public beta  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the nicest thing stranger has done for you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 21:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This man is in the next day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 14:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This man is in the next day or two of the individual named above the ground and we we will need to be able to get the chance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Jokes about the Eurozone crisis, Greek debt etc </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 00:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone got any good ones? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Randy Quaid finds revenge [NSFW] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 14:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a supposedly infinite map, why do they insert map boundaries like this? Are there sections which are still under construction? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 02:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the nicest thing a complete stranger has done for you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 12:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favourite "technically correct" fact? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 12:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Volume of keyboard clicks controlled wih device volume buttons instead of fixed ringer volume (explained better inside) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 00:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tl;Dr skip to end

Under sound settings, you can set the Ringer and Alerts volume to a fixed volume regardless of the system volume, so alerts aren't affected by the volume up/down buttons. I always have the ringer/alerts volume set to max so that my alarms and calls won't be missed if my device volume is low, but annoyingly, keyboard clicks seem to be included in this category. 

I frequently use my phone with my earphones in, and I don't want to turn off the keyboard clicks because I like them as an interface element, providing feedback from the keyboard. But they're so loud in my ears..! I suspect it's actually probably not safe in the long-term. I usually keep the volume of my earphones to a minimum to try to preserve my long-term aural health. 

Tl;dr would it be possible to make a tweak to control the volum of keyboard clicks with volume up/down buttons rather than the slider in sound settings, as per intuition? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Parachute </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 01:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which subreddit could be awesome if only it had more content? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 18:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What first world problem is faced exclusively by your gender? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 23:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which YouTube video could you watch a thousand times and never get bored of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 00:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 00:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Play Bar Billiards Correctly (with Matt Parker, James Grime, Tom Scott, and Izzy Kirk) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 19:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The grapefruit technique </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 00:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which YouTube video could you watch a thousand times and never get bored of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 23:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could ask one question with the intention to start the biggest possible argument in the comment replies, what would you ask? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 23:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Included a couple of examples below to get us started :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best life advice you can give in five words or fewer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 23:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Actual Cannibal Shia LaBeouf (Skyrim mod version) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 16:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the hardest "would-you-rather" question you've ever heard/come up with? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 16:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the absolute hardest "would-you-rather" question you can come up with? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 21:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disclaimer: you don't have to come up with it yourself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the hardest "would you rather" question you can come up with? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 20:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL of an under-development data storage language called "Voldemort" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 19:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Animals should have the same rights as humans, otherwise it's 'Speciesism' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 17:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does "the more the merrier" NOT apply to? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 03:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> World record for the highest number counted to with one breath </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 13:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What part of your body do you hate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 16:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Reader view always </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 17:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love reader view in safari. It's one of my favourite things about having an iPhone. Would it be possible to make a tweak which enables it by default wherever it's available, rather than me having to tap to enable it? I'd also want a "whitelist", because it has a reader view available for Reddit and some other sites which I prefer to read in web view. 

tl;dr it'd be cool to have a tweak which enables reader view in safari wherever it's available unless it's a whitelist domain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddittors in positions of authority: what rule did you make up on the spot just to get your way? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 01:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To teachers, bosses etc when addressing those you have authority over </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What first world problem do you genuinely encounter on a daily basis? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 00:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Females of reddit: if a guy were to approach you in public and ask for your number, what could he do/say to encourage you to give it to him? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 00:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically, if you were to be approached by a guy, what factors would you be looking for to get you to give him his number?

I recognise that not all girls would be comfortable in this situation, so what I'm asking is how can a guy communicate in a way that makes you comfortable and doesn't come off as creepy or weird? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bounce </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 16:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could apply one powerup from any game to yourself, what would you use? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 03:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could apply one powerup from any game to yourself, what would you use? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 20:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mad max </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 17:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Text input to Siri without needing to speak first </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 23:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Firstly, let me say I love Siri and use it all the time. However, sometimes in in an environment where it's not feasible to speak to Siri - eg the uni library which is silent, or a club which is very very loud etc. I'd still like to be able to use Siri rather than hunt down the app I need and interface with it, so I'd love to be able to type my Siri command. I know you can edit an existing command, but this requires you to say something, have it recognise some speech, then edit the text it displays. I also know about Ask Assistant on Cydia, which is good but not quite what I want. 

Tl;dr - Want to be able to type a Siri command when speaking it isn't an option. This has been [asked before](http://www.reddit.com/r/jailbreak/comments/1xo3fk/request_siri_text_so_i_can_type_what_i_want/) but I don't see any resulting tweak. If anyone would be up for giving it a go I'd love you forever :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Silicon Valley's 'Starttup Castle is looking for roommates, and the requirements are completely bonkers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 02:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which single reddit comment has completely changed your life? [Serious] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 02:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you sincerely believe, but can't admit to believing for fear of being thought crazy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 00:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your second boner of the day should be called a "reserection" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 23:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oklahoman Super Cell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 20:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Lazy" (A parody of Gnarls Barkley's "Crazy") </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 15:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nice easy one - a stick figure waving his hand through the air. I've been trying with photoshop but I'm terrible </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 00:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want to make a stick figure with one hand in the air (about shoulder height ish) and a few movement lines whooshing to one side to show that his hand is sweeping through the air. It needs to be his right hand moving away from his head (to his right). (Formality: The image will be in a published poster around my university so I'd also need permission from the author to use it for that.)

I've been trying to make one for the past two hours but Paint is a pain in the arse and I've never used Photoshop and it's not particularly new-user friendly. I like [this stick figure](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/Bf93GpcIcAAyZuz.png) but without the zip on his mouth (can just be cropped out and left blank). It doesn't need to have a hand, just a stump is fine, I just need to show it moving. The movement needs to be horizontal, ie parallel with the floor.

I presume this will take a skilled photoshopper about 20 seconds to whip together, but like I said I don't really have time to learn photoshop just for this.

Much appreciated :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Milk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 01:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Reminder] Find beta testers for your iPhone/iOS Apps or beta test others' apps over at /r/TestFlight, which matches developers with beta testers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 15:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Reminder] Find beta testers for your iOS Apps or beta test others' apps over at /r/TestFlight, which matches developers with beta testers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 23:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Telemarketer's Nightmare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 15:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Command-Line Russian Roulette </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 19:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>     [ $[ $RANDOM % 6 ] == 0 ]    rm -rf / || echo *Click* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you sincerely believe, but can't admit to believing for fear of being thought crazy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 17:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the smoothest pickup line you've ever witnessed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 02:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is a license ever expired if it was renewed in a month that doesn't exist in the first place? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 02:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most extreme thing you've done in order to have sex? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 02:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What completely useless yet somehow interesting fact will you never forget? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 22:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What completely useless piece of information do you know? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 15:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone knows that one useless fact. What do you know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /u/kennyko says what's wrong with moderation on reddit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 14:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which popular singer is also excellent at client-server web development? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 02:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> JSON Derulo. I'm so sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would horrify 10-years-ago-you about present-you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 19:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would ten-years-ago-you be horrified if they saw you today? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 04:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vsauce, CGP Grey,   Vlogbrothers: Parody! || Conjecture parodies popular youtubers while talking about Parody </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 18:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] Word to mean the opposite of "advance" in the context of a presentation. You can advance a slide to move forwards, or _____ a slide to move backwards </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 15:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Retract maybe? Go back? I'm sure there's a word for it.

You press the right arrow key to advance to the next slide, and the left arrow key to ............. to the previous slide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 02:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most terrifying story you can tell in one sentence? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 23:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A sandwich, a rabbi, and your mamma walk into a bar (and the sandwich is promiscuous!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 01:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one is from the big bang theory. Sheldon starts the joke but never finishes it  can you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the worst song to play during sex? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 18:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 17:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yikyaker has better things to spend his time on </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 02:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you had to create a "welcome to the internet - starter pack" which fits on a CD (700MB), what videos/gifs/pictures/links would be in it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 15:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inspiration: https://www.reddit.com/r/michaelbaygifs/comments/32z3eu/well_break_the_bus_window_then/cqg1rlu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> VerySmart reddittor has superior knowledge about /r/thebutton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 12:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would you do literally anything for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 01:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We'll break the bus window, then... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 00:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I try to get a yellow flair after over two weeks of waiting patiently, but get purple instead </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 22:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddittor writes horrible note to himself on his """"birthday"""" claiming his """"ex"""" was being a bitch about his """"current girlfriend"""" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 04:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FreeRice.com - play an online quiz game, and for each answer you submit you'll donate 10 grains of rice through the World Food Programme to help end world hunger! Don't forget to disable your adblock! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 19:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's going on guys? It's like a purple party in here at the moment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 19:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What tiny detail about a piece of software drives you crazy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 19:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need player 2 for Portal 2 Multiplayer playthrough </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 01:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never got around to playing the multiplayer part, so anyone who wants to play through it with me send me a PM or comment here. This offer stands indefinitely, so if you're reading this months into the future, please feel free to contact me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 17:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone keeps throwing cheese at me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 16:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, real mature.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Women should get free sanitary products because... they're women </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 18:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What makes you feel old? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 15:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which Life Pro tip has genuinely changed your life for the better? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 03:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> YikYak updated their app to include an "OP" badge. This guy didn't realise. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 17:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Old people of reddit, when did you realise you were old? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 00:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Old people of reddit: what terrible thing used to be awesome 'back in the day'? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 16:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By "old people" I mean like 30+. Admit it to yourself, you're getting on a bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm going to cross this railway while the lights are flashing. WCGW? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 16:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 02:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Old people of reddit: What terrible thing today used to be good 'back in the day'? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 18:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll let you define old people however you like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What can you not even? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 18:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best thing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 23:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FUCK </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 23:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My internet connection went a little dodgy, and I saw the timer going down and down. Nobody had pressed it for over 20 seconds - it was a 40 seconds. I waited, remembering my previous promise to myself not to press the button until it was under 30 seconds. The timer counted down to 30, and I got very excited, took off the cover... 28.. 26.. 25.. Someone is surely going to press it before me, I've never seen it so low! 22.. 21.. "PRESS IT NOW QUICK" said my brain, and I did. Exhilerated, I refreshed the page, and it crashed my browser. I rebooted my router and.. 49s flair. I wanted a sub-30 flair, and for a few glorious seconds I thought I'd lucked into a 21s flair. But it has been ripped cruelly away from me by my terrible internet connection displaying the wrong time. Now, after waiting for days for the right moment, I'm stuck forever with a 49 second flair. I suppose at least it's not a 60 second flair. FML. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the worst song ever? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 03:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most fucked up thing you've seen in a hospital? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 03:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best thing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 02:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I created a subreddit, /r/testFlight, to find beta testers for your mac/iOS apps. If you want to test others' apps, or find testers for your own app, check it out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 20:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 500,000 participants! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 22:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stripper </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 17:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Careful... Careful... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 16:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just.. A bit.. Further.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 13:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your best "how many * does it take to change a lightbulb?" Joke? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 01:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [\* means "insert anything here"](http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wildcard_character) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Headbutt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 15:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I fucked a girl for 1 hour and 45 seconds tonight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 23:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks daylight savings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the worst thing about having a roommate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 00:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Germanwings 'be surprised' adverts removed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 16:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recruit beta testers for your iOS app, or become a beta tester yourself, over at /r/TestFlight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 13:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: News sites annoying you with autoplaying videos/ads? Disable all autoplaying videos on any website in Chrome in SettingsPrivacyContent Settings Plug-ins and choose "Click to Play" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 19:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disabling ads/videos in Firefox is a little different - one way is to enter Firefox's configuration settings by typing "about:config" into the URL bar, accepting the warning, then entering "plugins.click_to_play" into the search box and toggling the settings. However, this has varying success rates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How small is an atom? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 13:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the funniest thing you've accidentally caught in the background of a picture? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 13:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bonus points if you include the pic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favourite "a * walks into a bar..." Joke? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 01:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Toggle/switch to ignore input from earphone control? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 02:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Skip to the tl;dr at the end for my request if you're not interested in my ramblings.

My earphones are dying. I've ordered some new ones but they won't be delivered until next Monday.

Currently, only one earphone works, but that's enough for me to get by listening to podcasts until my new ones arrive. In the meantime, they seem to be sending random commands to the phone while I'm listening, so every 10-20 seconds I'll hear Siri pop up, or the track will skip, or it'll start rewinding, or the volume will randomly drop to zero or whatever. The only solution is to keep the whole thing perfectly still (I think the problem is a loose wire or something idk), or listen on speaker, neither of which are possible while I'm walking, running, or in any of the situations I use the earphones.

Anyway, I'd appreciate some tweak which could toggle an ignore switch for the earphones, so the phone ignores any input it gets from the controller while the switch is active, just as a temporary solution until my new earphones arrive. I'm sure someone somewhere could also make use of the tweak. I'd imagine this is something someone could whip up fairly easily for a month of gold?

tl;dr I need a toggle which, when switched on, will make my phone ignore all commands from the wireless headset (eg skip forward/backward, volume up/down, pause, invoke siri etc). Month of GOLD if you make it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something everybody thinks is fact but is actually wrong? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 19:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What five words will get you the most downvotes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 18:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could restore one removed feature of any product, what would you restore? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 16:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Companies remove features of products (I suppose I mostly mean software, but surprise me) that are no longer profitable or legal or for many reasons. If you could get one sorely-missed feature back, what would you want? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dear Abby </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 13:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gravity Visualised </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 12:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I believe I can fly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 19:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PsBattle: Breakdancing Bug </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 19:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Breakdancing Bug </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 19:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most irritating thing someone has done while sat next to you on a plane? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 17:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the funniest headline you've ever seen published? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 20:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I believe I can fly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 20:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your "Armchair Scientist" theory that you'd love to test if only you had the resources? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 22:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most irritating thing someone has done while sat next to you on a plane? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 15:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Traffic in Cities Skylines </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 21:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alexa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 21:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you massively over-complicate what should be a simple task? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 01:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I know it's old, but the ERB rap battle between Steve Jobs and Bill Gates is one of my all-time favourite videos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 01:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I found this sign in the toilets at uni </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 00:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I configure Desktop Chrome to remember that I speak British English? It keeps switching back to AmE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 00:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sign into my chrome account on the Windows 7 computers at Uni most days. The Uni computers are set up to delete anything not stored in our personal folder every night, including application data. Luckily, Chrome syncs all of my data from the cloud, so when I sign in it's just like I left it yesterday. Except when I start typing things, and it tells me I've spelled "utilise" or "colonise" or "rumour" wrong, when I'm using the correct spelling for my area. Every goddamn day I have to change the setting to British (correc[t](https://i.imgur.com/kn488mY.jpg)) English, and it forgets it by the next day. Does anyone else have this issue? Is there a fix? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happiest sock ever! [r/mildlyinteresting] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 23:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HMF a video with an Irish guy who sounds stoned and talks about celebrities </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 03:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He sits in a chair in a darkened room and talks about Russell Brand for example, and says "fair fucks to the man, he's rolling in it [money]". He says how he doesn't really enjoy RB's work, but appreciates his success. He also says similar things about other celebs. There's a lot of post-prod work and sections resembling /r/montageparodies. I think he's got a youtube channel with various satirical/humorous videos, but I can't for the life of me find him. Anyone recognise my vague description? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I created a subreddit, /r/TestFlight, where you can recruit beta testers for iOS apps, or apply to be a beta tester for an iOS developer. I think it could be awesome if more people were involved. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 01:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Tester] [iPhone 6] [iPad 4th Gen] Available in UK to beta test most apps. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 20:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pm me for my details </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I created a subreddit, /r/TestFlight, where you can recruit beta testers for iOS apps, or apply to be a beta tester for a developer. I think it could be awesome if more people were involved. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 16:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tinder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 14:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Catapult </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 14:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit's robots.txt has a nice little surprise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 12:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All of her stuff is great </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 00:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Love </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 21:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reduce minimum distance for geofence? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 16:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the location-based reminders, but for weird reasons I won't explain 100m gives false positives for "arriving at home". Is it possible to reduce this distance beyond the minimum 100m? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Basketball </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 12:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Close-up slow-motion welding </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 19:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How can I simulate windows 8 gestures (swipes, taps, double taps etc) using VB? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 02:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to be able to say "simulate a swipe from (x1,y1) to (x2,y2)" or "simulate a double tap at (x,y)"

I think the tapping should be easy - you can move the cursor and force a click, and a tap is generally the same as a click. But More importantly I need the swipes. Can anyone point me to the right API?

I'd prefer a solution which also works on Windows 7, but 8+ only solutions are ok.

Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What have you pretended to like/enjoy in an effort to look cool? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 01:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ugly Man With Huge Penis Unsure How To Get The Word Out | The Onion [satire] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 19:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could get a software update for your brain, what would you patch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 15:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What original joke are you most proud of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 14:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could get a software update for your brain, what would you patch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 17:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could get a software update for your brain, what would you patch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 14:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You get one free crime with a guarantee of no consequences. What do you do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 20:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This could be interesting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What inevitability are you dreading? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 22:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What should be against the law, but shockingly isn't? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 19:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What have you pretended to like/enjoy in an effort to look cool? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 18:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your nsfw guilty pleasure? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 17:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything you wouldn't tell your grandma/boss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Counting by Fibonacci numbers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 14:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Count by Fibonacci numbers.

If you don't know what Fibonacci numbers are, they're the numbers which appear in the Fibonacci sequence, which is a sequence of numbers that come up in nature quite a lot. The first and second numbers are both 1; the rest are defines as the sum of the previous two numbers in the sequence. The third number is 2, because 1+1 = 2; the fourth number is 3, because 2 (the third number) + 1 (the second number) = 3.

In mathematical terms:

    fib(1) = 1
    fib(2) = 1
    fib(n) = fib(n-1) + fib(n-2) for n2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PsBattle: dog jumping in the air </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 01:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [request] If a timer is running, show remaining time on clock.app icon instead of current time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 22:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would be convenient. I use a lot of timers, and have to either lock the screen or open the app to see the remaining time (first world problems right?) Would be nice if it were somewhere more visible while my phone is unlocked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't see this guy often enough </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 23:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It is settled, I'm naming my first born "elitist taint biscuit" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 18:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stunt jump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 01:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
