<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2577</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you know what an oxymoron is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mum was fed up of buying 'expensive' party poppers for new years so one year she bought some really cheap and dangerous looking ones from chinatown.

She wanted me to test one but I didn't want to use them as they looked dangerous, so she had a massive go at me and so I did. It exploded it my hand and gave me 3rd degree burns on the hand (fingers) that was holding it. Still have the scars now and that was a good 15 years ago.

She made me take a week off of school so people wouldn't find out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mum does this but with wrapping paper that I wrap her presents in.

She buys really cheap and crap paper when she gives the family gifts and I buy decent one so she saves it and uses it for other gifts (for her friends. My parents aren't even poor.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly have tried but deep down I know that either I'm hiding an attraction to them or that they are for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had an old boss that used to make us have lunch with him everyday. Dude we need a break away from you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When a child that isn't yours is massively misbehaving and you tell them off, so that they stop.

9/10 the parent get's annoyed mostly because it implies that they can't control their child. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When a woman says that she's an independent woman. Honestly I just hear narcissistic bitch.

You're suppose to be independent when you're an adult, it's not an achievement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Netflix, killed Blockbusters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think ice breakers work or is it better just to say high my name is 'x', you look like you are worth talking to?

Works every time :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 16:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surely it was worse to have a drink with him in the 80s, at least now he won't try anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 16:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Elite four. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 12:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not gonna lie I did read that as noice too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 01:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't feel at all bad for not remembering whether of not you dream of her. It is by no means any sort of reflection of how much you loved your wife

What would you like to talk about? Anything we can help with? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 00:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing; as always. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 16:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> London defo has a few level 40 players. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 15:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talk to the hand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 15:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With all the magic in Game of Thrones how did no-one detect Jon Snow's really parentage :s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 12:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also helps against trenchfoot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 04:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know I never thought about shaving my feet until I starting doing karate (at uni) and a guy said to me 'wow you have hairy feet', I just assumed that was normal until I looked over and saw that everyone else had shaved theirs.

I shaved them a few days later and my housemate said to me wow your feet are looking super clean; she hadn't realised I shaved them so I guess they must have looked super dirty before :O

They do look nice tbf but I wish someone (esp my family) would have mentioned it sooner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 04:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just all Mediterraneans really (speaking as one). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 04:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always feel sorry for men that haven't mastered the art of stopping a boner from happening. You have to focus but once you've mastered it, it's actually pretty easy to do, you can feel and control the blood flow to stop it happening.

Obviously v helpful in your teens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 04:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would you make up such a stat :S, for most of a female's life they are slower.
  
   As men age, the speed of their urine stream declines. In fact, men urinate faster than women up until around the age of 50, and then women urinate faster.

Loads of sources back that up.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 04:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surely every man has grown up living with a women :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 04:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fat men get that too don't they :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 04:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why I have a fake e-mail with all fake details on it.

My real e-mail is solely for e-mailing friends and family and VERY rarely someone from work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 04:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I turned up for an interview and they asked me why I was 30 minutes late.

I got the interview through an agency (Adecco) and they told me 1345 (in person   e-mail) but it was actually at 1300. I thought I was turning up 15 mins early at 1330.

I was actually at Adecco's office before hand, just to practice the interview questions (technical stuff) and I left there at 1315 as it was a 15 minute walk away. So it was utter bs that they thought my interview was at 1345.

I told them my agency got it wrong but that I did apologise and assured them I'm very punctual.
I did the rest of the interview and tbh I nailed the questions and they said I had the job and would call me later with the proper offer.

When they did call they said that they spoke to Adecco and that they said that I was lying. I did not get the job offer.

I called Adecco and the stupid women just shouted at me that I was wrong, despite me having an email showing I was right. Still angry now, was a great job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 03:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All about those gains. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 03:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the amount of injunctions we have that mean you can go to gaol if you publish the actual truth but the celebrity has a legal injunction which means you can't discuss it on a public forum. Even saying 'x' has an injunction can get you into trouble. It's ridiculous.

And powerhouses like google are in on it and make sure that zero results come back if you type 'x' super injunction.

Imagine if Obama slept with Trump's wife but you could go to gaol if you mentioned it online because Obama has an injunction about the story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 01:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Priests jokes, how retro :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 01:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You wang clan aint nutin' to fuck wit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 01:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's from when Pegg is pretending to be 'yarp' and wants to say no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 01:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not all heroes wear capes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 01:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah Kristin Kreuk, my childhood crush and she's only 33!

Still enough time to marry her :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 01:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eastern European? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 21:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just gave you your 1,000th vote, 10% of the way to 1 million. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 21:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On Sunny beach Bulgaria it's bizzare. It goes normal family beach, nudist section (not closed off at all, then continues to be a normal family beach after that. Apparently the rope on the beach floor signifies nudist section but it was really weird to see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 21:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should put this in the jokes subreddit.
Jokers that wear bright neon clothing....
you can run but you can't hide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 21:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The amount of times I've posted a breaking news story on here and then someone posts it 30 minutes later and that trends is just unbelievable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 21:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Current theory is that you can only move between time machines so if you invent one right now you can't go back from 16/10/2016 but you can go forward as much as you like (and return), providing the machine still exists in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 20:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sidenote for Americans: When Brits say 'alright' they're not actually asking you if anything is wrong, it's the same as saying how's your day; they're not actually expecting a proper answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 20:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Spaniard I make the odd mistake now and again when I'm writing in English but it is bizarre when I'll post a serious comment and someone will just insult me because of my spelling and not actually reply properly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 20:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> came in for this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 01:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always find it weird that when you ask an honest question on here you get downvoted :/

It doesn't look at all like a snes controller though. Did Xbox copy their design from someone else? I can't imagine Nintendo would have 'invented' this controller without the Xbox one existing, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 01:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow was not expecting so much downvoting, was just pointing out what are the odds of two abortion threads being both on the front page and next to each other. People get angry about to smallest things on here :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 20:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I genuinely hadn't seen a wi u controller before. How are they legally allowed to blatantly rip off the Xbox :O? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 20:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ramsay is Scottish though :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 18:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Used to be fun smuggling them in for my American friends :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 19:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Waiting for the missus to get ready. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 19:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wear fairy wings for mine, it's amazing how many people want to talk to you when you're wearing wings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 22:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be more concerned if you didn't recognise your house on a map :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 00:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 8Y8Y

Currently on 4/7 looking for 3 kind souls :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 18:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude you could move to Europe our drinking age is 5!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 14:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long before he mentions dickbutt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 11:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why has it taken you guys so long to do this, we've been doing this for decades :O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Less than one euro to the pound at many UK airports </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 16:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 15:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously Time Man of the year Adolf Hitler :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 15:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bet the money has come in handy now that he's retired. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 14:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reservoir dogging: How one man's trip to his local reservoir changes his life forever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 14:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whiplashing: The story of how a car collision changed one man's life forever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 14:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Schindler's listing: One man's quest to get his restaurant listed in the Michelin guide to Berlin but with critics on their way, he makes a shocking discovery about his oven. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 14:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> John Wicking: After losing everything; John embarks on an epic quest to make the perfect candle to make up for losing his old flame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 01:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like that you thought we needed linguine explained to us :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 22:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speaking as a Spaniard it has to be bullfighting. I honestly haven't met a Spaniard who was anti bullfighting (usually it's just foreigners that are). It's bizarre that people don't see it as animal torture/cruelty. You are literally stabbing an animal slowly to death.

The defenders always so but it's part of our culture. So was slavery and child labour but we got rid of that. Not all things about our culture should be kept.

Honestly you wouldn't believe how often I argue with people over this. We even have a bullfighting channel (in hd no less) so you can watch animals being stabbed to death over breakfast :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 22:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Britain the papers do a 16 countdown (age of consent here/when you can publish their breasts). It's absolutely disgusting but widely accepted. One paper has daily pics :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 15:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone people want to be president, some are happy to just take photos of themself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 15:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You only have to watch friends to see what the attitude to being gay was a decade ago. Still quite shocking in all honesty.

Imagine trying to make Ace Ventura today with the transgender mockery scene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 03:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the only video of a dick hitting a bitch in the face that I've watched today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 03:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Barack Obama enjoying the great outdoors. ](https://i.imgur.com/oXshaxA.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 08:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lovely picture.

I'm also amazed this has got to the /all front page but only has 13 comments :X

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 07:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bottled water is only the norm in America.

Us Europeans are quite happy to drink tap water :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 07:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where I live condoms cost $2 each; lets be conservative and say I go through 200 a year. In the last decade alone that would cost me $4,000.

Abortions however are free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 07:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got one when I lived in China and obviously they don't have any health and safety regulations. It was like getting tasered :X </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 07:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like this should be a title for the guys at writing prompts to work on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 07:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He didn't tell it right. Took far too long to get to the punchline. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 07:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the end of each month I used to have $2,500 surplus, which obviously didn't make me rich but it meant I didn't have money issues. I traveled a fair bit/took decent holidays and socialised a lot with various groups of friends and life was good. I had zero complaints.

Then it all came crashing down with I lost my great job (company folded) and haven't found a replacement job yet (despite searching like a maniac). I haven't been out in 3 months because I'm too poor and at present I -$200 in the bank. It is fucking depressing being poor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 03:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quite frankly this sucks as I've been using my Chansey with it's CP in the 400s to demolish pokemon with CPS in the 8/900s so as to get 1,000 each time, often I can take down two in a row.

Levelling a gym from 1-10 doesn't take that long with Chansey.

With this update there's no way I could gain 2,000 with one pokemon, so now I'm wasting more potions/revive and battling is going to take much much longer :(

I would be happy however if you had the option to disable level adjusting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 23:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For my group two of the guys get constant calls from their gfs so I doubt they'd want to play :D

The rest of us wouldn't get a call as the wives/gfs know not to call unless its an emergency. Then I'd be in too much of a rush home to stay and pay :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 20:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having missed out the last two festivals I was already anxious sitting in the queue. But thankfully I managed to get tickets this year.

I selected London tickets but they sold out when I went to pay so I selected the nearest available city, which was Bath and they had tickets for Thursday. Managed to get them.

Can't describe how happy I am, Glastonbury is my happy place :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 10:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 1,000 yard stare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 23:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had no idea places opened on thanksgiving. That be like opening on Christmas for the rest of us :X </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 17:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had that happen to me once and I can still vividly remember the feeling of my bones suddenly feeling like they weighed a ton.

I only wanted to get a glass of water from the coffee table next to the sofa. It took all of my strength and me mentally saying 'your bones don't really weigh a ton you are just tripping balls, FOCUS!' to be able to move one arm from my lap to the arm rest. I gave up after that as I realised there was no way I was going to be able to hold and lift a glass of water up to my mouth :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 04:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys have to pay 6k to have a baby, WOW!

Come to Europe, it's free here.

Avoid the UK though, not a fan of immigrants atm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 00:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having never seen the original video before this is the only version that I will ever know and I love it!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 19:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw it for the first time this year and thought it had aged terribly. I wish I could have seen it at the time. But I didn't find it intense at all, especially after modern films. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 18:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should be called the death of batman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 11:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, that they should have asked here;
I don't like chocolate, neither does my close friend and also my cousin.

They could have had 3 people within a minute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else think of Afroman - Because I got high, when the closing credit music plays? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 01:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Colombians votes 50.2% 'no' to a peace deal with Farc rebels. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 01:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 01:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They amount of women I've dated that have spent well beyond their means by it's ok because daddy is picking up the cheque.

You are not strong, independent women if you still rely on your parents financially because you can't live within your on income.

Grow up and stand on your own two feet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 00:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I present facts, with a colour coded map and yet there's always someone who says no that's wrong. I don't think you understand what a fact is :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 00:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is what I am. It's amazing that I got downvoted because I'm both white and hispanic. This place sometimes :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 22:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Went to see the game, didn't hear or see any Americans in the crowd at all. Was quite bizarre as 99% of the crowd didn't know any of the rules and people kept asking me whats going on :D :D :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 15:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is she still relevant :S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 04:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deathman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 20:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THANK YOU :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 03:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Soviet Russia computer cleans you.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Disney announces live action film remake of The Lion King: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 01:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 14:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When your friend breaks up with his gf she becomes dead to you too. No exceptions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 14:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Made the mistaking of trying to help a close friend with a new department in his company (for free) and after putting in over three hundred hours in 3 months (along with me having a full time job) he actually had the audacity to criticise me for not getting enough done. When I questioned how much he'd done, his contribution amounted to around 12 hours work in the whole month. I later had a private look at his computer and he basically spents the day watching youtube videos.

We also interviewed a few people and it was obvious to me who the best candidates were. He however chose 3 'hot' women, who quiet frankly were very under-qualified and interviewed poorly. One he solely chose because 'she had big breasts'. He slept with all of them too!

I quit before they started and the department closed not long after as he is obviously a lazy mofo and the staff were useless.

About a month later he asked if I wanted to create a startup with him :D :D :D
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 14:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had many a book and film ruined because you know there's a twist but the idiots that mention it never seem to think they've ruined the experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 17:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My car has a half horn feature, it that not normal :O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 17:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting that he chose God save the queen for his song of choice; the same queen's whose laws would later force him to become chemically castrated for being homosexual.

It's ok though as she pardoned him in 2013 :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 03:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $12-15 for a cinema ticket in Britain? Where

It's minimum $15 in most places. My local ones are $26. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 22:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When not just type define:word and it will give you both an explanation and an example :S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 22:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I figured out the perfect game technique very early on and tbh it ruined wii bowling for me :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 19:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It mostly because all questions that needed answering have been answered, we mostly just come for the map updates now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
