<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1195</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 05:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd make it rain donuts everywhere around the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 05:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bronn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 05:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently the latest report is that she's in intensive care.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 01:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's great news - I hope that the recovery process goes well for her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 23:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not seeing anything else on Twitter besides what we already know: that she's in critical condition. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 23:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not seeing any further updates on Twitter at the moment from major news sources besides the fact that she's in critical condition. I'm really hoping that she pulls through.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 23:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any updates, guys? I'm saying a little prayer right now for her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 22:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nooooooooo. 2016, let her be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 22:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't you dare, 2016. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 18:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's hoping that it comes out this weekend! *Crosses fingers* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 03:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite gag was Rhea physically moving the camera when it was about to focus on a particularly racially insensitive aspect. 

Looking forward to the finale next week! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 02:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really sucks that he's no longer showrunner of Star Trek: Discovery, though. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 02:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty awesome how Mads Mikkelsen has now been in three massive film franchise films (Casino Royale, Doctor Strange, and Rogue One), and he's been terrific in all of them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 00:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIP your karma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 23:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a big guy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 23:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's nice to see. I'm hoping it has a solid drop this weekend (even though it won't have the amazing second weekend The Force Awakens had, of course).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 18:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it did have a built-in fanbase already with the fans of the video game series.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 15:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank fucking God. It would be bizarre if it wasn't, considering the tone and content of the original film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 06:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Creep - Radiohead  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 05:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's some Oscar-caliber acting right there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 01:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obi-Wan Kenobi (with Ewan McGregor starring, of course).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 18:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, this looks terrific. Looks like they nailed recreating the tone and atmosphere of the original film. Ryan Gosling, Harrison Ford, and  Denis Villeneuve are all involved with a sequel to one of my all-time favorite movies? I'm fucking sold.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 16:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Terrific weekend for Rogue One - I think it will have excellent legs as well. It's a real crowd pleaser. 

I'm not surprised by Collateral Beauty bombing. Reviews were terrible, and it looked very unappealing.

I'm still hoping that Arrival ekes it to $100 million+ - maybe it will get a re-release with some Oscar nominations next month? That should boost its gross.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 16:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am so fucking excited for this trailer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 16:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Disney immediately greenlights Rogue One Two: The Search for More Money* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 19:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Superb number for Rogue One. It will be pretty fascinating to see what kind of second weekend drop it has.

Moana held quite well in the face of the huge competition from Rogue One.

Excellent expansion for La La Land as well. I'm hoping it does really well in wide release next weekend. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 17:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Terrific number for Rogue One - I'm glad to see audiences are really digging it. 

Pathetic for Collateral Beauty. I'm not surprised, though - it received terrible reviews, and it looked very unappealing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 02:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was awesome! Vader had one of his best moments as well. I can't wait to see it again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 18:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very good number - I'm in the theater now waiting for this movie to start. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 18:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Impressive number for Star. I hear it's pretty bad, though, so I expect its ratings to fall quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 16:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This movie has a fantastic cast - that's for sure: Tom Hardy, Kenneth Branagh, and Cillian Murphy!

The cinematography looks to be superb. It is a Nolan movie after all. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 07:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be sure to join us at /r/crazyexgirlfriend for weekly episode discussions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 07:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, it is unfortunately the lowest-rated show on broadcast network television (for the second year in a row). I'm hoping that due to The CW/Netflix deal, the huge critical acclaim, the many nominations and awards it receives, and how generous and chill The CW generally is that they renew it for a third season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 07:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> C-R-A-Z-Y!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 04:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Margaery Tyrell disrobes in front of Renly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 18:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The novelty of The Voice has really worn off. I wouldn't be surprised if it starts getting consistently below a 2.0 soon. 

Nice to see Timeless stay steady. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 21:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's great in Sound of My Voice as well (which she also was a co-writer on).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 18:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It had a terrific drop this weekend indeed. I'm hoping that with the Golden Globe nominations it received today (along with possible Oscar nominations next month), it will gross $100 million+ domestically.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 20:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It had yet another superb drop this weekend indeed. It's really developed some great legs - if it gets some major Golden Globe nominations when they're announced tomorrow (exciting!), it could even get to $100 million+. Here's hoping!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 20:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't wait to see this movie. The brief snippets of songs from the trailers sound terrific (I love musicals), it looks beautiful, and Emma Stone and Ryan Gosling are both awesome. I seriously doubt it will be in the Harrisburg, PA area by next weekend (where I live), but I'm crossing my fingers it's here by Christmas weekend at least.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 19:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good drops for both Moana and Arrival (yay!). 

Solid number for Office Christmas Party, especially considering the not-great reviews.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 04:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, his transition has been quite the massive clusterfuck so far. If his tweeting recently indicates anything, we're going to be in for a rough 4 years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 03:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://tvtropes.org/pmwiki/pmwiki.php/Main/GettingCrapPastTheRadar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 18:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks terrific. Does Fox plan on making more of these movies after this one, or is this supposed to be the conclusion of the series? I'm hoping for the former personally.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 09:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goddamn, this looks terrific. I'm psyched.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 05:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was great as Renee Walker (Agent Hotness) on 24, so I look forward to seeing her on this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 04:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Renee Walker from 24! (affectionately known to many fans of the show as Agent Hotness).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 22:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IT'S A LION! IT'S HUGE!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 21:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The greatest! They're going to do things you won't believe!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 21:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's very true - a 2.3 18-49 rating is still impressive in this day and age for a show on a major broadcast network. That's a better rating than every drama and broadcast television currently airing, outside of The Big Bang Theory, This Is Us, Empire, and Modern Family. 

Even though this is a ratings low for a NBC musical, I sort of doubt that NBC expected this to outperform The Sound of Music or The Wiz. Both of those shows had garnered decades of goodwill from generations of audiences, while the Hairspray Broadway musical has only been around since 2002.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Solid number for Hairspray Live - I heard it was quite good. Too bad about Designated Survivor reaching a series low.

Oh, Empire - how the mighty have fallen. It's pretty amusing how close the trajectory of the show has mirrored Glee's rise and fall - it had a great, widely-buzzed about first season that was breaking records, followed by declining ratings after the buzz wore off during the second season and the quality went way down. I honestly wouldn't be surprised if it falls below a 2.0 at some point this season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be sure to join us at /r/samanthabee for weekly episode discussions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 00:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When it's been breaking ratings records this season? Lol, nope. Keep dreaming, Trump.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 23:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! His show has been on fire ever since Trump was elected. His monologues and other studio bits have often been pretty great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 23:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them was still a blast, IMO, even with his appearance. It was much darker than I anticipated as well. That death penalty scene...god damn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 16:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's going to get cancelled when it's been getting record ratings this season? Lol, no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 04:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AIDA NOOOOOOOO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 23:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plus, Dean killed Hitler. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 16:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is definitely one of the best Fringe episodes. Peter Weller gives a terrific performance in it as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 14:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wrote the musical score for Rogue One as well - that's pretty exciting! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 06:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The writers attached to this film have actually written some good movies in the past (Iron Man, Black Hawk Down). It would be interesting if the fifth film of thIs franchise actually received a Fresh score on Rotten Tomatoes (much like Fast Five finally did with The Fast and Furious franchise). And, hey, both franchises both star Tyrese Gibson (he's back for this one as well)! Maybe that's a good omen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 05:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That logo at the end is fucking sweet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 04:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a TV show, buddy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 04:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw Fantastic Beasts yesterday. It was really good and a lot better than I thought it was going to be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 18:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Secrets and Lies is definitely not getting another season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 03:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks pretty damn cool! I especially love the shot of Tom Cruise rolling around in the bus - the action elements look badass.

The cast is great, too! Consider me sold.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 03:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks pretty damn cool. I especially love the shot of Tom Cruise rolling through the air in the bus. 

I'm excited! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 03:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Terrific holds for Moana and Arrival - I'm really happy to see the latter have the best drop of the holdovers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 01:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tweeted several SNL writers/actors about my pitch. Maybe I'll hear back? That would be pretty sweet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 01:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did tweet Colin Jost (who's one of the head writers there), Vanessa Bayer, and the official SNL Twitter account about my idea. Maybe I'll hear back! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 20:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent news - having more Claire Temple and Misty Knight in my life is always a good thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 20:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's hoping they do a cold open soon with Alec Baldwin as Trump watching a Trump impersonation on SNL. This is followed by Baldwin's Trump addressing Trump to the screen a la House of Cards.

Trump would go fucking ballistic, and it would be GLORIOUS.

Do it, SNL. Make America proud.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 20:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's hoping they do a cold open soon with Alec Baldwin as Trump watching a Trump impersonation on SNL. This is followed by Baldwin's Trump addressing Trump to the screen a la House of Cards.

Trump would go fucking ballistic, and it would be GLORIOUS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 19:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a very shitty week, this has been a piece of very uplifting news.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 00:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, man, that bit with Drax at the end is fucking gold. It's going to play like gangbusters in theaters as well (presumably in front of Rogue One).

I'm so happy that we get two MCU movies next summer. Life is good for movie geeks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 00:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Ring Two  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 21:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great drops for Moana and Arrival.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 20:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Possible season-high for Crazy Ex-Girlfriend? WOO HOO! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 04:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "This is my favorite."

Lol, Trent. So weird.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 21:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a very well-deserved accomplishment - it is definitely my favorite movie of this year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 21:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that's really disappointing news - I was hoping that this would be the best Star Trek series since Deep Space Nine (as a result of Fuller's involvement). Here's hoping that it doesn't suck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 18:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Terrific number for Legends of Tomorrow and a massive increase from the previous episode (thanks to the DC crossover). It will be interesting to see how The Flash/Supergirl musical crossover performs next year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 16:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that the vast majority of Redditors would disagree with you there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 18:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent number for Arrow - the big numbers for the DC crossover continues! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 17:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I accept your apology." 

He was fucking scary as hell in that scene - I really would love if he received an Oscar nomination. God knows that he's overdue for one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 19:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be sure to join us at /r/TelevisionRatings for more analysis and discussion of TV ratings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 19:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A 1.5 for The Flash is absolutely huge for The CW. That's better than the vast majority of dramas on the major broadcast networks these days. This DC crossover week is really paying off for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 18:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1.5 for The Flash? That's freaking huge! Congrats on the huge victory, The CW! This crossover week is really paying off for them.

Superb number for This Is Us as usual.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 18:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's amazing news - easily the best entertainment news of the year, IMO. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 18:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a very good number for the Supergirl DC crossover episode - The CW is going to be quite pleased with the performance of their DC shows this week. I imagine that The Flash, Arrow, and Legends of Tomorrow will all get nice boosts. 

It's also extremely impressive how last night was the highest-rated night in five years for The CW. Bravo! They have so many good shows these days. 

Be sure to join us at /r/TelevisionRatings for more analysis and discussion of TV ratings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 18:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very good number for the Supergirl DC crossover episode. The CW is going to be pretty happy with the numbers for their DC shows this week. 

Impressive number for Lucifer - Fox must be pleased that it and Gotham have remained steady.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 01:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, this is the beginning of the end for Quantico.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 21:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the 3-day weekend, it only dropped 7% from last weekend (which is terrific). It's going to do a minimum of $80 million or so domestically, and it could even do $100 million+ if it gets some award nominations (which looks likely). People are really digging it. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 21:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you excited to see Evangeline Lilly as The Wasp in the Ant-Man sequel?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 01:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very true - at minimum it will top out at $80 million or so. But it could very well gross $100 million+ (especially if it picks up some Golden Globe/Oscar nominations, which is likely).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 21:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ant-Man is surprisingly really good - you should definitely check it out. Even my mother who normally doesn't care for superhero films at all enjoyed it (probably because it's very unconventional and more of a heist film/comedy with some superhero elements).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 21:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I loved Ant-Man. I personally think it's by far the funniest of the MCU films, and I enjoyed how it was a heist film with superhero movie trappings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 20:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arrival also made $13.5 million over the 5-day weekend, raising its total to $62.4 million. For the 3-day weekend, it only had a 7% drop from last weekend (which is terrific). 

Almost Christmas also rose 5% and Hacksaw Ridge only dropped 18% from last weekend. Both had great holds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 21:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Superb number for Moana - it should likely have terrific legs as well. 

Fantastic Beasts continues to do very well, too.

Nice to see Arrival have a big increase on Friday - I plan on seeing it for a second time tomorrow. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 21:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Friday estimates per Box Office Mojo (as posted by Dr. Lecter on World of KJ): 

1. Moana - $21,826,000 (+120.4%) - $47,411,000

2. Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them - $18,550,000 (+92.3%) - $129,678,123

3. Doctor Strange - $5,435,000 (+116.5%) - $197,159,475

4. Allied - $4,940,000 (+112.7%) - $9,962,000

5. Arrival - $4,515,000 (+102.5%) - $55,652,300

6. Trolls - $4,200,000 (+240.1%) - $128,996,662

7. Almost Christmas - $2,310,000 (+110%) - $31,388,865

8. Bad Santa 2 - $2,295,000 (+68.8%) - $5,219,533

9. Hacksaw Ridge - $2,240,000 (+94.8%) - $49,038,382

10. The Edge of Seventeen - $1,140,000 (+115.1%) - $8,453,770

11. Loving - $613,000 (+202%) - $2,985,771

12. Rules Don't Apply - $600,000 (+110%) - $1,200,000

And just for lulz:

Billy Lynn's Long Halftime Walk - $80,000 (+27%) - $1,463,724 (its Friday PTA is $68 and it is down 77.3% week-to-week)

http://www.boxofficemojo.com/daily/chart/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 18:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2016 is a cruel bitch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 06:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boobs are amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 05:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hannibal  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 05:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Staying at home on a Friday all day (and having off of work).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 21:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Terrific number for Moana - looks like another likely $300 million+ grosser for Disney.

Very good number for Fantastic Beasts as well.

I hope that Arrival and Hacksaw Ridge have big increases this weekend, since there will be a huge number of people in the mood to see some acclaimed films.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 01:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that's how you do a fucking great poster.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 21:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You only use 10% of your brain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 21:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Patrick Stewart is fucking amazing in this film.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 03:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe Liam Neeson will finally get an Oscar for this film? Here's hoping.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 01:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be sure to join us at /r/TheGoodPlace for weekly episode discussions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 00:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Big Short was terrific, so McKay could definitely do a great job with this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 02:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, my little cousin who loves these movies is going to be traumatized by this.

Get ready to grow up FAST, kid! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 02:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck! Here's hoping that isn't true. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 23:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that Arrival will do very well over Thanksgiving weekend. I wouldn't be surprised if it barely drops (or even increases) from this past weekend. Since it's a holiday weekend, lots of people will want to see why it's so critically acclaimed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 18:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope that Yeezy gets some psychiatric help after this. I personally think that his music is often brilliant (My Beautiful Dark Twisted Fantasy is a terrific album), but he's clearly deeply troubled.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 04:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HODOR!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 04:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Biden memes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 20:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arrival and Hacksaw Ridge (which had by far the best drop of the major release holdovers at 37%) should both do very well over Thanksgiving weekend, I think. 

I think that Fantastic Beasts will perform fine in the long run. A final domestic cume of at least $210-215 million is assured.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 23:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this point, I would say - hell, yes. The performances and cinematography are wonderful as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 20:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best episode yet! This easily gets an A. This is incredible television, and it's the most well-produced horror show since Hannibal.

I would so love if this received a second season. If not, at least we got a terrific single season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 20:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Easily the dumbest boycott I've ever heard of. Hamilton is completely sold out until like next November, you dumb fucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 19:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This show has been really incredible television - easily the best and most well-produced horror show since Hannibal. It's a damn shame more people aren't watching - this will likely be its only season. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 19:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did anyone else notice that "assassination" was misspelled on the news broadcast? Whoops, lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 19:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad to see The Exorcist rise a bit - it's such a good show. Shame this will probably be its only season - it's the best horror show on network television since Hannibal.

Crazy Ex-Girlfriend is staying steady as well. Nice! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 18:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any political figure that actually believes in gay conversion therapy and then attends a Broadway show (the Mecca of tolerance and gay culture) deserves to be booed.

Fuck Pence and his intolerance. I hope that he gets booed at every public appearance for the rest of Trump's presidency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 18:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any political figure that actually believes in gay conversion therapy and then attends a Broadway show (the Mecca of tolerance and gay culture) deserves to be booed.

Fuck Pence and his intolerance. I hope that he gets booed at every public appearance for the rest of Trump's presidency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 18:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it has a terrible title, very mixed reviews, and the whole concept of it just doesn't seem very appealing to most mainstream audiences, I think. Its box office failure reminds me (and the folks at World of KJ) a whole lot of The Walk last year, which also arrived in theaters DOA.

Oh, Sony, you and your baffling green-lighting decisions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 17:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very solid number for Fantastic Beasts - I think it will have good legs, especially with the Thanksgiving holiday weekend right around the corner. I know that it's a lower opening than many expected, but it's still going to do very well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 16:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 05:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Midnight screening of The Rocky Horror Picture Show  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 05:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's pretty fucking awesome. Bravo!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 16:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a very good number - I'm seeing a $70-75 million weekend (at the very least) based off of that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 17:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deathly Hallows Part 1 is actually my favorite Harry Potter film as well (along with Prisoner of Azkaban). I've seen this opinion reflected quite a bit elsewhere, including among readers of BirthMoviesDeath. I guess that might be a minority opinion among Potter fans, but I think that it's a beautiful and haunting film.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 18:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This Is Us continues to do amazing - once again beating The Voice. Wowzers. 

Glad to see The Flash do very well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 18:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like that theory - post-election fatigue/depression probably contributed to a big weekend box office total this past weekend as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 03:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loved the Jon Stewart cameo at the end! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 23:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank fucking God.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 06:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. I'd also argue that his name is less tarnished now - The Visit was a huge hit and pretty well-liked overall.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 23:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This series was awesome - here's hoping that they do it justice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 18:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YUUUUGE number for 60 Minutes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 18:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Arrival has a great chance of having a good second weekend drop, since it's the zeitgeisty film of the moment that everyone's talking about. Gone Girl - another film aimed at adult audiences that opened in the fall - didn't have a great Cinemascore either, but everyone wanted to see what all the fuss was about, so it had very good legs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 18:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Terrific film - beautifully shot, incredibly moving, with an excellent musical score. I can't wait to see it again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 18:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Accountant had a great drop as well. 

Loving did pretty well in its limited release - I hope it performs admirably as it continues to expand (especially with some Oscar nominations, hopefully).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 18:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here! Saw it yesterday - the movie was terrific. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 18:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fixed! Sorry, I was on my iPhone, so it wasn't formatted right. Hope it looks better now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 17:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weekend estimates per Box Office Mojo (as posted by Libs on World of KJ): 

1 1 DOCTOR STRANGE BV $43,032,000 -49.4% 3,882 - $11,085 $153,014,169 2

2 2 TROLLS Fox $35,050,000 -24.8% 4,066 +6 $8,620 $94,014,315 2

3 N ARRIVAL Par. $24,000,000 - 2,317 - $10,358 $24,000,000 1

4 N ALMOST CHRISTMAS Uni. $15,564,000 - 2,376 - $6,551 $15,564,000 1

5 3 HACKSAW RIDGE LGF $10,775,000 -29.1% 2,971 +85 $3,627 $32,264,321 2

6 6 THE ACCOUNTANT WB $4,570,000 -22.2% 2,342 -346 $1,951 $77,725,755 5

7 N SHUT IN EC $3,700,000 - 2,058 - $1,798 $3,700,000 1

8 4 BOO! A MADEA HALLOWEEN LGF $3,550,000 -54.1% 2,104 -130 $1,687 $70,408,079 4

9 7 JACK REACHER: NEVER GO BACK Par. $3,325,000 -39.0% 2,584 -495 $1,287 $54,586,711 4

10 5 INFERNO Sony $3,250,000 -47.3% 2,656 -920 $1,224 $31,582,015 3

11 8 OUIJA: ORIGIN OF EVIL Uni. $1,783,000 -53.9% 1,538 -842 $1,159 $34,293,090 4

12 9 THE GIRL ON THE TRAIN Uni. $1,677,000 -37.7% 1,008 -564 $1,664 $73,380,130 6

13 11 MOONLIGHT A24 $1,360,802 +10.2% 176 +93 $7,732 $4,778,462 4

14 10 MISS PEREGRINE'S HOME FOR PECULIAR CHILDREN Fox $1,245,000 -39.3% 955 -755 $1,304 $85,192,107 7

15 12 KEEPING UP WITH THE JONESES Fox $550,000 -49.6% 510 -554 $1,078 $14,276,578 4

17 15 DEEPWATER HORIZON LG/S $407,000 -45.7% 390 -393 $1,044 $60,597,287 7

16 27 LOVING Focus $532,000 +233.3% 46 +42 $11,565 $740,191 2

21 42 THE EAGLE HUNTRESS SPC $209,002 +297.5% 31 +27 $6,742 $297,446 2

26 N BILLY LYNN'S LONG HALFTIME WALK TriS $120,000 - 2 - $60,000 $120,000 1

29 N ELLE SPC $56,012 - 2 - $28,006 $56,012 1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 17:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an excellent drop for Doctor Strange - a Marvel movie possibly dropping under 50% this weekend? Veterans Day and the movie being damn good is going to give this film some nice legs.

Terrific drop for Trolls - it might be hit hard. H Fantastic Beasts next weekend, though. 

Great opening for Arrival - I had a feeling it would break out. Paramount's marketing has been terrific, and the reviews have been amazing.

Very solid number for Almost Christmas as well  - it will almost make its budget back in one weekend! 

Glad to see Hacksaw Ridge holding very well - I expect it to continue to perform great throughout the holiday season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 22:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like that C Cinemascore was just a prediction - Cinemascore is poling people for their scores tonight. So we should see Arrival's real Cinemascore tomorrow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 21:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **EDIT:** Some on World of KJ are predicting a C Cinemascore for Arrival, though. It looks like it might be one of those movies that the critics adore, but audiences don't - apparently the film gets pretty heady, complicated, and weird. I can't wait to see it, though. Maybe it will pull a The Wolf of Wall Street/Contagion and have decent legs despite a not-great Cinemascore, though. Anything is possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 18:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa, series-low for Grey's Anatomy. It's so bizarre to see it below a 2.0. Post-election depression made it drop, perhaps? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 17:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great number for Arrival. This bodes well for its weekend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 01:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the most rewatchable show ever, IMO. It's such an optimistic and funny show, and it's nice to watch a sitcom where all of the main characters are fundamentally good people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 01:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FATALITY!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 01:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty ashamed to be a Pennsylvanian right now. But at least the county with the city where I work (Dauphin County) went blue!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 04:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Member 'I've got a bad feeling about this'? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 04:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa, uncensored F-word from Mr. Garrison! Damn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 03:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/southpark  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 03:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They sell this in the parallel universe (the Redverse) of Fringe, I'm sure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 03:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the darkest timeline now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 03:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NPR ran a story earlier today about a historian at American University who nailed his prediction of a Trump victory. He said that he received a lot of grief for it. I bet he's feeling mighty vindicated today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 03:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/tulsi  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 16:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God help us all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 07:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who voted for Hillary, what will the concession speech be like for her?

Also, isn't it tradition for the president-elect to ride along with the former president on the way to the inauguration? Man, that's going to be an awkward ride for Obama and Trump.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 06:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to bed now since Trump almost certainly is going to win.

America, I'm very disappointed in all of you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 05:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, shit - things are getting really close in Michigan! Slim chance I know of Hillary winning, but still... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 05:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a fan of Last Week Tonight - man, John Oliver is going to FLIP HIS SHIT on his show this Sunday.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 05:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump's won North Carolina. Fuuuuuuuuck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 04:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So...does Clinton have any shot at getting 270 electoral votes now? Which states would she have to win? I'm not seeing it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 04:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This night fucking sucks. Really, America??? Really - you're electing this guy? This sentient septic tank?

Well, at least late night comedians will have material for years, I guess. *Sighs heavily* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 04:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is now up to a 92% chance of winning the presidency, according to the New York Times. 

Man, the pollsters were so fucking wrong. Whyyyyy, America?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 04:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump now has a 87% chance of winning the presidency according to New York Times. It just keeps getting worse and worse... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 04:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump up to 81% now of becoming President on New York Times. Ugh, this fucking sucks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 04:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worst. Night. Ever. Why, America, why?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 04:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NY Times now predicting 73% chance of a Trump win. Fuck me... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 04:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can do it, Hillary!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 03:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus fuck, this is scary!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 03:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 03:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, this is sooooooo much closer than I thought. Whew... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 03:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still a lot of votes to count in heavily democratic areas in North Carolina. *Crosses fingers*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 03:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is leading in the Electoral College at the moment. Eww.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 03:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dat big Pennsylvania Hillary lead tho :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 02:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NY Times currently predicting 285 electoral votes for Clinton (on their live results forecast).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 02:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NY Times currently predicting 304 electoral votes for Clinton (on their live results forecast).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 02:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> C'mon, Hill-Dawg!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 02:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pennsylvania is starting out blue! Let's hope it stays that way. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 02:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy fuck, Hillary is leading in Texas with almost half the vote in, according to CNN. Imagine if she somehow won? :0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 02:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like there's still a lot of Florida votes to count in Broward County, Miami-Dade County, and Palm Beach County (all of which are heavily favored to Hillary). Don't give up, guys!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 02:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tammy Duckworth won! WOO HOO!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 02:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn it, Florida!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 02:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty amusing to see Texas blue at the moment, even though it's very early.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 02:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's hoping for good results for Hillary in PA (my home state)! *Crosses fingers*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 02:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BTFO Trump - look at all those Hillary wins!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 01:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, snap - Hillary currently ahead in Florida, NC, and Ohio!!! Looking good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 01:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's on CNN right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 01:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, shit, Hillary is winning Florida right now!!!! Awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 01:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Niiiiiiice. Good news for HRC!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 00:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it begins... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 23:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks pretty damn good for Hillary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 22:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! Which town in Cumberland County? I'm from that area.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
