<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3614</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure about it after all this attention. Eather way it would be hard to chose someone since a lot of people were asking about it. I dont know how to make any auctions right now and i am not sure if it would be ethical. And lastly it hs created a wonderful memory for me right now. So there are few moral dilemas right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. I hope I wont let u down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, I myself have started few years ago with oils, they havent worked for me at all, then I moved to acrylics. results were a bit better but i guess that wasnt for me either. Then I moved to watercolors and I sticked to it until now. cant say that everything always goes as planed but it makes me happy, and thats the important part I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 20:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to make things easier here are some links:
instagram: http://instagram.com/continuum_transfunctioner/
facebook: https://www.facebook.com/martin.majercak.1
feel free to contact me or to follow
Etsy will be set up this week, so please be patient. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 19:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I really hope I will get the possibility to see them in real life. Ill have my fingers crossed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 19:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> these are really great! thanks ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 18:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> actually me too :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 17:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you but i am really not used to this kind of attention and such reactions. Its a brand new feeling for me really.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 17:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> everything that is right now on instagram and sashe are originals. also when etsy will be set up there will be only originals. but if there will be demand for prints I dont see any reason why not to do it. and thank you for the compliment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 17:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> glad I could help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 17:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you for such kind words and  also thanks for the patience.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 17:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> right now I work mostly with watercolors and canson paper /so mainly this style and medium/. try the instagram until etsy will be ready. http://instagram.com/continuum_transfunctioner/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 17:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad I could be helpful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 17:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well first of all I use paper that is suitable for watercolors, I use montvall, fabriano and canson papers which are 200g, 250g, 300g,400g. when you use such heavy paper it will prevent any damage or buckeling, also i use masking tape. but before using the tape try it first if it doesnt rip the paper, since this has happend to me few times and it brings tears into eyes when there is piece of paper torn out with the masking tape. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 17:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as I mentioned give me some time please, this all is just too much for me. to be honest I wasnt able to do anything meaningfull today. but I hope etsy will be set this week, so stay tuned and be patient </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 17:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> makes me happy and proud, thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 15:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No not ink. Its chines white watercolor in tube. I can send you a link for it if i manage to find it somewhere.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 13:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right now Slovakia only. But this week I will log into etsy to ship internationaly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 13:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this case for nothing. I just have a really messy table because i need to have everything at reach. Thats all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 12:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> right now only a slovak website, but as i promised few people here already this week i will set up etsy to ship internationaly. so be patient please and stay tuned. I never thought of such positive reactions so never really thought of doing etsy n stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 12:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad i could help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 12:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 11:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of the woods, wtercolor, 2016, 35x50cm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 11:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qsiWszjkPcM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 11:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> by painting in separate washes, to get the foggy feeling you paint wet on wet, to get more details and avoid mixing colors you have to paint wet on dry. but make sure you use the same hues /my opinion/ and the brushes isnt as moist as in the wet on wet stage, more dry, less water, more pigment. hope it helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 11:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> glad to do that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 10:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Z </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 10:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 10:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After all these reactions I am not sure right now.Not because i would like to get as much money as possible, but because it has created a wonderful memory and has created this amazing feeling i never felt i guess. But I Will create etsy this week with my works, since there are a lot of them everywhere in my flat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 10:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> never thought of anything like this. This positive reactions and overwhelming comments are new to me. like new new. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 10:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I myself need a little teaching </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 10:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.instagram.com/continuum_transfunctioner/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 10:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is too kind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 10:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> will do it this week </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 10:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hopefully one day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 10:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please wait until I make and etsy account, I never ever thought of such a positive reaction so never really thought of selling international. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 10:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i do : https://www.instagram.com/continuum_transfunctioner/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 10:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> During the first wash where sky and background were created I did some brush strokes in the foreground with just water and bit of pigment. Then during second and third wash I just put paint on the spaces were paint already was. So there were this spaces that were left in the end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 10:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there are many chinese whites in tubes that can be used for this, i use Winsor Newton Cotman, but i know that also Daniel Smith makes these. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
