<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1565</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 14:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hungry Hungry Hippo. I would love to see Trump's hair after an intense battle against China and Russia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 13:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are an asshole. I'll bet that's you in the video trying to incite a reaction from the cops just so you can have it on camera and then point the finger in anger. What reason was there for the guy (you?) in this video to do what he's doing other than to try and capture a "gotcha moment" against the cops. A shameful and pathetic way to live your life, and it speaks more about the type of person the guy in the video (you?) is, than it does about the cop who has to deal with assholes like that all day every day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 23:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I have read, using a persons breath is not effective. The test must be done using saliva. There are one or two companies in Europe currently pioneering a roadside, saliva based test IIRC, but the names elude me. The test is a simple swab of the mouth which is then run through a small machine carried by the officer. I will look for the names of the companies, unless anyone else here knows what they are and can fill in the gap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 23:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The minimum age recommended by the task force was 18, because they know that 18-20 year olds make up a HUGE segment of the market. If you make the age too high, a large segment of the market continues to buy from the black market, which is what the government wants to kill.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 22:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do whatever you need to do to ensure this sub does NOT become like the weed forums on Stockhouse. They are full of spam, pumping, bashing, fighting, name calling and downright lying. There is one good post for every 20 sometimes and it's a total mess. I don't know how you prevent that, but hopefully someone does.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 01:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Picking THE weed stock that will do the best is tricky, and whichever one(s) turn out to be the winner(s) will be accompanied by every shareholder saying "I told you so". At this point, if weed is your interest, then owning a diverse mixture of the bigger names may be the best way to start that way if one fails you have other exposures. In my opinion those are Aurora, Aphria, Canopy to start, with other names like Supreme and Organigram being close runners up. No doubt I have missed a few, and hopefully others can add to the list with any I have missed. There could likely be further consolidation in the sector too, so keeping an eye on a few smaller names with potential could be a good idea too. 

The companies who can produce for the lowest costs, and who get a license to sell oil should do well, as oil sales could be very valuable to the company as not everyone wants to smoke cannabis, and oil typically sells for more than dry bud. 2-3 times the value of dry bud if I understand correctly. 

I would say the biggest thing to be aware of going into these stocks is that they are volatile at this point, so you have to willing to stomach the ups and downs, which isn't always easy to do. 

Hope that helps and good luck. You have lots of company along for the same ride. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 14:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good idea. Do it! Post it to the personal finance sub and you will have a proper answer to every question in no time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
