<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1549</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 09:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow, 25 years! That's amazing! 
 Thank you. Gives me a lot of hope - the general consensus when you google BPD isn't great vis a vis relationships. 

 Thanks. Hope all is well with you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 07:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice one, well done you !!! so proud :)

 happy birthday! anything nice planned? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 07:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you so much! Hoping to never do it again. Scary times. It's still more than half my life. 

 Hope things are good with you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 07:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey there 
  
 The main thing I would say is validation. When they have emotional outbursts because it's raining and it said it wouldn't and they wore non-waterproof shoes (for example), their emotions are very real. We experience things a lot more than most; a good mood is the Best Mood and a sad mood is the saddest that anyone has ever been. And these moods might be fleeting but they hurt or they're very intense, and very real to us. People telling us not to be silly are The Worst because often we know we're being silly but we can't stop it. 

 Also the bunny boiler stuff gets old after a while. And lots of people with BPD will have scars from self harm, or a history of suicide attempts, or a history with eating disorders. I don't know if that's the case with your partner or what but often strangers think they can ask us about this sort of thing. I cover my scars to avoid it but if my sleeve slips I get drunken boys at parties saying "woah, emo's over," and having a good laugh. So tread carefully there. 

 Also, and this ties into the validation thing I mentioned earlier, lots of people say "oh, we all have mood swings!" or "you'll grow out of it!" or treat the identity disturbances like a joke. "None of us know what we want to do when we're older", I get told, but for me it means my politics can shift from left to right wing, depending on who Im with. My accent changes. My style of dress veers from preppy to goth to mod to hipster, without ever mixing any of those elements. My favourite bands change, and my entire demeanour changes  I can be arrogant one day, meek the next, belligerent another. It is exhausting. I am trying on different people-suits until I find one that fits, but in twenty years Ive not found one yet. Dont try to pretend your agony of indecision about which uni to put first on your UCAS form is comparable.

 
We're very sensitive. We're like burn victims. And as BPD is cluster B personality disorder ("dramatic"), yeah, we're dramatic. It can be a lot for some people; it was too much for my friends. Oh! We're also not inherently manipulative. If we were it would be in the diagnostic criteria. 

  I really like that you're asking this question, go you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
