<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1239</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 18:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So how can I do that line and unlock the benefits without gaining new levels  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dark sigil in NG+ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 18:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I go into NG+, will I gain extra levels again by talking to Yoel and progressing that quest line? I'm considering my level meta and don't want to go outside of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 05:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should address the fact that 60% of migrants aren't refugees but young men using the open borders to get entry into the EU. Once here, they form ghettos and routinely harass women and cause conflict due to the fact that they hold cultural values that do not match western standards. It's not a matter of tolerance when the culture in question views women as subhuman property. What we need is to focus on vetting the ACTUAL refugees and improving their standards in their camps to work towards protecting and empowering those among them who are secularist and capable of being the future Muslim secular movement that is the only hope we have of fixing the Islamist Middle East. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 03:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Way to strawman right off the bat, really shows your capacity for discourse. How about not covering up mass rapes for starters? Is that a problem for you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 01:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's funny coming from a country that is suppressing countless rape victims of migrants for the sake of multicultural bullshit. Great news but honestly not enough for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 09:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did he make sure to DCAP BTLS? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 16:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would honestly be easy to ask for movies that are historically accurate since almost all of them, and probably all of the big ones are very inaccurate  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: why we need 70+ gender terms </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 01:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CMV: (LGBT folks needed)our 70+ new genders and sexualities are nothing more than turning quirky personality traits into a means to hijack the suffering of the LGBT people who are truly facing body dysphoria and bigotry. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 20:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 19:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Credits Theme from Baldurs Gate: Throne of Bhaal. The nostalgia is real.  Also the soundtrack to Fallout 4 and Last of Us. Both of those games were miserably depressing, which is exactly what I loved about them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 18:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look up Megan Phelps. She was his granddaughter and left the church in her twenties. The WBC very much believe what they are doing is an act of love given they believe these people will end up in hell if they don't convince them. Funny how perspective works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 21:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lovecraft was right.

This also counts as "the most horrifying thing you can imagine about space" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 21:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to be the type to say "if we allow human life to be ruled by reason the possibility of life is destroyed". I was super idealistic and a romanticist. Then I got hit with reality pretty hard when I fell on some bad times and realized i was actually a egotistical privileged liar who was full of himself and doing that stupid teenager thing where you try to pretend you're the most interesting personality when you actually have no real substance to your actual self. It was just another phase, and I came to realize the I was actually a pretty boring and empty person deep down. Then I realized religion was the same thing as me: a bunch of lies and fantasies that talks itself up to be solid gold and the ultimate truth. After a stint of getting into trouble and acting like a punk to deal with what honestly wasn't a big deal in hindsight and realizing one day that I was being a fool, I stopped pretending to be something I wasn't and grew up. Along with that came a lot of reading and the realization that being as reasonable and rational as possible is the only way to live in reality. Its still not perfect, but I feel a lot better about the direction I'm going. I certainly feel like I'm being more honest, and I think that's something we should all take more seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 03:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Thoughts and prayers" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 07:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being a PC/social justice attention whore and using tragedies as an opportunity to make myself look progressive on Facebook </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 05:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 01:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Opening band for Zac Brown at Fenway. Bunch of country girls with terrible voices screaming about Jesus for 30 minutes. They kept stopping after each song so the black lady in the band who had a remotely decent voice could rant about how much she loved Jesus. Zac Brown was amazing , even with far seats, but it was hard to hear because a third of the crowd kept screaming "FREE TOM BRADY" the whole time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 01:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. Sounds about right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 18:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never said dark souls tries to be the witcher. I said the witcher is everything that dark souls pretends to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 04:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I felt like the entire difficulty of Dark Souls was in its terrible controls/mechanics, but still, great design and scenery. Can't find an equatable atmosphere.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 02:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't agree less. Neither are perfect but the Witcher actually has more substance to it than "attack. Roll. Block. Attack. Get one shotted. Respawn. Attack. Slip off cliff. Repeat" it's endless rolling around and poking enemies to death vs having to assemble unique combinations of oils, poisons, bombs, potions, signs, attack styles, dodging, and more for each different kind of monster. Not perfect, but far more engaging and enjoyable than the endless rolling around trying to avoid getting hammered into the gravel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 22:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those jobs are exactly the type I'm interested in is the problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 20:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just have to wait for Mass Effect Andromeda </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 20:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You really need to be able to burst damage. I build around blade spin and stack as much point investment in quick attack as I can. Get bleed ability maxed out on that tree, and rune craft your blade to have the extra meter of range while twirling and then hit him as soon as he touches down. When he flies up to hit you with the bat cannon, roll towards him and try to get under him to take minimum damage  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 19:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly livid the duchess wasn't an option. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
