<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3535</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can picture the sparring matches between him and Wrex/Grunt/Drack.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No spoilers] If you could have one character from another Sci-Fi franchise join your squad, who would it be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could be the squad from the Shepard trilogy or Andromeda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hawaii Five-O is one of the corniest shows on cable TV right now, and there are quite a few times where they screw up not only the SEALs but the Navy in general, but I can do you one better. 

A few weeks ago, I caught an episode of NCIS: New Orleans where the main plot revolved around the investigation of a BUD/S student and some of the stuff I saw were: 

1. There's a "pilot program" for BUD/S students at the Stennis Space Center, and theres even a scene where they show students on a mini O-course five feet from where the booster rockets would be.

2. The actors keep pronouncing SEALs like the s was part of the acronym for the entire episode (Like the lines "SEALS trainees don't take days off", or "He was quitting SEALS") 

3. They don't know what BUD/S stands for, they just say "Basic Underwater Demolition SEALS" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 10:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course. When I say its a comedy, I mean the so bad its funny kind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 09:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen the entire thing. twice. For me, it more of a comedy than anything else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 09:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read somewhere that the waters in the pacific usually stay around the 50s or so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 08:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be more specific about my condition, I was exposed to negative  5 degree weather with a negative 6 degree wind chill when I got it and according to the doctor that treated me, being exposed to weather similar to that could do just as much damage in less time.  I don't know if this breaks rule 5 or not, but are BUD/S students exposed to  that kind of weather? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 07:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kind of do, but was hoping that someone with hands on experience at BUD/S would give a second, more optimistic, opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 07:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good one. I think that's the only depiction of SEALS conducting an operation without any weapons (I know its a Disney movie, but it always stuck out to me because of that) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BUD/S and the cold </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 07:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the biggest reservations I have in regards to trying out for NSW is how often BUD/S students and team guys interact with the cold. A couple of years ago, I had a case of second degree frostbite which caused permanent nerve damage in both my hands as well as severely lowered my tolerance for the cold, an example being that holding a fairly cold item or exposer to slightly cold weather can cause my fingers to stiffen and eventually go numb. Does this hurt my chances of doing well in BUD/S and later on as a member of the teams? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 06:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 06:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Much appreciated dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MEA Spoilers]:Does anyone know whether or not Scott and Sarah Ryder can be different ethnicities? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 06:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 06:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously? Do you know the episode title? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Worst/funniest portrayals of SEALs in the media </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 06:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's not a whole lot to this question. I just wanted to know what are some of the worst or so-bad-they're-funny depictions of SEALs in pop culture you guys have seen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know and I really appreciate the advice I got. I was just trying to get some different perspectives.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried talking to an officer recruiter about a month ago, but I'm a sophomore so they told me wait until you're a junior or a senior and contact them then. As for a SEAL mentor, I haven't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From Federal Law Enforcement to NSW </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In recent weeks, I've had the opportunity to meet a few reps from several federal law enforcement agencies at my university, and what I've learned has begun to get me thinking about the possibility of a career. However, I still want to be an officer and, hopefully, a SEAL. Is it possible to go from a career in federal Law enforcement into the teams? Has this kind of transition before in NSW? Should I attempt the reverse?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 05:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you if any team guys go to the Diplomatic Security service at the State Department? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 05:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really appreciate your 2 cents man, thanks for responding.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 04:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true. Did we ever find out if the Alliance brass shared the council's disbelief in Shepard? I know Anderson and Hackett were on Shep's side and I just assumed the rest of the Alliance gave him/her the benefit of the doubt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 02:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah. Sorry about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 01:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh. Was hoping a C-sec agent got fed up with the Council's incompetence and and took matters into their own hands.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 01:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shepards or the counselors? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 00:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cue a renegade interrupt where Shepard just lays out the council.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 00:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 23:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What made you decide to leave MEPs and go to CBP instead?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 22:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair point. I couldn't help but think of Nelson from The Simpsons and his laugh when that cutscene played. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What could have been a good I told you so moment with the council in ME3? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 22:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 12:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it common for former team guys to go to the tactical divisions of federal LE like the HRT for the FBI, the SOG for the Marshals, or the FAST teams for the DEA? Seems like that would be a good middle ground for guys looking for a future in Federal LE, but still want do some of the high speed stuff they're used to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 07:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the input. Using one career as a stepping stone is definitely not my intention, and I hope it doesn't come off as such. My issue is that there are two things I'm very passionate about and want to do and do well, its just that I can't figure out what order to do them in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From federal law enforcement to NSW </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 20:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In recent weeks, I've had the opportunity to meet a few reps from several federal law enforcement agencies at my university, and what I've learned has begun to get me thinking about the possibility of a career. However, I still want to be an officer and, hopefully, a SEAL. Is it possible to go from a career in federal Law enforcement into the teams? Has this kind of transition before in NSW? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 18:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was a big help. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 23:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you know why its not possible for civilians? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Appreciate the response anyway. thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 20:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there anything a civilian can do to make their packet stand out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EOD through OCS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 20:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently, I'm in my second year of college and intend to get a commission via Navy OCS with the intent of going to either NSW or EOD, however I don't know a lot nor have I been able to find a lot of in depth information regarding anything regarding the training process, career path, or responsibilities for Officers. Can someone inform me about how difficult it is for an OCS candidate to get an EOD billet if there not prior enlisted, as well as the typical career path of an EOD O? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 08:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, there are a tone of games with modern settings, but just because the setting's been done before, doesn't mean it can't be unique. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 06:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few ideas come to mind: 

1. Call of Duty Black Ops 4 which would be a return to WWII, but with a focus on the covert operations that took place during the war with Alex Mason's father as the protagonist. I think this is one aspect of WWII that hasn't been explored in COD, if not most fps games period, and could offer a lot in terms of mission variety, weapons, locations, and story. 

2. Call Of Duty:Warfighter, which would be a return to the modern day and tells a more personal story in the vain of Medal Of Honor Warfighter (hence the subtitle), but obviously much better. I would like to see Infinity Ward handle this, as they would have more experience dealing with modern settings, plus I think they're the best of the three COD studios in terms of storytelling, as evident by the MW trilogy and Infinite Warfare. I wouldn't want the setting  to be based in the Middle East or Europe, and would have it in Asia similar to Battlefield 4.

3. I remember someone in a different post suggesting a post apocalyptic COD. I could see a Mad Max style COD taking place in the remains of the U.S. with different factions fighting over remaining resources. 

4. Alternate History: Similiar to your idea about a steampunk COD, I could see Treyarch trying this out at some point. It wouldn't necessarily have to be alternate WWI or WWII, but if it were, I could see something akin to Wolfenstein:the New Order. 

5. Time Travel: This would be another Treyarch one, and would probably never happen, but imagine a game where each level takes place in a different era of history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say 4 WWII games is enough, but we're most likely going back to it. And just because its in the Modern day, doesn't mean it would deal with the same subject matter as the MW series. Also, the last MW game was in 2011, so a lot of stuff has changed in terms of weapons, tactics, and technology, so there would be a bit of a visual difference.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 19:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's actually where this idea came from. I too, don't think COD should go back to WWII because there is nothing new that hasn't already been done. Thats why, if they did go back to WWII, then I would want them to explore something we haven't seen in WWII, which would be the covert operations that took place during the war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Navy EOD through OCS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 19:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently, I'm in my second year of college and intend to get a commission via Navy OCS with the intent of going to either NSW or EOD, however I don't know a lot nor have I been able to find a lot of in depth information regarding anything regarding the training process, career path, or responsibilities for Officers. Can someone inform me about how difficult it is for an OCS candidate to get an EOD billet, as well as the typical career path of an EOD O? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 09:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wholeheartedly agree that the story sucked, but overall concept has potential. How many times have players wanted a COD story that humanized the characters and had emotion and impact? These were the things MOH:W was trying to achieve but came up short at. What I'm proposing is that COD try their hand at this concept and tell a story, one thats personal and focuses on the Warfighters, and I think if COD were to take the storytelling mechanics they've learned from previous games and apply them, then you could have a winner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think a time travel plot would work best for Treyarch since they do the more out there storylines for COD. There's a game called Darkest of Days on Xbox 360, which was about a soldier being pulled from the Battle of Little Bighorn by a group dedicated to defending the timeline. If they were to pull from that and apply it to the COD franchise and timeline, that would be something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not necessarily. Woods, Hudson, Bowman, and Weaver were all too young to be in WWII, and you don't need to run into Reznov or Dimitri. You could see WAW characters like Roebuck, Sullivan, and Miller, but since its so far removed from the events of BO1, you wouldn't need to reference or reflect it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have any ideas, please feel free to post them and discuss, I have quite a few of my own and would love listening to others input.  

As for a title, Call Of Duty: Black Ops IV would be just fine for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think both could actually fit into the Black Ops in WWII setting, as the British had the SOE conduct unconventional warfare in SE Asia, and the Finnish (or the Danish, please correct me if I'm wrong) did conduct raids on Nazi nuclear facilities.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they take the motion Capture, technical detail and treatment of cutscenes from Infinite Warfare and apply it to a story that focuses on the operators like MOH: Warfighter tried to do, then its a day one purchase for me. Call Of Duty:Warfighter anyone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, a Wolfenstein: New Order kind of setting wouldn't be a bad one for COD.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think COD could handle time travel? More specifically, could the fanbase handle it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think of the experimental guns created by both the Allies and Axis we would be able to use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember the file in BO1 saying he was in the Makin Atoll, but I don't know if he was in the raid in WAW.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually think alternate history is a good middle ground for those who want to go back to the past and those who want COD to go in new directions. I'm actually hoping Treyarch tries it because I think they''re more comfortable with the more out there concepts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [COD] A pitch for a WWII based COD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 11:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a lifelong COD player, I've been a fan of the franchise's attempts at trying something new in terms of settings, and I don't necessarily think going back to WWII is the best way for the franchise to reinvigorate itself mainly because we've had 4 games take place in that period and there wouldn't be anything new that we haven't already seen in 1,2,3,WAW, and parts of BO1. But, there is an aspect of WWII that we haven't seen much of that, in my opinion, would be a fresh new take on WWII for COD, and that would be the 4th entry in the Black Ops series that explored the world of covert operations in WWII with Alex Mason's Father as the protagonist. 

If you recall, the intel file on Mason from BO1 said that his father was in the Pacific theater in WWII, but it never said exactly what he did. So, what if Mason's father was a member of any one of the many specialized units the U.S. had during the war (the Alamo Scouts, the OSS maritime unit or Jedburough teams, the Marine Corp Raider units, etc.), and missions could involve jumping behind enemy lines to train resistance fighters, nighttime raids on Nazi/Japanese facilities, capturing enemy leaders for intel,a tutorial level at Camp X where the U.S. and U.K trained their spies, or any number of missions WWII covert units did. WWII was the birthplace of both modern day Special Operations units and intelligence agencies, so there is an entire world that we haven't seen in any WWII set fps.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
