<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3323</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 01:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got my posters, months ago, yours must be messed up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 06:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just complain to Club Nintendo, if they mess up on items, they repay you back in large ways, I got two more poster kits for their mess up on my first. If anything they can tell you the status. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I animated the FNAF 4 Plot meme </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 06:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 06:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> because making themselves seem like they're the better and more powerful dealer with a bigger bargin, makes them look like first priority. In other words, a small item for a big item is easy to take advantage of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 04:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get Punch Out, it's meant to be played on wii controllers and is worth it (I bought it did not use my reward to redeem) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 04:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well duh, you were trading a mewtwo code, who would pay 10-20 dollars worth for a $4 code. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 04:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol he's right  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 17:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 months for my poster kit, 4 days for my other two poster kits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 04:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 04:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure, you'd have to give me the rep of the middle man/mod, considering how your account seems like it was just made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 00:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol did you say free and good hahaha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 20:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it doesn't come, definitely complain to club nintendo, if they think they mess up or do, they'll send you 2 more as a bonus, now I have 3 poster sets :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just Another Walk Test </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 21:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 21:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Punch Out in my opinion is the best game only because it actually uses the wii controllers on how they were made to be used. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I found a chocolate Santa in my Easter basket </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 21:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Attention Whore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China has developed a liquid metal that can transform into any shape. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 20:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While the U.S. has created a breakfast sandwich with Hash Browns now at Taco Bell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you call a Whore shot by a sniper? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 21:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 360 hoscope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you call a Whore that was shot by a sniper? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 19:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 360 hoscope  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Macho Man Flipnote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 18:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 04:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used the card, but I'll be back with a more reasonable card deal. If you want me to pm you when I get another card I can do so, sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 03:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you it does sound like a scam, I'll just trade for a higher priced card when I trade off this one I have on me, and return some other time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 01:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 58463 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why was the Black Man a bad sniper? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 20:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he was blind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 04:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so sorry he rekt you in gta </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 04:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know for a fact this is from snl, thanks for bringing it back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 04:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you call Annoying Orange and his gang having sex? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 04:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An Orangy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> why was the clown sent to jail? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 06:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> August 9th 1988 the childhood clown Tibbles was drinking on the job one day, he was tired of his dead end job. Evidence shows he drank half a bottle of Vodka. He approached a kid and said,"Do you waaannnt to see a magic rape, I mean trick?" The boy said yes without out knowing the clowns true intentions. The clown took the boy backstage, then picked up the boy, placed his hand behind the boys head and screamed,"HEY I FOUND A QUARTER IN YOUR EAR!" The boy laughed in joy then without hesitation the clown took a knife and stabbed the boy, on gta 5 multiplayer. Even though the clown never harmed the boy, he was arrested for drinking on the job and hoarding a barrel of cocaine in his showroom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Animatronics Sell Chocolate To Foxy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 05:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to kill your wife </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 03:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How to kill your wife, Step One find out some way to get a wife, Step Two kill your wife. If you failed to complete Step One you can't kill your wife. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the difference between a goat and a black guy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 18:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The black is a homo sapien and is nothing like a goat, why hell would think they're alike you racist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why did the black boy not want to go to school? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 02:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the KKK was there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many pigeons does it take to change a light bulb? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 02:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know, I was hoping you'd answer.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Salvage Loves Gold Animation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 05:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 04:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> confirmed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 04:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. 1

Trade Completed With /u/hellr4isEr

GameStop for Eshop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /u/subject3323 GCX Rep Profile </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 02:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Redditor since Dec 12, 2013 
* If you have been linked to this page, please make sure that you're on the real /r/GCXRep, and the user who linked you was indeed me, and not someone with a similar username trying to impersonate me. Note that just because you're reading this doesn't mean a scammer didn't include this note in their fake profile to trick you into a false sense of security. Double check, and don't get tricked or scammed! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you call a prostitute working for Disney? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 08:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> High Ho, High Ho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 00:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh wait I just realized you're not the guy who started this thread XD, lemme wait for him to reply and I'll get back to you XD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 00:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I thought you'd go first but if that's the case do you have a link for rep? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 00:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no, not yet I was waiting on you to reply. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 00:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> got it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 23:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if you're still trading I'll trade a $25 dollar gamestop card for a code of wii fit u, it may seem like overpay but gamestop prices the game just 5 dollars more pre-owned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
