<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3359</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 23:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CZ is still fine, it's not supposed to be a run and gun weapon anyway imo. You should use it as a pistol when holding a close angle and try to get an easy frag to pick up a weapon on an eco.

If you buy it as a sidearm on buy rounds... well, don't know what to tell you other than not to use it on buy rounds lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 23:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fiffy = bae 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 23:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, they actually look pretty much alike lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 21:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would be nice :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 20:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, source? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 18:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> JKS' party face lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 17:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very informative and straight to the point, great video. Screw the ones complaining about your accent, you were perfectly understandable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 17:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, all I can really say haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 17:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly, look at Guardian for example. He was able to adapt to the AWP in a way no other player could. I mean sure, others are good, but I'd still call Guardian the best awper in the world right now.

I wouldn't mind adapting to the recovery time nerf, but like you said, how the fuck do you adapt to RNG? That's just pure bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 17:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know higher ranked players thought it was OP as well, myself included, however it was mainly low ranked people complaining about it. Not trying to discredit OP at all.

Hated playing against it myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 15:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of people in the community, mainly low ranked players thought the AWP was very OP pre-nerf. TBH, how the AWP is now actually seems better to me than how it was. 

I don't at all agree with the rifle changes, also considering NO ONE asked for them. Literally no one. The main 3 rifles were the only weapons I thought valve just wouldn't touch since they were nearly perfect, except that tapping wasn't as good as in other cs games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 00:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you retarded? Haven't you seen the other shit storm in posts about the rifle nerf?

I personally don't give a fuck about the recovery time, them making spraying more inaccurate and more RNG based is infuriating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 23:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They made m4a1-s and AK way more RNG based lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 23:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check SlothSquadron's thread in full details of what got changed. 


https://www.reddit.com/r/GlobalOffensive/comments/3w1azc/in_depth_analysis_of_december_8_2015_weapon/

Rifles


Pre-update values are on the left, Post-update are on the right


AK-47
InaccuracyCrouch 4.81 - 5.00

RecoveryTimeCrouch 0.381571 - 0.45

RecoveryTimeStand 0.46 - 0.60000


M4A4
RecoveryTimeCrouch .302625 - 0.43

RecoveryTimeStand 0.423676 - 0.525


M4A1-S
InaccuracyCrouchAlt 3.68 - 4.10

RecoveryTimeCrouch 0.302625 - 0.43

RecoveryTimeStand 0.423676 - 0.525


No InaccuracyCrouchAlt for M4a4, http://i.imgur.com/lePWkQ6.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 22:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun fact: The m4a4's spray didn't get changed, only recovery time. They only changed the spray of m4a1-s and AK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 23:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Savage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 23:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the BM shit by Fnatic this match, love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 12:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be a step in the right the direction, however, you could still easily pre-fire spots with left click. One hit to the body with armour as well? No. Just no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 10:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry but as an EU player who floats around LEM/Supreme I almost never seen anyone buying pistols on pistol round. Nor do we see it in the pro scene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 01:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally like to play open world games such as the Fallout or Elder Scrolls series. Can get invested in them for hours on end just exploring stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 01:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, he plays CS:GO with Ethan from H3H3Productions. He played with LOLYOU on stream a couple of weeks ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 00:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=laiQiBFfmyk - Surprisingly, it wasn't me who killed you :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 00:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The weapon is so incredibly stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 00:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's been there for a long time buddy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 00:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Trust me guys... The community will love this." -CSGO Dev 2015 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 00:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If only valve could just revert the update... wouldn't have to go through all this trouble, but no. They decided to add skins for the R8 so removing it will be impossible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 00:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I never use the AUG/Krieg. The thing is, valve is trying to make all weapons viable even though that's just stupid. They nerf things to make other things viable, even though the things they nerf are just the correct and best way to play. Now people will still use the AK/M4, even though they could switch AUG/Krieg. When they nerfed the M4a1-s people expected a lot of people to switch to the AUG, did it happen though? Nope. Nearly everyone kept using M4a1-s or M4a4. I genuinely don't see the point of making things viable when every weapon already is viable just in different situations, which valve does not seem to understand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 23:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah in nova... nice flair. Obviously global. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 23:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was all for buffing first shot accuracy, and SLIGHTLY nerfing pistol accuracy for SOME of them. This shit? It's retarded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 23:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You realise tapping wasn't improved...? Spraying/bursting/tapping all become worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 22:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, but what about pistol rounds? It's dumb to buy anything other than armour/nades on pistol round. A glock is just not on par with the USP/P2K. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 21:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not keep the bloody rifles how they were? They were perfectly fine for god sake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 21:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't see much difference on a wall, you do while actually playing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 19:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He said in April which is months away... That's why I said fairly soon implying it'd be another couple weeks lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 17:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> one will be released fairly soon due to the operation and de_newke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 16:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We awp now boys! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 16:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do we really NEED new guns? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 10:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 20:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't say shit about your HS%, just said it's not an accomplishment if you idle for a really long time and get 19k hours on the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 19:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> who? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 19:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I cannot fucking stand this shit man" *walks away from computer* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 17:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you get to global, there is still a huge skill ceiling left open. There a very large skill gap between new globals and globals which have been there for a long time. If MM get's boring, move on to FACEIT (EU/NA), ESEA (NA) or CEVO (not sure if this is very good in either NA or EU). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 17:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 00:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To stop hackers and smurfs, once you get your rank you can play as much as you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 18:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://csgo-stats.com/me-shoe/ - 0.03 KD and 12k "actual gameplay hours" so yeah, it's just been idled lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 18:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not much of an accomplishment since it's just idle hours and not actual gameplay... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 14:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Allu was on Mouz before together with ChrisJ, either of them can rifle as well (Allu is probably still better at it than ChrisJ), but it has been done before. They used to be the online upset team. Also, their double awp setup could be deadly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 13:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe a bit more than market price, not by much though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 13:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbh I'd like to see him on Mouz again with Gob B as coach </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 09:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shiny shit is the shader setting, not graphic/texture quality </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 09:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Silver 2 pre vac </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 21:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On such a crucial round as well, rip </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 05:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And he's got quite a lot of fans lol. The whole of ex-TSM has been choking lately, can't just blame Device. Before Cluj TSM and especially Device were insane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 04:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> de_sync </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 23:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, he is very overrated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 22:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not that he's not good at tapping anymore, tapping got nerfed a very long time ago and the first shot accuracy just got fucked over. I do however agree with you that he is unwilling to spray in situations when he is supposed to, which does indeed fuck his team over but also himself. If Valve buffed first shot accuracy, we could see ScreaM going godly again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 22:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thorin wasn't hating on him, just saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 22:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were black and also very long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 16:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd prefer the golden one since I like shiny gold skins such as the case hardened and brass skins :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 16:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> upboat this, love the way the m4a1-s golden coil looks but I use m4a4, so pls gaben </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 16:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was so awkward for both players... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 16:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> World record belongs to GeT_RiGhT, sorry :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 01:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you ever have sex with a tranny/shemale? If so then why? Also, what are some of your favourite fetishes/things to do in porn? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 22:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GET ON THE HYPE TRAIN BOYZ, CHOO CHOO! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 21:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No shit, but that means we won't see pros play it anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 20:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they remove dust 2 I will probably hang myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 18:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like Tim when he's not obnoxious and shouting his lungs out :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FUNNY PRO MOMENTS! #9 by chhrz </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 16:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 21:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most likely on idle servers lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 18:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "They were never amazing at playing against Fnatic and to be fair" Neither of them were amazing against each other. They've got a new line-up though so yeah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 16:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ken isn't all real hours, he's got around 2500 actual hours where he's played. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 16:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://csgo-stats.com/conusoid/ - only a bit over 800 actual hours played lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 16:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can run multiple games at once and they count hours individually so it's possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 21:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thing is though, NiP likes playing against both TSM and Nv, they feel comfortable playing against either of those teams and can be good against them. They were never amazing at playing against Fnatic and to be fair, they have a new line-up and a different IGL so it's harder to read them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 00:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I genuinely didn't, I read it yeah but I actually do wear mine backwards. When I told my friends they thought it was weird as fuck lol. Thing is, it sounds perfectly fine to me it's just a bit awkward because of the mic attached to the headset. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 22:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Titty in yo face?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 22:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Took the caster a moment to realise haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 18:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> +1 for creativity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 13:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was playing on stream with LOLYOU a couple weeks ago. He's DMG btw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 14:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I know, 32 hours still seems like very little time for getting all achievements in this game though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 14:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vertibirds can take quite a bit of damage. It really depends on where you shoot it and on what difficulty you play though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 14:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Companions dont take rad damage, and tbh, the radiation there isn't even that bad. You could probably do it with a couple radx and radaway and normal armour instead of a hazmat suit/power armour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 14:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In just 32 hours? You didn't just use the achievement hack, did you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every wondered what a Glowing Deathclaw looks like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 14:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 05:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thing is, Shox basically took over Maniac's role and Shox was better at it in almost every single way. No point kicking other players when they have roles which belong to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 01:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> god speed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 21:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gladly haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 04:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #17 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 04:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spread them, then I'll spank you ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 21:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, really? That sucks. You should still just be able to find that armor randomly in the wasteland tho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 20:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Find Court 35 if you are level 26 or above and you should get the full set :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 16:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sean will be coaching if Swag get's unbanned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 18:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's now stuck in communication hell along with Fox lol. Norwegian and Swedish are alike, but Danish isn't if i'm right. Not sure though, but that was the reason schneider left Dignitas so I'm just assuming the languages aren't alike. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 23:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those teams would be awful tbh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 23:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's barely any difference, when I ranked up I didn't notice much difference at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 17:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to get this for 3 months straight, getting 7 days. Turn off your router for a minute or two when you can, don't reset it but actually fully turn it off. Should fix it.

If not, it may just be your router which is the problem.

Only applies if you get this issue multiple time though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 03:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just saying, but they fixed the lag after the first two days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 03:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All pro players love the booths and think they're great, the only downside is that it feels like a bloody earthquake sometimes lol. 

With the old setup players still had to wear headphones which blocked out A LOT of sound and had to wear earbuds under those for the in-game sound, whereas now they can just wear their own headsets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 01:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prize pool: something more than fucking 250k </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Did you even check reddit? NO. Block communication." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 01:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 13:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> made 2 euros profit with envy autograph stickers, good enough lol. Seems like sticker investing just doesn't work at all anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 16:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this was at 15-14 then it would've been great, but this isn't really that special. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 12:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worst thing which could happen is you break even if you sell them on first day at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 18:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And LG beating Fnatic, becoming 1st seed and giving fnatic 2nd seed, so fnatic fell out in the quarters because of that. If Fnatic didn't lose against LG, they would've most likely gone to the semis/finals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 18:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Allu is not amused :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 18:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didnt stop moving, soz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 16:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All issues from day one and two have already been fixed, just saying. C9 also just isn't good, there are no top tier NA teams anymore. Liquid may become one in a couple months or maybe we'll see an American shuffle, but we'll never know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 16:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Niko hates how G2 are really hard to read. They're extremely unpredictable and just really rely on their individual skill.

Sure, mouz has all the tactics but they don't have the raw skill G2 does to win aim duels. He's also probably a bit salty about losing to them.

I remember a tweet he posted a couple weeks ago saying something along the lines of "GG G2 can't win against such stupid plays". He said something like that after losing a match online against them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Props to JKAEM and Fox of G2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 16:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 20:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what a legend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 22:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 21:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assists don't play a part in your elo. Only things the elo system cares about is wins and MVPs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
