<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2519</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 18:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least with the Falklands it was mostly to save British lives who lived there - not a lot of Americans living in Somalia  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 14:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact you were born then and still don't know hurts me. I was born in 1995 - all I had to do was talk to my dad - hey what was it like during the Falklands war papa? 'Oh yeah it was kinda of scary because they began circulating rumour about a draft and a lot of ships had been hit by Argentine planes'

Basically Argentina have always claimed the island but its population is almost entirely British. They invaded and the British went down there to liberate it and succeeded. As recently as 2014 (2015?) they had a referendum to stay part of this country so the war was legitimate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 07:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like season 6 but when you take it as two episodes- feels like one long one tbh  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 07:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is exactly was I was talking about such shit humour 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is 'Reddit Humour' (in particular joke comment threads) so cringe-worthy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 06:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 05:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's also FDR and Eleanor Roosevelt too!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 14:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'And this picture is when the Death Star tested its weapons system on Jedha'  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 02:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So 10 massive multiplayer maps with various game modes and a campaign isn't a lot of content these days ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 17:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vader year one - something like that where he is learning to get to grips with the suit and himself  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is 'Reddit Humour' so cringe-worthy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 16:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is 'Reddit Humour' so cringe-worthy ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 11:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 10:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yes because now we have to love everything to be all wacky ! GTA V narrative was shit compared to GTA IV and the gleeful murdering hackers in Watch Dogs 2 are way too over the top  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 10:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not being funny but I think Luke Cage is one of the worst things I've watched this year and found Coulters performance awful. I really like all the other Marvel stuff and found his performance way better in Jessica Jones. I don't know why everyone has gone mental about how good it is. The only decent episode was his backstory in prison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 19:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [TV] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me at the beginning of 2016 vs me at the end of 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 19:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 13:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol alright mate - could just act like a Trump supporter and not give a fuck  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 07:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm assuming you don't exercise ? I have to go at least 3 times a day. If you actually do exercise your body is amazing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 23:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely understand he two difference between them. But they often become the same thing. I think it became slang from straight people saying to other straight people 'that's so gay' but then evolved into a word to describe pretty much everything negative  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 23:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A '10 year old from 2005' is exactly what I was in that year but have just failed to kick the habit of saying it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 23:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay fuck off  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 23:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I guess that's true but at the same time a lot of slang is just what people grow up saying. Like 'peng' 'ting' 'rah' all being common slang words in London </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 23:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I understand that POV  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 23:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I don't use it as an insult I generally say 'that's so gay' if I say it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 23:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I get that  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 16:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nixon was probably one of the smartest presidents (especially in terms of foreign policy) he revived a briefing everyday, even on the stuff him and Henry Kissinger were deeply involved in. Trump needs that briefing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 19:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I agree there is a lot of work to be done in terms of equal rights I was just making the point in the early to mid 2000's there was a lot less progress mad than there is today. And I think making it the same as the n word goes abit far but agree it's bad all the same  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 19:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay thanks for the reply and everyone says dumb things doesn't mean they aren't intelligent - I've just always said it and not didn't used to be seen as bad really (even my old English teacher said he struggled to stop saying it). Everyone is learning to be more accepting sometimes adjusting to the language can be hard  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi LGBT community - just came to ask... what do you think of the word 'gay' as slang? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 13:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was born in the mid-90's and grew up at a time where the strive for LGBT equality was still pushing for real change. I am not LGBT, I am straight, but I am really passionate about equal rights for all. One of the worst things I do is say the word 'gay' as slang. Growing up everybody said it and you wouldn't even get in trouble for saying it in front of a teacher (I assume it's a lot different these days). While I now say it less I still occasionally will say it. What do you guys in general think of this word when used as slang to describe something not specifically gay? Personally I know it's bad because it's often used in a negative context and I try and stop myself but I see a lot to people equating it with the N-word which is think is a bit too far. The N-word was used to remind black people that whites once owned them and they were their property - the word gay used to (and still does to some extent) mean happy and was later used to describe homosexuals. Anyway want to hear people's opinions - I do know it's wrong at some level though and I'm trying to change it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 15:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get Far Harbour no question  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doom multiplayer dead on Xbox One ? (Europe/UK) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 15:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 14:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have found it pretty good at a couple ranges but I guess that is me coming from the Lewis Gun  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Support rank 10's: what do you think of the two guns you unlock at this rank? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 05:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 02:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lewis gun and being patient is also a good support role  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 02:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use Lewis Gun low weight. Use the bipod for long range engagements, and it's decent up close aswell nearly rank 10 on support  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 02:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Play a different mode maybe ? Sounds like you are only playing conquest. And you uninstalled the game to be dramatic? You're hard  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is quick match for operations going to be a thing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 02:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 12:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha u got me it was actually a cross!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 05:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's changed it apparently  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scored an absolutely disgusting goal in PES 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 04:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 02:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That gun only has 47  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 12:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does my dick grow 5 inches when I see a soaking wet dogs cunt !?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 12:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a rather gargantuan penis that everyone always comments on  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 12:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys cry racism when it suits you, but will happily say black people have lower IQ's because of their race  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 12:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hard man I don't want to mess with you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 12:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't hate many people but I absolutely loathe Jimmy Fallon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 04:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 03:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jona Lewie - Stop the Calvary </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The only Christmas song to listen to while playing BF1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 03:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 03:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well 'Amiens' is already in the game so no it's not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 21:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This the same Washington Post that smeared Bernie every step of the way until Hillary lost and they did a complete u-turn!?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 03:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty bad for some other guns but good for this one  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 03:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I was so annoyed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you find a nice place to set up your Lewis Gu-oh fuck off! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 22:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 21:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I'm over here visiting my hundredth barren wasteland... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 16:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still feel ashamed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 16:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lewis Gun or MP-18 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 16:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a slang term from South Africa meaning buddy or mate  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 07:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No he's not. On most liberal issues Biden usually put pressure on Obama to be more left and not concede.  On foreign policy he's a lot more left wing too and always pushed Obama for less force in places like Afghanistan. Obama talks the talk but in all honesty is centre right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 03:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No thanks ! I really like Biden and he's left of Obama but the country has to be done with the old democratic establishment  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 23:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 16:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the script in general was absolutely awful and cheesy. Luke Cage in Jessica Jones might aswell be a different character from the one in his own series </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 15:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know some people just like playing games and not watching others play </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 06:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Geography is the number one thing people are utterly stupid on. A prominent gaming YouTube personality who gives it the bigun on social issues and the like thought New Zealand was in Europe. No he wasn't talking about Zeeland  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 06:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mate thought the USSR was the UK and America together... had to explain it was communist Russia - which he didn't even know had existed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 16:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New photo mode and looking up in the cockpit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 16:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's sucks until you find a good planet for a base !!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 06:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the campaign is really good too be far emotional!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 06:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Campaign is way better than multiplayer this year  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 05:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yeah that is true - Ford wasn't as much as a bully though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 05:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet you were 3 years old when it came out originally gtfo!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 05:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I feel it's mainly LBJ  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 05:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To a certain extent but not loads  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 05:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Religion is a lie get out while you can !  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 05:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't have a long attention span and everything has to be flashy for you to like something than no. Boardwalk is one of the greatest shows of all time imo opinion but you really have to appreciate it as a whole - the great writing and sometimes irrelevant conversations, the authenticity, the history - it's a slow burn. It's mostly about the character journey as people and where they all end up in the end compared to the beginning is great to see. It's a lot more classic gangster than Sopranos but one of the main writers of that show made Boardwalk so I don't think you will like it. Suits is garbage in comparison to this show  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My first screenshot I've uploaded to Reddit-I think it's pretty nice! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 05:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which President is Frank inspired by? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 01:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I always thought he was LBJ. A Southern Democrat who was chief Whip, Vice President, taking over as President during the term of another. His political operations are also quite bullying like LBJ. When he's President he operates abit like Nixon with his mass surveillance and I guess somewhat like Bush Jr with his war on terror. What do you guys think ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Holy shit - what an amazing campaign!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 16:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spoilers - well for a game written by BJ Blazkowicz, and Nick Reyes, himself this was pretty emotional. The last couple missions were so great the feeling of impending doom. The way everyone sacrifices themselves one by one (even that pilot who flew into the AA gun without question got me upset). When the quartermaster stays behind, or the chief sacrifices herself, don't even get me started on Ethan! Ballsey to kill off most of the cast and some of those recordings at the end brought me to the point of tears. Kash, Ethan and the Quartermasters one - oh god hold me!!! Overall hugely surprising and very emotional I am so pissed off that this is the Call of Duty people are voicing anger at - it's the best one in years!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 08:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This trailer was like the sequence in Trainspotting where he tries to get clean  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 08:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks very metal gear-like - especially the way he commanded the 'skulls' . Reminded me of Skullface and his unit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 02:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No they didn't. I always assumed it was money but it's reference a lot later on. It's why Nucky isn't as well off later on  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 22:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exchange for money - FBI ask Eli later why Nicky pays Al money every month  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 19:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Curved dicks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 08:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Fox News credible at all ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 08:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New imperial armour, cheat room, new towns, witcher armour, different faces for children, more natural NPC chatter, faster horses, better rain,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 07:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 00:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really wouldn't say putting the game in Afghan is a criticism of America. Yeah they funded many mujahideen groups to fight but it was Pakistan that help found the Taliban and ensured they won the civil war and Mullar Omar, Bin Ladens old comrade , became leader following the soviet withdrawal. Bin Laden was basically finished before Omar invited him back. The US didn't play a massive part in this conflict. They helped sure but an Atheist communist regime wouldn't have survived in Afghan forever. Let's not forget the Chinese also gave the guerrilas a lot of assistance. I feel the critic of America is more apparent in the conflict in Angola   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 00:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah thanks - man this sucks! Hurts so much atm!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the difference between the game modes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 03:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mainly what is the difference between creative and normal ? What are the pros and cons of both compared to one another?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 03:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Play it again.... johnyyyyyy guitarrrrrrrr  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 10:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://history.state.gov/historicaldocuments click on the administration u want then type in key words you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 10:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I guess there isn't the only one thing I'd say differently about McNamara is that he felt really guilty about getting the US into the war but was good he tried to stop the bombings  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 03:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm doing history at university. We are reading old top secret transcripts from the Kennedy, Johnson, Nixon and Ford administrations where they talk with their staff. Every time I read it I imagine what Donald Trump would have said during the Tet offensive, fall of Saigon, the Yom Kippur war, the overthrow of Diem and I die a little inside. How can we go from all these smart (even Nixon as corrupt as he was) to a complete and utter moron !? 

Side note - Bush Jr's transcripts are still classified but even he would understand things way better than Trump-and bush was an idiot  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 03:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My worm has grown  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 03:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate sand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 15:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Geography is important  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 14:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This might not fix the game for a lot of people but this I what I wanted. Give me places to store my resources and a place to build and that's a good enough goal for me to grind. I loved exploring this game but now it has a purpose which is great  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 21:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I guess but not really an excuse could do something more like the Last of Us to reflect his inexperience  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 20:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I for one am happy about this update. I enjoyed the game for about the week and have good memories but like everyone else when I discovered there wasn't much to play for I stopped. I've really enjoyed all the shit posting and roasting of sean Murray and hello games but if they make something cool I will happily go back to NMS. I am a gaming editor at my Uni's entertainment magazine and I buy most games - but NMS did provide me with genuinely cool moments that I will remember for awhile so will happily support new content for the game  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 18:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do get that and I guess they got rid of competitive multiplayer too so shooting isn't as important   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone ever get the sudden urge to play then realise the game has nothing to do ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 18:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It fun to fly round the planets but without even a tiny purpose it's pointless. I mean even if I just had a small build-able bass that would be enough of a hook to reel me back in  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 18:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's definitely the worst thing they did. Take Mafia III, if released to mediocre reviews like NMS but the developers have been in constant touch with the community in adding free updates to the game. Now these updates are not anything amazing but people did ask for them. They left stuff out like outfits for Lincoln and put it in when people were upset. NMS promised loads and never said a word when most wasn't in the game  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 13:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah the kill quick I guess  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 13:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely disagree with this - GTA V is basic but nice and smooth  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shooting - Watch Dogs vs Watch Dogs 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 06:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am soo happy they have made so many great improvements from the first game but am I the only one who feels the new shooting totally sucks? The old one had great gunplay but this one feels clunky and makes it a lot harder to aim than it needs to be - am I alone in thinking this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 21:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the soccer is contributing but when I run it's brings out injury - guess I'm overdoing it the running type exercises  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 21:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And how would they rule over everyone else ? It's a popular vote between a or b - states lines don't matter  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 20:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? Why does state lines make a difference? More people wanted her to be president she should be president because it's the genuine will of the people - how can you argue against that? States have their own senators and federal governments for them to vote on - why isn't the president decided by the whole will of the country? It doesn't make sense anymore  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 20:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's sucks but she knew the score - reform is needed but we just have to accept the results. No one was making a lot of noise about the electoral college before the election. But as it has affected democratic victories a lot they need to go hard on getting it abolished-please democrats don't be weaklings for once!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 01:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arsenal always come fourth. That's all you need to know. Even when they come second they actually come fourth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 22:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow got a lot more comments than I expected ! Thanks guys you have all been really helpful thanks for being a great sub Reddit in helping me out!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Running vs cycling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 23:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So sorry if this isn't the right place to ask but feel it's relevant. So recently I've started playing soccer again and combining with my old running schedule it's brought out some bad injuries. I keep getting muscle strains and the like popping up in different places when I try and run every so often. So I am falling back on cycling when my body can't handle running. 

I usually run for fitness and to keep in shape - my question is - is burning 500 calories in a cycle the same as a run? I know it sounds dumb but as running helps burn fat around you stomach - does cycling do something similar ? Or does it just workout your legs ? What is the major downside of cycling over running ? 

I am abit of a noob but a replay would be appreciated from anyone !  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 07:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine this war Hillary and Chelsea was listening in - Republicans would be frothing at the mouth!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found this in Watch Dogs 2 - words to live by! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 07:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 18:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same thing happened here with Brexit. White working class really stuck it to the political elite by ensuring a right-wing Tory government will rule for at least the next ten years. A government that largely works against the interest of the working class-and you thought Cameron's centrist governments was the worst! Johnson, Fox, Leadsom and May are not doing anything for your prospects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 18:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apart from Frank is essentially LBJ with a dash of Nixon than anything like Obama - Petrov is Putin though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 17:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may be right - Seljuks came abit later  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 13:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you seen the Pacific!? He is actually one of the leads and it's great  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 10:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have like 4 now  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 10:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guessing it could be from Viking mercenaries who fought for the Byzantines against the Seljuk Turks? Or some Arab emirate  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
