<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3594</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 08:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never actually played the game but I've watched it for years now and I feel like I could play i with no trouble (after learning the keyboard shortcuts) I never really understand when people say paradox games are "too complicated" with the exception of HOI 3 it doesn't take that long to understand one of their games  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 14:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> VIC 3 confirmed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 04:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gov. Johnson although I'm sure you have been asked this question a thousand times and I have not heard the answer because I do not follow you too well, if polls show you at 15% and you do get to join a debate against Donald trump and Hillary Clinton, which one do you feel you would be more critical of?  (Or I should say which one would you attack more when they say something you disagree with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 02:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for making everyone in Wisconsin look like assholes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 23:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ass effect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 20:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As Burnie has also said Gavin doesn't try to come off dumb he just messes up the phrasing of words </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 08:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in Milwaukee and to all of those people saying how they are being hypocrites and stupid for beating white's I agree but you must understand I've been through that neighborhood and it is one of the lowest income and segregated neighborhoods in America.  These aren't people doing just because they hate white's, but because they are angry and frustrated that their life will never go anywhere.  there aren't any opportunities there.  You'll live with your parents many join gangs and that's all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 07:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually more segregated there are actually more smaller pockets like there is a very large Laos population in 1 neighborhood and nothing else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
