<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3065</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 02:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We could be taken out by a large asteroid tomorrow so he could be right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 01:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I'm talking about!  I need to find a great deal like this one of these days.  This old stuff was built to last and that Chinese crap is designed to fail on purpose so you have to buy a new one, I believe the term is planned obsolescence.  Anyway, great find and happy machining! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 07:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We only have EMD's and GE's running now at U.P.  If I had to pick one I would say I like EMD's better because for some reason GE made it a pain in the ass to get to the #2 and #5 traction motor leads.  Thank god I am skinny with long arms or I wouldn't be able to fit in there to disconnect them.  I worked on both tonight and the EMD's seem better thought out and the components are easier to get to although the air start sucks when it runs out of air...no air start GE's.  They each have their pros and cons but all smell like shit on the inside because of the port a potty in the cab. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 06:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With your mouth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 06:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hated it.  Although my last two years I went to votech for half the day and took diesel mechanics, that was the only subject I actually liked and now I fix trains! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 04:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A couple weeks ago I killed probably a couple hundred migrating butterflies with my truck on a road trip.  I felt a little bad because they were just passing through and I wasn't the only one on the road that day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 04:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The military.  I was making $73k by the time I retired at age 39.  Now I get paid $24k per year in retirement for the rest of my life!  Also working for the railroad...$30 per hour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 02:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man that's quite the project but where else are you going to get a lathe for that price!  I never really got into machine work, I'm too impatient, even though my dad has a lathe and mill.   When you need to make a part for something they really come in handy.  Awesome job saving this one from the literal scrap yard! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 06:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turn off the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 06:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carhart jacket, redwing boots, dickies pants and shirt.  Tells me he's a working man and likes to wear quality work clothes.  Hilfiger is for fags and kids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 05:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not very. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 06:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you must have met yum yum and sum sum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 04:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just don't like washing dishes after a party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 04:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So loud all the time!  But it looks like you guys are always having so much fun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 02:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After I clicked the link I thought to myself "better not be a dog pic".  Nice view! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 05:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> V8 supercars are awesome!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 04:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea!  Where did all this stuff come from and what was before it?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 04:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it was like being in the Matrix, time slowed down and the other guy was moving in slow motion but I was moving and thinking extra fast.  I was maybe in 9th grade at the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 04:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taking Fire on the discovery channel...it's as real as TV can get. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 04:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Starts with an H and ends with an E...5 letters total </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 04:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edmonton? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 01:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure he meant a bowl of oatmeal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 03:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sea wolf...the arcade game where you look through the fake periscope at the pizza place.  http://www.pinrepair.com/arcade/seawolf.htm
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 05:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been retired for 2 years now after doing 20 in the AF.  I didn't get shot at or was never in any danger so with that said...I'm used to coming to work and thinking of the 100 things I have to do once I get there, not any more.  I don't miss that part at all.  I miss being around a group of people that wanted to get shit done so we could cut out early on Friday.  Now I work for the railroad and it is the complete opposite mindset...don't do too much work because you will make everyone we look bad.  It's their fault they look bad.  I miss having a competent support system for solving issues.  Now you have some fucktard who is related to someone higher up fucking everything up and nothing ever gets done.  I swear I felt like I was surrounded by retards for the first year and a half but then realized these guys have given up on life and don't give a shit, it's really strange.  Another thing, I'm used to moving every 4-5 years and I used to start getting in a rut after being at a place for 3 years.  I find it very strange to think of being in the same place FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE.  It's hard for me to blend into the community where I have settled down in because I don't have anything in common with anyone so it seems.  I'm sure I will get used to it eventually or perhaps run off to Alaska...it's awesome there and Texas sucks.  Ok I'm done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 05:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a show on TV called drugs inc, I make my kids watch it whenever I see it on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 05:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Walking off the field with my diploma... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 17:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think of it this way...now the kids don't have to grow up with junkies for parents, they actually dodged a life bullet right here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 06:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had more broken teeth than collar bones...teeth are bones also. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 05:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I was very lucky to get it.  I also have an old large pipe wrench that I got out of my grandfathers barn after he died, I've even had to use it a couple of times.  Same here, my great-great grandfather and great grandfather were both farmers in southwest Michigan, my grandfather was a construction electrician and my dad was an electrician and I'm an electrician on locomotives.  I was fortunate enough to have been around my grandfather quite a bit when I was a kid and he taught me the value of hard work and how to take care of things to make them last.  These old saws are the epitome of hard work because that is all they had to cut firewood to keep their family warm during the winter.  We take chainsaws and power tools for granted now days because that's all we know, I like using these old tools for what they were intended for and it reminds me of working with my grandfather.  But you are right, these old tools were built to last unlike most of the plastic junk they have out there now.  Companies have figured out the planned obsolescence part and design this crap to only last a few years until it breaks therefore keeping them in business.  Almost all of the old farmers have sold out to corporate farms in our area of Michigan which is too bad but that's the way it is.  Anyway I'm glad to see younger people (I'm 41) interested in this stuff as well.  It was good talking to you and have fun with your saw project! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 04:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the one I have:  https://imgur.com/a/pfb0M  Good luck with your saw, you never know someone might buy it for that much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 02:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you heard of a website called crosscutsawyer.com?  I think the forums are dead but they have a bunch of good archived info on saws.  They have vintage catalogs and I was able to ID my saw from their 1953 catalog.  The No 113 in the ebay ad has a curved back and the No 13 has a straight back (mine has a straight back).  Mine is nowhere near the condition of the eBay saw, that one looks like new!  But yea, mine doesn't have any rust but it's not shiny either and the handles are in great shape, it's still pretty sharp too.  I plan on handing it down to my son when he gets older, he is 7 now so I'm going to have it for a while.  I make sure to take it down off the wall and oil it down every once in a while to keep it looking good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 18:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also have a saw that was passed down to me.  It's a Simonds No 13 crosscut two man saw that originally belonged to my great-great grandfather who was born in 1879 and died in 1928.  I thought about cleaning it up and sharpening it but not sure if I want to ruin the patina because it was well taken care of and used quite a bit.  You can see where they had to make the teeth longer by filing down the gullets and it is still sharp enough to cut with.  I'll probably leave it alone for now and keep an eye out for a one man saw like you have to practice on.  Let us know how it turns out if you do restore your one man saw and how many hours it took.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 06:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never actually restored a saw but was thinking about doing one so I did some research.  I saw somewhere a guy used a lanskey stone and some kerosene to get it nice and shiny again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 18:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This would be the way to do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 18:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's complete BS, that is nothing short of a cop out on your own children.  If my kids ever get mad at me for disciplining them they will soon realize their mistake.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 06:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had the same "problem" for a while when I was around 16-18, I never really noticed it but my friends did.  I just thought it was normal so didn't worry about it.  Way later I was diagnosed with dysthymia and that's probably what it was when I was younger.  I'm fine most of the time but when I'm under stress for a prolonged period I start having issues.  Just keep hanging out with your friend and go do fun stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 06:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did some acid and Satan approached me (didn't see him but he talked to me) he offered me the power of night vision and it actually worked because I was walking around my basement with the lights off and I could see everything.  However I knew better than to trust him and decided to go with the good side and a feeling of overwhelming peace and tranquility covered me and I knew I had made the right choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 05:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joined the military and retired from that at age 39 and my retirement pay is $24k per year for the rest of my life.  Now I work at the railroad making $30 an hour and will get a pretty good pension from this some day on top of my military retirement.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 04:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I joined the military to get away from my loser friends and dead end job.  Best decision I ever made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 04:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same way you found the dog yesterday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 04:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was actually propositioned by some Walmart hookers, they were even wearing sweat pants lol!  It was when I lived in Las Vegas so go figure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 04:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The autobahn with no speed limit...although Americans will never be able to follow the rules so it would work right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 02:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And we all eat cheese burgers!  I know I do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 02:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at the rich guy and his water.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 02:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A simple "yes" or "no".  If you are being asked a direct question, do yourself a favor and do not ramble on.  This will make you look like you are trying to hide something.  I've had to question people before and most of the time after I asked the question and someone gave a short "yes" or "no" I would deliberately pause for a little bit to create the awkward silence.  Most people can't resist the urge to say something and that is when they let more info slip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 02:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, I don't trust anyone unless I already know you and then you have to earn my trust. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 02:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only gay if you like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 02:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I already have AIDS now bend over boy" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 01:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 6' 1/4" but I just say I'm six feet tall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 01:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Release the demon seed!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 01:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And then Hitler tried it again after Napoleon had failed...stupid Hitler. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 01:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carried a sawed off shotgun and some weed in my car...luckily didn't get caught.  The gun by itself was a felony and add drugs into the mix and you never know how the judge is feeling you might get to do some time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 23:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My kids will watch videos on YouTube of other kids/adults playing Minecraft.  Then they will replicate what they just saw...YouTube is great for teaching yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 05:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A video of a Russian soldier getting his head sawed off.  Seen that shit like 15 years ago and still remember the sound he made through his new throat opening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 05:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm willing to bet the meme thing will be over soon.  It will be called post meme. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 05:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why run?  You will only die tired...I'm staying home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 04:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You assume too much.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 02:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I joined the Air Force when I was 19 and it was the best decision I have ever made.  It was that or stay in a dead end job making $7 an hour with my loser friends.  I got to see the world and I learned a trade that landed me a job after I retired from the military.  Also I was able to transfer my GI bill to my kids so they can go to college and hopefully have more choices than I did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 02:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's all he knows folks, please pitty the fool for for he knows not what he is similar to pigs not knowing they smell like shit.  Baiting the troll, been doing it for years kid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 02:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Learn how to fight MMA and go on to win the championship.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 01:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm all for the death penalty in this case.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 01:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go away troll. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 01:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you expect, during war people get killed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 23:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean common conspiracy theory, not knowledge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 21:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a terrible website...full of ads </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 06:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trucks are better...in Texas! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 06:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck her right in the pussy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 06:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pop that pussy by 2 live crew...album was called as nasty as they wanna be, I think </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 06:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well here we are then, somebody needs a girlfriend and somebody needs a boyfriend...now kiss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 06:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would punch my old boss in the face with a 2x4 turned sideways right in the teeth...hate that guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 04:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HERO with Jet Li!  Awesome music, awesome cinematography, awesome fight scenes, awesome plot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 04:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They got the sound right and some tactics were thrown in...best fake gunfight out there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 02:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spread lye on the floor, it will burn their legs off.  My dad did it to a rat infestation under our shed and it worked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 01:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's just like, your opinion, man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 07:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talk to my union rep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 07:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That fucker is sleeping outside tonight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 05:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's good to hear because I don't check on my kids Internet usage.  According to my grand parents I was raised on TV, now my kids are being raised on the Internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 05:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or has wifi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 03:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Insanely" "hand-crafted" "up-cycled"  Try one of our insanely hand-crafted pita sandwiches made from pure up-cycled beef products.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 02:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your point sounds like what Walmart did.  They were able to out compete other grocery stores by having the most efficient supply chain which in turn allowed them to lower their prices.  Let's say there was a cap on businesses.  Walmart would probably only be in Arkansas but now the other, higher priced stores are still in business elsewhere taking in the money because they can raise their prices as high as they want since there is no competition from other stores.  Bottom line, caps would stagnate competition and prices would soar.  All bad for the consumer (me and you). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 02:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You also need to remember these guys were taken away from their country as a collective group and they were rationalizing to each other how they were going to act in front of the Englishmen.  In other words they were getting their stories straight in order to get better treatment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 02:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The spin:  Why should I bust my ass to accumulate all of this wealth and CREATE JOBS just to give some lazy people a free ride?  Do you think I have some vault full of gold coins that I swim around in all day?  No!  My money is tied up in assets such as my factory where I employ hard working Americans that are not laying around their free house provided by the government.  If we were to give hand outs to everyone out country would cease to be the world superpower that it is.  Need I say more? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 02:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just declare all "illegal aliens" US citizens then tax them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 01:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With your infant sized penis... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 01:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lightly salted peanuts, not the ones covered in sugar.  Those little mini cheese wheels.  Sardines. Smoked oysters.  Fig newtons.  Kippered herring.  Baby carrots.  Raisins.  Apples.  Those mini oranges.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 01:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do all my own work on my cars except wheel alignment so all that stuff.  If I layed it all out on the floor in my garage you wouldn't be able to walk without stepping on anything but it is pretty small.  I also like old vintage tools to hang in my garage.  My favorite tool is a two man saw that my great-great grandfather owned and used to cut firewood with back in the day.  My newest tool is a manifold gage set for residential air conditioning, I just used it today to put more refrigerant in my system.  I only buy stuff as I need it.  The way I see it, if I can buy the tools and do it myself to save money then that's what I'm going to do.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 01:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Milwaukee cordless for me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 00:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe switch it up and play hard to get </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 00:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the big screen tv and pile of money lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 06:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not the destination, it's the journey.  I would love to bike pack the alaska highway and live in Alaska. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 06:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mustang valley would be one of those life changing journeys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 17:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You test the gay porn and I'll test the straight porn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 07:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about a super advanced AI robot that knows it's dying? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 06:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They go for $1 on eBay with free shipping </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 06:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was way ahead of the time and didn't even know it.  I was the only one in my school that listened to death metal, hardly anybody else had even heard of it at the time.  Bands like Napalm Death, Obituary, Grave, Cannibal Corpse.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 05:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, keep your hands where they can see them.  Second, answer the question truthfully and treat them with respect.  This greatly increases your chances of getting only a warning if you were speeding.  Don't listen to these guys telling you to act like a smart ass and start asking the cop questions.  This will only escalate the situation against you.  The goal is to be nice and not give them any more reason to look further into what you are doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 05:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Invent a carbon absorbing machine to reverse the effects of global warming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 05:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Q:  why do birds fly south for the winter?  A:  because it's too far to walk! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 05:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you 100%.  Snowden did nothing but undermine the security of our nation and weaken our position as the number one superpower.  He should be extradited and brought to trial as the criminal he is.  This way if it is deemed he actually helped our country he will be absolved of any wrongdoing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 05:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I'm talking about.  Tweakers can't be reasoned with, just burn their shit down and the cops probably won't even care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 05:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pixel...my daughter plays minecraft </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
