<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1137</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 13:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the FPS good at 1080p? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [question] Logitech 930c for ASMR videos? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 12:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was planning to buy an Logitech 930c, but i was wondering if it can record at 60 FPS on either 720p or 1080p?

And when its at 1080p, does it at least record in 30 FPS?
I will also be buying a Blue Yeti because the mic on the camera is probably bad.

Any help is appreciated! :) Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Logitech 930c? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 12:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please Help! Logitech 930c or 920c for Simple youtube videos?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 00:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys,

Im gonna start making videos for my channel again, but i need a new camera. 

I was thinking of the Logitech 930c since im on a budget and i dont really need the best of the best.

But i was wondering, can the 930c record 1080p with 60FPS? Or does it have to be 720p when recording with 60FPS?

Thanks!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Draw my Anime character! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 01:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there! I've had a character in my mind for so long, and i've designed this charcter over a long time, in order to become awsome! The big problem is, that i can draw at all :(

Thats where i need your help! Anyone out there who can draw Anime characters! Now to explain my characters Personality (If it matters): His name is Hinoru. He is a quitet calm man in his 30's. He travels the world alone. He enjoys strong alcohol and smoking his pipe. Not too many people know who he is by appearance, but his name has made its way all across the world. He is said to be the strongest man in the world, but noone really knows, since no human knows how his power works. Noone who has fought him have ever lived to talk about it. He is not a bad person. He travels in order to destroy evil, not just your every day evil like bandits, etc. Real hell evil. Vampires, sadistic murder clans, etc. He saves small villages from evil creatures and people. He never takes credits for doing any of this, he never asks for anything in return, he simply leaves. 

Now that you have a small image of what kind of dude my character is, this might help you draw him(?). Now over to the appearance, i have taken inspiration from alot of my favorite characters from different shows when constructing this character in my head. Here is a link to an Imgur album i made, wich contain all the characters i have taken inspiration from, and so it could help you draw my character: 

Imgur Album Link: http://imgur.com/a/JAGzt 

Now to the details: Body shape: Hinoru is a average tall man, he is not extremely tall but he aint short either. The 3rd Kazekages body shape is pretty much perfect, but Hinoru would be more muscular. 
Eyes: I always loved how the 3rd Kazekages eyes so these are pretty much perfect. (And yes the black around the eyes can be added too). 
Scars: No visible. Hair: The 3rd Kazekages hair also fits good. would be nice if it could be a bit more thick. Clothing: 
Hat: No hat. 
Jacket/Coat: I love the 2nd Mizukages kimono, i would love this but with different colors. Black with white stripes.
Under Jacket/coat: Just add some simple dark grey T-shirt or something, i dont really like the 2nd Mizukages dark green sweater. Pants: I like the casual 4th Kazekage, his pants would probably work fine. 
Shoes/Legs: I would like Hinoru to have Luffys sandals and the ''Bandages'' stuff at the same place as the 4th kazekage has it. Gloves: No gloves. Scroll: I would like him to have a big scroll haning from his back like Jiraiya has. 

Thanks! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 16:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Men for alle dere som vil se flere bilder som disse fargelagt, bli med i facebook gruppa mi "Nordiske Militr Samlere" s kommer de i fleng! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 14:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahah takk :) , fr nok vente litt fikk nettopp advarsel fra Admin her p siden at jeg ikke m poste s mange like bilder :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Norske Soldater passerer Grendi, under invasjonen av Norge 1940. (Fargelagt) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 12:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 12:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much! How can i credit you if i post this one facebook? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 08:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bare hyggelig :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Free] Pilots from the Norwegian 332 Squadron and their Mascot Goat (Mads). 1942. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 23:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 23:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Skal prve  f det til :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 20:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> S mange modige karer gikk bort :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 20:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dette er han som fargela bildet: 

reddit.com/u/CanadianColours </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 20:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> De er det alts! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Norske soldater i sterdalen, under invasjonen av Norge 1940. (Fargelagt) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 20:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Free] Norwegian Soldiers passing by Grendi, during the invasion of Norway 1940. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 15:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 15:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 15:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will do, thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Norske Soldater i Dirdal, 1940 mens de gjr seg klare for tyske styrker. (Fargelagt) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 14:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 12:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Btw is there any way i can credit you if i post the colored one on Facebook? Want people to know that you did this job and not me :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 12:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Btw is there any way i can credit you if i post the colored one on Facebook? Want people to know that you did this job and not me :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Free] Three Norwegian Soldiers taking a break, 1940 During the invasion of Norway. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 15:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 14:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much! You did an amazing job!! ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
