<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1417</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's my first professionally shot gig, it was at a BBC competition. I didn't win but still had a great time. Let me know what you think. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-24 11:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 15:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That reminds me of a story I heard when I was viewing Universities. One of the students doing a tour of the campus told a story about people being really protective over their food stuffs in shared accommodation and one student thought his milk would be safe by leaving a note on it saying 'I've spat in this milk' and when he went back the next day there was another sign saying 'so have I.'

I never went to that Uni... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-18 11:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It makes me wonder how much advertising we subconsciously fall for every day without realising it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-04 11:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This doesn't look to have to same humour as the original. It looks like it's going to straight up scares which isn't what the original was all about. Then again it was a film of its time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-03 18:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember listening to his 'Funhouse' show on Spotify at work and literally crying with laughter the first time round. He's utterly hilarious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-03 14:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever thought that he's actually a constant. He's actually the same guy in all of these things and ties their universes together... just a thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-19 15:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well fuck me, that's one awesome commercial.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-09 15:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How had I forgot about Breakbot?!?! Thank you good sir I've got my afternoon is [set](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z85p4_nhXys feature=related) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-09 11:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The longer the BWAAA the greater the dread](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gvaszet0-WA#t=0m08s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-09 11:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The longer the BWAAAAA the greater the sense of dread](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gvaszet0-WA#t=0m08s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 19:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the subtle background touches like the circles all joined by a line, be it the film reels in the background or the design on the carpet, little things you wouldn't realise were filtering into your mind but the whole time influencing your thought. I think Derren is amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Derren Brown tricks Simon Pegg. Check out the subtle language and hints in the background. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 17:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-22 11:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonder what the dancers were thinking? "Yay, they like us" or "Are we going to get gang raped here?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-22 11:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of Madeon's remixes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-19 15:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Relevant](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EbUjTOhFBTk feature=plcp
) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-25 11:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link to the [video](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IwcTiuxzqv0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-07 12:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to post this myself but it said you'd already done so. I can't see how it didn't get picked up on here. It's awesome. So more karma for you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-07 12:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't know how I feel about this, a load of prisoner doing the hustle. Are they forced to do this? Do they get their sentence reduced? How are they so awesome? Where I can join? All these questions and more swirl round my tiny little mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fucking hilarious Irish, rapping comedy duo - The Rubber Bandits Live in Edinburgh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-03 17:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 18:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to take a heckler apart (starts at around 2mins) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 13:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-17 17:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Un-fucking-believable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Serious WTF comedy - Keith the Magic Homeless </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-16 19:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-09 14:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved the Address Unknown side story, I always sat by every TV to hear the episode. It added something else to the universe of the game that just made it stand out for me. Also I would watch Address Unknown if it was a real show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-05 11:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know I would freak out if that happened to me, very much like that guy did I suppose. As for Trick or Treat I think there are a few videos on YouTube, it was a pretty entertaining series.

EDIT: Here's a Trick or Treat video where he turns people into statues - http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8KNakFGU_b8 I can never tell if it's fake or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-05 11:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually not one for London gangland films, Danny Dyer and his ilk ruined it for best part of a decade but that actually looks really good. The lead looks like a believable hard bastard. Also like the way it's shot. Will have to check this out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-27 16:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah cool, be good to meet a fellow redditor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you guys think of the Promo for my new Edinburgh Show? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-27 11:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-26 18:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A similar thing happened to a good friend of mine and he handled it like a [king](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=y4wY3ItGvyc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What.the.fuck? A Family Guy Porno with Ron Jeremy... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-19 11:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-14 19:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok now that is a film I would pay to see. Even if Link does get his face re-arranged. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-14 18:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't say they're 'crazy' facts but more interesting fact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-12 18:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel so welcome on Zombocom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the funniest websites I've seen in ages </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-12 17:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-08 12:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God damn that's hot! I need some time alone to think about what I just saw and how I feel about it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-06 20:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's the audio played through her phone or Derren says something. I think gassing her would've made this trick a bit *too* real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-01 14:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know much about Castlevania as a series but this looks pretty awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-23 09:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [What ya doing in the mulch, ya mulch fuck](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RKjYLQp60Xg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spitting Lady Interupts News Report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-22 10:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-18 18:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks man, means a lot :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-18 17:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a stand up and so is Luke McQueen although I don't know him. I've posted [videos](http://www.reddit.com/r/StandUpComedy/comments/lkbty/i_beat_a_night_which_encourages_the_audience_to/) of me doing stand up. I don't know Luke personally but my mate does, he's the one who passed this onto me. You can Columbo it all you like I've got nothing to hide. I don't believe it's viral but if it is I've been duped.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I've got a nice c*nt though ain't I?" - World's classiest girl on the train...  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-18 15:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-18 15:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend showed me and the first video I thought it was entertaining and might in some way work but then he sent me this one I just sat opened mouthed and though "You've fucked it there mate...." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-18 14:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's mates with a friend of mine, the story is mad. He drunkenly kissed a girl at a party and then told his girlfriend (i think the very next day) and she left him. He was mortified so he did [this](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I3sZohPeu1M feature=relmfu) then followed it up with this latest video but still hasn't heard back from her.

I thought it was admirable at first but this latest video is just awful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guy cheats on Girlfriend and tries to win her back in the WORST way possible! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-18 13:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-14 12:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to cuddle the shit out of that little bundle of joy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-08 16:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure there's a song about this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-08 11:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Dad told me about when he bought this album from the record shop and it was a really cold and icy day and he took almost an hour to walk home as he only took tiny baby steps so he wouldn't risk falling over and breaking the record. 

It meant so much when he gave it the to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is a pretty cool YouTube channel all about Wine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-08 11:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not sure which subreddit this should go in but this tune is amazing - Juiceboxxx and Dre Skull - Center Stage (Curses! Remix) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-04 18:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-02 13:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cacao to cacao! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-01 17:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well to be fair Edinburgh was much rowdier but I figured that was just the festival. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-01 16:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that the reputation we have? I do the London circuit and I've not been heckled that much, I say on average it's about 1 in 8 gigs you get someone mouth off but even then they're not often aggressive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-25 16:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I won a free computer game by getting the high score on this level at my local games store. I never had the game but everyday on the way home from school I played it. I chose The Thing fro XBOX. Ah man the memories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-24 13:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah man I hope you're still going!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-24 10:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now with ultimate 'Night Sweats' mode and 'Divorce' setting for when your spouse just *"Doesn't know you any more!"* **WAR!!!!!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-23 14:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing video, although I do kinda feel like this music would make you feel guilty every time you shot someone...which is not why I play games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-20 09:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sir make a very good point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-19 13:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're gonna need a bigger....moat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-19 11:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair I think the Portal gun wins out if you put it like that, I'd never seen anything like the Cerebal Bore and was blown away by it...then again I was like 13, so maybe you're right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-19 11:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but to me the gravity gun, laptop gun and cerebal bore are imaginative, you really thought 'wow' when you first used it. The others are just powerful...although the Chainsaw will always be very cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you think is the most imaginative weapon in a game? My favourite will always be the Cerebal Bore from Turok 2. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-19 11:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-19 10:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Britain the norm is your GF would give you a mean look and tear you a new one when you're home. I personally have never had to carry my gf away from another woman...then again I've never had a hot pottery teacher talk filthy to me, but I can dream. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This guys girlfriend goes mental at slutty pottery maker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-18 18:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-18 18:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you answered your own question there... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-18 18:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't care this already is front page, take more of love and upvotes!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-17 18:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no other way of putting it, this is fucking AWESOME!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-13 14:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOVE LOVE LOVE this! The bit where her eyes light up at 0:42....amazing!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I caught a bartender doing this I'd go fucking mental! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-12 11:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-11 16:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This takes me to my happy place </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-11 14:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This used to get stuck in my head all the time at the worst possible moments. Playing rugby, when taking exams....during sex. 

Humming never helped things either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RIP PAT BUTCHER! :'( </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-10 17:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My mate makes awesome videos of American history. Time to learn about the motherfucking Panama Canal! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-13 17:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-08 16:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a similar one, "Finland....really? Ok then."

Best weekend of my life! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-08 15:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Well played](http://assets0.ordienetworks.com/images/GifGuide/clapping/taxidriver.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-22 10:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-22 10:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been at it 2 years this month but that video was from 4 months ago, I've done Edinburgh festival since and feel a lot more confident. I'm back at the Comedy Store this month and really excited/nervous. Should be fun though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I beat a night which encourages the audience to boo at The Comedy Store, London. It was a scary experience! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-21 22:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-30 11:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a stand up Comic on the London Circuit and if anyone did that they'd get fucking crucified. I've witnessed it myself, one guy kept coming to clubs doing Bill Hick material thinking no-one would know. At comedy clubs you have comedians and comedy fans, watching comedy is what they love, so chances are someone in the crowd will know the material and chances are that person will be drunk or proud enough to call the thief out on it.

I'm pleased it was so shit, the guy is a thief with no real talent. It angered me what the final judge said. If your own material is shit, don't do comedy. Don't try to make a living or get praise for other peoples hard work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
