<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject350</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-24 14:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problems, dont worry mate. Thanks for your help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-24 00:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh and Antipodes an Aussie/Kiwi cafe? esp with a Flat White on the menu! Can always count on an Australian cafe for good coffe but I may be biased. Will def check it out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-24 00:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, couldnt have gone to Nuremberg although wanted to, decided on Berlin because the museums! and they are mostly open. Got us tickets to the Reichstag too.. so happy about that! 

Thanks for your info, seems to be panning out OK now isnt it. I'm Googling and saving all your links, much appreciated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-24 00:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really, if you wouldnt mind.. haha go on then.. table for 2 on the 26th (if open?) for Kay, please. I've ordered in Thai, Czech and Malay at previous occassions before.. survived so far :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-24 00:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And its not far from where I am staying, thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 23:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 23:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *spine chills* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Put our Christmas tree up earlier and puppy jumped up next to it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 23:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 23:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much. I Googled before and seemed like things would be open etc. Plus it's our first Christmas here and thought it'd be a good time to see Berlin. Obviously not my brightest moment. 

Like you said not much I can do now. Still keen to have a good time so will try and make the best of whatever is open. Between your suggestions and others I think it might just be OK. I've just finished reading the lonely planet Berlin guidebook and getting really pumped. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 17:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thought I'd ring and get a reservation. But the lady on the other end didn't speak any English and I don't speak any German. Great socially awkward moment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 10:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously Samsung loves making these really bad tech ads. Anyone remember the Beckham one for s3.i mean what in the whatever was that..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 10:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, always in need of a good suggestion for a local restaurant. Not far from my hotel either. Excellent. Thanks very much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 17:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They shall not take my fapp rights away </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 17:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't sound very promising. Perhaps a bad timed trip awaits us? At least they're keeping a few markets open for tourists like us. Also got tickets for the reichstag as it's open and some museums never close too. It's just that I think the trendier side of things would be shut down. 

When I trawled through TripAdvisor some weeks ago the general feel was that most of Berlin stays open.. 
Surely McDonald's would be romantic that night then :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
