<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1499</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 10:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of Peter the Great from Russia actively discouraging beards among the nobility at one point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 10:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not too sure if turkey at the moment is still a democracy or a "democracy" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 10:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should see the numbers for WWI and WWII east front, furthermore Stalin's purges, they vary a good deal too but it doesn't change the fact that it happened </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 10:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude... don't advocate killing another human for their beliefs. Or belittle people's deaths for any reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 08:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reraise only made him cast it again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 08:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used Cait sith: toy solider, Aerith: white materia, Ystoll: wall, Gabreth(Basch brother): his BSB, and Firon: weapons master. RW shout.

I had slowly, very slowly out healed and out mitigated the dmg while ever so slowly picked each one of them off. It helped to have status resist accessories. I mastered it surprisingly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 09:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rule of thumb is don't pull if you can clear all content for that specific realm. (I would also add pull if you need to open up more characters for different strategies) 

Plus anniversary banners are around the corners, I done how have 190 mirthyl saved for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 08:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stalin was a manipulative Bastard who went from somewhat paranoid to full-blown paraboid. Let's go before Stalin possed all the power, when Lenin was alive. Lenin did not want Stalin to come into power, I forgot what particular reasons, however Stalin manipulated people around Lenin to prevent orders and information that would hurt Stalin from reaching other ears. After Lenin died Stalin would kill off his potential rivals to assume power. He later even killed off his allies over time that supported him to power. 

Now there were some positive outcomes that came out of this, such as later when fighting a bloody war against Germany dissent was squashed and treason kept low, allowing a 'harder' response to Germany. Was it worth it, potentially the reason Russia could fight such a war? Up to you to decide, I kinda avoid what-if history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 11:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would think that it was free and the owner was giving it away, and then take it and disassemble it for engine parts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 11:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slightly bugs me that they used Russian letters to produce English sounds rather than having a Russian translation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 10:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are probably not down voting because of a vendetta, it's more to inform further readers that what he said was false. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 09:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude just listen to /u/quelar he is not trying to insult your pride or anything, he is just keeping the subreddit the way it should be </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 09:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Red XII, he is my only decent 5-star sup with a SB (protector's roar; which I can never decide if it's good or bad) I know he is a fairly strong charecter all round but I dislike using him and feel that he is a waste of my slots (he isn't but I feel that way) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 04:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what the radiation? The bombs were popped mid-air so it didn't last as long as you think (though the radiation in the aftermath was quite a sum even if it relatively didn't last long)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 03:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 22:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much of sucidal thoughts are brain chemistry vs the persons *will*? Best I could phrase it. How some sucidal inclined people can be talked out of it while others need meds. Furthermore do they *need* meds? Or is it something to hasten turning the person's mentality away from sucidal thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 22:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marking this thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 10:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got a concussion from falling backwards on concrete around my own height, was pretty bad too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 09:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The story and detail in each environment was also great, many places you would never have to go into for the main story but were there for you to explore. (Though the first time I went into the Necrohall I got nearly wiped in a few seconds) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 09:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are not alone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 09:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny myfirst play through  'A' team centered around wakka, kimahri, Auron, and tidus as a substitute. I never used Riki  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 09:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the subreddit https://www.reddit.com/r/FFRecordKeeper/ 

   The community is fairly helpful, and the community resources are well organized. On top of that it's anniversary is in march so it's a great time to start with all the extra stuff everyone is getting. 

   One Con it's a gacha game but even if you get the worst weapons and everything it's only a small drop in penalty provided you follow the right strategy and not try to steam roll things later on. 

   It's fairly generous with giving you 'mirthyl' that you use on the gacha to acquire good gear and weapons. Plus it's guaranteed if you save 50 mirthyl that you will get at least 1 good gear/weapon. However mirthyl is constantly handed out and it's not unreasonable to get 200 mirthyl in one day if you have a lot of spare time, (especially easy if you are just starting out) I average around 8 mirthyl a day but I only spend 10-15 min a day playing.

   Oh there's also a multiplayer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 09:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah the opening blitz ball scene. Brilliant music. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shame he met his end to a duel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was he the one who died? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 08:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember the first time I played winning with a last ditch kimari self destruct </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 09:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Care likely said cannibalism did not happen for reasons mentioned in the article. At least for that particular siege  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 10:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow I'm surprised, though it does explain why it felt that his writing was on a low level, at least the few books I have read by him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 10:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah when wars and revolutions sponsored by various countries were for the greater good on the surface but below the surface... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 10:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While emotional people might start agreeing with you more if you verbally assault who you are debating with, I would recommend that you refrain from doing so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 10:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I wouldn't put it past people to adopt an idea that is an existential threat to the country, i.e. "Global warming is a hoax" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 10:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bolstered most of the population in a minority of countries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 10:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this thing a bot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 10:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was he being sarcastic? I never learned whether Orwell was a modernist or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 09:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *jokingly* I find it a bad sign that he is already campaigning to get reelected before he is even in office for a year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 04:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am confused on what do you mean "bagged on the state of airports before." Do you mean bagged as in negatively affected? Or bagged as in complained about airports?

And why I think trump will not benefit the state of CA is he has no reason to do so in my opinion.  The majority of CA voters have no love for trump. In my opinion he is not a man of character that will benefit others without cause, instead I perceive him as vengeful given his ongoing feud with judicial courts and media. (Particularly concerning for me is trump's labeling media as 'the enemy of the people' somewhat reminiscent of demagogues such as Mao and self-obsessed dictators such as Stalin) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interested thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed it's only the spillway, though it's easier to lump it together with the dam, apologies for any confusion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No trump won't, at most we will have a wall built despite if the funding was diverted to better projects it would benefit more people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And not imperial  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 23:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before Azir went to shit, I used to cringe whenever someone rushed a nasher's tooth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 22:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's near maximum capacity, and it's not the only dam on that river </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 22:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CA invested quite a lot in water management, furthermore CA is investing even more; the thing about the dam failing? I'm putting that down to whoever is in charge of the dam's fault or plain bad luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 09:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to exercise my friend  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 06:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not as viable vs a regime that has no ethics in my opinion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 21:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enchant totem? Check

Kunka AoE attack? Check

Any invis? Check

Walrus punch? Check

You are now good to go to kill all of the enemy in 1 hit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 10:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked most of the tactics naming sense, though I agree you on the machinist. In my head he has always been mustardo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 10:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It makes sense if it was after John Locke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 10:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly thought more of blorg from stellarsis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 06:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The crater /u/thisisveryright posted a link https://youtu.be/te-ihMHRtJ8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 06:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Took me only 20 or so tries (but this was on an emulator playing at 30% speed) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 05:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before it was on steam I ran it on an emulator and and would run at 600% speed at times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 05:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really gets you into the game, I also enjoyed X from how badass the music was and how well it fit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 05:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dam I was cut between X and XII

X intro music (other world? By blackmages) is really good, I use it as an alarm clock.

EDIT: Maybe not black mages, perhaps the song was mislabeled? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 05:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dam why do people put so much effort in this things? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 04:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before the Nazis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 04:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was entertaining </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 04:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *shrugs* it must have been cheaper or something, very few, possible none, towns/cities are designed for no reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 04:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know there was one dropped of the Canada coast which they never found. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 04:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like slave empires and will often modify the populations of my planets to trailer to each planet for a specific purpose, where I can build tier one of whatever resource building and leave it to a sector knowing it won't screw up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 02:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So space AIDs was spread </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 01:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 01:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Post a few, I'm interested  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 01:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the term </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 01:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At /r/programerhumor someone a while posted something similar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 01:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I instead of planets with a single focus in mind, creatively named Mineing, energy, and science 1,2,3,...

The planets focus only on one thing to get the most out of multipliers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 00:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the AI can get the "science ship goes to another dimension and comes back altered" event.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 00:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was really cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 23:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what my parents told me, while some did drink it, it wasn't the majority. The ones who did were looked down and thought to be slightly unstable/ dumb. (I'm not the best translator) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 18:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had made a mistake in mentioning the M line in WW1, I knew France had did some fortifications but did not realize that it was not the M line, apology for the confusion I caused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 18:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most cities start as rural farming towns that just expand over time, few of these towns before modern times 'planned' their expansion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 18:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bots are useful but I think they are triggered just a little too much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 18:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed there was more damage, I'm just a proponent of nuclear power and feel obliged to correct misconceptions on radiation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 18:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So pretty much like Russian serfs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 09:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Took me until the ship to understand how to activate mobility mode, when j started to use a steam controller. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 09:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now he must redo it just because of a split second... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 08:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my games my team only goes for it if bot is getting camped or we are so afar ahead we get it just cause. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 08:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 reasons I can think of at the moment,

 1st volcanoes tend to form near fault lines, volcanic soil is very fertile great for farming, further more mines is a possibility.

2nd fault lines near coastal areas, coastal areas are great in a commercial sense as coastal area's weather is more stable and year round temperatures as well, ports are really good as it's cheaper to move across water. In some cases salt production. And tourism

3rd oil potentially, not sure if it's Due to chance or caused by fault lines but there are quite a few oil reserves near faultlines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 07:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Multiple drugs at the same time can have serious complications </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 06:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was due to puritanical roots they wanted religious freedom. They were persecuted and the founders probably did not want that. Note that there are many sects especially at the time of Christianity, some which would oppress the others given the chance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 06:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a bot if you ever mention vict0rs. Wr1te history it will pop up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 06:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neither am I </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 06:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They popped the bombs mid air to increase explosive AoE, a side effect of doing that meant the ground was much less radioactive. They rebuilt the cities not too long after WW2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 05:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone make this into an actual remix? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 05:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I I know it wasn't poor but it's a target </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 05:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 05:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only time to use K-bullets is when a plane is disabled and in the midst of repairs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the way how the Germans went around the line caused Briton to enter the war. (Belgian, Germany invaded neutral Belgian to go around but Belgian was under the protection of Briton... so Briton declared war on Germany) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Eve teasing?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was recorded in ancient China about a supernova appearing in the sky, it was so bright that it was brighter than the moon. Wonder how they felt about that around the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 11:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's pretty cool thing. I like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 11:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking about doing a ffX torment run with, Aerioth and her BSB, ekiko (IX) and her bsb, ystol and her wall nothing else. Tidus with BSB, and Red X (VII) and protecter's roar. What are my odds of just healing through it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 11:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it rhymes, you are showing off! Bad, bad! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 10:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It took me many many tries to fight the first boss in dark souls 3. After attempt number 35 I got him to half health only to be scared out of my chair to find it transform thinking, nope, dark souls is not for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 10:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some animals in different areas act differently. squirrels in my yard run at the sight of my. In Yosemite I walk away from my car for roughly 20 seconds and come back to find 2 squirrels in my car eating my bread that was in plastic packaging in my car. When I came closer one of them jumped at me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 10:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the gases from decay build up (from bacteria I think?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 10:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anymore? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 10:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was going to post more but coming from an immigrant family it might be different than from the majority. 

Government programs that taught financial management such as look for sales, balance your books, look for coupons, search multiple stores. 

Particularly we came from the USSR where the economy was quite different so my family really benefited from these goverment programs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 10:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? I... I kinda liked that crispy part, I thought it was a nice taste (but too much is sickening) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 10:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read somewhere that he likely did not have it, if you are very interested in this I could try to find it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 09:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I think Oliver bit the bullet for the higher ups </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 09:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Laughter is the best medicine, however if you are laughing for no reason, you need medicine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
