<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2728</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would you break up with your SO? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People of reddit, how did you cope with the stress of school? [SERIOUS] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did you learn to tie your shoes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 02:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the creepiest website you have stumbled across? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 02:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 02:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like i would have had a similar experience if i would have made a move. Last year in my senior year of highschool, one of my teachers would always make eye contact with me for long periods of time, especially if i went up to as a question she would hardly listen and just stare at me. She treated me "better" than other students, would laugh at my jokes, and would always touch my shoulder. Couple of times she made excuses to see me after class. If i was gone she would repatedly ask students where i was, when i would be back etc. However she was engaged and i was in a relationship so i guess we were both reluctant to make any moves and even though other people noticed it as well, i was very skeptical because i didnt exactly know how to deal with a teacher having a crush on me. However, i do always wonder what could have came out of it if one of us had made a move, and slightly regret not doing so. Wrong place wrong time i guess. Maybe one day i can redeem myself, if not with her than another teacher, probably would have been a great experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People of reddit who have had student teacher relations, how did it happen? And was it worth it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 00:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People of reddit, how would you describe reddit to someone who has no idea what it is? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 05:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is one situation you thought you would never get out of, but eneded up working out in the end? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 04:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 04:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first one is the picture perfect breakup thats how i wish all breakups ended up sadly its not like that. Second one hurts man, one of my worst fears is my ex will go with someone she formerly said wasnt a problem or one of my friends. Im sorry to hear about your experience man, but if yhats the way she treats you, its best that you just move on and forget about her. You can do better. And it will get better.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors with a previous SO what was your worst and/or best breakup experience? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 04:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 03:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im talking about the first person...EVER to find out. I know they werent stupid, but they had to find out somehow right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 03:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For one he was definitely smarter then everyone else </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I cant seem to get comfortable in my bed at night, but when i wake up it feels like im on a cloud. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 03:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 03:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Similar to my gf... badoom tss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 02:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much for this advice, helped me realize a few things. Ill try and update you if i can as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 00:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My life dream is not to recieve a pm from you  you are my type jesus! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did you overcome your procrastination? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 00:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 00:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know ive realized this now but the next step is finding the right time to do iy and more importantly how? Ive been with her for almost two years and she was my first, i was not hers. She had a dark past and has some issues that are out of my reach of helping her and they really affect me as well. I just dont know how to bring myself to end it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 23:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have broken up a couple of times but not a real break up if u get what i saying. But the last one was the most serious, she just said we should break up out of no where she was saying how she doesnt really have feeling for me anymore and she admitted shes very manipulative and can get me to do what she wants. But then the next day she blew up my phone saying she wanted me back and stuff and i took her back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do i know if my relationship has run its course? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 23:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My gf [F/18] and i [m/18] (were both almost 19) have been dating for almost 2 years now we met in HS and would see eachother everyday and now that we go to different universities we see eachother only maybe once every 1 or 2 weeks. However i feel like at this point we were only staying with eachother because its kind of comfortable and "routine". I dont really like this and ive confronted her about it before but she always changes her answer. How do you know if a relationship has run its course and when its time to end it? And how do i end it? 

I know i left a lot of details out, so if u would like to know anything else just ask. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your "guardian angel" moment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 23:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 22:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In one of the earlier friday the 13th movies, the guy in the wheelchair was about to get some pussy. Then, jason came out of no where and macheted him in the face and ended up killing the girl...smh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could relive one year of your life, which year would it be and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you just walked into the forest and never saw him again? Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you think your life would be like if your parents NEVER said no to you as a child? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do we feel that to retreat under our covers is safe when we are afraid in our dark rooms at night? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your experiences in the forest/woods? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a paranormal even that occured in your life in which you have no explanation for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like you have a guardian angel, youre very lucky i think we've all had similar experiences. But the fact that it was so vivd to you and no one else saw it is pretty trippy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 08:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just gotta ask...was your glitch in the matrix story about you working at subway true?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
