<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject375</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 00:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there is a way to make it work where you could set Crayak up as the one who sent the Capasins. He played with civilizations all the time, maybe he is the one who influenced the initial attack on Ellimists home world.

That being said, I think the main antagonist of The Ellimist isn't one person, but the perpetual "a new player has joined the game" where after he beats one challenger, a new appears.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 16:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Animorphs has a serialized storyline and a slow progression that would make it hard to do a good stand-alone movie. I imagine you would need a trilogy or some such. If you could convince one of these old curmudgeon movie execs to pay the bills then go for it! But I think that another option could be to put out a stand-alone Ellimist movie that could garner the hype for an eventual Animorphs trilogy. The nostalgia factor could be replaced with curiosity, considering most Animorphs casuals have not read any of the Chronicles series and might want to see what it's about. And if you set up an interesting universe that makes people want to see more, which is what you need to tell the full story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know the image of the Ellimist on the book cover? I think he looks good like that, and seems humanoid enough. You're right though, the CGI effects would cost a fortune! Perhaps the movie could be computer animated? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Ellimist would make a great movie, I think. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 10:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading through this subreddit's archive, it seems as though a potential movie deal for The Animorphs was considered and then shortly thereafter shot down due to perceived disinterest in the series.

I think a remedy for a lack of interest could come from an initial standalone Ellimist movie. The Ellimist, while connected tangentially to The Animorphs, does not necessarily need the context of The Animorphs in order to be a good story.


Roughly speaking, The Ellimist is a gamer who is terrible at games. The whole story revolves around him being challenged by gamers progressively better than himself and getting schooled a bunch of times before finding cunning ways to overcome his enemies. Every time he wins, he just moves on to the next level and encounters a new boss, so to speak. Through his progression from challenger to challenger, he becomes more resolved, wiser, and eventually omnipotent. This is a guy who started out just playing video games for fun in his spare time, and ended up becoming one of the most powerful beings in the universe (that we know of). I think this concept would have mass-appeal to a movie audience, and especially to gamers.

Obviously a few things would have to change. The ending would have to be more conclusive, while not absent of sly references to the Animorphs, it would have to have its own stand-alone conclusion.

If this is successful as it's own movie, we could perhaps see more of The Chronicles series brought to the screen. Again, there would need to be some changes, maybe to the continuity, but they could all work as their own stand-alone movies without any overt reference to the The Animorphs. Then once all of those are done, give it a few years and release The Animorphs on TV/Movie, if there is a demand for it.

The Ellimist is an appealing story for sci-fi fans even if they know nothing about The Animorphs. In the series you explore several different non-humanoid alien species, and planets, that would satiate any sci-fi fan's appetite and potentially the movie could lead the way for others, if there is a demand.

It's rather rare in my perspective for a character who starts out as a less-than-average bloke to make his way through the game of life and come out a Demi-God. Even in some of the better series of our days, like Game of Thrones, everybody has a secret bloodline or prophecy or special skill. Even The Animorphs went this route when we found out that they were probably hand-selected for the job. 

I just think this movie would be received well by the general audience. I'm not saying it would explode at the box office, but might be more of a sleeper hit that tantalizes people in to wondering what else the Ellimist universe has to offer. Even if it is the only movie of the entire series to get made, I would be happy that the story gets told. I think Ellimist's character progression is just super cool, and the world created around him is one that we don't really see much in movie or television. 

What do you think, would you like this idea or is what I just wrote an affront to all you love and hold dear? I catch myself thinking about an Ellimist movie once every few months and I don't exclude the possibility of it happening, we might just have to wait another 20 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not supposed to be an alternative for driving within a city, it's supposed to be a quicker alternative for people to travel from Orlando to Miami, and back. The geography and highway design of Florida makes it a three or four hour drive on a hellish highway to get from one city to the other. As an Orlando native, I have only been to Miami twice because the drive is just that terrible. I could easily see myself going with my girlfriend to Miami for a day or a weekend if it only meant a 30 minute trip. I have reservations about the application of this technology but if it works I would gladly use it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He campaigned on non-interventionist policy, of course his voters would feel duped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
