<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3772</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes, now a days you cant believe anyone, even this is taken everywhere . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brutal punishment system for getting pregnant in Uganda </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Funny Protest against NZ Government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, you can follow those as well . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uber Under Criminal Case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No one will tell you these three initiative ideas if you want to think positive get motivated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay now its time to become inspired if you are thinking that you don't have enough motivation to inspire from, let's try something new but before that let us think what we usually do if want motivation? we read someone's success story , we watch someone's inspirational videos, read motivational quotes etc.
 In this modern world we have everything in front of us to get inspired from and its so easy . but the most important thing is the inner urge what we need most. and we can achieve that urge by doing something very simple. those are-

1. Walking : Yes its an exercise but while walking the hormone that will release , will improve your memory and thinking skills. you can think about a lot of thing. it will improve your contraction on certain things that are going in your mind. 

2. Chewing Gums- really ? are you laughing ? But yes its true, chewing gums actually helps to improve the our brains function. and it will improve our mental health to think positive and creative.

3. Singing in the shower- if you have habit to listen song or singing in the shower then yes, you're in the right track, you will feel motivated that time and your inner you will scream and tell yes I can, you can think about the ideas that are going in your mind, and you can find out the solution. 
these all are psychological matters of our everyday life and if we can make these possible, we can solve anything, so just walk, sing and chew gums.   
    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems he is trying to get the attention of someone but didn't get at all. My poor babe 3  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suddenly when you become famous </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spiderman Home Coming Meme </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Even the suicide is committed but I am single . </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 14:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wowwo  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fascinating Beauty of Twilight [1080X810] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 14:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
