<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2240</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man Who Wrote One Haiku Convinced He's Next Great Poet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 23:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SEATTLE, WA  Brady Adams, 24, wrote a haiku about beer when he was drunk last week, leading him to believe that hes the next Walter White, or Edward Ally Pope, or whatever, he claims. The realization came when his haiku received high praise from his buddies.
	Dude, you gotta read that poem! My mans a genius! exclaimed Bradys college roommate and fraternity brother, Chuggs. Upon hearing his accolades, Mr. Adams immediately sent his haiku to the Poetry Foundation magazine for submission. Unfortunately, his 15 minutes of poetry fame were over.
	It was the worst poetry Ive ever encountered, said Poetry Foundation magazine editor Cornell Bouvier. I cant even use the term poetry for what that nightmare was. As soon as I saw it, I evaluated where Ive gone in my life. I graduated top of my class at Dartmouth, and went on to study the genius of William Shakespeare and Alfred, Lord Tennyson. Now Im reading a haiku, which was nowhere near its traditional form, mind you, about beer that had a sparkling review from a man named Chuggs McFartburger? Its clear now why I submitted my resignation forms, finished Mr. Bouvier.
     At press time, Mr. Adams could not be reached because he is too busy funneling alcohol in preparation for working on the next great American novel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook Boldly Decides To Add A Meh Button </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 23:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MENLO PARK, CA  Facebook founder and CEO Mark Zuckerberg announced today that Facebook will be adding a meh button, in addition to a dislike button, for users who feel total and complete indifference toward various posts. This development comes after a new poll claims that most Facebook users just dont care anymore.
	I think were already the best social media site out there, and this feature just makes us even better! said an overly-excited Mark Zuckerberg. We here at Facebook are proud to do anything, and I mean anything, that makes a users experience more enjoyable, and puts a ton of cash in my pocket! Mr. Zuckerberg finished.
	A recent mandatory Facebook poll entitled How can WE help YOU? was the vehicle for making the discovery. 34-year-old Boston resident and Facebook user Paul Hamilton remembers his time taking the survey. It kept coming up and wouldnt go anywhere, so I just took it. It asked what we wanted changed most and I said that I hate seeing pictures of my friends kids. The kids are cute, my friends are great, but for some reasonGod the button will finally allow me to be me! 21-year-old Tiff Wilson, of Tacoma, Washington, expressed similar sentiments. I hate seeing pictures of meals. If I wanted to see them, Id be eating the food! I love food, but I only use Facebook to stalk my ex, mock my friends, and read the news. This is what has been missing from my life! By the way, hashtag pray for Fetty! she concluded. Cincinnatis Felix Guzman, 39, proved no exception to these feelings. Seeing vacation picturesugh, shoot me now! This is what a meh button is perfect for. On one hand, Barcelona is an awesome city. On the other hand, I didnt go on the trip, and I havent spoken to you since high school, so I dont really wanna see the pictures. The button will be the yin-yang balance Ive been craving.
	At press time, it was discovered that the button had been released to the public. Its first use was a review of this article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Father And Son Both Uncomfortable During The Talk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 22:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TAMPA BAY, FL  Bill Sanders and his 11-year-old son, Doug, have both admitted to feeling uncomfortable last week when Bill gave his son the sex talk. The two stated that the conversation, which lasted approximately 12 minutes, was incredibly awkward and changed their relationship forever.
	I always wanted to be a father, began Bill. Cant lie though, I always wanted a girl because then Id never have to give her the talk. I would just have to beat up the boys who tried anything related to the talk. Dont get me wrong, I love my son very much, but this is just something I never wanted to do.
	Doug also felt the awkward aura in the room. Id heard about this stuff from my friend, Greg, who heard about it from his brother, Tad. So when my dad was explaining this, I knew about pretty much all of it. But he sounded all scientific when he was talking, and it was justweirdand gross.
	So how does this relationship get on the right path again? According to psychologist Dr. Wanda Levers, it already is. The fact that this father was willing to talk to his son and educate him in a relaxed and comfortable environment proves that there is a lot of love there and this relationship is on the right path. However, Mr. Sanders is not necessarily in full agreement.
	Things feel awkward now, Mr. Sanders began. The relationship dynamic has changed. I want to, you know, play baseball with my son, but we cant say balls anymore without just feeling weird and depressed.
	Bills wife, Alicia, is completely fed up with this whole situation. Ugh, men! she began. How hard is it? You have a quick talk, just some explaining, and its over as quickly as ripping off a Band-Aid. A simple in and outoops, no pun intended, she finished.
	At press time, the awkward tension in the house still hadnt subsided. No word yet on Bills ability to talk to his son about Dougs end-of-elementary-school boys-ask-girls dance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Local Man Not As Badass As He Thought </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-05 18:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CHICAGO, IL  Dan Barker, 24, came to the disappointing revelation this week that he is not quite as badass as he previously believed. The discovery came when a group of high school popular kids referred to him as sir instead of bro.
	I wasshocked? Appalled? I dont even know how to label it, Mr. Barker noted, fighting back tears. The whole ordeal came at a very fragile time in Mr. Barkers life. I was just laid off at my job to be replaced by a robot, my girlfriend cheated on me with a ping pong instructor, and, once word got out about the incident with the high school kids, I was denied entry into the Society for American Badasses, finished Mr. Barker.
	Mark Taylor, President of the Society for American Badasses, or SAB, stated the importance of upholding the groups integrity. We cannot have a person admitted into the Society who remains submissive in a situation like that. If he could not garner favor from the children, he shouldve shamed their leader and gained respect from the others. That would have been an acceptable alternative, explained Mr. Taylor. Mr. Barker pleaded for another attempt to enter SAB, but was denied the opportunity. Yes, Dan has met the other criteria, such as having a cool job (a food truck review blogger) and he does a perfect impression of Da Bears! from SNL, but nothing is more badass than your honor, and he tarnished his, finished Mr. Taylor.
	At press time, we discovered Dan Barker was arrested for breaking into a high school and trying to shame the students who wronged him. The SAB chose not to comment on the situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Area Man Sees Everyone He's Ever Met At Gym </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-05 17:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DENVER, CO  Hoping to start leading a healthy lifestyle, Gary Peters, 29, recently joined the World Gym of Denver. The self-conscious mortgage broker quickly made a horrible discovery about his gym: it is filled with people, especially people he knows.
	I get on the elliptical, and before I even start working out I hear, Hey, Gary! It was my high school friend Doug who I havent spoken to since our senior year. It was incredibly bizarre, a horrified Mr. Peters elaborated. He also detailed how he encountered his coworker at the treadmills, his girlfriends best friend at the free weights, and his middle school biology teacher in the steam room. I thought world was just the name! I didnt realize every person in the world would be there, finished Mr. Peters.
	Things have gone on a downhill slope for Mr. Peters since the terrifying day at the gym. He hasnt left the house in two weeks! his girlfriend, Tabitha, explained. Mr. Peters has increased his caloric intake tremendously, and sources tell us that is incredibly dangerous for his health since he quit the gym. He also cant even watch sports on the TV anymore. We watched one NFL pre-season game and he was out of breath. I know the Broncos had an exciting pre-season, but he was out of control, Tabitha finished.
	At press time, the only development of note was that Mr. Peters purchased a Bowflex machine, along with dozens of Billy Blanks Tae Bo DVDs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 23:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol I love this so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ISIS Open Mic Night Not As Fun As Expected </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 00:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AL-RAQQAH, SYRIA  Hoping for a night of debauchery, ISIS militants held an open mic night, where members could take the stage for three minutes and perform their hidden talents. However, the night quickly turned into what was described as a giant disappointment.
	Achmed was so very excited to go, and he was talking up his act for weeks in advance. But you know what happened? He sucked! He gave a whole new meaning to bombing on stage, an angry Yusuf explained. Achmed defended himself by simply stating, Well, at least I tried, you jerk! Sources tell us that the name-calling was a big part of the evening, along with tattling and what was described as general hostility.
	With the evening being a resounding disappointment, there have been no updates on the upcoming ceramics party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 05:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much! I appreciate the kind words, and I'm glad you enjoyed it. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Grader Hopes Friends Don't Blow It Again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 03:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SAN JOSE, CA  The first day of school brings a new year and a new chance to reinvent oneself. Or at least thats what local first grader Jesse Hopkins hopes for after a disastrous year in kindergarten. Disastrous is really an understatement, began Hopkins. All I can say is this  pick your friends wisely.
	The warning he muttered comes after Jesse learned the hard way what happens if you have the wrong friends. Ive got a lot of friends after last year, but the two I was stuck with  Pat and Liam  nearly destroyed my credibility, said Hopkins. Jesses credibility is quite strong for being so young. His older brother, Sam, is one of the most popular kids in the fifth grade, and is en route to becoming one of the coolest kids in middle school. 
     Jesse knows he needs to ride on his brothers coattails to begin his life of popularity, and to surround himself with cool friends to ensure it continues. But the opening of Ms. Bakers kindergarten class nearly destroyed everything he had set up. The first week, Pat cried incessantly about missing home, and then called the teacher mom. Those are big no-nos. Liam, in both the second AND third weeks of class, peed his pants. The three of us our neighbors, so were friends by association, and that nearly ruined my cred. Fortunately, Ive cast them away and can once again return to establishing myself as the cool kid.
     As the school year approaches, the entire district plans to keep an eye on the first grade and monitor the developments of Jesses social life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sizing Up The Competition  By Donald J. Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 05:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NEW YORK, NY  Hello, everybody. This is business mogul and 2016 Presidential candidate (future winner, as I call it) Donald J. Trump. Ive been getting a lot of publicity lately for my remarks. Im here today to describe why my remarks are not brazen, but rather credible. Here, I will discuss exactly why each noteworthy Presidential candidate (from both parties) does not stand a chance against me. Lets start with the Republicans:

CARLY FIORINA  The good for me is that her background is in business. A person with a background in business shouldnt become a politician! What the hell do they know about politics?! The bad for me is that I just said that

DR. BEN CARSON  For me, its good that the man is a pediatric neurosurgeon, which means that hes too smart for the average American. The bad for me is that hes a pediatric neurosurgeon, so unlike any other Republican candidate, he has half a brain and some experience doing good for the world.

MIKE HUCKABEE  People wont like that. Its why no one voted for Jim Wuther-Schmucker in the last election. Also, he made that statement alluding to the Holocaust. Thats a big no-no, even for me. The bad part for me is thatthere actually isnt a bad side. I shouldnt have to worry about losing the nomination to this bass-playing nitwit.

JIM GILMORE  The good for me is that no one knows who the hell he is. No, seriously, who is this guy? I cant really evaluate someone if I know nothing about them. I want to at least keep this semi-factual. Maybe?

LINDSEY GRAHAM  The good for me is that no one likes her. She hasnt contributed much, and shouldnt stand in my- what? Ive just been told by my editor that this is actually a man. Moving on.

BOBBY JINDAL  I cant say anything bad about him. Truly. He was incredible as Dobby the House Elf in the Harry Potter movies.

JOHN KASICH  Whats to say about this man? I could never lose the nomination to him. Hes the worst things to come out of Ohio since The Drew Carey Show.

MARCO RUBIO  There is only good for me in this case. I dont speak-o the Spanish-o, but I know that no is the same in both languages. Ive got nothing to worry about here. Ill make sure this Desi Arnaz-wannabe builds a wall from Miami to Havana, built by Cubans, and paid for by Cubans. Mmm, now Im hungry for a Cuban sandwich

GEORGE PATAKI  Apparently, this man was Governor of New York State. Thats great and all, but hes a terrible father. How do I know? Ive seen Hey Arnold! and I know that his daughter, Helga, is a bully. Do you really want to vote for someone who raised a bully? No  vote for the bullyme.

RICK PERRY  Hes stupid, old, andI forgot the third one. Boom.

RAND PAUL  I hate this guy. Seriously, who does he think he is? I dont care who his daddy is, having terrible hair is MY thing. So take your Jerry Curls and get out of the race, or Big Daddy T will be gunnin for you even harder.

RICK SANTORUM  He introduced his children to a dead fetus that wouldve been their little sibling. Just sayin. Also, never look up his last name on Urban Dictionary. Never.

JEB BUSH  Look at the first two installments of this trilogy. Part 1 vomited on Japans Prime Minister at the time, and Part 2 ruined this country worse than obesity. As my alternate slogan goes, Dont vote for 3, vote for me.

TED CRUZ  He was born in Canada. Nuff said.

CHRIS CHRISTIE  Do we really want to give a new meaning to big government?

And for the Democrats:

LINCOLN CHAFEE  Come on, his name isnt Presidential. It sounds like when I go for a run with twenty dollar bills in my pocket.

MARTIN OMALLEY  He hails from Maryland. Does he really think he can help this country? What will be his first order of business, ensuring every town has as many mini golf courses as Ocean City? Next.

VICE PRESIDENT JOE BIDEN  If I wanted to be led by a doofy old man, Id vote for Johnny Knoxvilles character in Bad Grandpa. Have fun on your choo-choo trains, Joey, because your next station isnt on Pennsylvania Avenue.

BERNIE SANDERS  I would never elect Doc Brown from Back to the Future, and Id never elect Vladimir Lenin. Combine the two, and you have this man. Jumpin gigawatts, comrade!

HILLARY CLINTON  Shes a woman.

Well, this has been my 2016 breakdown. Ill see all of you in January 2017 when Im sworn in as Commander in Chief.

- Donald J. Trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dog's Internal Monologue: Drop The Steak, You Bastard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 01:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ROANOKE, VA  Having been waiting impatiently for what seemed like a lifetime, Zeke, the 4-month-old Jack Russell terrier of the Hamilton family, could not contain his desire for the familys dinner one Thursday evening: a London broil. 
     As the family enjoyed their savory meal, Zeke couldnt help but notice that Ted, the father of the family, was carelessly dangling his steak over the table on his fork. Everyone knows he has notoriously shaky hands, but as soon as the meat would come close to falling off the table, he somehow saves itjackass, said Zeke.
     Zeke describes his growing depression in his home. I know kibble is good for me, I justjust want human food sometimes. They get me lots of toys, and thats great and all, but human food would be great. Maybe some chicken, maybe some steak every now and again. Am I not a good boy? Zeke asked, holding back tears.
     Zekes owner, Ted, weighed in on the situation. I never realized it hurt him this much. We always look out for his best interests, but maybe some meat every once in a while wont hurt him. Zeke was pleased to hear that Ted would be on board with this dietary change. The only other opinion we got was Gregs, Teds 8-year-old son, who merely commented, Wait, our dog can talk?
     Zekes future looks a lot brighter. The possibility of new foods is alive and well, and Zekes courage to stand up for himself leaves the world thinking one thought: Whos a good boy? Whos a good boy? You are. Oh, yes, you are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Racist Old Man Learns Taco Bell Here To Stay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 19:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ROCKVILLE CENTRE, NY  Abel Winters, 81, reluctantly came to the realization that the local Taco Bell would not be leaving his neighborhood anytime soon. The octogenarian bigot expressed concern about what the local establishment means for the country.
	They come here, stealin our jobs and our restaurants! Mr. Winters exclaimed. His ramblings stem largely from the fact that, before it was a Taco Bell, the lot used to be Joes All-American Burger Joint, which was closed down by the health department. This countrys going to Hell in a handbasket real quick! Couple people get E. coli and now an American burger shop is replaced by some Mexican taco stand?! I didnt fight the Nazis and kamikazes for this! This was a point discussed by one of his childhood friends, who also lives in the area.
	Hes damn right he didnt fight for this to happen! You know why? He didnt fight! I was sent off to Normandy while he went to Juilliard. Most he did overseas was performing with The Andrews Sisters as part of the U.S.O.! Hes off his damn rocker! yelled William McDermott, a childhood best friend of Mr. Winters. Mr. Winters expressed discontent with his friends opinion. Hes a damned fool! I know he eats at the Taco Bell and the Chip-ole-tee or Chipotle or whatever the hell its called!
	The manager of the Taco Bell, Steven Ramirez, also weighed in on the issue. I dont know why hed hate us. Even if its because hes racist, 85% of our staff is white teens looking to make a few bucks. Even Im only 25% Hispanic, the manager stated. This old man marches outside our restaurant with signs like, Go back to where you came from! but I was literally born and raised in this town, finished Mr. Ramirez.
	Mr. Winters continuously called for an end to Taco Bell, and also expressed anger towards the ethnic sounding name of Fuddruckers.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 02:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely love this guy. I'd gladly take a road trip with him anytime! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 23:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll still take that as a compliment, so, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dumbass Teen: Shawshank Redemption Just Okay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 03:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ANAHEIM, CA  Jenny Harrison, 15, embarrassed herself on Tuesday by describing The Shawshank Redemption, cinemas greatest work, as just okay, I guess after watching the masterpiece for a high school criminal justice course. Alarmingly, Jennys indifference towards the awe-inspiring film stems from a lifetime of being unimpressed by sheer brilliance.
	It all began when she was a baby, began her father, Dale Harrison. We would give her strawberry-banana baby food, and she would be reluctant to eat it. Strawberry-banana! Its as addictive as crackI shouldve realized our future then. Her mother, Blanche, also remembers disillusionment during Jennys toddler years. We played Candy Land together, and only one of us was into it. Guess which one it was. Spoiler alert: it was me! What sane human being doesnt like Candy Land? I was incredibly alarmed. Fearing developmental abnormalities and future ostracization, Blanche took her daughter for a work-up at the pediatricians office.
	Yes, I remember that appointment quite well, began Dr. Thomas Monroe, Jennys pediatrician. Mrs. Harrison rushed Jenny in during a fit of panic. I assured her there was nothing to worry about, but not even my extensive training could make her comfortable. I mean, its Candy Land for Gods sake. What kid doesnt enjoy the Gumdrop Mountains, or the Lollipop Woods? Kids a freak, but theres nothing wrong with her. This appointment haunts the family to this day.
	Mr. Bob Fuller, Jennys criminal justice teacher, was also blown away by the revelation. We went around the room talking about the movies the students watched and their reactions to them. The first student to talk watched A Bronx Tale, and said they enjoyed the film a lot. I considered this a win for my project. The second student to talk watched My Cousin Vinny and also really enjoyed the film. Again, I felt success. Jenny was third, and when she said the film was okay at best, things got chaotic. One kid stormed out, two got sick and had to go to the nurse, and methe project was a week ago, and I havent returned to the school since. I consider myself a failure as a teacher. Mr. Fuller was unable to continue the interview.
	In the days since the project, Jenny has been under close scrutiny from the school psychologist and a state-appointed psychiatrist. While her future remains unclear, her journey to making proper judgments will be assisted by a team of professionals who have some semblance of what greatness is.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man's Social Life Damaged Following iPhone 6 Purchase </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 01:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SPOKANE, WA  Dave Elliott, 27, recently upgraded from a flip-phone to the new iPhone 6. While the upgrade increased Daves game-playing opportunities and the number of resources available to him for his paralegal job, it also brought a sharp decline in Daves social life.
	Dave and I used to hang out every Wednesday for a guys night. Now Im lucky if I see him once a month, remarked Hal, who was once Daves best friend. I guess what I mean is that I just kind of miss him, and I wish he would be willing to have some fun again soon. Dave did not share the same sentiments. Social interaction? Pfft, please. If I need to talk to people, Ive got my girl Siri ready to go whenever I need her, explained Mr. Elliott. The need for a significant other in his life also remains a complicated area. I use OkCupid and Plenty of Fish all the time! I mean, I use them more because theyre fun as hell apps and less for love, but at least its still exposure toyou knowpeople.
	Is Daves behavior normal? Dr. Jill Peterson, a psychologist based in Seattle, told us how what Dave is experiencing is a growing trend in this technology-dependent world we now live in. The social dynamic has changed, Dr. Peterson began. Not too long ago, people would expose themselves to opinions and risks, and provide second chances if need be. Nowadays, we remove ourselves from situations where these kinds of things can occur. Its easier to trust angry birds than colleagues and friends, she finished.
	So what does the future hold for Mr. Elliott? Not people! Haha! he joked. But seriously, I expect I will be cripplingly lonelynot that it will matter once I became the master of Fruit Ninja and sell that free U2 album  for a profit!
	Friends and family of Mr. Elliott say he has only left his house twice in the last three months, and if he follows through with his plans of buying an iPad, they will hold a formal intervention.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Toddler Union: Republicans Not For Us </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 00:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MILWAUKEE, WI  The Union for American Toddlers, or U.A.T., the nations largest union for toddler rights, released its opinion of the first Republican debate, with less than desirable reviews for most candidates. The unions representatives stated a great displeasure with nearly all of the candidates. Time and again, they have disappointed Americans, said U.A.T. leader Timmy Gibbler. Gibbler continued, They dont seem to show a desire to ameliorate war, and as an organization focused on domestic issues, this concerns us. We need to know that our next President will be there for us. That he or she will stick up for our rights. This is what we need, and we were upset with the lackluster display during the debate.
	With time running short before the election, the union is deciding where to throw its support. No one has approached us with any offers yet, said Gibbler. This disappoints us and leaves us confused for 2016, he finished. So where will this growing union place its support? That is the question the U.A.T.s analytics department is trying to figure out every day.
	Its a tricky time in U.S. politics right now, said Stevie McPoyle, head analyst for the toddler union. Normally we throw our weight behind the Democratic Party, and with every member being in at least the 60th percentile for our ages, thats a good deal of weight. We figured that since the Republican Party has upwards of fifteen candidates, we might find one to support. However, all we have seen is a bunch of, pardon my language, poopyheads, finished McPoyle.
     Were most likely going to go Democratic again, said leader Timmy Gibbler. Gibbler went on to say how the union will most likely announce support for Bernie Sanders in the upcoming months. We feel as if Hillary Clinton is untrustworthy, began Gibbler. We here at the U.A.T. agree with Bernie Sanders approach to corporate greed, as well as his pro-nap time stance. Suffice it to say that were feeling the Bern! Haha, sorry, I couldnt resist, finished Gibbler. With the 2016 elections looming ever closer, it is important to keep an eye out on where those in Washington turn for support in the final few months.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
