<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3901</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Uncomfortable Effort of Thinking (including an interesting section about how the advertising industry utilizes 'engagement' for manipulation) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 08:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "If Martin Luther King had a sneaker deal, we would still be on the back of the bus." - Dave Chapelle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 07:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just saw the [teaser](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0TRqE7rmi3g) for Dave Chapelle's new comedy special and thought this line packed quite the punch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 10:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true, but eating soy products directly is *far, far* more efficient and takes up *far less* land area than eating soy via eating animals. The **kcal per land, water and energy cost** on a plant-based diet is vastly greater than on a meat-based diet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 07:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not a solution. Edge isn't ready yet and still causes issues on some sites, as well as lacking some features. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 07:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I calibrated my XPS 15 9560's screen with my X-Rite i1 Profiler last night and now all sRGB images look wrong in Chrome.

Any idea what's up there and how I can fix it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After calibrating my XPS 15 9560 screen, Chrome's views sRGB images as much too dark and contrasty. Microsoft Edge looks fine. Any ideas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 07:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 08:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nur so:

Ein mnnlicher Hund ist ein Rde. Ein weiblicher Hund ist eine Hndin, keine 'Rdin'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "If you're a libertarian Donald Trump voter, you're the most misinformed voting class in America." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 10:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed, I posted it there first: https://www.reddit.com/r/LateStageCapitalism/comments/5wb81j/tech_and_the_fake_market_tactic_in_one_generation/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 10:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Future generations will be more savvy. Like my granddaughter. She just sent me a snapchat.

I bet she's great with 'the cyber'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 10:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't hear 'crying', I hear valid criticism about lack of regulation and awareness towards those areas where these stockholder interests don't align with society at large. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 09:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It spreads whatever people want to spread on it.

Technology is merely a multiplier and enabler of human traits and behaviours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **[Amazon has an overwhelming market share lead](http://sc.cnbcfm.com/applications/cnbc.com/resources/files/2016/12/23/onlinemarket.jpg)** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what the author says.

These pseudo-market patterns also mask patterns of subsidy, like the fact that Ubers current operations are subsidized by investors to the tune of $2 billion per year. Thats a cost that will be immediately passed along to consumers as soon as Uber succeeds in displacing conventional taxis.

(...)

Just as Uber subsidizes fares during the phase when theyre displacing regulated taxis, Facebook subsidizes publishers ad rates during the phase when theyre displacing third-party advertising networks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The internet has never been more centralised around Facebook, Google and Amazon as it is now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think the problem is with startups, who indeed would be harmed by regulations requiring *'millions in capital to even be able to legally run a company in the sector'*.

I do however think that companies in systemically critical market positions like Facebook, Amazon and Google could and should be regulated a lot more thoroughly against anti-competitive practices such as the ones described in the article.

However I also fully agree that decentralised blockchain-based technologies could partially help with issues like this. The crux of the problem isn't technological though, it's economic/political/social/cultural. Even the best and most decentralised protocols don't solve the problem as long as we continuously give up our freedoms (often unknowingly) for a bit more convenience and *'better user experience.'* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tech and the Fake Market tactic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for cross-posting! I wasn't aware of this sub - nice to have found it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Subtle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are secret algorithms in a black box more transparent than a taxi driver taking a long route? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tech and the Fake Market tactic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tech and the Fake Market tactic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Reddit clone where in order to comment, users have to first answer an easy question about the article's content (defined by OP as part of post submission process) to make sure they've actually read it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In one generation, the Internet went from opening up new free markets to creating a series of Fake Markets that exploit society, without most media or politicians even noticing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 18:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tech and the Fake Market tactic: In one generation, the Internet went from opening up new free markets to creating a series of Fake Markets that exploit society, without most media or politicians even noticing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 18:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "A developed country is not a place where the poor have cars. Its where the rich use public transport."

 Enrique Penalosa, former Mayor of Bogot, Colombia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 12:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I turned off uBlock Origin on Discord  as you can see by the icon on the top right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/Dell/comments/5vusmm/nvidia_hot_fix_37877_drivers_for_9560/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously. I'm not affiliated with Microsoft in *any* way.

Is this just happening for me? No idea why Chrome is acting this way on Discord. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA: Dell XPS 15 9560 1.1.3 System BIOS has been released on Feb 23 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 13:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is Discord glitching out on Chrome for me? On Edge it looks fine. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 09:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 09:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's use the biggest film of the decade as an example. Now it's not a sequel, remix or adaptation, but it is a genre film -- sci-fi -- and most tellingly, it's a member of a tiny sub-genre where sympathetic white people feel bad about all the murder, pillaging, and annihilation being done on their behalf.

I call this sub-genre "Sorry about Colonialism!" I'm talking about movies like Dances With Wolves, The Last Samurai, The Last of the Mohicans, Dune, Lawrence of Arabia, A Man Called Horse, and even Fern Gully and Pocahontas.

* **[Everything is a Remix Part 2](https://youtu.be/Z-HuenDPZw0?t=2m17s)**

I really enjoyed the film and watched it many times. But it *is* very much a stereotype at this point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The full 24-minute documentary can be watched here:

http://www.fresnobee.com/news/nation-world/national/article128729769.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hollywood's Greatest Trick (OFFICIAL TRAILER) - a documentary about the exploitative VFX industry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The full 24-minute documentary can be watched here:

http://www.fresnobee.com/news/nation-world/national/article128729769.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hollywood's Greatest Trick (OFFICIAL TRAILER)- a documentary about the exploitative VFX industry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 09:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I exported alembic and rendered in max and vray, but only so I could use the render farm at work.

Source: https://vimeo.com/205194484#comment_15476686

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 09:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What makes someone a scientist exactly?

I think the concept of *'being an X'* is fallacious, reductive and unhelpful.

It **[doesn't help the person identifying as X](http://paulgraham.com/identity.html)** and for most X it doesn't help others make meaningful assumptions about that person referred to as an X beyond the most basic level of nuance and differentiation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck this shit.

'Edgy' criticisms of the system are the new hot commodity. Listen to Katy Perry, be a rebel!

 "If you search for moral wisdom in Katy Perry's lyrics, then kill yourself."

 **[ - Bo Burnham](https://youtu.be/ByC8sRdL-Ro?t=1m47s)** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, the soviets and other communist striving societies glorified war, a lot.

That makes glorification of war a good thing then? I'm sorry, is everyone losing their minds here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **[Bo Burnham's](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ByC8sRdL-Ro)** newest special **[MAKE HAPPY](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iE5WwlwJeDQ t=2s)** is also on Netflix. One of my favourite specials in a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WALL OF DEATH - Houdini 16 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 16:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 10:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Genau solche Infos wollte ich wissen. Gibt es hierfr irgendwelche Artikel/Berichte/Belege, die die Gesetzsprechungspraxis in Deutschland beispielhaft belegen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 10:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Das sind die absolut grundlegenden Basics der gesetzlichen Theorie. Ich wollte mehr ber die Praxis und Beispiele mit genaueren Details wissen.

Laut Gesetz hier kann der Vermieter einen Mieter problemlos rausschmeien, sobald der mehr als zwei Monate mit der Miete im Verzug ist. Das deckt sich nicht wirklich mit den Behauptungen, es sei in der Praxis viel schwieriger fr Vermieter, mit solchen Mietern zu verfahren. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 08:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't say automation is *good* or *bad*.

Just what its effects will be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ich hre oft, in Deutschland machen Mieterschutzgesetze es Vermietern besonders schwer, gegen Mieter vorzugehen. In welchen Fllen ist das zum Beispiel so? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 08:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kennt jemand Beispiele dafr, wie in Deutschland Mieter durch Mieterschutzgesetze strker geschtzt sind als in anderen vergleichbaren Lndern?

Und in welchen Fllen es fr Vermieter besonders (womglich unangemessen) schwierig ist, gegen problematische Mieter vorzugehen?

Ich hre oft, dass die Mieterschtuzgesetze in Deutschland dafr verantwortlich sind, dass Vermieter hier eine *enorme* Sicherheit erwarten bevor sie einen Mietvertrag unterschreiben - also mehr Vermgen, sicherere Arbeitsvertrge/Einkommensquellen, am besten auch Familie, etc. auf Seite des Mieters, als sie es in anderen Lndern ohne deutsche Mieterschutzgesetze tun wrden.

Denn wenn in Deutschland mal ein Mieter sumig wird mit der Miete, ist es angeblich absurd schwierig, ihn loszuwerden um keinen Mietverlust erleiden zu mssen.

Wei jemand hier, wie die Lage tatschlich ist? Wenn ich als Mieter meine Miete nicht mehr bezahlen knnte oder wollte, was wrde das passieren? (Nicht, dass ich das vorhabe - bin seit 7 Jahren ohne Probleme in der gleichen Wohnung. Frage aus reinem Interesse.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 08:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Automation will cost much more jobs in a much shorter time frame than can be compensated by a decrease in world population. And in actual fact the world population isn't decreasing at all but still rapidly growing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 08:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Population growth is being driven by the developing world, but birth rates are going down dramatically with development there, as well.

**[Not as dramatically as one would hope.](https://i.imgur.com/Lde9KSI.jpg)**
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same problem here as well.

I just unplug the cable and let it run on battery when it disturbs me. Supposedly keeping the battery between 50% and 80% is better for its longevity than keeping it at 100% all the time anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Urteil Bundesgerichtshof: Bausparkassen drfen Altvertrge kndigen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 21:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 20:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No proper touch keys support and drivers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The continent gets 117 percent more sunshine than Germany

Um... what does that mean? Surely a continent as massive as Africa would get *a lot more* than just slightly more than double the amount of sun as a small country like Germany?

Are they just talking about sunny days on average? Seems like a silly metric in this context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> XPS 15 9560 internal speaker volume varies strangely on sounds from Chrome - sometimes it's really faint even though all volume sliders are at 100% </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 09:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anyone experienced this? For some reason the volume on the internal speakers for audio coming from Chrome sometimes becomes really low even though I have everything set to max volume.

However, if I start a video file from the SSD the sound is the proper volume. What's up with that?

Chrome is at 100% in the Volume Mixer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 07:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  For web browsing, it helped to change the graphics adapter used for the web browser to the dedicated one instead of the integrated.

Where can you set that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 23:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, stop thinking purely in categories of winners and losers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rede Martin Schulz "Arbeit in Deutschland" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depending on what kind of work you do, MODO can be fantastic or it can be pure cancer.

I made a few **[videos](https://blenderartists.org/forum/showthread.php?395328-A-MODO-artist-learns-Blender-Newest-video-7-Parenting)** comparing MODO and Blender (and Maya). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They look fantastic and super-useful!

People who think UI design is *unnecessary fluff* don't understand usability and efficiency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The moral is to not compare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What technologies/languages are used to create a cross-platform desktop application like Affinity Designer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 16:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been wondering - does anyone know what technologies are involved in creating a desktop app such as **[Affinity Designer](https://affinity.serif.com/en-gb/designer/)**?

Which languages does one have to know?

What knowledge is necessary?

I presume that for example the image manipulation / vector graphics tools require mostly Linear Algebra?

What languages would this be written in? What frameworks would be used?

Just trying to get a better overview of the world of professional software development in a variety of settings and applications. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 16:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wei nicht ob 'bayerisch' aber frnkisch schon (ich komme aus Franken). Insbesondere Pnktlichkeit ist ein groes Ding.

Unpnktlichkeit wird definitiv als Mangel an Respekt, Rcksicht oder Zuverlssigkeit interpretiert.

Das merke ich bei mir selbst noch immer... habe das Gefhl, ich sei der einzige in Berlin, der immer pnktlich ist - und muss dann immer auf andere warten. Das strt mich dann doch immer etwas, auch wenn ich stets versuche, mir meiner Konditionierung bewusst sein sein und keine bswilligen Absichten oder mangelnde Wertschtzung auf die andere Person zu projizieren. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 16:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The full lists also includes Starbucks and L'OREAL:

http://worldsmostethicalcompanies.ethisphere.com/honorees/

http://www.forbes.com/sites/karstenstrauss/2016/03/09/the-worlds-most-ethical-companies-2016/#2e60086c73dc                        

Not only do companies self-nominate themselves, they also pay $1500 for their nomination.

Complete and utter bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> H M named as one of the world's most ethical companies in 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 16:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Schner Gedanke, aber leider funktioniert das so nicht.

Fleischessen - selbst lokales - ist weitaus ressourcenfeindlicher als vegetarische/vegane Ernhrung. Nutztiere fressen tonnenweise Futtermittel, die zum berwiegenden Groteil in Sdamerika und Asien angebaut werden, und zu massiven Regenwaldrodungen fhren.

Keine Frage: Lokales Obst essen statt sich tglich mit Mangos und Ananas zu sttigen, ist immer eine gute Idee. Aber wer glaubt, mit Fleischkonsum und Sdlandfruchtverzicht effektiv fr die Umwelt zu engagieren, sollte sich nochmal genauer informieren. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ich kenne Leute, die ein schlechtes Bild von Berlin haben - aber keineswegs aufgrund irgendeines der von ihm hier gelisteten Punkte. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 14:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bei der Wahl zum Berliner Abgeordnetenhaus zog die AfD in vier von fnf Bohnsdorfer Wahllokalen aus dem Stand an SPD und Linken vorbei

Dass jemand, der in diesem Umfeld aufgewachsen ist, in Bayern und der CSU eher sein Glck findet als in der Berliner Innenstadt, wundert mich wenig. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 14:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Die Heimatverbundenheit, das gelebte Brauchtum sowie die soziale und christliche Komponente in der bayerischen Politik empfinde ich als uerst vorbildlich gegenber der CDU. 

Kann mir jemand erklren, wo die CSU sozialer und 'christlicher' (in echter Tat, nicht nur im Marketing und Ritualen) ist, als die CDU? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
