<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2621</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just broken up with </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 02:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He blocked me on Facebook, didn't return any of my texts or calls. He didn't say anything. I went to tag him on a post and his page wasn't there. This is how I found out. Still haven't heard from him. I feel like shit. 


What would you do to feel better?


Edit: seriously you guys are amazing. I'm crying right now because you are all so kind. Thank you all so much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 20:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turns me on xD  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cry probably  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Daniel Radcliffe  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No fap totally works. A old fwb bottom had the same problem. Also don't worry about it, it's not a big issue as long as you're having fun  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 17:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never had a problem with any hair. Don't worry about it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 17:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess the beard is my trick then lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 16:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone had to start somewhere  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 16:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just have to own it

My bf is smaller than me and I love his cock, some hook ups were bigger and I loved those too. 

All guys were/are insecure about dick size so they are nice about it. Plus five is plenty to play with ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 16:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You really just have to go up to him and ask him out. 

Something like "wanna get coffee in a gay way?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 16:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Possibly

Here I am as clean shaven as I get lol
 http://i.imgur.com/yGPWiiS.jpg 

Edit: ignore dorky look on my face lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 16:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just the clothing and beard style age me up I think  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 16:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks xD

...I totally blushed lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 16:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Squats and sit ups, style the beard. 

That's the trick, I'm only 23. birthday is soon xD  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 16:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Show her a pic of the kinda guy you want to look like, I'm sure she'll have a few ideas. Plus fashion has a lot to do with how things look together and that crosses over the different styles. 


Good luck, I'm sure you'll look fine ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 15:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just remember that people are into all sorts of things. 

Often people aren't into the type they fall into. Someone out there is into you

For example I look like this and am into twinks 

 http://i.imgur.com/fvCdPCs.jpg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 15:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you know how tv shows always have the girl with a stereotypical gay friend. 

What you need is the stereotypical straight girl friend. 

Go to a cute friend and tell her you like guys and need help choosing outfits. I went to a slightly slutty ex gf to help me out (I'm slightly slutty too so no shame lol) 

She should totally be able to help you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 04:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God did I need this thread...thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 04:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm kinda the guy you say you're attracted too and I love twinks. Not just for sex either. 

Don't worry about changing yourself, I have friends built like me who are into twinks too. 


I'm usually really good at writing long motivating advice but I'm so tired lol


So what I have to say pretty much boils down to this: don't change yourself for someone unless they'll change for you too, you will find someone, you will be happy. 


Msg me if you wanna chat more. In the morning I'll be good with advice again lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 04:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem with being LGBT is that there is no map to our lives, it's a blessing too but god is it tough. 

Straight is easy, there is a road map on how their lives will go. 

We aren't so lucky. We have to discover it all ourselves and will have to defend our decisions over and over again. 

It's tough but I have faith that you'll overcome everyone's judgement and do what makes you happy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been two years and you are looking for an excuse to not do it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have never fought with any of my exes or my current bf and none of those relationships felt fake. 

Don't be afraid that you don't fight, just talk with eachother and try to understand. Don't be afraid if you fight either. Things will work out if you both want them too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually just prep all the ingredients for my dinners and breakfasts. I'm going to try this though :)

Thank you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This are shitty right now. The world sucks and it isn't fair, people keep telling you the world gets better but it never does for you. I've been there. 


Life is a really hard fucking thing to do. Everyone is living their happy lives but we go around having to fight and beg just to scrape by. 


What do we get out of it?


We get a story. We are not the people who were handed everything, things always got rougher for you and they never got better. The other people out there don't understand what it's like. They haven't lived the same life as you. 


So why is it you should stick around? 


It's because someday you are going to find someone who is where you are now and it's your job to help them. 


There is no cure, life doesn't get easier. Though you will get better at handling it, sometimes you will be overwhelmed by it but you keep on because how can you let this stop you. Everything that's happened to you before vs what is happening to you now...you can't let this be the thing that takes you out. 


There are people in the world who are going to love you for just being you, your dad was one of them. He will not be the only one. 


You can make it, I believe in you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol I had dental work done and didn't realize pain killers made your eyes red xD 

Here is a sober pic then...no way I was high at Christmas lol http://i.imgur.com/1ZRDe8m.jpg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How will you ever be sure he isn't cheating. How will you know that he didn't just inform you because of the hiv  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope everything goes well. I'm sending good vibes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks 
This how I look lol http://i.imgur.com/mSTjlm4.jpg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 18:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bf didn't see a doctor after this and he got a massive infection, like bed rest for weeks infection. 

The doctor will give you an exam (finger you) then give you some pills to take and if you don't heal up then the doctor will scope you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 18:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretend I came up with a clever conversation starter and message me back...we can talk about turtle stuff  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I keep up with the diet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 18:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 24, 6'4", 260lbs and bi

I carry my weight really well and people always say I look normal. My bf really likes the way I look now and tells me I don't need to worry about dieting but I want too. 

I've done calorie counting before and have lost a lot of weight that way. I used to be 310lbs but I'm having a hard time getting back on the horse. 

I bought all the stuff to start meal prepping but I still have a hard time not just being a fat ass. 

Any advice at all would be wonderful xD 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember that you've made it this far and have faced worse. Or if this is the worst then pretend you are future you just remembering this happening to you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used these (I'm bi)

To girls "I've decided I'm gay"

To guy "I've decided I'm straight" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was slapped and popped a boner  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On FaceTime with someone else jerking on the other end  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's when you go to say I love you and instead of anxious you feel relief  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something more creative than this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...they do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Things like you make me feel like I can (insert humble brag) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> John snow nude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want to hold his had as we watch movies. He has been really sick lately and we were afraid for his life for a while. I would just love to sit on the couch watching movies with him not being in pain. I'll make his favorite brownies too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was almost in an accident that I would have been at fault for like three hours ago. Other guys breaks were on point. I need to not drive when I'm worked up  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obgyn  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My ex's twin brother's cock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend loves doing this, everyone in the group has a power he's observed and they all get names. 

Mine is called "I can do better" I can complete any task after seeing someone else fail it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you have to work up to this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Licked my cum off a stuffed bear  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was nicknamed screw driver...because I'm a tool and have a nice dick lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking a friend so she could loose her V-card </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll notice when they compliment you, they are actually complimenting themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plunger in the O.R.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 20 nuggets large fry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first guy I fucked is an actual millionaire. That whole night was weird but it was alright sex.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Layer outside in the cold for hours not talking. It was boring af </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I either walk to the bathroom and pee or in the summer I go off the balcony  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My time to shine!
I dated a guy that's a twin. He is gay and his brother is straight. My guy ha a tiny dick (like 4in). I am friends with the brothers gf and she showed me a pic of the brothers. His is like 6in or more. They looked a lot alike though and the one I had tasted great xD 
She said the brothers did too ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 03:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry for your loss. He sounds wonderful  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 04:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love that thing in my mouth xD  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 03:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found out a couple months ago that my best friend was jerking it to me for years...I was not ok with that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 11:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> South Bend Indiana  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've battled weight for a long time now. I started loosing after I hit 250 in high school then went down to 200 then back to 280 (6'4") I went down as far as 220 then got into a relationship and over the course of three years I got up to my max at 310. I am down at 255 and it's still coming off. Being this big for so long and continually going up and down gives you absolutely no idea of your true body image. In the mirror I still see the 310lb man who hadn't touched a weight set in years, even though everyone I know comments about how handsome I look or how I look a normal weight. I go to the gym and get hit on and it feels great but then I look at the wall of mirrors and see an ugly fat ass that can't get his shit together. 

This is the problem with weight loss, it's in your head as much as your body. All of the times I lost weight before this I was using fad diets and speciality weight loss exercises. This time something is different. I looked not at my weight but my life and decided that I wanted to be a person who eats real food for meals, whose average meal was hone cooked and could come from a garden. This isn't a diet with an end in mind like the others, it's a new life path. 

I'm not sure how much I helped...if any, but I wanted you to get an idea from someone who has been where he has been. 

Bf thought I should include a current pic to show you what I still think of as an ugly fat me 
 http://i.imgur.com/lfXq57N.jpg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
