<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject322</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 23:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw some one shout my name. That's amazing I've caught on like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 23:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it? This pleases me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 21:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You shall join my Pantheon, as ScarletF the Viridian god! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 21:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All praise be to me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I made an empire in the Robin Chat, and my computer froze. I came back much later to find I was raised to godhood by followers I had not met during my time in chat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 21:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 21:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya'all are lame. Upvotes are for posts that contribute to the subreddit, and I gotta say. This post in this subreddit desrevs up votes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 25 [M4F] Toronto - Looking to discover more of Toronto this Summer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 23:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, hey clicked on my link did you? Dandy.
I'm six three, brunette with glasses a beard and a tattoo, and a voice like honey.
But hey, listen, I could go on and on about myself - Tell you about my hobbies like reading. How I devour novels within hours of buying one. I could tell you how I absolutely love day dreaming, or that I enjoy long, long walks (Sometimes both at the same time.). My favorite style of music? Geek Rock. Not that you'll hear it from me. Or how I was working with a rocking tech company a few months ago, Nerf Wars were one of many office hazards. If I was embarrassed about the fact, I'd probably try to hide the fact I like gaming, video and table top, but if someone were to ask me. I'd probably let them know.
You may also hear rumours that I'm a fantastic cook. Not that I'll confirm them, but I'd be lying if I denied them. Haha
Maybe I could tell you about how I love watching videos from TED.com, or that I really enjoy listening to comedians as I work? Nah. I'll keep that to myself too. How about the fact that I'm a huge comic book geek, and I enjoy telling people about all the easter eggs in the movie we just watched? No no. I might come off as too nerdy if I told you that!
Ohh I know. How about that I love hiking and camping? A good beer, and a campfire is a good night in my book. Hmm... But if I said that, then you might start thinking I was a rugged outdoorsy type. Which I'm not. I just like certain things like that, I don't do them often enough for my liking though. Ok. Well. I guess I'll keep my mouth shut for now.
So yeah. Those are just some of things I wont tell you at the moment. Wouldn't want to waste your time eh? Anyway. If you got through all that, I think I'd like to know about you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 23:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah. Thanks. Posting from mobile. I'll repost, I appreciate the heads up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 18:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's actually pretty brilliant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 14:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> exactly. Super powerful if you use them right, but you need to be good to do it. High risk, high reward. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 14:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TLV should get a third ult, level ten you get fang as a forthbhero, level 20 you get scorch as a fofth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 18:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shining shimmering splendid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 00:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> regret. Because sadness can be fun, stories are mad more fulfilling by it, but regret...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 00:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zheng He for life! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 06:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My pleasure. Your wife might be acting like a potato, but it's coming from a good place. Ya got a wonderful lady here, who'll be a fantastic mother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 06:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, everyone wants to name their kid Turbo, secondly, lay it out like this.

"Honey, I love our pets, you see that right? AND I love you. Picking up another pet though, would add to some stress I'm already feeling, and I want to be at my best for you AND little "Turbo" when we're finally lucky enough.

I am 100% committed to our rescue plan when we get our bigger home, I'm 100% committed too you, and I'm 100% committed to being the best father I can be. 

I feel for the cat, for all the cats, and dogs, that we cannot take in, but we are not a rescue yet, and we don't have the time and resources too commit to another critter. I'm not trying to be the final decision maker here. But for us to take on caring for another creature's life? That needs us both to make that choice, together." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 06:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, your honey is being a potato here. The cat box thing, awesome decision for the future health of your future baby. Perfectly reasonable. But if she wants another cat, she has gotta realize she's putting that burden on YOU and not herself.

Do NOT get another pet, because guess what, it'll stress you out as you've said, and that'll cause fights. Add a baby on top of that? Or even a super pregnant wife who (Rightly, because she's super pregnant) wont be doing much, if any of the pet care.

You've said it yourself, she will always want another pet. This third cat wont be the last. You want  bigger home to feel safe and secure an you'll be helping a lot of animals when you can. 

PS: You're not the "Final Decision" when it comes to getting a new pet. It's a 50/50 split, and needs to be unanimous. 

Like of you wanted to call your baby "Turbo Saxaphonic" if it's a boy or "Tina Saxaphonic" if it's a girl. Your wife needs to be okay with that. And I really hope she's not. Those are terrible names for a baby, what's wrong with you? Haha

But my point stands. You're not the bad guy for preserving your sanity. You cannot save every animal, but you're saving four which is a lot more than most people can say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 02:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, who'd get your vote? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 20:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My hero </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 22:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People want both. More options are not bad.

Besides, hero league draft you need a certain number of characters. Quick draft you can have doubles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 05:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hockey Xul.

Hockey stick instead of scythe
Hockey gear on skeletons
Skeletal mages are goalies
His q could be a hockeyvstick smacking a hockey puck at him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 20:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they do comment on it, but not really address it. But the fact they acknowledge it is super cool. Thanks very much for sharing.

PS: I totally see why they don't address it. It would turn into a huge shit show if they let it, and I'm sure we're all glad it didn't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] Every post in this thread happens to Bill and Linda, chronologically, if something kills or permanently maims them they remember it happening, but with no effect left on them otherwise. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 20:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 20:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh jesus. That's cute and funny, but imagine if a male guest did it to ellen with the same excuse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 19:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're saying you had no interest in young men and just wanted to draw pussy all day? I think OP in the image might be on to something! /s (So people know this is a joke) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 20:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are great fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 17:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't Nerzul, the Original Lich King, a pretty important Orc? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 16:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Play their games. They're Amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 05:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Lost Vikings next. They're a ton of fun and are pretty badass/heroic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 04:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? So in an hour? So excited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 04:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which timezone dose fates release at midnight in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 04:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks really cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 04:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source on that skin? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 18:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhh I see. My mistake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 17:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the video you mention you cannot see XP which is the vikings main metric but that's wrong. XP is very visable and you can clearly see the lead the vikings supply. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most interesting fictional species, either for sci fi or fantasy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 00:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most interesting fictional species, either for sci fi or fantasty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 00:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 18:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank god that shield of Kael's got a time nerf. I rarely ever see it get destroyed so the amount nerf might help too. But it lasted way too long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 18:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those who can't be bothered

FALSTAD

Hammerang (Q)  

BOOMerang (Talent)  

Damage increased from 121 (+4% per level) to 150 (+4% per level)
  
Hinterland Blast (R)
  
Base damage increased from 411 (+4.75% per level) to 475 (+4.75% per level)
  
Developer Comments: Were primarily seeing players run Basic Attack builds as Falstad, and would like to make mage Falstad a bit more powerful. We also felt that Hinterland Blast isnt doing enough damage with its higher cooldown, so were further increasing that damage.

  
JAINA


Basic Attack damage reduced from 89 (+4% per level) to 60 (+4% per level)
  
Frostbolt (Q)
Damage increased from 160 (+4% per level) to 190 (+4% per level)
  
Cone of Cold (E)
Damage increased from 189 (+4% per level) to 200 (+4% per level) 
  
Developer Comments: Were starting to pull Basic Attack damage out of characters who dont rely upon it, namely Jaina and Kaelthas. For Jaina, this will make less of her damage guaranteed and allow for more advanced plays. Jainas win rate is also a little on the low end, so we want to offset the Basic Attack nerf and add to her overall power by buffing Frostbolt and Cone of Cold.

KAEL'THAS


Basic Attack damage reduced from 87 (+4% per level) to 65 (+4% per level)
  
Arcane Barrier (Talent)
Shield amount decreased from 200% to 150%
Duration reduced from 6 to 4 seconds
  
Gravity Lapse (E)
Stun duration reduced from 1.5 to 1.0 seconds
  
Phoenix (R)
Cooldown increased from 40 to 60 seconds
  
Pyroblast (R)
Damage increased from 730 (+4% per level) to 810 (+5% per level)
Cooldown increased from 50 to 100 seconds
  
Developer Comments: Kaelthas is a powerful hero with too few downsides. Were nerfing several aspects of his kit, and are still planning a Talent overhaul coming soon. The stun duration of Gravity Lapse is too long and guarantees kills more often than we would like. Reducing the stun duration makes it less frustrating to play against and adds a bit more counterplay for the enemy team. Phoenix is the drastically favored Heroic Ability right now, and its up far too often. By nerfing its cooldown, while also pushing Pyroblast to create more impactful moments, we expect there will be more situations where Pyroblast is the optimal pick.

NOVA


Snipe (Q)
Damage increased from 268 (+4% per level) to 295 (+4% per level)
  
Snipe Master (Talent)
Damage bonus increased from 5% to 12% per stack
Maximum stack bonus increased from 50% to 60%
Maximum stacks decreased from 10 to 5
  
Developer Comments: While we are happy with the variety of Talent options Nova has after the rework, her overall damage is too low. We like Snipe Master, and it encourages a different playstyle, but a single miss resets a ton of progress toward the Talents reward. With these changes, players will get more out of Snipe Master without having to rebuild so many stacks after a miss. Weve heard a lot of community feedback and suggestions about not removing stacks as long as your Snipe hits something. Weve discussed this, but feel that even if Snipe misses the intended target, it still hits something the majority of the time. By making this Talent sharp, with an obvious downside, it allows us to crank up the tuning and really celebrate flawless Nova play.

THRALL


Basic Attack damage reduced from 173 (+4% per level) to 165 (+4% per level)
  
Sundering (R)
Cooldown increased from 70 to 80 seconds
  
Developer Comments: Thrall sits near the top of our win charts, so we feel that small nerfs to his damage and most-picked Heroic Ability are necessary. We expect this to only slightly nudge Thrall down, as were otherwise happy with how he is currently being played.

SUPPORT
 

REHGAR


Ghost Wolf (Trait) (D)
Basic Attack damage bonus reduced from 100% to 75%
  
Lightning Shield (W)
Damage reduced from 36 (+4% per level) to 30 (+4% per level)
  
Developer Comments: Rehgars new Talents have opened up a number of different strategies and builds, which has been exciting to see. We like this more aggressive playstyle, but noticed that the majority of Lightning Shield Talents are now clear winners. Focusing nerfs primarily on Lightning Shields damage will help to reduce Rehgars win rate and open up even more Talent options.

WARRIOR
 

DIABLO


Fire Stomp (W)
  
Fire Devil (Talent)
  
Damage reduced from 23 (+4% per level) to 17 (+4% per level)
  
Developer Comments: Diablo has hovered near the top of our win rate charts for a while. We wanted to see how the Tyrande nerfs would impact him first, as we know those characters have very strong synergy together. We havent seen much of a dip in Diablos win rate, so were targeting a must pick Talent with this nerf.

BUG FIXES
  
Art
  
Lunar Jainas legs will no longer separate from her body on endgame score screens.
Battlegrounds
  
Dying will no longer cause the players Healing Well cooldown to reset.
Heroes and Talents
  
Fixed an issue that could cause Greymanes Gilnean Cocktail to deal more than the intended amount of damage in certain situations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 03:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it a port of the GBA version? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 02:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a battlefront game? Nice  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 02:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooh I forgot there was a PSP version. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best PsP classic games? I just got one, and am looking for some gems. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 02:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best PsP claasic. I have a love for RPGs, and strategy games. Been playing Valkyria Chronicles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 16:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you add the "no redscreens -review" into the target box? What is a target box in fact? I'm still new to all of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dragon Quest Heroes Slime Edition two missing files for it to run? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 03:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've begun setting up my own twitch channel to help support and promote this game, what are some things you like to see on channels, what makes them great? I'd love your advice as someone just starting out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 02:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The best kind of smack down, facts vs blind guesses. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 21:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Diablo/Starcraft Cross universe mini story (LOTV spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 22:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After the fall of Amon and Highlord  Ma'lash, Alarak had his dissenters. Those who believed their god had not fallen, those who would take Alarak's place. But with Ma'lash gone, they had no way to commune with their lord Amon. So they turned to forbidden texts and ancient scriptures. 

Whispering into the void and beyond, the Cabal called out to the dark voice, begging to hear whispers, even a murmur of their god's greatness.

But in their haste, and inexperience, they pushed too far. Breaking the boundaries of Time and Space. And they caught the attention of Azmodan, Lord of sin. He heard their pride, and their greed, and their lust for power. He echoed it. Promises of golden thrones and all of the Protoss at their feet. They need only call him forth.

And so they did, for months they toiled at the summoning. To breach realities. And soon, the time had come. His heralds in a circle, chanting pulling, calling. Azmodan rose forth, ethereal. His physical body could not fully manifest, and this would not do. An entire reality void of Angels and Demons and Nephalem to plunder. He would manifest. So he reached out, to the psionically charged Templar round him. Felt them resisting his pull. 

Then the weak link showed itself, and he whispered into the mind of his new thrall. "Slay your leader. He will not serve my glory, he is holding me, and you, back. Take his place." And so he did. Reaching for a ceremonial dagger, the traitor slew his leader, and opened his mind to Azmodan, but soon he was overwhelmed and possessed. 

Using the knowledge found within this body, Azmodan forced his will unto the others, pulling them into an Archon of Demonic proportions. And that is the birth of the Dark Archon Azmodan, and the greatest civil war the Tal'darim had ever seen.

Xul, sensing a disturbance in the balance of his world, followed the vacuum Azmodan left with his absence. Arriving at the site of Azmodan's husk of a body, Xul used ancient magics to tether this dead body to it's soul, and to pull Azmodan home.

But the Demon's new powers were too great, and it was Xul, after losing a battle of wills, that was pulled into the Korpulu sector, among a crowd of Dark Templar, who had sensed this disturbance through the void.

Explaining himself, and the situation, the Dark Templar trained their new guest, in the ways of the void. Bringing about the first Human Dark Templar. With his void scythe in hand, Xul would restore balance, or die trying.

He, how ever, was not the only one to realize the situation, Tyreal forced himself through dimensions as well. Arriving upon Zerus, the planet home to the Primal Zerg. Being assaulted day and night, eventual he was overwhelmed and his essence consumed by the Zerg. But his is an angelic essence, and not so easily controlled. He wrested back control of the essence in the nearly mindless Zerg that consumed him, and became reborn, as a Pack Leader on Zurvan, rising an army to combat Dark Archon Azmodan.

Now, that many holes began to be punched into their realities, more people and relics were being pulled from Sanctuary. Valla and Johanna found themselves aboard the hyperion, during one of Egon's experiments. Valla took to the Reaper Program very quickly, and Johanna received a modified suit of Murader armour, with a Medic's shield.

Sonya, arrived in the heat of battle between Hierarch Artanis' forces, and Azmodan's legions. Some of his people still held on to the Khala, and one of Azmodan's lieutenants was able to force their minds from their bodies and into that psionic link. When he tried this trick on Sonya, to see what would happen, her body was forced into that of an Empty Zealot, her rage giving birth to psionic blades hotter than any before.

Li Ming, was captured and studied by the Purifiers, eventually blinking out into the vacuum of space in an attempt to escape, killing herself. But the Purifiers were not without mercy, and copied her mind into a new body, built for channeling magical energy, even better than her one of flesh and blood.

The black Soulstone was even pulled across realms, embedding itself in a Hybrid Behemoth that had escaped the fall of Amon, giving Diablo a physical form like no other.

Kharazim, found a home among the High Templar, and was especially fascinated by their mastery over their minds.

The King of Khaduris Leoric, however, found himself aboard Zagara's Leviathain. And together, she and Abathur, shaped his bones anew. Blessing him with muscles and an exoskelton to act as their champion in this coming war between realities, and as King of the Swarm.

The Butcher, found it's way to Zerus after Tyreal, the tribal leader, had taken his forces and departed. On this world, unlike Tyreal initially, the Butcher thrived. And though it would not join the war between these new powers, with it's hunger and the essence of the Zerg, it would become a threat to the Korpulu Sector in it's own right.

- And that my friends, was a shodily done fan fiction pulling together several skin ideas I had for Diablo characters based in the Starcraft Universe. Obvious Nazeebo would throw broodlings and banelings and the such, but I wasn't sure how to work him into it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good overlays for HotS streaming? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 01:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys. I was wondering if anyone knew of any good overlays for Heroes of the storm? I've just started streaming, and I wanted to look fancy too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favorite adult joke hidden in children's media? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 19:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What positive word, sounds really creepy when used as a compliment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 11:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey guys, back when it was announced, there was a big community helping folks power level in Diablo III to get the mount. Are people still doing that? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 20:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Want to solo games in low MMR? Try out The Lord of "Win" my man, AZ-MO-Fuggin'-DAAAN! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 08:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What show do you really wish had just one more season? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 00:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Made a bet that the second hero was going to be Necromancer. Xul just bought himself for me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 17:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With how often safety on the topic came up, as a little one, I used to think I'd be on fire way more often </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 17:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For anyone wondering what Twitch channel they can watch chair league matches on here's one </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 21:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> twitch.tv/josheb

He'll be streaming starting at 5:00PM PT
I'm on team Clutch Bot and would love to get some of that Reddit love for my team! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some party building games like Pokemon/shin megami tensei? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 05:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know about 
Dragon Quest Monsters 1,2   Joker
Azure Dreams, PS and GBC
Digimon World 2, 3, dawn, dusk, DS, and Data Squad (The gameplay of 1 is not quite what I've got in mind.)
Final Fantasty Tactics has an element of it too it, though that's not the main focus.
Robopon 1 2
Fossil fighters 1   2

What else is out there? I'm sure there are more I know about and am just missing, but I'm also sure there are some I've never heard of! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Don't pick the Lost Vikins" "Abathur = GG" "Murky is noob, don't pick" Don't be that guy people. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 22:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Young girl doesn't know how to hang up a phone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 09:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When people say it's easier to make in game money in LoL than it is in HoTS point them at this picture. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 08:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/6CnCmHT.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Azmodan Skin idea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 23:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://vignette4.wikia.nocookie.net/pixar/images/5/51/Henry_J._Waternoose_III.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20110426151326

Demonic warrior
http://greeting-cards-4u.com/platinum6/pictures/images/GraphicsPlus/Toons/Disney/MonsterInc/MikeMI.jpg

Demonic general
http://www.oocities.org/monsters_inc_fan/sully.jpg

Demonic grunts
https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/236x/19/40/e8/1940e8c0f5e56de3504d534c0b93d264.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 24 [M4R] Toronto - Back in the city as of an hour ago, and I feel like getting out tonight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 01:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All my house mates and friends and what not are still gone on vacation (Except one who is sick) and I'd love to enjoy a night out. Food, drinks, dancing, karaoke, games what ever I am game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Type "/join happynewyear" into the chat to join other folks who're flying solo this new years eve! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 03:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three StarCraft map ideas, mild LOTV spoilers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 23:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One lane, no core, giant jungle, mercenary "forts"

In SCII LOTV there is a map where you need to have units surrounding a character, so they can feed off of your unit's psionic energy, and push their opponent back. The opponent has the same mechanic.

How that would work, is you and your team go in the jungle (littered with roaving gangs of zerg that you fight for xp soak) and fight various protoss mercenary camps, sending them middle lane to push. This would mean you'd need people mid to clear enemy mercs and minion spawns, but not too many or your team might get ganked  or overwhelmed by the feral zerg.

There are also merc "forts" which serve as an objective of sorts. When you capture them, they stay captured until they're destroyed by the zerg or your enemies, and the constantly warp in units like Zealots, stalkers, or Immortals.

The bosses could be stone Zealots, and the forts could upgrade to get collosi eventually.

This would be a very different map, but siege heroes would be very valuable for their ability to push forts, and the middle lane(which would be heavily fortified to make up for the lack of two other lanes.)
This map could release with the LOTV character Alarak.

In fact, the mercs being from the Tal'darim makes sense, since they follow the strongest leader.

Building on this is my Zerg map theme.

The Zerg home world from HOTS.

Four lanes (crazy right?) with plenty of feral zerg roaming about. As you kill more and more zerg, the Primal zerg tribe leaders awaken, one in each lane. When you kill them, their lane gets pushed in by groups of primal zerg.

Kraith, bottom lane, sends roaches down his lane. (Least impactful, very good for soaking tower ammo.)

Then its the fire wyrm guy. He sends hydralisks. Very high damage, low HP. You need to guard them.

Then the Swarm host queen. She spawns swarm hosts, huge pushing power siege unit.

Lastly, top lane. Zurvan. If you defeat the most powerful primal zerg, he sends a combination of all the others.

Mercs on this map could be a zergling swarm, a camp with two Ultralisks, and a Brutalisk for the boss.

This map could release with Dehaka.

And I had an idea for a terrain map. The idea comes from "devils due". A map where you mine minerals for Tosh. It is another two lane map, the middle being a pool of lava, with some bridges you can cross to get to camps on islands and then the other side.

Eventually the lava will drain in one of two sectors,(Top left, or top right) and a command center will drop and begin producing SCVs for each team to harvest minerals. You need to protect your SCVs while killing those of the opponent, whereas the command centers will constantly be building them as long as there's no lava.

As your team collects minerals, you'll hire progressively bigger and bigger Terran Mercenary waves. War Pigs, hammer securities, siege breakers etc, down the strongest lane.

This map could release with Gabriel Tosh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Out of curiosity, why is playing as the LITERAL devil, more okay than having a character who smokes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 09:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't a "Bring back his Cigar" thing. A genuine question as to why the Devil (Diablo) doesn't bring the games rating higher than a cigar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of The Lost Viking's lines are "Dashing through the foes" with that in mind... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 09:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~To the tune of Jingle Bells~  

Dashing through the foes  

In that Lost Viking kinda way  

Through the Nexus we go  

Smurfing all the way  

Ho ho ho  

Bells on Towers of Doom   

Ringing our win right in  

What fun it is to smurf and troll  

In this Hero League tonight  

OH!  

Jingle bells Stiches Smells  

Lunara laid an egg  

Sgt Hammer lost a wheel  

And Nazeebo got away hey! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dustin Browder mentioned some heroes deserve a third ult. Who do you think it is, and what ult would you pick? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 03:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The only video you'll ever need for success while playing The Lost Vikings - Guaranteed, or your plunder back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 23:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Lost Vikings' third ultimate discussion - Fang and Scorch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 01:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there folks. So awhile back Dustin Browder tweeted that he wanted to give Zagara a third Ult, and there was no reason heroes only needed to have two. This got me to thinking, what other hero needs a third ult? 

Well. What are Ults? Abilities that really resonate with the character. Something that really shows who they are, and what they can do in their game worlds. Then I thought about the Lost Vikings. Both their ults don't really reflect their games. At all. The death one would never fit, and the boat one, though it reflects their viking heritage, never comes into game. (Other than in unplayable scenes) So they really do need a new one!

So. One thing I loved about their Master Skin, is it's a real progression of the characters to how the look in Lost Vikings II.

What else does that game introduce?
http://www.codiekitty.com/File/2004characters/Fang.gif

Fang and Scorch! At level ten, the vikings would get the ultimate "Fang" and receive a forth member. The werewolf of the same name. And at level 20, the upgrade would be "and Scorch" giving them a fifth member! 

Fang would have high attack and life steal,(And perhaps an automatic charge, like zealot charge? To represent his jumpy play style.) but very short melee range, Scorch would have a short ranged attack that did splash damage.

Now, the idea of them having two additional and permanent members could be problematic. I'm not so sure on the balance of that. So there are several ways this ability could be done.

First, is that they do become permanent members and you control them similar to the other vikings.

Second. When a viking falls in battle, Fang or Scorch spawns to take their place (Until either the backup hero is beaten, or all three vikings are on stage again.) This would give the vikings more staying power.

Third and least fun, you can summon them for a set amount of time to back you up in the fight.

What do you all think? Any suggestions? Anyone who is good with balance and numbers that could apply some numerical value to these two?

I honestly think that this ultimate is a much more thematically appropriate ult for TLV than what they have now. Also, neither Fang nor Scorch has enough to them to make them into a single character. (Though they could potentially be a duo character.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Toronto transplant from Nova Scotia looking for a Minor Christmas Miricale </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 03:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there folks, because ofbcorperate policy at the place I work, asking for time off this time of year is against the rules. Which is fine, and why I'm leaving out the name of the company. I've loved working here.

Now. Onto the issue. My grand father died this past summer and my sister, with the biggest heart I've ever seen, bought me a plane ticket home to spend Christmas with the family. She saved it as a surprise though, and I just found out about it.

I'm not letting her gift go to waste, but my employer is telling me I need to quit my job. I don't want hand outs or anything of the sort. I just want a new job. I'm back in Toronto January second and can start work as soon as the third. Does anyo e have any leads for someone with years of customer service experience, and some web development? (CSS and HTML 5, with some Java)

It would mean the world too me. Any job is good, I live right off of bloor and Spadina. I'm want to work hard and leave my family without worry for me. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lower case "h" is a chair, for the little man made out of "OK" to sit on. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 17:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which chat channels are the best? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 21:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, General, reddit, Cho'Gall, and lfg are okay, but I want to find more people to chat with. Now with the new mount requirments, I want to take some level 4s or lower under my wing and get them to level 10. I'm sure many of you have the same idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The gunners are mercenaries right? Why the balls are they so hostile? I want to hire you people! I want to work for you people! Where do I get a goddamn application? How do you get any customers or new recruits? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 09:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 24 [m4f] Toronto- You may have heard some rumours about me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 17:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, hey clicked on my link did you? Dandy. 
  

But hey, listen, I could go on and on about myself - Tell you about my hobbies like reading. How I devour novels within hours of buying one. I could tell you how I absolutely love day dreaming, or that I enjoy long, long walks (Sometimes both at the same time.). My favorite style of music? Geek Rock. Not that you'll hear it from me. Or how I was working with a rocking tech company a few months ago, Nerf Wars were one of many office hazards. If I was embarrassed about the fact, I'd probably try to hide the fact I like gaming, video and table top, but if someone were to ask me. I'd probably let them know. 

  
You may also hear rumours that I'm a fantastic cook. Not that I'll confirm them, but I'd be lying if I denied them. Haha 

  
Maybe I could tell you about how I love watching videos from TED.com, or that I really enjoy listening to comedians as I work? Nah. I'll keep that to myself too. How about the fact that I'm a huge comic book geek, and I enjoy telling people about all the easter eggs in the movie we just watched? No no. I might come off as too nerdy if I told you that! 

  
Ohh I know. How about that I love hiking and camping? A good beer, and a campfire is a good night in my book. Hmm... But if I said that, then you might start thinking I was a rugged outdoorsy type. Which I'm not. I just like certain things like that, I don't do them often enough for my liking though. Ok. Well. I guess I'll keep my mouth shut for now.

  
- So yeah. Those are just some of things I wont tell you at the moment. Wouldn't want to waste your time eh? Anyway. If you got through all that, I think I'd like to know about you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> QOL enhancement for Diablo: Make his trait something you can toggle on and off </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 20:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With Diablo's trait, he respawns in three seconds. SUPER handy if you're the first to go down during a team fight, and want to get back in there to wreck shit. But you lose all your souls. Loosing something like 1/4th of your total health, your regen goes into the shitter and you really lose your Tankiness and become an underwhelming brusier.

Now, if you're the last person to fall in a fight, then you're spawned in three seconds, only able to roam the fringes of your lane to soak meager xp and souls for a good while, taking you out of the game and making you not so useful.

Wouldn't it make way more sense, if you could make it so Diablo's trait was something you could control? Because the Lord of Terror is an expert at biding his time, and he wouldn't neuter himself just to get back into the fry more quickly. He'd get his arse handed too him! No. Diablo should be able to control when he respawns with his trait.

Take it a step further if you want, and make it for every second of respawn time, he loses two souls. It would still devastate his soul count, but it wouldn't remove him from the game. (Until late game, if you respawned right on death.)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your best "Happened to a friend of mine" story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 03:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What seemingly harmless lie did an authority figure tell you growing up, that you've believed for longer than you should have? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 21:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Meta] Can we have a no, "No Sob stories" rule? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 20:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> battle.net / heroes of the storm not connecting. What's the problem? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 16:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beeping distress signal near med-tek facility. I can't get it higher than 50% any suggestions? Or even, where it's at? haha </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 02:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One Punch Man vs Goku </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 05:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whenever I try to start "Epilogue, mission two" my game freezes. Any advice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 20:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Vulture, how to achieve it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 16:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With Legacy of the void out, it's only a matter of time before the reveal of the Vulture. The Star Craft II achievement mount. Armoured Dire Wolf for WoW, and Phantom of Mathal for Diablo.

Will it be as simple as clearing the campaign? Or do you think there'll be more too it than that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would be the best or worst song, for your favourite character? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 05:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You Sexy Thing" by Barry White for Azmodan, Lord of Sin. Best or worst song for him? You decide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [AMA request] Ice Cube, was your best day ever JANUARY 20 1992? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 03:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit spreads Cho'Gall - Post here if you will have the Seed, reply to Seed comments to make friends with that person and get your Cho'Gall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 01:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They should implement a commendation system, not just for allies but for enemies as well </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 15:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So. I just got my ass HANDED to me, by a Diablo and Zeratul (Some excessive soaking from their lost vikings helped but these guys had skill) and I went out of my way to add them as friends so I could message them and let 'em know what badasses they were that game.

I understand that'd be an uncommon reaction. But they played super well, Diablo body blocked me like he was actually controlling my character. It was beautiful. And that Zeratul? I wasn't alive for more than a blink by the time he'd do just that and cut my chubby throat (I was Azmodan. Making the early mention of getting my ass handed too me more impressive.)

Now, personal experience aside, I think that it would really help cultivate sportsman ship, if there were these little trophies one could assign to non friend list partners and enemies in Hero League. 

Some benefits for being given one of these trophies could be like, five extra gold for your next three games (The gold itself doesn't stack, but say you got two trophies, it'd give you 5 extra gold for six games.) It'd give people a very small incentive to just play longer, and play nicer/better. 

Two trophies you could give to the enemy would be 
"Nemesis - you earned this because an enemy hero saw you as a true rival!"

"Sweet Moves - You've earned this trophy because an opponent has recognized your skills"

Or some variation of the two. 

I played one other game with a System like this, and I really enjoyed it. I LOVED getting one of those little trophies and seeing my scores rise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mel Gibson's movie "Apocalypto" was actually a giant Where's Waldo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 23:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For those of you wondering who the three little viking dudes are are, be prepared to lose several hours of your day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 15:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heroes of the storm has a built in unit preloader, just scroll through each page of the hero section of the shop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 14:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, for those of you who aren't sure what a unit preloader is, basically, it's something you can run that'll load unit models for you, so the game doesn't have to worry about doing it later when it needs to. I don't know the exact science about it, but it makes the first few seconds of your game smoother and less jittery. 

It will not effect the quality of your game in anyway beyond that. This is one of the most useless tips you'll ever see. But it works. So there's that.

EDIT: According to /u/Jinyas it actually is useful for people with poorer hardware, because sometimes it can help you avoid that lag spike that will bump you out of the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just got a Wish spell at level four, want to wish for something fun, but not game breaking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 20:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, so I rolled super good on my loot table and got a Wish Spell. I could Wish for pretty much what ever. (At the very end of the game I wished for a flying pirate ship that was self manned so I could become a pirate king, and the DM said sure. But at level four that doesn't leave much to build towards eh? And I LOVE playing the game for the sake of the game. Not being the biggest and baddest. (Though my character is a badass Goliath Pirate.))

So my question to you guys is, what creative thing could you wish for that would be FUN and worth it but not broken?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tips on building a Cha based Sorcerer Gestalt. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 00:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys. So I love Cha, it my favourite stat. (RP is my Jam.) and I might be joining a Gestalt game soon, and they mentioned they needed an Arcane caster, 25 point buy.

I've never done Gestalt before, so what would be good with Sorcerer? I'll probably go Impossible Bloodline, since I love building stuff. But I'm open to suggestions.

Not sure where they stand on third party stuff, but let's assume any Paizo class for now. What kinda fun can I have? (Let's roll with an assumption of Core races, but I will be asking about advanced races.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The greatest marriage proposal ever aired on a cartoon, perhaps, on all of television (Gargoyles.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 02:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Artanis Discussion thread - so you don't need to start 50 when he gets released today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 17:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's out if you preordered digitally or if you proved a store preorder! 

What the title says. A thread to chat about Artanis/whine about not having him/brag about him being your new main even though you've only played one AI game with him etc. The world is your oyster! Just don't start 50 threads and flood the sub. Save that for the inevitable Zergling hero. (Or Zergling Murky skin.)

Hero spotlight is up
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oxRwiV44EtU


http://i.imgur.com/0hK3n3h.webm I feel like this play (From the video) is the embodiment of "F you, that's why." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you were adopted, you'd never know if you were half Centaur </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 02:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If someone thinks up a shower thought, identical to a popular one, nobody will believe them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 14:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I feel like plenty of roleplayers here know this feeling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 03:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What as the most inappropriate thing you have ever found hilarious? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 23:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Using a collection of pages with "boner" quotes from old batman comics, I wrote a new one! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 19:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/a/r3lZM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PsBattle: Mike and Sully cowering in terror </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 22:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have been looking for a Kingmaker campaign to join as a player for years now. Has anyone ever played it? Is it as fun as I seem to think it could be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 04:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The fact that I didn't click on the R/Creepy link that had it's colour changed, freaked me out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 05:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you're playing and decide that you want to win a game. Which hero do you pick, and why? What makes them your best? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 21:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I grab Azmodan, solo a lane with my laser build, and get 10k xp while everyone else is at 4k giving my team an obscene lead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who else thinks we're going to get a level ten Tass, Zera, Artanis portrait when he comes out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 17:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> By the end of this trial I have grown to love Abathur. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 18:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/qOZhFP7.png

Thank you for being with me from levels 1-5 when I had no idea how to be in lane to soak, so I hid in base.

Thank you for being there through my "Rebellious" years of 6-7 while I tried to Merc build/lane push every game.

And I'm glad you were there for levels 8-10 where I found my true calling as a body soaking, hat giving, Ultimate Evolution badass.

Compared to the cake walk that was Zagara, Abathur was a mother lovin' roller coaster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've been talking to this really cute gal on a dating site, who is into anime, and said she'd love an anime version of herself one day. I'm going to ask her out and would love to surprise her with that. Would anyone be willing to help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 20:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Transformation before and after! She was a real cow before, but now she's a sexy hunk of beef </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 04:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP]You travel back in time to meet a person who at one point did something impactful to your life, but you could never find them after that exact moment, you then realize that you were that person all along </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 17:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP]You travel back in time to meet a person who at one point did something impactful to your life, but you could never find them after that exact moment, you then realize that you were that person all along </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 16:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I tweeted to Ellen to try and be cute by getting her help to get me a date, retweet to help me get her attention? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 21:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cinder Skull Leoric - A skin concept </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 19:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, so I am not artistically talented enough to accurately portray this, but here are two images that will help.

http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_small/1/10354/1910151-403px_bandersnatcher.jpg

http://www.angelfire.com/mi/dinosaurs/images/casts/acrocanthosaurus_arm_cast.jpg

So, the idea is, he's a normal skeleton with only one arm, the bones are black, and he has fire all over him, his single arm is giant, the size of his club basically. So when he attacks, his animation is actually him taking a swipe and smashing with his giant arm.

When he uses drain hope, the fire launches from his claw to grab people, and his claw has no flames on it while he's attacking.

When he's using his E, his skeleton remains, while the flames fly away.

Skeletal swing is pretty much the same.

His tomb is actually stacked wood, like for a pyre, and if you upgrade it to deal damage the edges begin to burn, rather than spikes forming inside.

This also goes really well with his burning aura. Haha

Any thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] You are the great Orc poet "Unt Lick", come to the shinning capital of the pink skins(Humans, Elves, Dwarves etc) so you can show the other races just how cultural yours actually can be. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 19:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need help writing a "book of Orcish Poetry" the poems can be as crash and silly as you'd expect. The authors name is "Unt Lick." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 19:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of you might remember "Doctor Dok'Taur's book of stupid science" that we all had a blast working on before. Well, in the LARP I play him in, he found a "Book of Orcish poetry: By Unt Lick." and I would love to have you all help me again! Because I want to literally write this book out, and have a physical representation in game.
Some info about Orcs in game:
Orcs eat other races, they have breeding pits, they leave their children to fend for themselves in a big pen that they sometimes throw meat into for them (Other times the kids eat one another.)
A smart orc is still dumber than a stupid human (Hence why my Orc Doctor has a book of stupid science), but they are incredibly disciplined when it comes to battle, more so than any other race. That's why they're still around.
Basically though, they're what you'd expect from Orcs. I'd love to see what you guys can come up with.

And I'd love to be able to actually play "Unt Lick" in Pathfinder as an Orcish bard, using these poems every time I preform. Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need help writing a "book of Orcish Poetry" the poems can be as crash and silly as you'd expect. The authors name is "Unt Lick." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 19:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of you might remember "Doctor Dok'Taur's book of stupid science" that we all had a blast working on before. Well, in the LARP I play him in, he found a "Book of Orcish poetry: By Unt Lick." and I would love to have you all help me again! Because I want to literally write this book out, and have a physical representation in game.

Some info about Orcs in game:

Orcs eat other races, they have breeding pits, they leave their children to fend for themselves in a big pen that they sometimes throw meat into for them (Other times the kids eat one another.) 

A smart orc is still dumber than a stupid human (Hence why my Orc Doctor has a book of stupid science), but they are incredibly disciplined when it comes to battle, more so than any other race. That's why they're still around.

Basically though, they're what you'd expect from Orcs. I'd love to see what you guys can come up with.

Edit 1: Obviously I want to connect this to DnD, and I love the idea of being able to bring this book of poetry into my table top adventures too as an Orcish bard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bosses killing MULES with a mini root. Is it a bug? Or a feature? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 20:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even the Anubis Scarab dudes. They literally shoot one little green root out to one shoot a MULE, and I don't mean the larger circle root used to target players. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I too went to the reddit restaurant... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 22:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to ask other customers for sauce for any of the dishes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 24[M4F] Toronto - I figured I'd address some of the rumours going around about me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 21:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, hey clicked on my link did you? Dandy. 

But hey, listen, I could go on and on about myself - Tell you about my hobbies like reading. How I devour novels within hours of buying one. I could tell you how I absolutely love day dreaming, or that I enjoy long, long walks (Sometimes both at the same time.). My favorite style of music? Geek Rock. Not that you'll hear it from me. Or how I was working with a rocking tech company a few months ago, Nerf Wars were one of many office hazards. If I was embarrassed about the fact, I'd probably try to hide the fact I like gaming, video and table top, but if someone were to ask me. I'd probably let them know. 

You may also hear rumours that I'm a fantastic cook. Not that I'll confirm them, but I'd be lying if I denied them. Haha 

Maybe I could tell you about how I love watching videos from TED.com, or that I really enjoy listening to comedians as I work? Nah. I'll keep that to myself too. How about the fact that I'm a huge comic book geek, and I enjoy telling people about all the easter eggs in the movie we just watched? No no. I might come off as too nerdy if I told you that! 

Ohh I know. How about that I love hiking and camping? A good beer, and a campfire is a good night in my book. Hmm... But if I said that, then you might start thinking I was a rugged outdoorsy type. Which I'm not. I just like certain things like that, I don't do them often enough for my liking though. Ok. Well. I guess I'll keep my mouth shut for now.

- So yeah. Those are just some of things I wont tell you at the moment. Wouldn't want to waste your time eh? Anyway. If you got through all that, I think I'd like to know about you.

Here's a recent photo, by the by. http://i.imgur.com/kkkBVlK.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [M4F]Some rumours about me have been going around </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 21:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, hey clicked on my link did you? Dandy. 

But hey, listen, I could go on and on about myself - Tell you about my hobbies like reading. How I devour novels within hours of buying one. I could tell you how I absolutely love day dreaming, or that I enjoy long, long walks (Sometimes both at the same time.). My favorite style of music? Geek Rock. Not that you'll hear it from me. Or how I was working with a rocking tech company a few months ago, Nerf Wars were one of many office hazards. If I was embarrassed about the fact, I'd probably try to hide the fact I like gaming, video and table top, but if someone were to ask me. I'd probably let them know. 

You may also hear rumours that I'm a fantastic cook. Not that I'll confirm them, but I'd be lying if I denied them. Haha 

Maybe I could tell you about how I love watching videos from TED.com, or that I really enjoy listening to comedians as I work? Nah. I'll keep that to myself too. How about the fact that I'm a huge comic book geek, and I enjoy telling people about all the easter eggs in the movie we just watched? No no. I might come off as too nerdy if I told you that! 

Ohh I know. How about that I love hiking and camping? A good beer, and a campfire is a good night in my book. Hmm... But if I said that, then you might start thinking I was a rugged outdoorsy type. Which I'm not. I just like certain things like that, I don't do them often enough for my liking though. Ok. Well. I guess I'll keep my mouth shut for now.

- So yeah. Those are just some of things I won't tell you at the moment. Wouldn't want to waste your time eh? Anyway. If you got through all that, I think I'd like to know about you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [r4r] - Toronto [non-romantic] I saw, on the front page, the mini doc about offline dating. I want to take that further, and do a longer video about Modern dating. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 17:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will need at least two people for camera work, and a gal co-"star" who can show us dating from a female's perspective. But more "stars" of both genders, and all races, the better. Comment in this thread, who's in?

(Stars in this context being people who go out into the street and interview/ask out other individuals.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know if the court of owls collectors mask is comfortable to wear with glasses? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 05:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Little girl gets photoshopped into a GTA scene good guy EzArtPrints sends it to the family for free on a canvas. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 01:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was recently gifted a Hewlett Packard Officejet 4500 Wireless printer, but there is no power cord for it. I cannot find one on your store, or an affordable one(I'm a student) on the internet. Shipping always kills it! Any advice or help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 02:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PsBattle: This horrified girl's face </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 16:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dustin Browder favourited my tweet about adding a draft mode to quick match. Thoughts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 03:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He's not wrong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-30 22:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What the rest of reddit looks like when an R/Funny post makes the front page. Thanks for finding all the diamonds in the rough guys! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-30 03:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [META] The greatest Roasters of all time, expressing what people must be thinking as they post on this sub. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-30 03:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I even mirrored the image so you wouldn't need to strain yourself trying to read my shirt. Let's see how long it takes before you need to call out my beard. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 23:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the kindest thing you've ever heard of, seen, or had done to you, by/for a stranger? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 22:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remember the Orc Doctor with a shitty book of science? I've taken some of the gems I've come up with and recived from all over reddit, and added them to the bottom of this google Doc. Enjoy the fruits of your labour r/DnD! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 01:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, feel free to comment on other shitty science ideas that Doctor Doc'Taur might spout off!

https://docs.google.com/document/d/1b1yBa4a0EYuoEqhshzSQS2DwtV1DE_k4wqh6tvzUxRU/edit?usp=sharing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doctor Dok'taur's book of probable science, as it stands. Scroll down to page 3, ya'all helped with this so I figured I'd share. Feel free to comment more ideas! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 00:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am making a character for an RP, called "Doctor Doc'taur", his entire stichk is "Shitty science" what are some of your favourites that a medieval person could think up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 06:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best "Made up" but plausible sounding bit of science, you can come up with to convince a medieval person who travelled from the past, that this is how the world works? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 05:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need help writing a book of "Plausible Science" for an Orc character </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 05:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, so basically, what kind of thing would sound "about right" to a medieval person/Orc who loves science but doesn't quite get it. Here are some examples.

"Giant spiders eat people and forest animals because they have less than eight legs. Stand back to back with your legs splayed to fool them into thinking you're a spider."

"Things fall to the ground, not because they are heavy, but because the sky is a coward and pushes everything but pretty birds and tiny bugs to the ground. It is very scared of dragons so it wont touch them." - Gravity

"Your skin is also cowardly, that is why it moves out of the way of sharp things when you get cut, and you hurt because your skin is angry at you for letting it come that close to sharp things"

But I also want him to be spot on about things, that just sounds dumb to people of that time period

"You're sick because tiny little monsters are running around inside your body, and it makes you feel that way. You need to wash your hands all the time so you can keep them out of you." - Germs

The Orc's Name is Doctor Dok'taur, and this is his book of plausible science. 

I want to have pages and pages to reference. What've ya got? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need help writing a "Book of Plausible Science" for a Orc "Doctor" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 05:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, so basically, what kind of thing would sound "about right" to a medieval person/Orc who loves science but doesn't quite get it. Here are some examples.

"Giant spiders eat people and forest animals because they have less than eight legs. Stand back to back with your legs splayed to fool them into thinking you're a spider."

"Things fall to the ground, not because they are heavy, but because the sky is a coward and pushes everything but pretty birds and tiny bugs to the ground. It is very scared of dragons so it wont touch them." - Gravity

"Your skin is also cowardly, that is why it moves out of the way of sharp things when you get cut, and you hurt because your skin is angry at you for letting it come that close to sharp things"

But I also want him to be spot on about things, that just sounds dumb to people of that time period

"You're sick because tiny little monsters are running around inside your body, and it makes you feel that way. You need to wash your hands all the time so you can keep them out of you."

The Orc's Name is Doctor Dok'taur, and this is his book of plausible science. I want to have pages and pages to reference. What've ya got? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two Abathur upgrades I think would help a lot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 17:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I've been playing Abathur a lot lately (Mostly in quick match, god help me) and I've noticed something. His shield doesn't scale. Unless I had a glitch, his shield stayed at 140 the entire game! Decent at the very start. Terrible by the end. Raynor can do over 300 a hit at the end of the game, so the fact that my shield heals and increases speed is awesome. Other than the fact it doesn't scale up so a sneeze removes it from my ally before they get any benefits.

The other thing is, I'm sure we've all noticed the free slot abathur has when he's not hatted, and while it doesn't really need anything there, I think something neat would be a "blinding cloud" like the defilers from Starcraft, or Vipers from Starcraft II.

This would make it so enemies in the cloud would miss each attack, and give an aggressive Abathur a way to escape a Nova or Zeratul gank.

Tl:Dr Scaling shield and a blinding cloud for escaping would help Abathur big time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some fun ways to build a PC Necromancer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 17:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's assume the Core rules only at first, so we can have him in every game. 

Then move to Advanced rules for added fun if you can think of any.

I'm curious about playing a Wizard, since I've never played one before. (I've played like every other class.)

But also very curious as to how a Cleric might manage as well.

Extra question. Could a Druid manage with an undead animal companion? 

Could you get a Vampire or other undead companion with the leadership feat?

Edit: Oh and I'm looking for more flavour rather than optimized. So have fun with it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Online][Pathfiner] Player looking for a new twice monthly group. I did a lot of dming for awhile and want to get back in the PC seat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 06:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey folks. I was looking to find a game for every second Friday or Saturday starting this Saturday Ideally, but the one after next if nothing else (I have a Larp I'm going too next Sat.)
I'm happy to play in any setting and I'd be thrilled to play starting from a low level and building up. I also roleplay pretty well, I generally use Skype for communication. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone want to play on Roll20? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 05:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Being dropped into leaver que for lag </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 03:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anyone else found they fall into the leaver que when they lag out? Like. I've had games where I dropped right as we were winning and been placed in the leaver Que! 

I'm getting tired of it really. I mean, it's only happened four times. But each of those times it just took too long to reconnect to the game, and it was over by the time I could. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] A week late, but I return with yet another plee ye lords of Pizza. Please hear your lamb's call and at long last accept this offering of Pizza themed memes and jokes and information! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 21:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We shall begin with this peasant's insulting mistake to ye oh lords http://i.imgur.com/gvHOU17.jpg

Then, this this former celebrity's descent into Pizza worship! His are the hymns of your greatness! http://i.imgur.com/H1W8RYz.jpg

This guide on how to get laid, as truly Pizza is the only afrodisiac man needs http://i.imgur.com/5eGYeIm.jpg
Or this tale, of how your missionaries go above and beyond their station to bring joy to your worshipers! http://imgur.com/a/FodFS?gallery

And this recipe to cater to your finger food needs! http://imgur.com/a/Hj9Vb?gallery

And take this photo, showing that even our most adored worship at your plate! http://i.imgur.com/PfozKEX.jpg?1

And this, the only accurate predictor of your people's preference in online communities http://i.imgur.com/wYwl9nh.jpg

And here ye, even our pets share our love of your greatness! http://i.imgur.com/ZAJhaZt.png

Here you see that Random acts of your greatness transcends the borders of this site! http://imgur.com/a/YMUgl?gallery

One of the greatest failings of humanity http://i.imgur.com/Uo2JyAi.jpg

And this blasphemer's theft from your priests! Strike him down with a saucey vengeance! http://i.imgur.com/K9zOMj6.webm

And when all else fails, when you know not what topping to order, the answer is obvious to all! http://i.imgur.com/1KgUFWd.jpg

This slightly nsfw tale of how one of your missionaries grew wise to those trying to avoid paying tribute! http://i.imgur.com/jPn4TbL.jpg

And this rendition of what I wish more than life itself for my future! http://i.imgur.com/Z69iRLJ.gif

How I envy this worshiper her challenges! http://i.imgur.com/FaDKTvR.jpg

And here, the most sensual display of pizza any has ever beheld! http://i.imgur.com/UzqfR9e.gif

How your priests prepare your greatness around the globe! http://imgur.com/t/pizza/MdCQX

And here I have found that even the most holy of holies is a worshiper at YOUR temple! http://i.imgur.com/WzTn5PK.webm

And to further warm thine heart! http://i.imgur.com/haJVGLC.jpg

And here oh great ones! The miracle of birth in motion! http://i.imgur.com/KCDx1vF.webm

And here you see the heroisim of your preiests as one of your worshipers uses prayer to reach out! http://imgur.com/a/I9PHi?gallery

Now we see one of your worshiper's in their finest vestments! http://i.imgur.com/KC2o02z.jpg

This radical proves that there is no wrong way to order pizza. http://i.imgur.com/F5UGmEN.png

And this youthful worshiper using your glory to save the life of a loved one! http://i.imgur.com/nJGkSmL.jpg?1

And lastly, this comic, that extols the greatness and love that is pizza. http://imgur.com/gallery/pxvC6

Please oh great pizza lords! Hear the humble prayers of this student, tired of rice beans and homemade fry's. Grace him with your cheesy glory! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What sounds like the most interesting click bait title you've ever read? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 20:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yeah. Fuck you Trevor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 07:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are we telling Trevor this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was a game changing moment in science, history, art war, etc? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-22 02:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Protoss themed skin ideas for the upcoming Legacy of the Void! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 16:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Archon Azmodan
High Templar Jaina
Zealot Sonya
Immortal Sgt Hammer
Hybrid Diablo


How about you folks? Any ideas as to what could be a cool Protoss themed look? 

Maybe Zerg or Terran to help balance all this out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
