<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2746</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Craftsman no longer considered "buy it for life"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-11 15:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 03:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, can you explain what all that means? I am a rotten photographer in need of schooling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 01:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do please enjoy this upvote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 14:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You fix this by ignoring those "beautiful sentences" when you sit down to write.  Just put your character in motion; that's why we read, to fall in lust or love with your characters, or to hate them, or just to see them move across a ballroom floor.  But move they must.  All of the lovely phrases will come on their own time, in a natural way.  Or they won't.  Sometimes movement is enough to carry a story.  In the words of William Goldman, "It ain't about inspiration.  It's about going into a room alone and doing it." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-30 22:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have a complicated username, but I agree with you nonetheless.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-30 22:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why wouldn't he? He has a history of tweeting things to build anticipation as a release date draws near. Seems like all the vitriol inspired by the renders would elicit a response. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has Joe B. even hinted that these recent renders are accurate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-30 22:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like most of you, I'm underwhelmed by the possible outward appearance of the two new Lumias. I'm hoping the renders represent old prototypes. Any clues either way from the Man himself? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-30 17:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want a Surface phone that looks like my beautiful Zune HD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 20:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My three-year-old 920 looks better than these. Sigh. I will stick with this trusty phone until a nice alternative arrives. Microsoft designers, go home; you're drunk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 16:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I occasionally run a search on my favorite author to see what the world is saying about him.  : ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 15:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just found this post.  I'm late commenting, but anyway . . .

I am an enormous Bradbury devotee.  But I've never agreed with him on this.  Yes, college English teachers do know more than you about writing.  Every year I look at 200 freshmen in my various sections of Comp I, and they can't find their way around a sentence without a map, sextant, and divining rod.  Those are not 200 Bradburys out there.  Those are 200 non-English majors who've been arc-welded to their phones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 15:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, I get that.  I understand the concept of "movements" to help us categorize authors and their influences.  But I'm talking about "style."  Lovecraft, Ligotti, Matt Cardin, and other writers of weird horror have many things in common when it comes to stylistic choices, tone, adjective use, and narrative voice.  I was just wondering if someone had offered a name for that style.  At any rate, I'll keep reading them.   : ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 05:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same experience here. I still rock my HD on long road trips. Gorgeous design. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a name for the writing style of folks like Lovecraft and Ligotti? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 22:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their works tend to have long, dense paragraphs, full of vivid description.  Their stories are often told in first person, with the narrator making lengthy observations about their environment and their own emotions.  Maybe these are traits common to the horror genre, but is there a name for that style of writing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 15:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand the significance of this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 14:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another Firefly vote! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 23:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fell in love with the story when I was young, and now I teach it to college freshmen. Glorious, indeed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 19:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just named my favorite Bradbury story of all time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 01:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm interested in hearing more about solo war games. Could you point me in the right direction or offer any insight or links?  Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 13:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cleopatra and the Society of Architects. I truly love this game, but it's not exceptionally rated at BGG. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 13:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A DM should be fully prepared. You need to have read the entire module and be comfortable with it. Knowing the end of the adventure might have significant influence on how you adjudicate something in the middle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FURY ROAD: Where is it placed in the MAD MAX chronology? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 18:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anyone stated if the film is set in between those of the original trilogy?  Or is it a sequel to those films? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 03:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the interconnected Marvel Universe. Just wait. Soon they'll embed key plot elements in the commercials. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 02:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch AGENTS OF SHIELD tonight and find out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 06:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know only a handful of the bands mentioned so far. I am culturally illiterate. :-( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 00:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Paizo supplied a lot of books for the project, but I'm not sure about the details.

I think that if enough gamers knew about this, that young gamemaster in Uganda would find himself funded for quite some time.  : ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 22:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome.  When I was in junior high, a discovery of RPGs really changed things for me.  I am so happy for the opportunity to help promote such a cool project. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 19:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone should support his project, regardless of the edition or game system we prefer:

http://www.crowdfunder.co.uk/the-village-roleplaying-project/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Young Man's Noble Pathfinder Quest in Uganda </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 19:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 02:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, I came here to say those exact words. I hate seeing Fox News links in my daily feed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 15:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is "Sauber" pronounced SAW-ber or SOW-ber? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 13:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all need to submit Cortana feedback on this issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 14:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm no workplace psychologist, but I'm not sure a desire to win can overcome the negative context of this relationship. But I hope for the best. I would love to see them succeed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 04:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So a driver is intent on driving for a team that doesn't want him.  Does either party actually expect this arrangement to result in points this weekend? What a disastrous start to the Sauber season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft sold $10.75 billion in debt. What does this mean? Why was it done? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 13:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 00:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A sophomoric stunt to sell a book.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 18:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool. My 920 continues to serve me well, but I look forward to a new flagship soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does the light background consume more battery life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 16:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always used the dark background, but the light can look nice with the proper home screen. Does it put more strain on the battery? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 14:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've voiced it before: Cortana needs to ignore news sources as the user commands. I hate seeing Fox news in my daily feed. I wouldn't visit their site even if the road was paved with bitcoins.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 23:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I use the Lumia Camera to keep the subject in focus but with a blurry background? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 16:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know nothing of photography. Where can I find tips on learning to take cooler pics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone here use the watch pocket in your jeans? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 17:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since I was a kid, I've been wearing Levi's jeans, but I've never found a use for that little pocket. Is it just for looks and tradition, or is everyone but me making use of it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 23:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thomas Dunne, an imprint of St. Martin's. What a great colophon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With the season complete, what is the extent of changes that teams can make to their power units before next season? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 21:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm unclear on the "engine freeze" rules. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 04:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. Great information. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
