<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3944</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 17:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it has more than 100 base speed, go for its offensive stat and speed... then HP. That's just my rule of thumb.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 17:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To add; Pokerus only spreads after battles, and expires after midnight if the pokemon isn't in the PC. The benefits of Pokerus will still apply to the cured pokemon, but will be unable to spread it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 09:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jynx
Dunsparce
Breloom
Everything that's not Staraptor
Swoobat
Aromatisse/amologogogogoga </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 09:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn if only such a douchebag trying to be hilarious was able to contain himself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever seen a Genesect in the GTS? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 07:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I try to search for it in the GTS, but nothing comes up. Is it really that rare? Victini and just about every other event legendary shows up, just not Genesect. And Mew I think. Is this intended? Or are there really just none for trade? Or can they not go through the GTS? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 07:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like someone applied the filter... Called. Uh.. Cutout? And just simplified it to like... Three colors.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 07:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gallade. It's like having a friend/body guard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 05:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Commented on this post </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 03:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. That's annoying. Like, why even put the interaction in the game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 03:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My electric/fighting type would be some kind of mammalian creature... Perhaps simian in appearance... He could learn some punching moves. Hmmmmm. Maybe his name would be Electrifighter... Electrivire... Hmm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 03:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like bug types... If they have a steel type attached... And mega evolve...

And are named Scizor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 03:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clawitzer... Mantis Shrimp op

I might be biased because I use these, but I also really like Gallade and Golurk shiny... And Volcorona.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 03:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ash sucks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 00:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Putting megathread in a title doesn't make it a megathread </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 23:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pokebank only holds 3000... Not as many slots as you think if you're a breeder.

Edit: but that's irrelevant. I don't know if other people share my view, but I like accumulating all of my trainer stats.. OH, the biggest thing, being able to rename pokemon (being the OT) I wanted to reset my X game, but I wouldnt be able to rename the pokemon I transferred from there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pokemon should have New Game + </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 23:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You keep your Pokedex, items, and PC Pokemon, but you can't use them until you finish the epilogue... The incentive for New Game + would be the allowance of 20 more boxes (or so) for beating the game... I love playing through the game but... Collecting everything is a nightmare.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 23:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm an armed security guard and I feel weird sometimes... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 23:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 17:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 17:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Luxury balls all day err'day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 09:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 02:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Childhood improved* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 01:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought you couldn't post shiny pictures of pokemon? (Genually new) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
