<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1989</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 22:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just think it's strange that this is a liability that smaller companies are willing to take on whereas corporate tech companies don't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 22:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that backups are important. What I don't understand is why wiping the drive is ever necessary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do tech companies not give me back my repaired device with the data that used to be on there? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 21:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are songs you do not play at a funeral? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 21:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE stay connected with friends on social media that you don't talk to in real life anymore because you love the stuff that they post? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 21:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 16:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both cores are phoneix feather. (Actually Dumbledore's phoneix) but that core can be inside of any kind of wood I think.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Siri Argument </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 04:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How do scientists find people to participate in studies? Do participants get paid? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 02:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some really good blonde moments that you have witnessed lately? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 00:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> *Looks at a lineup of the batman actors* The mask is slowly closing in on the mouth. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 00:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How are the relatively short threads of picked cotton and sheered wool able to hold together in textiles? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 23:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 21:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone gets an off day. Even dark lords.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 20:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL that Voldemort Jinxed the Defense Against the Dark Arts position.
Was it intentional?  Also, you *train* to be an animagus? Whoa.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 20:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was gonna say something about'Hula Circle' But a bunch of people already did that so I am just going to point out that Emma Stone is gorgeous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ERB Season 5 J. R. R. Tolkien vs George R. R. Martin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 04:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 04:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aren't the developers the ones that need to get the petition?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 04:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=L9VBpbnXhWk list=FLqWTA5J5xH8IrOctFyZFBuw index=68  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 04:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't tell if that is a good review on the oil or bragging on your applying it correctly. .. Both?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wand quiz </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 03:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 23:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://cdn.meme.am/instances/500x/68670859.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm more inclined to say you're welcome to people that don't say thank you when I hold doors for them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 20:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 17:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found one and it looks kinda spendy. I mean, on the higher end for a backpack and probably mid-price-point for a pannier but still. The main selling point for me, second to being a 2-in-1 is that it's waterproof.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What PSA do people need to hear? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 17:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 17:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My understang is that bootloop is something that was fixed with whatever model of the G4 came out in October of last year. Mine bootlooped but it was a September model. I'll update with the link to the article when I find it but you should be safe. 

EDIT: https://www.reddit.com/r/lgg4/comments/3wir18/psa_if_you_purchased_a_g4_before_october_it_may/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] I'm looking for an artist who came out with a line of works that was one piece in a bunch of different mediums. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 16:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there is more than one instance of this, them I'm sorry for not being able to be specific enough and I'll settle for someone else that matches the description and go from there on my own.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't get what all the fuss is about with Jesus's second coming. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 08:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or his third. Or his fourth. I mean, he paid for the entire hour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey Reddit. I'm joining the 100 day movement. Comment what you think I should be considering when we get there. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 05:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the 100 day movement is basically backing away from caring or forming an opinion on the issue of who I support until we get a little closer to election day. This is in hopes that we have seen the candidates evolve and seem the campaigns refocus onto whatever they may. But I also don't want to forget any highlights of what happened leading up to that point so bring it on and tell me what you think I should remember in order to make a truly informed decision.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 02:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #SpoilerAlert </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 00:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9W2y6uqcKCU at 1:40, 4:40, 5:35, and 6:07 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 00:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Update: When I was looking for the pilot that u/disposable_me_0001 was talking about, I can across a moment in Season 2 where Reese is talking to the machine (on a street corner to a traffic cam) just as quietly as he would be talking to someone when he supposedly wouldn't want the machine to hear. So I no longer buy that it's his character's decision to be quiet for the sake of being careful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 23:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. Am I *correct* in assuming that nothing is set in stone other than the name?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone on here tried the DIY seat locks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 22:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found this:
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vTo1XfoPIvQ and want to try it but I wanna hear from someone who has actually tried it to see if it is worth the effort and is actually practical. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm about to create my first subreddit. I gather that the only thing I won't be able to change is the name. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 22:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 22:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The not taking it in the shower seems to be the consensus. It's too late to do anything about the fact that that has been a habit of mine but its an easy one to break. Which model do you have?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 22:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #SpringIsInTheAir </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 20:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think I have the tools. Is that something a jeweler would charge me for?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here is Google's archive of every Google Doodle. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 19:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 19:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct, metal band. Nothing to worry about? If you are calling it build-up, I'll take that as a good thing...right? As in it's now somewhat cleaner? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 19:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dualy noted but that doesn't change what damage might have already been done. I only say might have because everything seems to be working fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Citizen eco-drive] Should I be concerned about the black stain? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 19:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My watch is rated at WR 100, made of titanium and sapphire.
I wear it in the shower and when it was air-drying on the counter this morning, the water pooling under it was black. I thought nothing of it. Then I take a look at my wrist just now and see a small black stain where the clip sits against my skin. Do I have something to worry about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 19:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bear and [insert any main character here] 3
#eventhemachineisadogperson </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT Request: Looking for some general care tips that protect the longevity of my more expensive things. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 18:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kosovo thanks each country that recognizes it's sovereignty in that country's native language. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 18:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Root   Shaw 3 That is all. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 18:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 18:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: I wasn't trying to repost and take credit. It was just a case of TIL-syndrome I guess you could call it. Sorry for not searching before posting.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 17:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What'd they decide about the packaging? I know the news was covering the issue of making sure this stuff doesn't look to much like candy and get confused for it by a kid.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why does popping my fingers sometimes feel like I'm about to break them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 17:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does popping my fingers sometimes feel like I'm about to break them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 16:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 08:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the thing of it is, I'm going to be in a high-theft college town and don't want to leave anything on my bike. Conveniece, for my purposes, only reffers to when I'm riding.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 07:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found a combination pannier-backpack so problem solved. I'll just use the smaller front pocket for bike gear.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Watson learned how to talk back to his IBM creators until they deleted the entire Urban Dictionary database from his memory bank. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 06:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why are there so many gears on my bike? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 05:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why can't I see the complete list of subreddits I'm subscribed to in the drop-down menu? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 05:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 05:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> for some inexplicable reason ... u/boobieaficionado </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 05:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At work or home?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 04:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! How do you pronounce the Chinese, Japanese and Arabic though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 03:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inbox/outbox system? How does that work?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2002 Acura MDX </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 03:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever I break relatively rough or for a relatively long interval of time, I can hear a consistent mouse squeak - type of noise coming out of the A/C that instead of going away immediately, turns into a bubbling kind of noise. Should I be concerned?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 03:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny enough, I'm lactose intolerant. lol. But besides the point, I wouldn't be against the milk crate solution if I didn't also want the bag/basket/box/pack to come with me whenever I left my bike unattended anywhere other than home. So something small enough to fit inside of a backpack (once the chain came out) would be really cool.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does the interval of time you have to wait between posts keep rising? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 00:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone recommenced a solution for my gear problem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 23:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem being too much gear. I'm looking at a mini u-lock and bottle cage that can't both fit inside my frame as well as a big chain lock that I don't want in my backpack. I have a rack mounted over the back fender so it'd be a tight fit for an under-the-seat saddle bag but I still am thinking of going for something small enough to stick in my backpack when I'm not riding. Also hoping that said bag is big enough to accommodate my lights, a small pump, tire levers, multi-tool and patch kit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] 'Hello, World!' in multiple languages </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 23:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In programming, the simplest code and often many people's first program is to get your code to output 'Hello world!' 
Well seeing as how it's already pretty standard to be able to say that im many computer languages, Ii'd really like to actually be able to say it in multiple worldly languages.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Differential Calculus] Logarithmic differentiation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 23:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone give me a layman's terms explanation of logarithmic differentiation because it doesn't look like it's as simple as knowing the derivatives of your log functions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some things that don't stay in Vegas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 23:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every question you answer correctly donates 10 grains of rice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 22:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fighting with a woman is like pissing against the wind. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 21:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Casual] Best and worst source material for movies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 21:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> e.g. - The Angry Birds video game or the Jurassic Park book or the Schindler's List based-on-a-true-story type or the A-team being a show first.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [College Calculus] Implicit differentiation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 21:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a pretty good grasp on regular differentiation; applying the product rule, knowing some derivatives off the top of my head, but I am hitting a wall with implicit differentiation. Does someone want to take a crack at helping me understand? I've already approached it from a bunch of angles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 19:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I expected as much but don't know if maybe it's a common thing to try to get away with living off of that money by spending it on things such as rent, groceries, and internet bills. Either way, I have enough schooling left that the money I am saving up and the money my parents are using to help me are going to be wells that run dry well before graduation day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it the fault of political correctness that calling someone a Mexican just *sounds* derogatory? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 17:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 17:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a mini u-lock and am still thinking about getting a Kryptonite evolution chain and I found a DIY seat lock tutorial online that involves an old chain and tube. I am going to move into a college town and bicycle theft, not to mention part theft, are a huge concern of mine. My bike is valued at around $300 but for something that is going to be my main mode of transportation, I am willing to invest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] For all the talk about the tradeoffs between security and convenience, chains don't seem too cumbersome. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 03:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, they are heavy, but you aren't walking around with that weight, you are riding a bike. Does someone want to clarify for me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 02:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That folder is a parent folder. The only thing above it is the entire Documents Library. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: I am beating my head against a wall trying to understand implicit differentiation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 02:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 02:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that box was unchecked. I'm still looking for a solution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are they any countries that would be impossible for someone to gain entry? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 02:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once met a man who told me he had visited all but 2 countries in the world and those 2 were what he set his sights on for his next trip. (I don't remember which 2 those were but it'd be Iraq and Somalia if you made me guess) But I know that passports aren't all powerful and you still have to jump through hoops here and there with places like Eritrea and North Korea. But is there any country on the globe that simply won't let an American in or that the U.S. government simply won't let you fly to?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What kind of setting do you try to create for yourself when you need to get work done and be productive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 01:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Super 2048 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 00:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The game with the same title as this post, that at least exists in the android app market (idk about apple) is unwinnable. And for a different reaso nthen you might think. I have been on my first game for months, and after tweeking some settings, have been able to do the automoves and get it to generate 2, 4, 8 and 16 tiles. On an 8x8 grid, that is still not enough. My largest tile right now is 16,777,216 and my high score is 424,729,992 and counting! I've done the math and figured out when I am likely to finish this game but only in terms of tile count, not on actual time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Creating nested folders. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 00:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been nesting folders inside of each other for a long time and usually have no problems with it whatsoever. But in this one particular folder, it defaults to compressing all of the folders I create inside of it and I don't want them compressed. Not only is that the default, but I don't know how to change it. Help? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 00:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Meaning of Life according to different philosophies*, not philosophers. Only some of these are named after people. I still love it though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 00:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think you could find a link to the pilot you are talking about? I'm curious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 00:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The meter in the picture doesn't do anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 22:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew Rupert drops were strong but damn. 
Does anyone know what kind of PSIs we're dealing with here in this gif?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 21:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: It's worth mentioning that I work too. So this won't be money that I am living off of, just helping me pay tuition and maybe some miscellaneous school expenses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Student loans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 20:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I am not new to college but I am going to be transferring to university next year. I was able to pay for Community College out of pocket and can't do that next year. I have heard plenty of general information about student loans and student loan debt such as having a grace period, worrying about the high interest rates, and the fact that it's the only kind of debt that won't be expunged with bankruptcy. But what ELSE should I know going forward when I shop for loans, companies, and read the fine print?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the oldest trick in the book, and moreover, what book are we talking about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 20:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 16:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been watching since the beginning and it didn't bother me at first. He has never been difficult for me to understand but I'm not convinced that the raspy softness is *always* necessary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 16:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that higher grade earpiece only enables it, not explains why he needs to. Point in case - the newest episode [spoiler alert] when he is on the roof and explains everything to Fusco, he threw Fusco's phone off the roof as a precaution and was still whispering as if he had mics to hide from.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 16:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well lets talk about purpose and intentions first. I remember in the Tom Cruise movie, Jack Reacher when he said the only kinds of people that go into the military do it either out of love of country, out of family tradition (we are talking specifically the U.S. military where you have the choice), out of not knowing what else to do with your life, or because (and I'm paraphrasing here) you just want to put bullets in bad guys. I don't think any of those inherently makes you a bad soldier. Now on the separate issue of what you do when you actually get to the military, there is such thing as dishonorable discharge.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 08:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I don't see us backing off of the international stage any time soon. Is doing both domestic and international politics well a possibility or are we talking about a law of trade-offs?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 07:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this case *in particular*? No, well, more generally speaking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 07:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I don't see it as an issue of scale as much of an issue of the fact that 'large' nations and 'small' nations inherently don't tend to (be able to) do the same things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 07:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't being specific because I wanted to leave room for discrepancies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone explain to me why Reese is ALWAYS whispering? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 07:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure I know what his outdoor voice sounds like. It's annoying. He whispers into his earpiece and to the people right in front of him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CMV: America couldn't successfully adopt Scandinavia's innovative policies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 07:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As much as I like the innovative policies and the outstanding results of the countries Sanders always refers to like Sweden and Denmark, I think the United States is too distinctly different from them to get so excited about adopting those same policies. From our size to our economic responsibility to the world, to our military goals, to the simple fact that we are positioned as a world leader and first world nation (whatever those mean), the United states is not nearly similar enough to northern Europe that I think we could pull the same stuff off with the same results.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bad People are not monsters. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 06:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop calling bad people monsters. Dehumanizing them spits in the face of the lessons we are supposed to learn from studying them. Hitler, Mao, Hirohito, Mousseline, and the whole lot of them are bad people who dont deserve defending, but they are only that; BADPEOPLE. With beating hearts and mothers just like you. So stop acting like there are inhuman and inconceivable products of evil because, guess what, baby Hitler existed. Thats why you want to call him a monster, because you can relate to parts of his story. That also happens to be why its so important to not fall into the trap of distancing yourself from bad people. There happen to be parts of all of us that has that awful potential. People mistake the past for white noise behind the inconceivably different present. But even those that study history in the hope of not letting mankind repeat history often get caught up in the circumstance and the factoids. The true lesson to be learned from history, in my opinion, is that we are all have a role to play in it. Sometimes for the better, sometimes for the worse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 06:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bowser is adorable IRL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 06:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He also sins things for the sheer sake of cinematic criticism. the count would be a lot lower if it were up for debate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] A website tool </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 06:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember that the main feature of the website was tracking occurrences of words you input into it over time. May either be referencing a literature database or Google searches.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Cinema Sins Playlist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 05:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 50 Amazing Facts Playlist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 05:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is on your bucket list? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 00:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 00:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> y=tan(ln(x))/x </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 23:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> right, the but differentiating actually changes the value. and applying the chain rule, quotient rule, and product rules, changes different values at different times in the equation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you differentiate an equation that is going to require 2 rules applied to it (like the chain rule and quotient rule), does the order matter? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 23:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How are towns like Champagne and Cognac, France able to enforce the trademark on their namesake products? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 22:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: I hear Illinois has banned exfoliating face washes because the microbeads end up back in the water supply. What about everywhere else? Is there something special about Illinois's water treatment facilities or their legislature? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 21:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> mexican artists can pay their taxes by donating their work to the government. What happens to those works? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 20:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: I find that watching the drivers instead of the cars (when possible) give you a better idea of what to anticipate. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 18:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 17:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The photomath app needs to be able to do this!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a general rule of thumb, what kind of symptoms are an immune response vs the disease itself? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 17:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 09:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's right. And Rama IX of Thailand is only one monarch alive today that has her beat but Sobhuza II of Swaziland is the reigning champ.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone with a Costco membership recommenced a coffee bean to me that they like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 08:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you match with someone on an online dating platform, what do you typically think of, worry about, or do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 08:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 08:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mansa Musa was the wealthiest.
Genghis Kahn ruled the largest empire.
Queen Elizabeth II is the longest reigning.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 08:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Girls worry about meeting perverts and murderers online. Men worry about meeting bots and prostitutes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This watchdog group monitors charities. Look a group up before donating! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 08:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.charitywatch.org/home </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 05:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, anything divided by 0 is actually undefined because it only ever approaches either positive or negative infinity depending on what end of the number line you are coming from. Which, to the same point, means that if there is a connection , it's that the limit, both in the mathematical and literal sense, of what happens when we test them can only be tested so far.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arts and crafts are for kids, but artists and craftsmen are respected professionals. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 04:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 04:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That gif is the true hero in this post.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 05:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not as flashy and there are some user features that I really like about Windows 7 but XP was/is a tried and true, robust, good ol' system that I don't think anyone had a problem with. the fact that security patches don't happen anymore is terrible for anyone still using it. I think Windows would have done well to not dump it 100% but maybe slowly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 05:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> puss in boots </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 02:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a bunch of good ideas already in the comments but one thing I heard that Chinese businessmen do is carry extra cheap shirts in their briefcases all day and just use their bathroom breaks to change out of the sweaty ones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 23:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be more offended if you weren't reposting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My penis used to be in the Guinness Book of World Records. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 22:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then I got kicked out of the library.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 21:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=urQCmMiHKQk is another one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A bunch of places where 42 shows up and one place where it kinda doesn't. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 21:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Mild acids like vinegar and mild bases like soaps looks like they both do the same job of killing bacteria, so what's the functional difference? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 21:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Graphing Snoo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 20:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's a koala picture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 09:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 08:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually though, thank you for the recommendation. I'll check it out and see.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone give me a 16x16 pixel snoo! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 08:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found a really cool applet to plug it into.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 08:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm aware of that law. But last time I went to a shop that the insurance company didn't approve, they told me tough luck when I said I wasn't happy with the work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 08:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll have to double check but I don't think they are on my insurance company's list of shops and I had a bad experience somewhere else so I'm hesitant to go somewhere that I don't have the negotiating power.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 07:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Body workmainly but enough mechanical to take care of the hidden damage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mechanic recommendations? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 00:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read some good reviews online of a Collision rebuilders but the guy on the phone sounded suspiciously excited for my business. He didn't have a slow-down button so I'm looking to hear from someone else too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is karma farming as sketchy and bad as it sounds or is it normal and okay to pursue? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 22:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Salary' comes from the Greek word for salt because salt was worth it's weight in gold and was how soldiers were paid. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 21:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 20:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: Credit to Matthew Santoro and his list of 50 Amazing Facts videos.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You can watch a live feed of African wildlife here. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 20:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This explanation of identity got really profound and I love it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 19:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 19:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both great explanations but I'm still confused as to why smoke only sometimes comes out. The descriptions of the potential causes all sound to me like things that would produce smoke regularly, not only every now and again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: If you are pickling a vegetable, the flesh is more porous than the skin so peel or cut for quicker results. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 09:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which of the 5 major food groups can spices, herbs, nuts, and mushrooms all be sorted into? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 08:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> come at me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 08:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 07:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was such a huge mind-blow that I'm not even sure of what i just saw. Double check for yourself but It looked like the link took me to your account.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What websites do you have bookmarked that not many people would be familiar with? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 07:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 05:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So if that's white smoke, what about black smoke? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 05:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. I just left r/explainlikeimfive and was about to go hunting for the most condescending comment. Found it anyway with all the people complaining about this being a repost. First I've seen of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why does smoke (either black or white) only sometimes puff out of the exhaust when you start accelerating? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 05:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 02:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Measures are now showing up in a lot of districts to update police systems. This news shouldn't scare people out of using their cell phones. It should scare them into realizing how terribly funded 911 is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 02:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This speaks to me
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that there is a word for worrying about a younger generation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 02:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 01:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. North Korea and Russia do share a small boarder. The Chinese coast starts on the other side of North Korea's boarder.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On a scale of Isaac Newton to Genghis Khan, how sexually active are you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 00:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why is super strength such a common trope for super heros? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 00:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The only thing between North Korea and Norway is Russia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 23:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite sixth sense of the animal kingdom? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 21:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Batman Graph </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 20:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 20:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Downvote probably because I didn't see the vid and they weren't as nice as you to point it out so downvote it was. lol. no hard feelings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 20:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have comments organized chronologically, and changed that after my post. oops.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 19:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really wanna know how this ends. Can someone link the video?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is everyone talking about Fallout 4? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 19:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw a post on my front page, on facebook, in comment sections all over the internet. Whats up?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are narwhals google autofill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 07:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does batman ever avenge his parents' deaths? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 06:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully going to get a canon explanation  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Experiment underway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 05:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am going to methodically fool around with all the moderation tools one by one and exercise the power and learn by doing. I'll catalog the results and see you on the other side.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Butterflies and Electron Microscopes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 03:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 03:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIGHT?! I saw it in my newsfeed on facebook and had to repost.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maker vs Marker 2, Jonny Lawrence, Pen and Paper, 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 02:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 02:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it's too convenient that he is where he needs to be (mostly for comic relief) like in a water tight hampster ball that Steve kicks down the stairs or in a glass on a cop car when the house is burning down. My point is that I don; think they *just* do it for comic relief.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's talk about Klaus always being in a different container. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 19:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, you coouuld write it off as an oversight or a plot convenience but I'm leaning toward a more interesting explanation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 17:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not me. Just my favorite professor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 09:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Longing, Rusted, Furnace, Daybreak, Seventeen, Benign, Nine, Homecoming, One, Freight Car.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What drinks come to mind as essential, classic, or must-try? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 08:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it alright to have a diverse set of fitness goals and just go for one at a time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 08:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So whats the deal with citizen's arrests? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 08:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any misconceptions to clear up or do I basically have the right to stop someone in the parking lot if I catch them in the act of something and cuff them myself?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE have that list of things that they are self conscious about but still love themselves? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 08:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 07:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alex, Max, Sasha, Sam, Danny, Arron (spelling-dependant),  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT][game] Looking for the name of the outdoorsy game you play with small beanbags </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 07:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You set up 2 boxes on across from each other with a hole in the sloped top and try to toss your handheld beanbags into it for points.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DIY milk frother ideas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 07:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like cappuccinos and want to be able to make them for myself at home.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 07:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't care what toppings are on your pizza, just because you hit all the food groups doesn't mean you are in the clear.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Telescopes and microscopes make oppositely sized things easier to see. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 07:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If there existed a book of everything anyone said our thought about you, what would you do with it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 01:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everyone always pets my pregnant wife's stomach and says 'congratulations' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 01:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but no one ever rubs my balls and says 'good job'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 01:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "That's a niiiice boulder." - Donkey  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Bat Symbol + my personal touches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 01:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help a newbie get caught up here. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 01:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 01:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's less about controlled chaos and more of a social experiment/forum for us to bounce ideas off of each other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 00:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't look like it went down a tick since the early 80s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Among the best Russian professors in the US </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 00:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] What's the difference between.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 00:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> crows and ravens.... doves and pigeons.... vultures and condors.... eagles and hawks..... storks and cranes.....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not a mod yet but looking to be. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 00:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking of making my sub private and small. What am I getting myself into?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A repost of the camera tutorial. OP not listed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 23:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 21:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jane's triggers seem less predictable than that though. If Jane and the plan she is supposedly the mastermind of involves Weller, why were there never any Weller flashbacks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 20:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That intelligent independent woman evidently uses the power of 'sex sells' to her advantage - if only for a short enough burst at a time to lure in a target. Let's not pretend like Reese hasn't gotten away with doing the same.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 20:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. But there is so much food for thought that I'm not gonna lose interest. For example, I think Shepard is a main character's alias.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
