<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3183</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ITT: people who didn't talk about it beforehand? Or was this the talk where they were denied?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but why the size difference? a feedback loop or protection and motivation? circle jerking ego striking and motivation?  
  
two wildly different beasts of the gym cohabitating. interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that escalated quickly. 
  
Lol, in reference to how sciency we got so quickly, but there's a small but there too.  
  
You sciencers sciencing so hard!  
   
My gf's mom mentioned all the Earthquakes around the world happening while telling me about the one in NZ. She then proceeded to say "It's the warning signs."  
   
...  
  
So what say you now?!?  
  
On a more serious note, is there connection between all of that plate movement. It would appear so but then again NZ and Italy are pretty far apart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> everyone in this thread might find this interesting:  
  
[evolution of reddit](http://www.randalolson.com/2013/03/12/retracing-the-evolution-of-reddit-through-post-data/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Duuude, that was like the first year or two that it didn't have subreddits. That's waaaaaay back. And kind of naive to hold on to as the standard to-be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont get that feeling at all. 
  
And the best thing about reddit is, if you don't like it, don't hang out there.  
 
/r/askscience /r/askhistory /r/[you're-favorite-board/video-game]  
  
THere's a lot of places that are still interesting and cool. Different than what reddit was, sure but still interesting and engaging. And even intelligent!. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The reality is that things change. THe grow, get bigger, become more expensive and need to adapt to stay around.  
  
You try to keep as much of it's inherent intent and values a part of it as it grows.   
  
And I think they did that. It's still largely a user generated content site. Unfortunately with that growth, the user base pushed it in as much of a different direction as anything.  
    
Just the way things are. 
  
I do give Reddit some credit though. It's nature of having 'subreddits' does allow for smaller, more intimate, places that fit to your tastes with their own individual cultures. That's really where I enjoy myself on this site. I browse /r/all and front page mostly like I would use facebook. If I still used it regularly. A better facebook. 
  
You can even unsub from whatever you want so you're front page is only shit you're interested in. It's pretty malleable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah man but it's a theme andstyle of stormwind. There's a lot of things done like that in the actual city too. 
   
I hear where you're coming from but just shedding light on the design and their thinking. Someone new to the game without any game knowledge would probably take it to represent what it does rather than where it's from.   
  
So, basically, you couldn't change just one. You'd have to change all of them. Although the other two are similar to their own original banenrs already. Maybe something with a gryphon on it? I don't know but something more thematically in line with lore is probably possible.  
  
That said, I do feel like that foot is representative of something or used somewhere in WoW/Stormwind before and isn't just a 'boot' they made for the banner. Could be way wrong about that though. Even if it was, it sort of just comes off like just a boot though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 18:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And for some reason Mike's bologna sandwich seems just a little bigger, and on the odd occasion she makes it on Italian bread. Once she even threw a piece of cheese on there and, it's possible but not confirmed yet, she's actually been making him ham and swiss sandwiches for the last two weeks.  
   
So not only is Sally playing some standard level office fuckery, she's probably bangen' Mike too. All I'm left with is a floppy white bread bologna sandwich, out an extra $6.50 a week, and Sally's too high pitched *'Thank you.'*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 17:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that takes some balls what those people did. 
   
I still don't think it's good to imply more guns = safer though.  
  
lol and i'm not baiting or anything. everyone pretty much agrees on gun in the house there's an increased % for suicide or injury by gun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 17:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to be fair we're also only 4 years out from sandy hook too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 17:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to be fair, this is *cool* but i'm not sure how effective a kid would be when shit actually hits the fan. even the adults for that matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 17:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but now everyone is just instinctively thinking you're spreading yeast infection around with your yeast infected d*ck... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 17:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> drug dog days at schools?!?!? that's insane! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 16:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol to be fair we're not game designers. And i think making calls like that comes with experience. I'm sure they thought of using the real one, that'so obviously where the idea came from.  
  
I'm sure they've had similar decisions to make and experience dictated which direction to go in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 07:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> type /join aispeedruns in chat to find people to just do the speedruns vs ai coo-op </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 09:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they should add in the spirit walker's 50% dmg redux between your four allies. Like dmg is spread over them. I'm not sure if it'd work but I was looking at the Tauren Spiritwalkre, the white tauren and thought it was a cool mechanic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 08:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the tauren spiritwalker would be dope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 23:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not even HDR or just HDR. That's probably straight up colorized honestly. Not just color saturation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 23:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm not even sure any of the buildings are real. WHen you look in the windows it looks like they're digitally made. Th canal could be real. And it could be done to a real picture or done and merged.   
  
ANd if it is just a flic, it's heavily edited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 17:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> actually that's not entirely true. It's just that our police departments have no problem extraditing criminals to each other or making arrests for each other. 
   
If I buy a gun in Pennsylvania and drive it into NYC, with my permits and everything and get pulled over and a cop finds it, I'm getting arrested. 
   
Even if it's legal where I live and I have the permit with me.  
  
So I'm really not sure wtf you're talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 16:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this whole thing is made pointless because when you think abut what's going on here...we're talking about people.   
   
And you're go to example is to say 'cattle.' At least don't whitewash it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 16:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can we add a relevant [jim jeffries](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0rR9IaXH1M0)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 02:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol...just a small FYI to both of you. You both seemingly have great English, native speaker or not.  
   
Be careful on Reddit and the internet in general. You'll pick up bad habits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 22:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> often shows are broken up into either plot driven or character driven premises. 
  
every once in a while something is good enough where both drive each other. i'd say between the MiB and Dr. Ford, sprinkle in Dolores, Arnold, and WIlliam (being a bit generous with WIlliam but w/e)m it's got enough of both.  
   
I guess part of me, when a show or story nails 85% of it so seemingly well, and I'm not just swayed by 'cool' factors of a robot theme park, I often call shit cool rather than call it good, but it deserves a touch of leniency in that last 15%.  
   
Especially if it's just smaller roles n stuff. Because ultimately if you have a small focus it's super easy to all have killer actors. But when you tackle something this large it becomes really difficult to do it all as well as Hopkins scenes.     
  
Especially when that's the bar being set. But i hear ya. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 07:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah i guess. just sometimes it feels like, especially with a show like this, we peer into so much and of course the cracks will show.  
   
when this guys serves his purpose for the most part and can be seen as part of the whole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 05:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know for all of men and guy's maschismo bullshit, when it comes to fights women truly have this innate sense to really hurt the other person. 
   
When I was younger and guys would get into a fight once in a while some dick would go into it trying to get an upper hand/really hurt the guy. The girls? Always were looking to scratch, bite, and pull hair to invoke the most pain possible.  
  
Got some scary instinct in there I reckon'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 05:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eh, in this context actually...thinking about it a 12-6 to the face might be more possible than a normal punch in some of the grappling and ground positions and i could see it being more damaging. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 05:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there was one of these done...i believe in a japanese mma fight, long time ago.  
   
dude's knee literally bent to a 45 degree angle toward his other knee. the clip's prolly out there somewhere but holy fuck was that shit rough to watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 02:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah wanted to add this. that it's what makes a sculpture seem more lifelike. 
   
my gf mentioned it to me. she said roman but being she's right here also said she could have been mistaken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 01:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i dunno the annoying crass guy to worker with? i think he plays it well. there's not much more to him for him to bring out the nuance of his character or anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 01:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the way she says "no" without moving lips or any feeling is jsut like...yes!  
   
me and my girlfriend imitate it all the time. just the littlest quietest emotionless no ever said by anyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 01:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol basically.  
  
and honestly, i'd rather not project any kind of theory onto my television shows. because they're for entertainment. at least the first time through.   
  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 01:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and i didn't get teh sense she was actually scaerd at first. not until she was in there for a lil bit and got the spooks. how anyone would act really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 00:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah thi was did it for me.  
   
was they mentioned dolores was off her timeline. and the 'oh she's with a guest.' thing.  
  
unless the ones controlling the control room are gen 1 hosts? but i dont think they'd have hosts run the park. that seems like a poor idea.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 00:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With a little bit of oil, mind you.  
   
Speaking out of experience eh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 00:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> good read. not sure how much that's def a 'male's' gaze vs just our one projections of ourselves in general. it's a bit assuming actually to think everyone doesn't suffer from that mentality.   
  
great read. one of the things that irks me at times about feminist theory is it gets too theorish. and i'm right there standing up for equality with the best of them. sometimes though, we're just human with human flaws.  
   
anyway, interesting read none the less. and the way this show looks at all of this is fascinating. to me though it seemes obvious. mostly because of the metaphors of the wild west adn manifest destiny and being a time where we left civilized living to the 'wild west' and built it back up again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 21:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> don't even justify that with an answer.  that's the most unreasonable response. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 09:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No shit, so don't draft him on a map where a weak early game can lose the game by minute 13, before you finish the quest. 
   
And that's being generous. Most just don't soak properly or have the ganking comp/rotation, or just high burst to earn kills in early skirmishes/teanfights.  
   
BoE comes to mind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 08:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and that turned him into a werewolf instead of a undead/Sylvanas thing?  
  
gotchya. so he's got some ruling experience is what i'm getting at. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 08:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's okay buddy. trump won. we're all sorry. 
   
gonna be an interesting 4 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 08:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It also hasn't been stated that there isn't a gold reward or alternative heroes.  
   
That said, the reality is it isn't skins. And with a 30 day stim pack you'll earn yourself at least 2 new heroes (30k) or a bunch of low gold amount heroes with the stimpack. So it isn't like you'll earn nothing.  
  
As for me, I got the 60$ year long stimpack and haven't paid cash for a hero in a long time. The skins argument just doesn't make sense because there's no utility there for new players and it just wouldn't happen. And they're still offering the brand new hero.   
  
And if you play overwatch you get those rewards too. So I'm not sure...it's easy to say, well if they were x they'd be worth y and it'd be that much *worse.* But it's not at the end of the day. And thinking of the 30 day stimpack, which will probably lead into the WInters Eve/Solstice event which will possibly provide xp too.   
  
I just disagree. Largely because they're not skins and only worth $ without a gold option. They do have gold option. Hell, with the stimpack in 30 days you could easily earn the 20k to buy two od them which some to spare. And you get the mount which you'd only get through this or with cash or a bundle, with cash.  
  
So, I don't know man. It just doesn't seem like that *much* of a snub if you're going to look at it like one. Imo it's not a snub at all. Because the reality is they're giving you 2 things anyone, one of which will earn you heroes. At least two 10-15k and really as many lower cost ones as you want. So, I don't know man. This just kind of feels like a younger mentality that's like, well I dont get *enough* or the same. It's *not equal* or it's not **fair!**   
  
And to some extent that's exactly what it is. I see the point you're putting forward is that it's not so much about being fair but that to some extent those perks are *deserved.* I'd say the reward is there. And a big part of that is pragmatics too. If you have those heroes, what let you pick another 5 random heroes? That's crazy.  
   
Instead of 8, you get 4. You get half the amount of rewards. One of which is a mount, one hero, one portrait, and, the cash only item that will earn you heroes (probably at least 2 of those other ones), the stimpack.  
   
So all things considered, that's really not bad. Would you really rather not the stimpack and 2 or 4 heroes? Or not the mount and heroes instead? I don't know man. It seems pretty fair to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 06:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm scared it's a joke  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 06:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah these streamers acting like this on stream is just blatantly unacceptable.  
   
out. of. control.  
   
!!! 
   
do i need to /s ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 06:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wasnt he a mayor of a town technically?  
  
i might be mixing up my lore b/w games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 06:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you get a hat, you get a hat, you get a hat, we're all getting hats!!!!  
   
edit: and for security purposes he could do evo on himself for a body double! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 06:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> each branch could keep the other in check...! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone talked about interacting with host Aeden on the Westworld website? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 21:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.discoverwestworld.com/#experience  
     
edit: Aeden was the name of my 'host' so yours might be different, I'm not sure.  

You can ask Aeden questions. Like how long can I stay? Max stay 28 days. Asked about Arnold I got:  
   
Not much is known about Arnold, but a closely-guarded rumor is that he partnered with Dr. Ford years ago in the early days of the park. He and we hosts had a special connection Why dont we talk about somethi    

  //ERR404HeLLiSeMPtyERROR//ERROR//V10L3nTd3L1G#t5  
    
 Hello! Its so nice to meet you. What questions can I answer about your upcoming trip to Westworld?  
   
Then I threw Hell is Empty into the chat box and got:  
   
SYSTEM ERROR /// RequestId: 8D1BB15A2068AAB6 ///   
    
Followed by the normal greeting.  
  
Anywho reddit, figured there's more to poke and prod and while I so eagerly wnat to take a real stab at this I know more people will just be a better approach. 
   
To satisfy some curiosity you cant ask about the maze, and he/she talks about the riddle of where to find it and that it's not for you. Have fun with it. Their might be something here. Or maybe not.  
    
edit3: missng letter  
  
edit4: 
   
When you type Violent Delight have Violent ends you get : 
    
SYSTEM ERROR /// h1 404 Not Found/h1 /// F8tlWtqcM6TXGQHF2MANhEZisOdNoteSh81kheTsXchFsxlMDb8kkZD8BBnY/t3o34IZRjPB8+4=
   
And that my friends is def a code/cipher mean to be broken. 
   
I'm not sure anything before it was, other than just l33t speak. The ID: Very well might have been and very well might be requesting Arnold's ID?  
   
Fuck, I'm supposed to be applying for jobs and getting some work done. God dammit ~~reddit~~ ~~self discipline~~ eh, fuck it, I love me a good challenge.  
  
edit5: quick frequency analysis.  
   
F8tlWtqcM6TXGQHF2MANhEZisOdNoteSh81kheTsXchFsxlMDb8kkZD8BBnY/t3o34IZRjPB8+4  

Removed spaces

75 chars
a : 1 ... 1.3 %
b : 4 ... 5.3 %
c : 2 ... 2.7 %
d : 3 ... 4.0 %
e : 3 ... 4.0 %
f : 3 ... 4.0 %
g : 1 ... 1.3 %
h : 5 ... 6.7 %
i : 2 ... 2.7 %
j : 1 ... 1.3 %
k : 3 ... 4.0 %
l : 2 ... 2.7 %
m : 3 ... 4.0 %
n : 3 ... 4.0 %
o : 3 ... 4.0 %
p : 1 ... 1.3 %
q : 2 ... 2.7 %
r : 1 ... 1.3 %
s : 4 ... 5.3 %
t : 6 ... 8.0 %
u : 0 ... 0.0 %
v : 0 ... 0.0 %
w : 1 ... 1.3 %
x : 3 ... 4.0 %
y : 1 ... 1.3 %
z : 3 ... 4.0 %

Letter frequencies


t : 6
h : 5
s : 4
b : 4
o : 3
n : 3
k : 3
z : 3
x : 3
m : 3
d : 3
e : 3
f : 3
q : 2
i : 2
l : 2
c : 2
y : 1
w : 1
r : 1
g : 1
a : 1
p : 1
j : 1
v : 0
u : 0
2 letter sequences


b8 = 2
sx = 2
he = 2
hf = 2
  
   
I'm suspecting that the / symbol is either indicative of this being a math equation that might give us the date of when this occurring. Or it's even much simpler. That the / is indicating the first part is solved by the second part. That the shorter sequence/divisor/denominator is the key word to the dividend/numerator/longer sequence.   
   
To figure out the shorter sequence probably requires some transposition but it'll be easier and is probably the place to start anyway.  
   
edit6: frequency analysis by section in comments. 
   
edit7: sooo, haven't applied for any jobs today, anyone have any pr/communications position entry lvl in nyc? lolol jp   
  
Have made some tentative progress though I don't want to post anything just yet.  
   
I'm also thinking that the =4 might be indicative of a simple shift cipher. Like the first part of the denominator is a keyword and the + 4 indicates a shift after the keyword.  
  
Edit8: If you type Hell is Empty These Violent Delights have Violent Ends (three times)...shit gets wild  
   
edit 9: And when I mean wild it says: 
   
TheseViOlNnTdelightshaveViOlNnTendsTirN82+rGXYRLzoOG1z3yZ9gINOf/F0AG5+IqwPOWeOYeh0GWR3VduOuMR9SVefEehcuCTpRldg=FLY Youre in a prison of your own sins. Hell is empty, and the devils are here. Arnold will come for you. 
   
edit10: there's a shorter, more neatly written summary in the comments section written by me  
    
   
edit11: shout out to /u/FertyMerty who posted this 22 days ago: https://www.reddit.com/r/westworld/comments/55v1e8/collection_of_all_of_the_clues_on/  
  
didn't get much love nor did I see that mah bad bro/gal...brogal 
   
edit12: i'm thinking it's a base64 code because of the inclusion or the symbols /, +, =, x; I've also eliminated some cipher possibilities but there the obvious ones. There's a very good chance this involves a key or keyphrase to figure it out.  
   
edit13: i wanted to add these images directly in case you didn't notice them in the other post. it's screenshots of the video. the intial screenshot I find the most interesting. [imgur](http://imgur.com/a/DW2WN)  
  
now videos can be base64 codes too. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey would anyone be interested in a twitter account that tweets about all HotS eSports? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 04:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd send out tweet 12, and or 6 hour notifications before the start of matches and then a half hour/when they start. I'd also try and do weekly updates.  
  
I know I forget about some here and there and thought this would be a big help for me and in doing so I would help any others.   
   
edit: for those interested i made the twitter account  
   
@WatchHotSeSport  
   
the s fell off, no room :(, give me a few days to  get going. I'm halfway through a spreadsheet of upcoming games.  
   
edit2: or for a few days I might just be regurgitating the side bar and giving reminders for that, which is usually the big ones but I'd like to include so am/pro am and  bigger/competitive chair league matches. And in general more relevant content from the bigger HotS streamers, something like Cavalier guests Educational scrims maybe, in the event nothing else is going on that day/time? But that's down the line. RIght now I'm just going to focus on the bigger HotS stuff for the first few days and then I'll be including all HotS matches, am/professional. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That WC3 feature for mini tournaments...that'd be dope!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 08:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you didn't see Mcintyre's rant on HL...or vlog, ;)... he mentioned a feature that I used to love from WC3. He approached it from a really cool angle of doing themed tournaments. In WC3 you did 1v1 Undead or 2v2 Human or Random even.   
   
I don't think we'd need to start there, but we could start with simple 4 or 8 team 5 man sign ups for tournaments. It'd also be a huge boost to the amateur scene if there was a way to host the tournaments in game and have open sign up. Eventually we could add tourney's with themed Diablo vs WC vs SC teams or Human vs Alliance or whatever other ideas are out there.   
   
He also mentioned a bunch of the game modes from DOTA that are clever and cool like Random/Limited Draft and a few other things that would add a serious element of fun to the game.  
   
Figured it was worth mentioning on a bit of a larger platform, especially with changes like Guilds or Clans coming up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've been drinken, I've been drinken... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 23:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Offering: English Seeking: French </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 22:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a native english speaker who also speaks some rough spanish. My spanish was a lot better but I stopped using it. I plan on starting a duo lingo course or something like that in French and would like someone to practice/ text with.  
  
Let me know if you're interested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woke up in the Kitchen Like... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 22:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So will we see the split push meta professionally? And along with that some other considerations... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 18:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mainly being that with Zagara and Anub on the same team it becomes a lot harder to land skill shots/orbs with all those minions created hanging around. Potentially more AoE like abilities like Jaina's Blizzard or AA heroes? 
  
I'm curious to see if we'll see more than Xul professionally now as well. I didn't catch the Miracle vs Tempest game but will watch the VoD sometime today. Part of me does feel like the Korean's are plenty comfortable relying on solid team fight fundamentals ad overall good lane management to counter anything.  
   
Ultimately, you can answer and curb the split push for sure or potentially trade structures with aggressive shotcalls or your own split pusher. I'm just curious how the meta will develop in general. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Offering: English (Native and English Major/Academic) - Seeking Mandarin/Korean (also interested in French) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 06:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Native English Speaker looking for a Mandarin Speaker and/or Korean speaker to exchange and teach one another. I am also pretty interested in learning French. And I'm not going to bullshit, I've romanticized the shit out of so it's my next 'romance' language to learn.   
   
Most importantly we need to get along. Like any working relationship if we don't mix well we won't get one another very far. So, initially it'd be nice to just exchange some ideas, music or whatever and make sure our initial impression is positive. From there, we can learn learn learn!!  
  
I'm a 28 y/o male. I speak some Spanish although it's rusty. Very interested in other cultures ad people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did i just miss it or do we still not have a Tempest Flair? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 06:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I looked for it after their Super League Season 2 win over MVP Black. I didn't see it but figured it'd be there with their prominence and position heading into worlds. Now post worlds!!? We need it asap! 
   
Also, maybe flair for Dami's Greymane, Lockdown's Ming/Falstad/ Hide' Rehgar? We could even just to skin versions of it and name it for them so people can show a flair for their favorite player on the character they used in worlds, maybe based on the skins they used? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey Blizz, could we get the builds that were used posted somewhere? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 23:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously in the future it's something that can be considered for all the games. For now I'd really love to see the builds of the final series if it's possible. I think it's something other people might appreciate as well.  
   
I know Gosu Gamers sometimes gets the replays to d/l and watch but that's a lot to see a build.    
    
edit: wow din't know hotslog had this. that's awesome. 
   
It'd be cool, and thanks if this gets a response. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here are your odds for winners. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 23:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a bit of a background understanding odds making. And while it kind of comes off seemingly as opinion there's a good bit of reasoning behind making odds the way they are. That said, here are my morning line odds for the HGC.  
   
Tempest (KR) 2-1 - Their bracket for the second group stage will provide excellent time to warm up against good challenging teams. Teams they'll beat though and move into the playoff with momentum.
 
eStar Gaming (CN) 5-2 - Their all star roster is looking fearsome. We'll see how it performs, but I don't expect anything less than the best. The pick.
     
MVP Black (KR) 4-1 - Renovatio I gave them a bit of trouble. The competition is catching up and if they go into Naventic on tilt from a loss to eStar, well it's up in the air.

Naventic (NA) 4-1 - Might be set up for a solid win out of the group stage.   
  
X-Team (CN) 5-1 - Not sure they'll have it in the tank till the finish. Second group stage may be it, the competition is real.
  
MyInsanity (EU) 5-1 - They looked really solid. And are coming into the second stage strong. That said, there's a lot of competition there to overcome.
   
Team Dignitas (EU) 5-1 - Haven't seen them perform yet and their group is challengin though. ?'s remain about working out their roster change.

Please Buff Arthas (TW) 6-1 - Showing great form. Upset GFE. Their on the fly decision making might prove lethal to their opponents. Also their group while competitive does open up some opportunity. 

~~Gale Force eSports (NA) 7-1 - Come November they'll be much higher, as for now, this is their first go on the world's stage and I doubt they fully grasp just how challenging it's going to be. Leagues more difficult than their recent tournament win.~~    
  
~~Renovatio (SEA) 10-1 - They've played some good games, might even take a game or two off the competitors but that'll be it.~~  
   
~~Big Gods (LatAm) 20-1 - The meta/mechanics are just not there from SA.~~  
  
~~Negative Synergy 30-1 - Also not there meta/mechanics wise.~~  
   
I was going to do some odds on other situations, like odds on GFE making it out of the group stage or Tempest *not* making it out of group stage. 
   
If this is around long enough I'll add it later. 
  


   
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heroes of the Storm eSports News   Recap - Big Weekend, Summer Champ Set, Pac12 Embraces eSports, Fall Schedule Set   HotS Future </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 00:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, it's my first in what will be a weekly or bi-weekly HotS eSports News and Recap show.   
  
Sorry for the super amateur quality. I haven't had time for the overlays/production related stuff I wanted to do but with such a big weekend I wanted to get the first episode out.    
   
[Main News Coverage](https://www.twitch.tv/romodc/v/70943583)  
  
[Extended Version, More In-Depth on HotS Future](https://www.twitch.tv/romodc/v/70924706)
   
1) 0:10 - Big Wins - GFE   Tempest Final qualifiers for Summer Championship  
   
2) 5:30 - Summer Championship Set - June 18-20th Dreamhack Sweden - All Regions have their representative teams finalized - Mewnfarez is still undecided on attendance 
   
3) 7:50 - Pac 12 Embraces eSports - Big deal for eSports, legitimizes eSports, HotD paved the way for this, More details in coming months  
  
4) 10:40 - Fall Schedule Set  Regional Schedules Set, Season ends w/ Blizzcon Nov 4 5 

5) 12:38 - HotS eSports Future - Overall approach to future and being a young scene  
            
   **15:21 - Shorter Version Ends**

   15:44 - Burbankgate and Burbank Analysis/Improvement  
  
   19:16 - Overwatch Effect  
   
   21:35 - HotS Strong Amateur Scene - Grats to Psistorm Gaming during Nexverse last night, HotS Amateur really is ProAm w/ solid quality play  
  
  23:38 - Heroes United - Ultimate Amateur Competition, Different Amateur tournaments act as qualifier for Heroes United over 6 weeks, promising strong development for HotS eSports  
   
  27:38 - Wrap Up          </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Everything] The real vision Bran needs to see (and we do too). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 02:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the answer to the question of Who pushed Bran off the tower?   
  
lol  
   
But seriously, how has he not looked to see that? The curiosity would be killing me, er paralyzing?  
   
I know it's all but confirmed to be who we think it is but still now that we're 1. closing open ends of season 1 w/ missing characters and scenes and storylines 2. filling in other gaps from more theory oriented storylines in a larger plot context </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [bug] Related with next image/image hotkeys not working. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 06:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *What's the problem?*   
 The next image hotkey doesnt work after I open one set of images. The post has 20 different 'galleries' of images w/ 4-6 images in each one about. After I use the next image hot key on one gallry it won't work on the next one.



*What other browser extensions are installed?*  
 A bunch.

*Did you read the known issues and search /r/RESissues?*  
 Yes it has a workaround for images ato expanding but not for when they do not respond to the hotkeys. i figure it was important to share that it appears, at least for me, to initially work but then stop in the particular situation. 



- Night mode: true
- RES Version: 4.6.1
- Browser: Chrome
- Browser Version: 50
- Cookies Enabled: true
- Platform: Windows

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for the location shoot of where Claire petitioned the king in tonight's (2.7) episode? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 08:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Great day! I got an STD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 22:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> great day! i got an std </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 21:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> did i miss something with the esl na summer qualifier? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 08:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> edit: lolol top 2 teams qualify...so they don't need to play each other i suppose...blah...  
   
i'm a quick learner, what can i say? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Friend is buying a boat, had a conversation on the price difference of two of the boats. I have a question or two. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 02:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has a boat at the amount that h will probably get about 30k for trade in value. The he plans on paying monthly payments to pay the rest off. Obviously none of this is happening if the monthly payments aren't well within reach. Simple interest as well.  
  
The price of the first boat he was looking at was 79,000. With the 30k trade in it would be 49k owed. 
   
The second boat is 107k. WIth the 30k trade in it would be 77k owed.  
   
My brother, who was discussing with the two of us, said he should just buy the second boat for 107k boat. He said that, essentially, it is only 28k. If our friend has 80k for the first one, the 28k on top shouldn't be a thing and well within his reach.  
    
I didn't really agree with that logic. If our friend was planning on using monthly payments, essentially, he doesn't have the 80k for the first boat. He can afford it but does that necessarily mean he should be able to handle the 28k on top? Like is it really only 28k? To me, our friend is starting with 30k. If he wants the more expensive boat he needs to be able to afford 77k, not just the 28k on top.   
   
Does any of this make sense? I think it's totally reasonable to say he could afford one and not the other. Then when you include the simple interest it's even that much more as well as taxes. My brother said, "Well a math guy or finance guy includes all those other number from the start. That it's a given and that essentially it's only 28k." To me, this was the biggest stretch and seemed ill advised. And of course, when everything is calculated and a monthly rate is worked out, our friend can see if he can include however much more 28k would be included into the monthly payment and adjusted for tax and interest. But to me, that means, essentially he is seeing if he can afford the full 77k and at that moment would be calculating the additional 28k.   
  
If this is crazy or doesn't make sense or isn't clear cause I mixed up my identifiers (the prices) just ignore it sorry. The 'conversation' got a bit heated between my brother and I. He was pretty insulting for some reason.   
   
He also started saying that if we're talking about buying 100k toys our friend can afford 28k. In reality, it didn't feel that way so much because he isn't starting with the 79k the 1st boat costs. He's starting with 30k and can afford the rest as a monthly payment. We are talking about a really luxury purchase. So I do see how there could be some latitude there. It isn't a stretch purchase either. It all comes down to if it is something that ends up reasonable. Our friend's boat is one of the few things in life that he really cherishes as a luxury.   
    
   
 Edit: thanks for the replies. i know i'm not nuts. my brother really ragged on me. and despite being, mostly, adults, it got to me. he does work in finance. and while i know that doesn't mean shit really, it adds a sense of 'leverage' to his argument. he's a bit of aggressive person at times. so it got to me this time, despite it seemingly being pretty straightforward. especially his sense of "how do you not understand this man! it's so simple!" That also got to me and really made me doubt myself for some reason.   
   
Thanks again. Really super not needed post but kind of just needed a bit of reassuring.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mahi's Saturday Night Netflix and Chill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 03:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Netflix and Chill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 03:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boss Steals, there's a lot of heroes who CC to steal bosses, I'm trying to make a video showing as many as I can! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 03:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tl;Dr want to put every kind of boss steal into one video. Please send to RomoHotS@gmail.com  
   
A couple people on here have sent me a few boss steals already. I was just going to put together a one or two minute clip. Then I got ambitious.  
   
 There are a ton of heroes who can or have stolen a boss. Whether their CC is intended for that like Falstad or isn't like Leo.  
   
When you think about all the boss steal's we've seen there are some really creative ones out there. 
   
Leo's Entomb preventing anyone from stepping on the cap point.  
   
Zag's Maw Eating whoever is on it (any Nydus steals out there?). 
   
Stitches eating a few people on the cap point.   
   
Gust and Force Walls obviously.  
   
Muradin leaps onto the cap and stunning the first or first two people approaching it.  
  
ETC powerslide + facemelt.

Tyrael blocking field with El'Druins might.  
   
There's a lot of them. Zera VP. I've seen a well timed Apocalypse and Overpower from Diablo.  
       
I've been searching through the subreddit. I also didn't want to use too many of my own. Plus they are mostly Falstad Gust steals. Plus I'd like to have plays that are recent.  So whatever kind of boss steal you have, even if it's a more common one, please send it to RomoHotS@gmail.com. Even if it is a team fight steal, send it, I'll check it out. There's some team fights with crazy things happening in them.  
   
This started as a small, quick, easy thing. I'd like it to be a bit bigger than a simple boss steal compilation though and really show some of the awesome creativity out there when it comes to stealing the boss. I'd like to show every hero that can steal a boss doing it and if not every single one, as many as possible. 
     
   
Edit: [Everyone is Awesome!!!](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3DWB7CBdvXU)  
   
Thank you all so much so far. Some really cool ideas have idea's and boss steals. Like Thrall's ult + Bolt of the Storm.   
   
So keep em coming! Also, keep listing different ways you can boss steal. Some awesome suggestions so far. I'm keeping my eye out for all em!
 
     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Make it Rank 1 Hero League - Tips and Tricks from the Pros </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 03:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Check out this new subreddit to find somewhere to watch HotS esports matches: /r/WatchHotS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 06:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's](https://www.reddit.com/r/WatchHotS/) the link. It's just a little something to help people find real world places to watch HotS Esports. Whether it is a local bar or local fan's living room casted from their PC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Welome! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 06:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to Watch HotS! Your place to find somewhere to watch HotS Esports. Whether it is online or at a local bar or someone in your area is casting to a big screen in a living room with couches!   
    
Maybe you'll just get together or find a new stream to watch here. Maybe you'll find a place to catch the matches this weekend at! Either way, good luck, have fun, and enjoy the upcoming matches!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A few of the Heroes of the Dorm games that have been played so far... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 05:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What can I say? I missed it last year and I'm pretty excited to watch this year. I've heard mixed things about it and I know it's not super league. I've been enjoying the Regionals plenty too. Just figured I'd hype up HotS esports as much as possible.   
   
So, if anyone else is looking forward to this and wants a little taste...here's a few of the games from some of the various elimination rounds so far...    
  
[NU vs UPenn](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BILirkx3nyA)  
   
[SMC vs Polytech](https://www.twitch.tv/ignisiagames/v/51387040)  
   
[UTSA vs Duke on KhaldorTV](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BdqElZDZCMY)  
   
[ASU vs UCSC](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K0CyXnTvT2k)  
   
The Duke game is from March 6th. The rest are scattered through the other earlier rounds/dates.  Just some more HotS to watch in case anyone was interested.  
   
edit: there' definitely a few more out there. I only included games where I could identify the school. Some are out there with just team names and some are out there with no labels at all really. Just a random custom game. I figured the ones with school names are more likely to 1. be legit and 2. more relevant, obviously than some potentially random game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question regarding replays?! And recording plays? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 00:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone have some input regardingwatching other peoples replays? I'm of the understanding they send them to me and I watch it in the game by adding the replay to my replay folder manually.  
   
This would be the best way because it'd lend itself to recording their game/plays the best quality wise and just in general.  
   
Or is this not possible? Do I have to watch it online on youtube or through their stream live and record it like that? That really doesn't lend itself well to recording the gameplay to be put together later in another video. It also hurts the quality and is generally a less desirable way to get clips together to make int oa video later.  
   
So does anyone have input or ideas or best practices or how they do it in order to make videos of it later?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> i love this sub! small lil recommendation though, let me know what y'all think!? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 05:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And it's jsut that when we post pictures of pens/hauls/pickups/trades/whatever(!) that we include text, either as a caption, comment, or in the post text that describes what pens, ink, maybe the stationary, and certainly anything else that we may include.  
  
Obviously we can all recognize a Pilot Metro or Lamy Safari but at a distance or glancing, especially when there's a group of pens or a bunch it can sometimes be hard to discern.  
   
The standard that /r/cigars uses for their pictures is where I got/thought of this from. It jsut seemed there's some parallels to our photos and community and I thought similar rules would apply/fit nicely.  
   
TBH adding captions to imgur albums is a pain in the ass imo. I do think that just adding text as a comment or post text is plenty.   
    
edit: was like wth inbox? oh yeah, lol made a post! haha, cool, hopefully a mod checks this out. and that said, we can make it a 'rule' and as a community encourage people to fulfill it. that way the mods aren't taking on too much and having to police every pic post. it certainly will hold true for vintage pens but imo i almost feel like a lot of those people do write what it is because we all like to brag a lil bit :). it almost feels like the mid range pens are the mot overlooked/hard to identify. that said, regardless, even after using fp's for a year i'm not a pro. i enjoy them but i'm also not super super active so there's even a bunch of entry level ones i can't ID on sight/at a glance.   
   
Overall I just think it'd really facilitate new members or popping by to navigate more easily. It'll be more user friendly in general. And it'll certainly lead to me more easily finding that new pen or two that I want to add to the collection.  
    
I'm pretty long winded eh? Maybe i'm just being thorough. But as an edit and general, "cool, thank you" addendum, this is pretty long. Even the original post, while arguably appropriately lengthed to explain the thinking and reasoning, seems long. Def need to keep things more pointed.
  
 Anywho, love you guys! And let me know if this is something we maybe could institute. Maybe it already is and jsut isn't enforced? But I'm always seeing pens and feelings like I need to ask, at least one or two posts every other day or so ish.                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                            </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Match Threads?? Besides Obviously Huge Matches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 03:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was wondering why we don't have match threads for live matches. Sure, games are only 20 minutes each but it's usually a best of three series.    
    
It's regional Qualifiers atm and Team Blaze vs Tempostorm was a solid match. One you could actually learn something from, was great to watch, and   So was the other matches today. Went here to talk about it and didn't see anything and figured this would be the place most of us would talk about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> do you use the in game twitch broadcasting stuff or external software (obs, xsplit)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 00:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wondering. I tried using the in game and it seems...buggy or jsut not working at all. I'll probably use OBS from here on out. Just curious.  
      
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Resizing and image, better in illustrator or photoshop,? Image needs to be almost half the size...this has been assigned to my gf from her boss, we appreciate any help. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 04:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tl:dr are these images too big to bring down yo almost half size? if not photoshop or illustrator and is there a tutorial out there for this I could watch/read. It's for my girlfriends job and we've never done something like this for print so getting a head start on it tonight. Thanks.  
   
  
Hey doing something a little different than I usually do. I'm resizing something but it's going to print.
  
Anyhoot, we would appreciate some insight into moving a head. I mean we're playing around with a lot of stuff but any feedback you could give would be appreciated.  
    
The magazine's specifications are 16"x10-3/4". DPI:266-300 Anything less than 266 DPI will compromise quality.     
     
THe images she sent me on average, er sent my gf, are 10.9"x16" at 300 DPI. 
    
So we need to get the images in half. That just seems like a lot. I've never had such a large gap to bridge I guess, neither has she. She's much more comfortable in Illustrator and initially was using that. I suggested photoshop. We're aware of the benefits of resizing in illustrator but being that it's originally a picture I wasn't sure if the resolution stuff with vectors would hold. Equally I thought that since it was a photo the resolution may have been predetermined and we'd have a better shot in photoshop to preserve that.   
    
Any tips. Any specifics we might be overlooking in resizing options? I unlinked them and try and get it to 7 by 10 by 300 with a small edge.  
       
They do want it to bleed to edge though. Any tutorials on how to do this? Because we'll watch it follow it? Or is this not possible with those original image sizes? Because to me that seems ambitious.  
    
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was WWII inevitable? I listened to the Hitler tapes and his conversation with Mannerheim made it seem like Russia was gearing up for war, beyond Finland, regardless of Germany's aggression. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 19:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey I found a couple posts about it but was wondering if anyone knew if the retail starter pack still gave the heroes/skins/mount as codes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 02:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that's pretty much it. Does anyone know if the retail starter pack that you'd buy in Gamestop still use codes to give the heroes? Does it also apply to the Rhonin Zeratul skin and the Golden Tiger mount?  
   
I'm asking, being that I started streaming, because I'd like to gift some of those hero codes/skins. I think the heroes would would be a great help to anyone who ended up with them. Would this also be the case if I bought the Retail Starter Pack digitally from gamestop as well?  
    
That said, besides ebay, does anyone know any places I could get codes from? Currently, they deduct the price of what you own from bundles rather than supply extra copies for you to gift. I'd like to be able to hold a giveaway or two. And if one of you maybe provides a real decent tip maybe I'll even give something out to a random person from the comments (once i get my hands on a few).  
    
If anyone has some skins they aren't using either let me know! I'd be more than happy to take em and/or pay for them through Google Wallet if it's needed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A 6 ounce plastic cup of water seemingly evaporated 3 separate occasions over different periods of times from a nightstand next to my girlfriend's bed. Any scientific understanding of why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 23:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What are some weird, not well known events/phenomena unique to your profession that you've experienced? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 04:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can be explained or unexplained. I know it's a bit similar to a question recently but it's been on my mind a bit lately. Kind of like as a paramedic I've had people just kind of know they're going to die or get this look, despite not being in that bad of shape or sick at all. Maybe similar to pilots seeing UFO's too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> this is pretty cool subreddit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 04:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i really like that women can have their own place to enjoy and talk about something, that can be so heavily male dominated, without some of the negativity associated with that male population.   
    
i think it's pretty awesome and with our perception of gender roles and associated activities that get tied to gender perception slowly changing, this is cool.  
    
good stuff meng!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Idea for Truly Unique Crafting Items that would make items that are one of a kind </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 04:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My idea is to create uncommon/rare/epic/legendary crafting tools. Like a Blacksmith's anvil, tailor's sewing needles, carpenters hammer, leather makers scissors/awl/punch (some creativity there). Could even make a blacksmith's hammer for weapons and an anvil for armor so there's more diversity. A carpenter's hammer for staffs and a plane/chisel for shields. These drops would make items automatically the color of the crafting item. So you could make a weapon starting at green. It would also imbue, and this is the critical part, unique stats. This way you can have crafting guilds that are making truly unique items that are potentially truly the 'best.' Obviously nothing that becomes so OP but they should appropriately give benefits. It would work seamlessly into the crafting system as it exists already and add some motivation for pure crafters to quest and adventure. It would also create some motivation for guild's to gain the items so their crafter's are making better items and their guild trader is being sought out during the week.
   
I got the idea thinking of an element of UO's crafting system. I have not seen anything since. I think ESO would take the idea and it would work even better with the traits of weapons and armor already in the game. It'd really be an awesome thing that elevates the crafting system more so than it already is, which is pretty great. It'd also add a sense of competition between guilds competing to craft the most unique/best items in the game and create guild's whose wears are sought after more so than other's each week based on the items they are producing. They'd also work with the location based set crafting by make items that are really on a next level and stand out for their true unique rarity.   
    
I think it adds an awesome element to the crafting economy and a great amount diversity to the sets, weapons, and armor being created, traded, and crafted.      
  
 Any thoughts? Criticisms? Ideas?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did they remove the recently played feature? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 07:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now when I open up my friends list and try to add the guy I just played I can't anymore. I've honestly had some of the most skillful games today. Drawn out, long, back and forth matches that were really just outstanding. I'd love to add those guys and laugh about it afterwards but you can't anymore. I get there are trolls out there too though. Anyway, was wondering if I was the only one or if this was changed with TGT patch/release? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> honestly, def going to buy the tbf </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 03:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty psyched just reading the commander descriptions. they look really interesting, really engaging and even playing as a soviet or u.s. alongside them is going to make the game more interesting. i'm pumped.   
    
and maybe will make up for some of those uneven matches since the brits might actually be able to carry a sagging teammate :-P   
    
jp, just being cheeky.  
    
but seriously psyched. was going to try them out and make sure i wanted to buy, and to some extent that's true. but i'm def going to buy them. they look fun and like it'll spice up the battlefield. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> hey bit confused about doing all this, sorry to bother yall. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 21:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I own the base COH2 game. I have most of the expansions. I don't see the Brit Free trial in Steam anywhere. Normally, with something like this it'd be added to my library automatically. I have a key. I jsut wanted to try it out before I purchased it.  
    
Any help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for Paralyze, we just played one of the best Mage vs Mage matches I've ever had. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 21:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll post some screenshots in a few minutes but we started out dropping he 0/2 Mirror Image with taunt. Me two of them, him one. The game progressed into a lot of skillful removal and secret play. Throw in a dash or two of luck as well for draws and certain effects and it was by far one of the best matches I've had. That and the Shaman who beat me with one health.   
   
Anyway, figured if he was on here to hit me up and figured I'd share such a great game. I'll add an edit after I'm done uploading the screenshots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I let the autofinish feature for deck building build a whole deck. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 08:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to see what happens. I'd also love to know if anyone has done this before because then I won't pursue it as fully as I plan on.  
   
I'm going to give it a shot with mage first. Mostly because, skill wise, I'm probably strongest with playing mage. I do plan on seeing is I'm able to complete my daily quests. I also plan on seeing if I'm able to win with all classes doing this.   
   
I think it's going to be interesting seeing what kind of deck it put together and how well it handles itself. I'm level 20 but this isn't about leveling or anything. It's just to see if the computer put together any strategies or possible combos and see how well the deck handles itself.  
   
I guess if a major streamer has done this already I'll save myself the trouble. If there is some interest in it I'll stream it and post my channel. I might stream a bunch of it anyway.  
    
I'll keep you updated as I move through the classes too.  
   
[Here's](http://imgur.com/a/CsKLO) an album of my initial two mage decks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey Reddit, what do you think about or do while you're stuck in traffic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-14 20:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tend to think about what other people are thinking about, making stories up about folks and stuff. One day I was thinking about who else might be a redditor around me and then wondered what other redditors do while in traffic.   
  
And because of reddit I get to ask!  
   
I guess as an extension of that, if you do make up stories about other people, like me, what's the most interesting you've come up with? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Modest Collection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 16:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Killing time during the Modest mouse prospect park show, </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 00:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im giving a friend a ride to the show. Probably going to grab a drink somewhere around there. Or anywhere really.

Edit: Great concert. Actually finished my Bk farmacy shake and grabbed a second from Mr. Softee. There's a guy selling these small rum/vodka/whiskey cocktails. They're these 8oz (probably) bottles  and are super discreet. Look pretty awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> hey folks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 03:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> interested in consulting.  
   
considering grad school, mba specifically. recommend a different grad degree?  
   
any other tips for taking initial steps into the field? open to internships, entry level positions, pretty much whatever I have to do.  
   
Spent a good chunk of my twenties freelancing, writing+design. Def analytical but can appreciate the client side of work, both due to history and because that's something I'm interested in.  
   
would love to, and very much appreciate, any advice.  
   
thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why did the judge rule in favor of the prosecution to exclude the information that it did, pertinent and from its own witnesses but ruled 'outside the scope (iirc)' of the trial, in Ross Ulbricht's trial? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 07:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> edit2: skip down past the first tl;dr/edit for the three things i need clarified and ELI5 as to why the judge ruled against the defense as not being pertinent or within the scope of the trial.  
    
The information that the prosecution objected to was their own witnesses, often DEA and DHS agents (iirc), claiming that they suspected at least two people controlling the Dread Pirate Roberts accounts. One even admitted it under cross examination and the prosecution objected to it and the judge ruled in favor of the prosecution. It seemed like the judge's ruling against the defense, essentially gutted the defense's case for him, I'm not sure how that makes for a fair trial. Particularly when the information was detailed by the prosecution's witnesses during the investigation or it was pertinent to the nature of the case on topics like encryption, cyber security, and cryptology. All of which would have shown it'd be nearly impossible for Ulbricht to act alone, or even have access to certain information like 'his journal.' It almost felt like the prosecution was desperate for a guilty verdict. Not getting one would really open up a door that LE fearfully never wants open. It's arguably still open but is currently a dangerous one to step through.
  
Along with that, the criminal investigation into the Baltimore DEA agents who allegedly stole Bitcoins during the investigation. Doesn't it speak to the character of the witnesses? Particularly guys and gals who are presumed to be good witnesses as federal agents and law enforcement?  
   
I'm not super sure about the details of the case. I mean the real nitty gritty. The judge struck down, essentially, the defense's alternative story that multiple people were behind Dread Pirate Roberts. They barred the professional and expert testimony the defense wanted to bring to explain how cryptology and encryption work that would show it'd be difficult for DPR to be one person. I'm not sure how encryption and cuber security isn't pertinent to this case. It seems extremely pertinent to the case, considering it took two years to find the guy and essentially happened by chance by an IRS agent using a google search, otherwise they never would have had his name, seemingly, The prosecution argued it wasn't necessary to bring in expert witnesses for the scope of the trial. But then they dropped the murder charges. Which makes me think those charges brought up the possibility of a second individual working the DPR account.  
   
Personally I think Ross Ulbricht played a large role, maybe received the appropriate sentence. It doesn't entirely seem like he received a fair trial. I think he has a great shot on appeal for either another trial or to be acquitted (overturned?). Maybe you're more familiar with the real nitty gritty of the details. I just watched the documentary about it.  
  
ELI5 how that information 1. wasn't pertinent, teh cyber security and encryption stuff, that was all used to encrypt his journal and access to certain things. and 2. how they could strike information said and detailed by their own witnesses as not within the scope of the trial when it was regarding the person or persons using the DPR account. Especially when that was what the defense was proposing as his defense. That doesn't seem fair at all.   
   
Anyone shedding light on this would be great. Thanks!  
   
TL;DR Explain the judge's ruling against the defense's case in the Silk Road trial.  
  
***  
  
edit: the judge ruled against two things, three really.  
   
one was the statements made by the DEA agents saying that they suspected multiple people worked the DPR account. They said so under cross examination that was struck down and was detailed in notes and stuff they took during the investigation. It seems this may be related to the murder charges and possibly why they were dropped. They also could have been dropped because they had a solid enough case with life already as the maximum sentence. That said, the prosecution wouldn't drop murder charges lightly and it would have even been better from a PR perspective and overall for the prosecution to make an example of him. A lot of the end of that point is speculation, particularly on the murder charges.  
   
two. the judge ruled against the defense's introduction of expert testimony that would have explained encryption and cryptology and cyber security. All of which was related to DPR's account and the journal he kept on his computer. They were planning on showing that it would have been difficult of near impossible for one person to operate the account based on this testimony.    
   
third. is the DEA agents from Baltimore (along with local pd iirc) who allegedly stole u to a million Bitcoin during the investigation and put it into personal accounts (perhaps fake vendor accounts? lol...speculating). Doesn't this speak to the character of the witnesses who are presumed good, solid witnesses. Discounting witnesses has always been a part of defense or prosecution strategy.  
   
So those are all things the judge ruled against for the defense. All of which hurt the defense, immensely. ELI5 how that stuff wasn't pertinent to the trial and how the trial was still a fair trial? How could the judge rule against that stuff and strike it out? It seems like it is directly pertinent and of great value not just to the defense but necessary to the trial as a whole. It almost doesn't seem like because of these details the defense's case and alternative story was gutted resulting in Ulbricht not receiving a fair trial. Very much related to the political pressure to obtain a guilty verdict (speculating)  
   
tl;dr2 needed to clarify the three specific points the judge ruled against in the case.  
   
ahhh i wrote a book. is the part 2/second edit clear? ill delete the first part i wrote if the second is enough. sorry!!!  
   
And ***thanks*** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 27/m/ny shiiit i'm getting old </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 08:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> or at least it feels like it. on the bright side i am working out, that insanity workout (it's brutal). got back into eating healthy. i was doing manual labor for a bit and then when i stopped i kept eating like i was still lifting all day. i put on like ~~10...~~25 pounds in 2 months, probably over a little longer. so now it's time to get rid of that shit. i'm 6'0 so going from 215 to 235 isn't the end of the world but still i'm not happy with it. plus i miss abs.    
  
 i sound vain. probably cause i am, a lil bit. i'm american, that's a decent enough excuse. maybe. eh, i'm flawed. i'm looking at mba programs. i write, read, fish, read more, game a lil bit, love the new yorker, love new york.    
   
love the beach and sun, and sand, and summer. and fall and spring. maybe not in that order. really enjoy the rain. lightening and t storms too.  
  
i wrote 2 books. now i want to work + grad school/mba programs. selling those books would be cool but reality is still not enough dough.   
   
life's just okay at the moment. if i'm being honest.   
  
so snail mail is cool. penpals are cool. pm's or email is cool.  
  
i got some solid stationary right now though and  a wax sealer i'm dying to use.   
   
but either way, i'm looking to bullshit. kik, here, email. snail mail.  
  
whatever's clever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> thought some of yall might find this interesting, hope solo's domestic violence record </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 22:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> those buffalo burgers... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 01:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "you do eat meat don't you?"  the principal megan says to theresa (ethan's wife)
  
i didn't read the books but i am hip the actually what's up.   
  
that said, i'm thinking the buffalo burgers aren't actually buffalo, perhaps?  
  
then again they serve steak as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> hey real life took me away for a month or two... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 22:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and i'm glad i'm going to have time to play again man. i was just reading an article talking about some stuff and i was like, i miss that game. now, i won't lie, i was getting a bit intimidated by the VR grind ahead of me since I was VR1 but I'm imagining it won't be so lonely with all the new players (caldwells silver).  
  
i guess my other issue is that it's summer and i should be getting outside. meh.   
  
I stopped playing right as it went B2P so i really haven't been gone at all (after taking an actual pretty long break). I loved it when I initially returned but real life grabs you by the balls some times and it's tough being a casual player, at least for me. Maybe I take my gaming too seriously?  
  
anyway looking forward to coming back. ilu guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> this place is awesome </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 18:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> seriously. my gf is firmly against kids, pregnancy, etc. i'm more along the lines of, eh, but no.   
   
don't get me wrong, i love making poor decisions. and a child that just happens to happen and come along, well then i think it'd be a good opportunity to pass my genes along.  
  
so, with that reasoning clearly absurd, i ~~highly doubt~~ won't be having kids.  
  
anyway. this place is pretty cool. i've heard about it, visited, lurked here and there. but now i'm subbing, cause yall make a lot of damn sense. and i entirely agree with a lot of the sentiment and examples of absurd behavior and entitlement associated with parents, who are oft ill equipped for their situations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How do Identity Thieves get credit cards in your name? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 18:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To me it i doesn't make sense. I'm asking because my Mom is going through this right now and the cops have like 0 clue who or what stole her identity. Apparently they opened bank accounts, credit cards etc. Like don't you need a mailing address for that shit? Aren't they having the cards sent somewhere? wouldn't that person know something? And like bank accounts have to have their statements sent somewhere.   
  
I'm not trying to make this a cop banging circlejerk, I'm 90% of the time sympathetic to the police. It just feels like there is definitely a physical link there somewhere and that it should be the weak part of the chain and instead nothing!!  
  
Anyway, if anyone could shed some light on this that'd be great. My googling has shown some people mail things to vacant addresses and stuff but that seems tough to do, it's not like a big package that'll be left out for someone to grab (like I've heard of people doing with pot).  
  
Anyway, sorry just curious. My dad is actually a cop and we were discussing it and couldn't figure it out ourselves. So any enlightening would be appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WSIB] Cities Skyline? or CS:GO? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 20:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cities Skyline definitely interests me. Big time. But I'm nervous it won't be difficult enough/challenging.   
  
Which is why getting back into CS has some appeal. Then there's Total War Attila and The Witcher III coming out. Then of course there's GTA V and Offworld Trading Company, both of which I'm really leaning away from (eventually OWTC though).   
  
but really I'm pretty much wondering if  Skyline is going to give me that challenge. I'm a Civ series fan (and did enjoy BE :-P). Prefer challenging games. Been playing ESO but don't have that time commitment anymore for the vet grind so it's been a bit less and I kind of want to do something else beside the RPG. I was kicking around XCOM but definitely prefer newer games. I'm a CoH, SC2, Civ, like I look for that depth and the challenge that come from the depth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> hey quick question... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 17:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cashed out 24k out of a vanguard fund last year. My accountant, said I won't have to pay taxes on it. I hadn't gone in to see him, my parents did (they knew I cashed it out, it was an UTMA and even though I'm 27 they hadn't legally kicked it over to me yet so I need mother's permission).  
  
It had gone straight to pay off debt (not student loans, actually my mom's credit card but that's another story). She didn't claim it on her taxes.  
  
I'm wondering why it wouldn't be *income*. I didn't make enough last year to even file, so I wasn't going to since I was exempt. Anyone know why he'd say that, in the manner he did?  
  
Everything I've looked at online, and gone  through with filing wise resulted in that as income. So I figured I need to file with an accountant but figured it wouldn't hurt to ask some people who might be familiar with it. Thanks.   
  
best,  
  
m </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MSDG Fri 7PM Beth Israel 15 street/1st ave </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 09:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sigh. Depressed, Again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 14:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Warning Scam Alert [serious] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 00:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [IIL] Terror At The Mall, [WEWIL]? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 10:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More like, If I found this interesting, What else would I find interesting?   
  
looking i guess for documentaries on war/terrorism. Restrepo is another i enjoyed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> those red flags </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 12:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> like trouble sleeping, loss of interest, appetite changes and weight gain/loss...like here it comes, episode #infinite. christ it's tiring.  
  
back on the meds maybe? maybe i can up my therapy to 2x a week. maybe ill go to one of those 28 day stays this time? haven't tried that yet...and shit was just do good wasn't it? now every fucking day will be a struggle to live, let alone to keep my job, my relationships ans everything else. the worst part, worst than staying in bed all day and worst than any of it is how scared i am at what's coming. and how draining it is. how tired i am to feel normal. yeah, i had a good year but it looks like that's coming to an end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> this is kind of interesting... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 11:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> add ons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 04:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> does anyone recommend a good add on manager? i used to just manage them by myself but right before i stopped playing i was thinking/discovered managers.  
  
any good recommendations? my addons are so out of date that i wiped them and am re d/ling so i figured i'd start w/ a a manager. i remember the one i d/led before quitting didn't port all of my addons in since i had d/led it separately and after i had a bunch of add ons already. also any new/really remarkable add ons you recommend out side the basics?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> hotseat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 10:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i was jsut thinking that the hotseat hting could make for some interesting gameplay if you played it by yourself. as long as you played to win with each civ it would interesting to see some of the situations that arise from playing several civs at once.  
  
so has anyone given this a shot?  
  
i guess it isn't that different from making teams and playing the civs yourself, not sure if it could be exactly the same.   It certainly could help to create some interesting challenge situations.   
  
that said do we have any challenges for beyond earth yet? if not, who's interested in making some? We can start with pure affinity challenges, harmony first? message me and we'll come up with something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I know you get this enough but I'm thinking of coming back... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 01:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've begun reading  The sidebar. I am a fan and defended the game fervently upon release. Eventually though it did seem a bit too unpolished. Like everyone where light armor/defaulting to certain builds where some others weren't even viable. I imagine this has changed though.

I also imagine its been cleaned up and balanced. I enjoyed the game for what it was but the flaws just piled up too high. Again I've begun reading the side bar and will finish when I'm home, also I imagine things have been smoothed out. I'm pretty sure I'm coming back and looking forward to it. I wouldn't mind hearing some good reasons/convincing arguments about coming back. I'll finish the side bar when I'm home.

Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Day 1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 15:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SO i managed to sit for 10 minutes today after i got dressed for work. damn that was relaxing, i'm not sure why i ever stopped doing this.    
  
i'm going to try and do ten minutes this evening too. ideally, i'll start 2x a day and grow out from 10 min to 20, to 30 until i'm at either 30 min 2x a day or 1hr once a day and another 10 or 20 or 30 min sit at another time each day.  
  
thanks to this sub, quite the encouragement to get me back on track. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> hey hey, copyfellas and gals... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 05:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so, i've received some great help on here and i'm really digging in and putting together some cool ideas/ads. i think i'm going to eventually have a solid spec book to show that is pretty comprehensive. from basic print ads, through a t.v. spot, through a radio spot, through twitter rep of a brand, etc. really thorough. i'm waiting to come up with a couple really unique ideas for a couple more to ice the cake/replace what i've done so far. 
  
what's the best way to present the book? make a portfolio website? use one of the free websites that put portfolios together. i've found a couple really solid ones that seemed to be used by professionals in industry. i guess my question is more that it's can kind of be difficult to display some of the formats, like tweets. does anyone use the old fashioned way of putting together a book still? or am i just being silly considering that?  
  
i guess i'm looking for some tips on the final touches of a book.best format to present it in. in addition to what i decide i'll definitely have a free account w/ one of thosep ortfolio sites too, obviously. being naive if you think it's okay to neglect that. obviously you're never completed with it but hopefully i'm done adding spec work to it.  
  
also, real quick, being that i am still working on it, just nearing completion, i also considered taking this http://adhousenyc.com/courses/. particularly the exploring the creative process 10 week class, one as a way to maybe hit on a better idea or two to add/replace w/ my current specs. it isn't as much of a commitment as full port school but should still lend a hand in putting together my book.  
  
so i guess that's it. any tips on finalizing/best medium/format to present my book. and any quick feedback on adhouse courses.  
  
thanks again. and thanks for all the help. this has been an invaluable resource in helping get into the profession.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> hey plan on coming back... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 04:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm wondering if there's anything i should know. i stopped playing after getting wiped by a lone tiger or two after dominating the whole game. i'm wondering what strats and stuff are popular? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> hey hey it's dat holiday season </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 15:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what are you thankful for as 201 nears its end?  
  
personally i guess i'm just thankful to be here, be in a positive mood (and not depressed), be working, and be moving forward as best i can. it's not much but i got something and that's better than a lot, and for that, i'm utterly, and sincerely, humbly, thankful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [U.S.] I'm having trouble finalizing my decision...push me in a direction...please! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 06:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, so I posted in /r/chromeos and had some help from those guys. I used this sub to much success and ended up buying my first chromebook after discussing it here.  
  
That one was killed and I'm looking to get another one. It feels like I'm looking at the Acer c720/720p, the HP 14 or the Toshiba Chromebook 2. They all have similar power under the hood. The Toshiba CB 2 has the Intel Celeron Bay Trail N2840 and the other two have the Intel Celeron Haswell N2955(u)(?). Tbh when you consider what you are using a chromebook for both of these processors are plenty. The tests and benchmark performances for these machines with these processors w/ 4GB of Ram are all fine and quick. They will handle themselves fine. They all come with 16 to 32gb of memory.   
  
The distinguishing characteristics are the Toshiba ha a 1080p screen. The Acer i can get w/ a touchscreen but that isn't that important.The HP comes in colored cases. 
  
  
I can't make up my mind for the life of me.  
  
http://www.amazon.com/HP-Chromebook-Intel-Processor-Memory/dp/B00JEP1NLW/ref=sr_1_21?s=electronics ie=UTF8 qid=1415941400 sr=1-21 keywords=chromebook+hp+14#productDetails  
  
i'm skeptical about this listing due to the lack of info.  
  
http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00N99FXIS/ref=pd_lpo_sbs_dp_ss_1?pf_rd_p=1944579862 pf_rd_s=lpo-top-stripe-1 pf_rd_t=201 pf_rd_i=B00N99FV76 pf_rd_m=ATVPDKIKX0DER pf_rd_r=0SZGPMQ65D91AQWTXXXY  
  
toshiba w/ bay trail  
  
  http://www.amazon.com/Acer-C720P-2457-NX-MKEAA-005-Chromebooks-Celeron/dp/B00KK8WNXY/ref=sr_1_27?s=electronics ie=UTF8 qid=1415941370 sr=1-27 keywords=chromebook+acer+c720  
  
acer w/ touch screen  
  
http://www.amazon.com/Acer-C720-3404-11-6-Inch-Chromebook-Granite/dp/B00KOUIZBC/ref=sr_1_4?s=electronics ie=UTF8 qid=1415941296 sr=1-4 keywords=chromebook+acer+c720  
  
acer w/ stepped up processor  
  
http://www.amazon.com/HP-14-Q039wm-Turquoise-Certified-Refurbished/dp/B00KTHV9UY/ref=sr_1_6?s=electronics ie=UTF8 qid=1415941400 sr=1-6 keywords=chromebook+hp+14  
  
hp 14 w/ colors...lol but haswell processor + 4gb ram, cheaper to orefurbed  
  
http://www.amazon.com/HP-14-q070nr-14-Inch-Chromebook-T-Mobile/dp/B00FGOTBQO/ref=sr_1_4?s=electronics ie=UTF8 qid=1415941400 sr=1-4 keywords=chromebook+hp+14  
  
HP 14 not refurbed...same specs  Both HP's have unlimited lifetime 200mb/month 4g coverage too.
  
  
help me out, please.  
  
I mean, the reality is w/ most of the specs the same and all of them being able ot handle what I plan on using it for which is mostly writing does it come down to aesthetic choices? I will use it for some light photo editing, maybe streaming PS and some light coding possibly (but again probably through an online IDE). ALl those machines should be fine though, especially for my primary purposes (web browsing/research+writing).  
  
Any experiences/feedback?  
  
  
Originally I was set on the Chromebook 2 from Toshiba. Figured the Baytrail wouldn't be too much of a hiccup and is really only slightly slower. Some reviews w/ benchmarks comparing these 3 machines actually had it performing faster so I'm not too worried about it. THe 1080p screen was pulling me in that direction. Now though I'm not sure. Plus though other two have their own strengths that I took into consideration and am now a fickle undecided libra.  
  
okay anyone curious i went with the HP, thinking about the free 200 mb 4g made me decide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> hmm,my 2nd chromebook purchase... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 22:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay guys . like the title says this is my second chromebook. my first one was destroyed in an accident. it was the 1st gen samsung and i was more than happy with it. moving ahead though i plan on using my chromebook for the same things i sued my original one for but as the chromeworld grows i want to be able to keep up. i'll probably be streaming photoshop and using google drive a bit more extensively (power point slides, excel sheets, etc).  
  
i really like the toshiba chromebook 2. for all intents and purposes i believe she'd keep up. i also am tempted by the 1080p screen. That said the 720 and 720p are both also tempting, but i think i'm shying away from them. I'm also considering the HP14, edem colors...  
  
I think all 3 (4 really) machines are good for my purposes as long as I can make sure it has 4gb's of ram. The HP's offer of free 20MB of data/month is also enticing. SO basically I guess I'm looking for help to make my final decision. If I game it's on my desktop. I also do some light coding but use the apps/ides to do it and didn't have problems with my original one so i imagine i wouldn't have problems with any of these far more advanced machines (sort of far more).  
  
Anyone have convincing selling points in one direction over the other? Your own experiences?  
  
I'd love to hear whatever your take on these machines is. I'd also like to make this purchase ASAP but like anything else I end up being exceedingly thorough.  
  
i guess my final decision would have to be any of these. I think that all of their processors, while somewhat concerned about the bay trail, I'm not too worried. Overall I need 4GB of Ram, and that's about it. They all are up to snuff.
  
  
edit: so I'm still pretty stuck. I made a post in suggest a laptop: http://www.reddit.com/r/SuggestALaptop/comments/2m9ccu/us_im_having_trouble_finalizing_my_decisionpush/ 
  
They all make sense. I do get that a N2995 processor is a bit more future proof but the Toshiba's Bay Trail would, ultimately, be fine. Also some benchmarks show it operating a bit faster. The HP has that free 4g things and the Acer has a version w/ faster processor+the possibility of touchscreen. While that isn't an isn't seller it can also be had for cheaper. Ugh, I'm bad at making decisions. Or maybe I'm justly thorough in making big purchases. Either way I hate this process.   
  
I was set w/ the CB2 w/ the 1080p screen but now I'm not sure at all.    
  
Heyy, I decided! I went with the HP 14. The free 200 MB of 4g was the selling point. I really didn't take that into consideration beforehand. It's a 2955u processor w/ 4gb of Ram. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: what happens to coke and pepsi in those videos when it is cooked? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 05:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is my understanding that the water and such is boiled off and you are left with the syrup and sugar making making a thick liquid, akin to reducing the coke or pepsi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> i need an answer...quickly...please lol </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 04:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay, so i see on amazon that i get the exoplanets map pack for "pre-ordering." now i'm going to 'pre-order,' even if it's only by a couple hours but i want to make sure i'll get the exoplanets map pack if i buy it through steam. i'd rather buy it through steam but i don't know if i get the exoplanets map pack.steam sometimes doesn't deliver these add ons/additions as promptly either,  i feel like (but could be way off base). Any tips/recommendations for where to purchase. I'd prefer to buy with steam but I'm not sure.  
  
also the urgency is obvious lol, i want to start installing it asap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google possibly replacing Nexus 5 with cracked screens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 03:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> best replacement screen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 09:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so my screen cracked. from a not so high carpeted fall it was a slight crack. it then got worst from being in my back pocket. Initially I was going ot use it but then functionality decreased from being in my back pocket, I guess. I certainly didn't drop it again/ I'm kind of pissed to be honest. Not so much because I dropped it but because the hone is so fucking fragile.  Nothing that happeend really warranted the degree of damage. Okay it fell, I'll take the slight crack. I'll even take the crack worsening but losing functionality from just being in my pocket (and the worst part wasn't even my back pocket) irks me.   
  
anyway venting over. i'm looking for a replacement screen on amazon. any tips? I'm going to do the repair myself i think. what's everyone's experience with broken screens? where would i send it out to? how much would it cost? and any experiences repairing their screens themselves? I saw one guy on here who did it and it looked great, there's where i got the idea.  
  

thanks,  
  
matt  
   
tl;dr experiences with cracked screens (sending them out/fixing them yourself                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                     ? best replacement screen from amazon?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
