<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1863</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that a Catholic priest was kidnapped and castrated by KKK members, including the Gainesville mayor and police chief, at the University of Florida in 1924 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 13:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The saddest story I read today: the family of teacher killed by manhole cover on 93 tells their story </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 13:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 13:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, the Cayman Islands are having cold weather this weekend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Voters who oppose politicians are the most active - "This helps explain why political attack ads are a crucial tool in politicians' arsenals" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 14:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 14:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll be glad to know that Dr. Stein won her hometown of Lexington by a vote of 10-1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 14:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I guess there was no evil Clinton plot to steal the election, just a data glitch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WBUR is having a public beta of a redesigned, modern website with better listening options </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 16:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 16:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless, of course, the money is actually used to build affordable housing, of which there is a notable lack in Boston. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 20:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.bostoncares.org/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shakespeare smoked! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 14:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 17:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glass will never be as ugly as concrete.  As long as it's cleaned once in a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 16:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could try contacting WCVB directly (they're still around).  Ask for their news library. One possibility is that it was on their news magazine show, Chronicle, which is still around.  It certainly sounds like a Chronicle-type subject. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Transparent Look For MassArts New Huntington Building </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 16:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 15:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are many people in America who take pride in having opinions NOT informed by reputable science.  And studies show that presenting them with facts doesn't change their views.

How can scientists get through to those people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 15:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the money. The political will.  There is one whole party in the USA that believes that private charity is better, and that if people are poor it is their own fault. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the homeless population is changing: its older and sicker; shelters aren't prepared </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 23:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What North America can expect from El Nino </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 21:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 8 scientists on their favorite science fiction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 04:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 04:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For years, Boston has celebrated [First Night](http://www.firstnightboston.org/) with a huge party.  It's a bit scaled back this year, but it's also free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
