<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3750</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 22:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard Jack Gylenhaal is better... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 15:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even fucking Boriello keeps scoring against us... Although that may have to do something with our atrocious defence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 10:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live pretty much in the country next door and its a reminder what we could have done if not for the hatred, since back then we were one country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 09:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its Sarajevo I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 03:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back when I was a kid, i just loved your team, I feel so bad seeing a team who was shoulder to shoulder with Real and Barca, struggle so much now. God I loved Albelda and Mendieta (only seen clips of him though). Even though i was a Barca fan i was still runing around and yelling Morientes whenever i scored in a pickup game, you guys were so nice to watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 17:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guess who has two thumbs and has fell in a manhole? This guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 15:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I quit a long time ago, and now I play only like 7,8 2-set matches with my cousin during the summer. I live in a small town like 20k people so its hard to find a hitting partner but I can still hold my ground against a lot of active players. Recently I beat my mate who didnt quit and has been training here and in Italy for the past 12 years, the end score was 6-4, 2-6, 6-4 and if I were more in shape I'd have done better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 10:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started training like twelve years ago and these were one of the first exercises we were doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 00:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His slice was a thing of beauty, atleast to me. I felt everytime he sliced it, the ball would get sawed in half. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 00:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When in the post match interview Fed said that he endured a tough loss aswell here last year, and Andy replied with "You only won 5 of them" was probably my favourite interview moment ever. Right beside when Fed said that Murray would like to win the first Australian open for british tennis in "what is it, a 150,000 years?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 22:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After that I started rooting for Roddick so badly, cause he did everything right but a bad backhand volley and a couple of funny forehands cost him the win pretty much. Shame that he never made it back into another big final again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I may just be a bitter Fed fan, but i dont think the '09 Wimby final gets nearly as much recognition as the '08 one, and i dont think it was much worse to be honest. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 21:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 07:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are striking but also suede, so honestly id rather watch them than wear them cause suede is a bitch to clean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My first pair of Air Forces ever, picked them up for 90 euros. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 01:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 13:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But Wolfsburg hosts Dortmund, not the other way round. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 13:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a fucking assist by Messi, great vision. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 21:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will it melt my heart? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 23:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speaking as a Fed fan, its so nice to watch a 1HBH withouth the gutwrenching fear of it ending up in the net.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 21:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God I hate serbian commentators. The guy on eurosport keeps trying to find anything about other players and divert it towards Novak. He just said that Monfils and his lack of interest in playing a game where he was 0-40, and 1-5 in the set down, were supposed to annoy Novak ffs... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 18:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They agreed to a buyout, and they are paying him around two mil a yer till 2022 i think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 17:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, Larry had financial stability, his income was certain whether he played or not, but Kyrgios has to play to earn pretty much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 12:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But he retired, which means the Bucks were left with his huge contract that they still have to pay off. In tennis if you retire, noone gives a fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 01:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For instance, im a two hander since i can remember, but lately, when i decide to go to the courts since i stopped playing competitevely, whenever i get a short ball i decide to let the one hander fly. Sure it feels amazing, but any deeper balls, or a bit higher i immediately decide to change my grip and go with two hands. I think a lot of people prefer the 2H cause its more comfortable and a firmer and better feel for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 10:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there is a certain difference between a DW and a Rolex, so i wouldnt make that sort of a comparison lightly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 21:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who turned water into wine, but when i put wine in a water bottle when i go for a run, suddenly i have a "problem". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 03:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hating the Lakers is like a religion, the reason i get up on a tough wednesday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 16:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats basically what i was asking. I worked physical work this summer, earned a bit, and money is no pressure for me but i just thought id check to be certain. 

Nah, gym requires work and i think my "2 photocopiers 1 guy and a palmtree" live show is doing quite well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 15:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just imagine Shakespear if he was retarded and a goldfish. So basically unconnected sentences, with grammatic errors combined with a plot that lasts as long as my memory which is 26 seconds when I write. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 18:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> L for Liverpool? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 03:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I trained swimming for like 3,4 years, although i stopped caring after a year and a half. Since i go back to training every few months i get tired very quickly. The trick i found, is limit the use of the legs in the first part since they tire you the quickest, if you want to rest a bit and go slower, and at like 250 start using them properly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 11:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is annoying when playing ofcourse, he would return a balistic missile, but later in his interviews he shows his kind side. I remember when he beat Fed in the 2014 finals, which I barely survived, i still hate that match, he said to Roger later on "Thanks for letting me win" which brought a smile to my infuriated face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 09:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Referring to cevapi as a traditional Croatian dish is blasphemy to the holy grail of them, the cevapi from Sarajevo, and im not even Bosnian so im not biased. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 04:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like Delpos forehand should be somehow forbidden, it looks like it could kill a medium sized dog.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 03:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just thinking about that. He wasnt during his younger years, his emotions got the best of him then just as Feds got him for example when he was hot headed, but Djokovic matured incredibly as a player and as a sportsman. Just like Roddick told Fed once "Id love to hate you but you're really nice", for me the same applies to Nole.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 03:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being a Partizan and a Boston fan, 2010 was a shitshow for me aswell. And being a Federer fan didnt help since he started getting old and hurting himself and Novak became a fucking Apache helicopter, almost unstoppable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 04:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They usually are but this was taken after about an hour of drinking and dancing so when they fall down i just tuck them up however and this is the result  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 04:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? Here they are like the go to shorts when you go out in the summer, like 95 percent of people here have them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 03:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flyknit in white is a bitch to keep clean, atleast mine were, anything and everything would get on there an fucking stay. However even though they seem nice in black as a casual shoe, i think there are far more prettier designs by Nike, flyknit for me isnt that great unless its in combined colors like the red AF1 Nike introduced a while back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 00:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought so, but i wondered since it doesnt show the main part, the thing thats hangs from it, the crystal or whatever...
Nah not diamonds these are my gifts 
http://imgur.com/a/xCVL8 
and the other one 
http://imgur.com/zIjt075 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 15:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So like a regular Melissa McCarthy?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 15:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Perks of Being a Wallflower.
Absolutely in love with this movie yet when recommend it to people they are either sceptical or surprised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
