<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject366</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 03:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you live in the area near our warehouse, which is in Troy, Michigan you should send in your resume.  At least we know that you can use the Internet, although you capitalization needs a little sprucing up.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 03:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The other day a sex shop worked did an AMA and she said that the brick and mortar store that she worked in served predominantly men.  I think this is fairly common in the industry.  Traditional retail locations serve more men, online sex toy stores serve more women.  It seems to make some sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 03:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a minute so I wanted to preach a little more.  The thing about companies that make expensive vibrators is that they have lots of people on staff that tell you how great they are, but lower priced vibes can often be just as good or better.  Don't get me wrong, I like LELO toys and they score really well on our in house test, but some brands that cost a fortune do not.  There is a product called the Little Chroma that costs $125 and is outscored by another vibe called The PleasureCraft that sells for $30.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 03:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually started an online shop that was totally private and people could be free to buy anything they wanted or needed in total privacy.  It all started with hemorrhoid creams, Depends, and condoms actually, but once people found out about the privacy, mostly they just wanted to buy sex toys.  I'm happy to sell them.  The drugstore business was really difficult.  There are a million, nice, inviting, convenient drugstores to shop within.  There are very few nice sex toy retailers.  It's easier in life to have weaker competitors.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 03:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first idea was to start a website where people could buy embarrassing things.  It is called ShopInPrivate.com.  It began as a place to buy hemorrhoid cream in total privacy and it worked.  But once we started offering totally private shopping, all of the customers wanted vibrators!  Eventually, the ShopInPrivate.com business acquired the Vibrators.com business, so now I run both, but for REDDIT's sake I skipped the ShopInPrivate.com in the title.  It's been a fun ride. 

I think peopel who have known me for a while are kinda impressed with how it has gone, but it is tough to meet someone new and explain what I do.  People jump to all sorts of conclusions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 03:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted this above:  I know people like to see proof, so I posted something on our corporate page about me doing an AMA today. Here is a link: http://www.priveco.com/tomnarpresis.html
That is my picture although my teeth aren't that white and I have a couple of more wrinkles than that. Also, I almost never wear a suit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 03:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We actually have a vibration measurement machine and a sound measurement device as well.  It might be less exciting than you think.  We also have a small group of advisors that tests them in a romantic sorta way, but the majority of the work is more scientific.  

The Hitachi Magic wand has been a top seller for the 14 years I've been in the business.  It's the "old reliable" of the sex toy business.  You should try it sometime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 03:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We go about 60% female based upon identifiable first names. People like K.C. you cannot tell and some names aren't recognizable.  We don't ask gender but we do sorta want to know how we are scoring.  It is important to us to be female safe.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 03:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for asking.  We like vibes that are three things:  Body safe, quiet, and powerful and we test them to find out.  Our best seller right now is called the Romance because it is all three and it isn't too expensive at $35.  http://www.vibrators.com/lamour-romance-vibrator.html

Rechargeable vibes are nice too, but they generally cost a lot more to get that one feature, so I'm cool without it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 03:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know people like to see proof, so I posted something on our corporate page about me doing an AMA today.  Here is a link:
http://www.priveco.com/tomnarpresis.html  
That is my picture although my teeth aren't that white and I have a couple of more wrinkles than that.  Also, I almost never wear a suit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AMA - Vibrators.com Founder/President Tom Nardone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 03:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feel free to ask me anything about the sex toy business.  I'll try to be good natured, funny, and willing to discuss just about anything having to do with my company.  In the 14 years I've been selling vibrators and other weird stuff online I have seen a lot.  

OK folks, it is after midnight now, I'm going to go to sleep now.  I'll log on tomorrow and answer more questions if you want to leave them.  Thanks for asking questions and for reading my AMA.  I hope it was interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 06:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I apologize that I took so long to figure this all out.  I am doing an AMA next Tuesday night April 23rd.  I hope you will ask me something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 06:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I apologize that I took so long to figure this all out.  I am doing an AMA next Tuesday night April 23rd.  I hope you will ask me something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 06:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I apologize that I took so long to figure this all out.  I am doing an AMA next Tuesday night April 23rd.  I hope you will ask me something. 

People choose all sorts of different shapes, although phallic usually sells best.  I guest nature is pretty powerful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 06:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I apologize that I took so long to figure this all out.  I am doing an AMA next Tuesday night April 23rd.  I hope you will ask me something.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 06:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't have to be embarrassed to buy an adult product.  There are plenty of stores where you can buy one in public.  Online there are tons of sites that will sell you one and then email you every week for the rest of your natural life.  Some people just prefer to buy a product from a company that doesn't share or use their personal info and works hard to keep the whole thing private.  That's us.  

But honestly, the thread is Ask Me Anything, not ask me to pitch you my company.  This is supposed to be sorta fun and funny, a chance to get an inside look at an unusual company.  

I'll be back on Tuesday night to field questions.  Talk to you then and I won't forget about you... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 06:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too.  I guess we are done then or are you going to have the last word? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 06:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My career developed slowly as my company transitioned from just ShopInPrivate.com to Bachelorette.com and then when we acquired Vibrators.com I started to be known more for toys.  

The most awkward moment was one time when I was driving our company van which had a "Bachelorette.com" logo on it.  I was filling it with gas and a car full of women approached me and asked "how much do you charge?" and I said "for what?" and they said "To take off your clothes!"  I paused and looked at them for a second and said "Miss, I don't think anyone wants to see me without my clothes..."   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 06:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started an online store that sells embarrassing items in 1998 and then just kept selling items people wanted to buy privately.  It's been a weird ride but I think we are still a very unique company and offer a valuable, private service.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 06:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't use anything that doesn't have FDA approval.  I'm not much of a condom user (wife and 3 kids) but the ones with the swirl at the tip are much better.  Is there a reason to stray from Trojan brand? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 06:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then don't reply... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 06:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a great product idea!  We will add it to the list!  Dr. Jerky's Keyboard Cleaner or something like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 06:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, I shot a video once of me removing my back hair.  It now has 144,000 views.  Ick!
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=i4CGohsHsd0
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
