<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3232</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Truly petty bickering in /r/OldSchoolCool over whether or not Ingrid Bergman is wearing makeup in a photo. "...you just wanted to milk one of Reddit's stupid circlejerks." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 03:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's a boy! Harvey, born 2-11, birth story in comments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 20:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In celebration of Mardi Gras, I made mini King Cakes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 01:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> God save the queen, the fascist regime! Potential H-bomb in /r/funny when one commenter knocks the British Monarchy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 21:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I made some Bialys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 16:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone here like Bialys? Recipe in comments. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 15:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ideas for foods to stock up on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 17:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So my due date is approaching in a week, and my doctor thinks it should be around that day or a few days after based on my last exam. For those who have some experience, what foods do you stock up on? I usually do all the shopping and the cooking in our home, and clearly that's going to have to change temporarily if I'm breastfeeding and caring for a newborn and recovering from giving birth. Any tips? Should I be making casseroles? Buying canned soup? Or should I just give the responsibility of securing groceries to my husband (we're both taking a couple of weeks off after the birth)? We've never done this before, so I could use the benefit of your wisdom! 

He is wonderful and will do whatever is needed, I'm sure. Also, his mother will be helping us out for a few days, too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hackles are raised over garlic in /r/food. "I personally live where we have a rich culinary tradition, and the idea of celebrating ketchup or garlic is pretty appalling." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 16:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The use of light in this figure is a one of the Kind Bart masterpiece." $2,954. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 15:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OP posts the meals she makes for her boyfriend who is trying to eat healthier, numerous children develop heartburn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 06:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dietary experts convene to analyze OP's slowcooker chicken thigh meal! 


**Primi:**

["The criticism is because this isn't a 'healthy' meal by almost any reasonable definition of the word healthy."](https://np.reddit.com/r/food/comments/430fgr/my_bf_is_trying_to_eat_healthy_amateur_meal_prep/czemed8?context=3)

**Secondi:**

["What exactly do you consider healthy?"](https://np.reddit.com/r/food/comments/430fgr/my_bf_is_trying_to_eat_healthy_amateur_meal_prep/czelsoc?sort=top context=3)

**Contorno:**

[Unusual argument about "earth-sourced" foods and what "natural" means](https://np.reddit.com/r/food/comments/430fgr/my_bf_is_trying_to_eat_healthy_amateur_meal_prep/czekjza?context=3)

**Dolce:**

[Boyfriend chimes in](https://np.reddit.com/r/food/comments/430fgr/my_bf_is_trying_to_eat_healthy_amateur_meal_prep/czekre7?context=3).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So no one told you votes were gonna be this way...You hate on Friend and then, your Karma's DOA! This /r/Television drama is not stuck in second gear. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 21:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I got my gummy bear mold! Homemade raspberry and pineapple gummy bears (instructions in comments) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 14:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I made fried shrimp with vodka-beer batter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 17:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone is very angry about an intricate Kindergarten lunch in /r/food. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 04:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A real slapfight in /r/cringe over how fake reality TV is. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 00:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just one more example of selfless public service. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 22:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well then...okay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 22:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smoked baby back ribs (3-2-1 method, recipe in comments) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 20:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I smoked baby back ribs for dinner last night! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 19:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baby back ribs I smoked yesterday for dinner [OC] [3456  2304] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 19:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Domo Arigato, Mr. Dramato! A full English breakfast inspires an argument about...sushi? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 03:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Footage of a "monkey willy" leads to a fight about child rearing and sex education in /r/videos. "Oh fuck off. You don't learn about sex by watching a monkey two pump." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 22:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5:Why do belly buttons pop inside out a lot of the time in pregnancy, but don't do the same with obesity? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 04:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Motrhead (Featuring Wendy O.Williams) - No Class [Metal] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 04:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My sister and I made a bche de Nol yesterday! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 16:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some commenters invest in a small drama startup in /r/delusionalartists when the topic of Steve Jobs' death comes up. "Fuck off with your fan boy bullshit." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 17:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Birthday dinner I made for my husband: Beef Wellington, roasted fingerling potatoes, braised lacinato kale + baby spinach, and miniature red velvet layer cake. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 16:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Made some marmalade yesterday (instructions within) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 19:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A fun and easy gift idea for the holidays: infused spirits (recipe in comments) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 22:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brief but glorious slapfight in /r/OKCupid between two users who appear to have a bit of a history. "I think, if you were to die, that no one would be bothered." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 16:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please sir, may I have some drama? Argument in TIFU over whether or not an allegedly poor and hungry family was really poor and hungry. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 01:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fake plastic drama in /r/dataisbeautiful. Are cell phones destroying the earth faster than fake Christmas trees? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 01:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Mandela Effect memory about the James Bond film "Moonraker" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 22:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like a lot of kids growing up in the 80s, I watched James Bond movies, including the (IMO) terrible 1979 offering *Moonraker*. I hadn't seen it since the late 80s, but I was sure I remembered that Jaws (Richard Kiel) ended up with a nerdy girl with braces. In fact, I even remember a scene in which he smiled at her (with his metal teeth) and she smiled back at him with her metal brace face. I would have sworn up and down that this happened, and I "remembered" it right down to the color of her outfit (yellow). Rewatching that movie recently, I saw that while that scene happened, she had *perfect* teeth, no braces. [Here is a picture of the two together](http://www.movie-moron.com/wp-content/gallery/top-tens/worst-james-bond-movies-jaws-in-love.jpg). I remembered a visual detail that was never there to begin with.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL at least 71 people have been killed by poisonous snakebites during religious services in the United States, including the founder of the snake handling movement, George Went Hensley. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 15:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [small Rant] I'm officially ridiculous </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 15:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last night I actually managed to burn my belly on the oven door while I was leaning in to use a meat thermometer. I woke up this morning with a red burn line right where a C-section scar would be--it looks like I had a C-section and I haven't even given birth yet! 

I feel like I did when I was a kid and went through growth spurts, because I swear I've grown out more just in the past week, and I keep losing track of where the bump ends! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Waffle House worker shot dead after telling customer not to smoke inside </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 15:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shepherd's pie, or cottage pie? A hot slice of meaty debate in /r/food. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 17:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is this omelette underdone? A few eggs get broken over that question in /r/food. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 14:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Emma Stone officially signs on to play Billie Jean King in Battle Of The Sexes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 15:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's a Walk-Off in /r/delusionalartists when someone praises Kanye West's fashion line </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 13:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Commenter in /r/pettyrevenge thinks cops make too much money, arguments ensue. "I hope you have to work a shitty, difficult job until you are 90." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 16:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Things turn sour in a post about Diwali sweets when one commenter says he doesn't like Indian desserts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 15:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Body cam footage of an SUV trying to run over a police officer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 14:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't think that's what's meant by "personal information." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 03:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it "lazy" to not make your own pizza dough? Opinions are tossed around like so much warm dough in /r/food. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 14:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Semantic slapfight over the meaning of the word "entitled" in /r/Tinder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 18:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Defend yourselves you fucking kids, don't just downvote." Debate about the pop industry and the merits of Katy Perry's music in /r/music. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 17:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Body image and "safe space" debate in /r/pics gets heavy fast. "I'm willing to bet money that you look liked warmed up dog shit..." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 05:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rule #1: No Rage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 01:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can't help but love Pangolins! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 17:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OP throws a birthday party for her pug--some of the members of /r/relationship_advice question her stability. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 15:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unusual drama in ELI5 about "vibrational frequencies" and emotions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 00:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Argument in /r/movies about Star Wars casting. Strong is this thread with the drama. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 23:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is what it sounds like...when dogs smile. Wait a minute, can dogs smile? Some folks in /r/aww discuss. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 20:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well, it's happened again: someone in /r/cooking says real chili shouldn't have beans, and others respond with plates of frijoles con drama. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 17:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mozzarella lovers bicker over quality and authenticity, accusations of food snobbery abound. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-11 16:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Very cool demonstration of the Mridangam, a percussion instrument from Southern India </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-10 21:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Busta Rhymes ft. Twista - Can You Keep Up [Rap] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-10 21:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that comedian Retta (Parks and Rec) is the niece of Ellen Johnson Sirleaf, the President of Liberia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-10 15:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alice Cooper - The Man With The Golden Gun (rejected James Bond theme) [Rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 02:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Breaker one-nine, it's clean and clear to Drama Town! Truck driver does an AMA, comments on a sexual escapade in his truck, alleged girlfriend shows up. Dramatic discussion of fake accounts and unsafe driving follows. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 17:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need boy name ideas! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 15:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're not finding out the sex of our baby until birth, so we're trying to be prepared with a name for a boy or a girl. We found a girl's name we agreed upon within the first month, but we still can't decide on a boy's name. Most of the names I suggest he vetoes and vice versa, so we have a short list and are looking for more ideas. We're hyphenating the last name, so I don't want something that is *too* long. We're both from the U.S. 

Our list of possibilities as it stands now: Harvey, Lincoln, Logan, and Apollo. Any other ideas?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A post about a survivor of the recent college shooting somehow leads to yet another argument about Caitlyn Jenner. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 20:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Royal Jelly," an episode of Roald Dahl's Tales of the Unexpected (1980). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 18:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone calls stealing a package a "victimless crime." /r/Whatcouldgowrong? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 05:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kenny Rogers and The First Edition - Just Dropped In [Psychedelic Rock] (1967) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 02:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What food do you find disgusting in theory but still delicious? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 18:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another argument over Ahmed Mohamed's clock, this time in /r/videos. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 19:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas Man Arrested For $4.5 Million Bitcoin Ponzi Scheme </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 05:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/funny lets it all hang out in an argument about a braless bridesmaid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 03:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This belt that Ed Gein made out of human nipples. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 22:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Ted Bundy, handling his own defense, asked a character witness to marry him during his trial in Florida. Due to an obscure state law, when she said "yes" on the stand their marriage was considered legal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 22:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hilariously pedantic slapfight in /r/AdviceAnimals about the correct uses of the terms "mods" and "staff" when discussing Reddit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 17:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finally had dinner at Girl   the Goat in Chicago! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 16:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Pikachu hat creates a big tussle in /r/pics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 19:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jerkin' 2: Electric Smugaloo -- Announcement Regarding Shitposts, Smugposts, and Circlejerky Comments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-07 14:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello dramanauts!

This summer we tried to reduce the number of smugposts, shitposts and circlejerky comments in SRD. We've received pushback from some members of the community, while others have been supportive. We've struggled to apply the rule consistently and continually run to risk of making some users feel singled out in a negative way. Most important, intervention by our team has not had the intended effect of reducing these types of comments. It is not our goal to antagonize our readers--rather, we want things to run smoothly and maintain a jovial and respectful atmosphere. As a result, we will no longer be intervening when it comes to all the DAE Reddit sucks! comments and similar jerks. If members of the community choose to call out comments they feel are circlejerky, you have our full support.


This is not to say that we have abandoned the hope that we can maintain a civil level of productive discourse on SRD. We want SRD to be both fun and a place where you can have a discussion that ventures outside the standard jerkbut its clear that the effort we put in to facilitate reaching this goal was not effective. We welcome input from the community on this issue. What are your thoughts and suggestions?


Going forward, we will still maintain other comment rulesno slurs, no personal attacks, and no flamewars/flamebaiting. These are pretty straightforward and have worked well in the community. 

EDIT: And yes, username baiting is still against the rules.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I now pronounce this drama: A superhero wedding cake leads to a debate about "social norms" and maturity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 17:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A hot cup of drama when someone distinguishes between hot chocolate and hot cocoa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 15:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deep fried fat drama in /r/WTF. "Don't sugar coat it or you'll eat that too." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 03:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You want salad gravy on that pizza? Someone doesn't care for ranch dressing in /r/food... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 21:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Commenter in /r/nottheonion mocks goth subculture and states "i have never belonged to a cliche ever." He doesn't receive a positive response. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 16:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drama from the Far Side: Someone posts a Gary Larson cartoon in /r/funny, and petty bickering ensues about whether or not it's okay to do that without the artist's permission. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 14:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Argument in TIL over whether or not the characters Friends got laid more than the average person. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 00:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A tempting assortment of charcuterie drama about the importance of plating. "Does anybody in this sub even know how to actually cook?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 23:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Things get catty in a post about a dog's dinner in /r/shittyfoodporn. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 06:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it "eating well" or is it "2 AM drunk food?" Or both? Commenters chew on American cuisine in /r/food, and some of them spit it out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-22 20:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The phrase "sleeping with the fishes" leads to petty bickering, grammar policing, and a guy who is documenting downvotes and gildings as they happen. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-20 18:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone asks for a TL;DR in /r/serialpodcast, and things get very personal very quickly. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-20 17:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OP's fiance has a taste for junk food, her parents have a taste for the finer things, and now there's the taste of blood in the water in /r/relationships </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 01:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drama in TIL when one commenter says he doesn't understand why people lock their doors. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 21:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Jean-Claude Van Damme was originally cast as the Predator and appears in the first few scenes but was replaced by 7'2" actor Kevin Peter Hall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 15:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Gene Roddenberry originally wrote Counselor Troi to have four breasts, but his wife talked him out of it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 02:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "One of the few people that tells it like it is" in /r/pizza starts delicious drama when he says some pizza doesn't appeal to him. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 17:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any green/veggie supplements to recommend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 22:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been eating greens like spinach and kale, but I'd like to supplement a little in smoothies. I've read about a lot of different green "superfood" products--obviously I wouldn't buy anything with green tea or dubious herbs, but I was wondering if anyone has found a good, safe product that is a good source (with stuff like kale, wheat grass, etc.)? As silly as it sounds, there are days when liquids just seem to be easier for me than solids. but I want to maintain good nutrition. Unfortunately, I own a blender but not a juicer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever cured your own meats? Well, HAVE YOU? Salty drama over prosciutto preparation and pretentiousness in /r/food </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 17:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steve Vai -- Paganini's 5th Caprice [Rock, covers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 17:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that in 1726 a woman named Mary Toft pretended to give birth to dead rabbits. The hoax resulted in a temporary decrease in rabbit consumption in Britain. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 20:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A man's Tinder pic leads commenters to debate the ethics of snapping buttcrack pictures at a Magic tournament </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 18:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brief but spicy drama in /r/KitchenConfidential about health code violations. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 03:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A post in /r/facepalm leads to a discussion of two-timing, and one commenter accuses others of downvoting out of "jealousy." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 00:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 8 people found dead in Houston home after homeowner exchanges gunfire with cops during a welfare check. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-09 16:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Time Magazine cover about VR spawns very real drama in /r/crappydesign. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-07 05:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Birthing Center vs. Hospital Birth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 21:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going through options right now and wanted to get some thoughts from anyone who has used a birthing center with nurse midwives (or had a doula present at a hospital birth). I'm taking a tour of one next week that's just down the street from my house, and then I'll be touring the hospital unit where my doctor works. I want to think about my options because I plan on going natural, and I want to be able to walk/move rather than just being stuck in a bed. What are your experiences/advice regarding birthing options?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weird drama in /r/askreddit about science and God. "Try and run God through the scientific method. Seriously, just try." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 04:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone asks for a recipe "converted into American" in /r/food--it doesn't go over well. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 01:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL at one time 7-Up contained lithium citrate. It was originally called Bib-Label Lithiated Lemon-Lime Soda. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 17:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is "barbecue" anyway? The terminology debate flames on in /r/food. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 01:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bickering in AskReddit about showing respect for restaurant servers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 15:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drama is brewing in /r/tifu over the merits of bagged tea. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 18:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Children have a slapflight about slapping children in /r/funny </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 04:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the MGM lion survived a plane crash and lived on milk and sandwiches until it was rescued </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 21:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Olive Oatman, a White woman who lived with a Mojave tribe for 5 years after being kidnapped at 14 and traded by a Yavapai tribe. Seen here with traditional Mojave face tattoo [1000  1478] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 21:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Touchy exchange about negging and game in /r/tinder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 21:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please Read Before Submitting New Drama Covering The Subs That Have Gone Private! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 02:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are currently keeping the updates on Victoria's dismissal and the wave of private subs within three posts on the front page: 

1)   [Live Thread](https://www.reddit.com/r/SubredditDrama/comments/3bxm5v/reddit_live_thread_for_amageddon_pm_or_reply_if/)

2) [second post with updated list](https://www.reddit.com/r/SubredditDrama/comments/3bxjyu/list_of_subreddits_suddenly_going_private/)  by /u/Diotic

3) [Original Megathread](https://www.reddit.com/r/SubredditDrama/comments/3bwgjf/riama_set_to_private_over_mod_firing/)  by /u/eonOne

If you have new info that has not been covered by one of these threads, you can let the OPs of those threads know to add them to their updates. We will be keeping track of these posts to ensure that they continue to be updated. **DO NOT** submit posts with titles like "______ has gone private" and just a link to the sub that's gone private. This does not provide SRD members anything to read because they cannot access the links. The rationale for this decision is that we want this information to be easily accessible and well organized for you, our readers. 

EDIT: In addition, please avoid posting comments like "Don't buy gold" or "That's it, I'm outta here." We're getting a great outrage tour of crazytown market as we watch Rome burn--there's no need to duplicate it in here. 

EDIT 2: In order to keep things manageable in the Live thread, please do not to submit subreddits to the Live thread unless they are over 20k subscribers. 

EDIT 3: We have temporarily removed the Live thread while we attempt to contact the author due to significant, pervasive instances of witchhunting. 

EDIT 4: Live thread back up and running as we have additional people working on it. We also have a post detailing the [response from the Admins](https://www.reddit.com/r/SubredditDrama/comments/3bytne/the_admins_have_broken_the_silence_with_posts_to/)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A sushi platter inspires verbal aggression in /r/food as a discussion of freshness becomes quickly heated...and personal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 15:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/relationships decides to break things off with OP when he asks about a friends with benefits situation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 14:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drama in /r/food over egg refrigeration. "Your stupidity and unsafe food advice make you downvote worthy." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 16:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More advice on parenting from AdviceAnimals. "...try your best not to do to it whatever your parents did to you." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 20:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wild-caught Alaskan king salmon with fresh corn and tomato salad [4147  2765] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 15:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wild-caught Alaskan king salmon with fresh corn and tomato salad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 15:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Debate over Bree Newsome's actions in /r/pics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 15:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A picture of a hot dog in /r/shittyfoodporn leads to a wonderfully petty argument about the car stereo in the background. This drama goes up to 11. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 23:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tangy drama in /r/cooking about sharing barbecue sauce recipes. "Why not practice making one instead of asking other people to give away their hard work?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 00:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the song "Radiohead" by the Talking Heads (for which the band Radiohead is named) was based on Stephen Tobolowsky's professed psychic abilities. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 19:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that in 1982, Key West declared its independence from the U.S. after the Border Patrol set up a road block between Miami and Key West </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 01:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It starts out as steak drama, then morphs into grammar drama! Magical transforming slapfight in /r/foodhacks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 17:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Return of Electro-Cures: Symptom of Psychiatry's Crisis? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 21:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Commenter in an /r/atheism thread says to OP "You know what dude? You're cancer." 41 child argument ensues. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 19:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hilarious slapfight in /r/crappydesign about bilingual signage. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 19:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two game show contestants don't know what a kilogram is. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 00:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Braised goat tacos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 22:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a post about the Miranda Rights, commenters do not elect to remain silent. "Is your ass ever jealous of the shit that comes out of your mouth?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 20:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I made braised goat tacos! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 19:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drama in /r/AdviceAnimals about hiring practices and applicants with "alphabet soup names." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 00:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tempers flair in an /r/pettyrevenge post about camping. "Seriously if NATURE is too much to share for you then fuck you." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 22:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Paul Quinn college in south Dallas converted its football field into a farm as a response to the food desert conditions in the area </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 21:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Argument in /r/movies about how much Entourage someone should watch to form an opinion about Entourage. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 18:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A wedding cake topper creates dissent in /r/gaming. "...unless this is in a backyard or an Applebees, I'd show a little more decorum than this." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 15:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OP in /r/relationships presents a custody problem, is accused of homophobia and heavily downvoted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 20:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crosswalk drama in /r/Chicago. "Look everyone, it's an idiot!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 21:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Argument in WTF over what "electrocuted" hot metal looks like. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 20:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where do the children play? AdviceAnimals argues about it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 18:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brief but tangy slapfight about pineapple in /r/foodporn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 17:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone who describes monogamy as "extremely, achingly difficult" posts to /r/relationships, conceiving numerous children </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 03:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This drama's for you! A joke about Budweiser leads to accusations of pretension and condescension in /r/jokes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 00:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that in 1992 Willie Nelson put out an album to help pay his tax debt. It's called "The IRS Tapes: Who'll Buy My Memories?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 18:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jiro dream of drama in /r/food. " Tone down your fanboyism." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 18:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More /r/Bestof drama, this time when a commenter compares the Fattening to the Charlie Hebdo Shooting. "kindly keep your words out of my mouth. it's unsanitary." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 21:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone comments "Dude, let it go" on a post in /r/videos about obesity. OP proceeds to offer him gold if he can prove he's not fat, long slapfight ensues. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 21:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Slapfight about violence in India vs. the U.S. in TIL "Not every country alludes to your crazy fantasies." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pinup Diane Webber, circa 1958 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 03:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The tsunami from the FPH quake hits /r/dataisbeautiful </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Argument over whether or not Reddit is going to start losing "normal" members](https://np.reddit.com/r/dataisbeautiful/comments/39fk2u/word_cloud_of_yesterdays_announcements_comment/cs2zh0w?context=3)

["You don't truly understand the complexity behind the situation..."](https://np.reddit.com/r/dataisbeautiful/comments/39fk2u/word_cloud_of_yesterdays_announcements_comment/cs31lo8?context=3)

[Debate over bias in the implementation of the rules](https://np.reddit.com/r/dataisbeautiful/comments/39fk2u/word_cloud_of_yesterdays_announcements_comment/cs2y6ph?context=3)

The [whole thread](https://np.reddit.com/r/dataisbeautiful/comments/39fk2u/word_cloud_of_yesterdays_announcements_comment/?sort=top) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An argument on The Bachelorette gets increasingly more uncomfortable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 18:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Delightfully petty slapfight over the merits of cosplay in /r/gaming </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 14:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Accusations of snobbery in /r/pizza. "When is the last time you had sex?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 20:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There once was a lonely OP, who went to a wedding date free. Online she mourned, and children were born--/r/relationships drama flows free! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 21:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Larry David had a lawyer named Lloyd Braun, for which the Seinfeld character was named. Braun went on to become Chairman of the ABC. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 05:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Highest grade kobe beef drama in /r/kitchenconfidential when chefs hash out the moral boundaries of preparing steak for customers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 19:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A cemetery sandbox attracts numerous children in /r/pics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 18:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP posts a picture of a sandbox built onto a grave so that a child can "play" with his deceased sibling. [Whole post](http://np.reddit.com/r/pics/comments/38pab8/a_mother_adds_a_sandbox_to_her_sons_grave_so_her/)

[OP responds when someone calls it "sick" and receives tons of downvotes](http://np.reddit.com/r/pics/comments/38pab8/a_mother_adds_a_sandbox_to_her_sons_grave_so_her/crwr7jk?context=3). 

[Someone describes it as morbid](http://np.reddit.com/r/pics/comments/38pab8/a_mother_adds_a_sandbox_to_her_sons_grave_so_her/crwr6ox?context=3) and, again, OP responds. Then someone points out that OP posted the [same article](https://np.reddit.com/r/MorbidReality/comments/38p5v5/a_mother_adds_a_sandbox_to_her_sons_grave_so_her/) to /r/morbidreality. 

OP gets called out [again here](http://np.reddit.com/r/pics/comments/38pab8/a_mother_adds_a_sandbox_to_her_sons_grave_so_her/crwr7yi?context=3) for the same thing, and again the downvotes pile up. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More than 19 children and counting get into it over The Duggar family in /r/nottheonion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 19:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Of Narcissism and Nude Photos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 15:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Background: OP in /r/relationships catches his girlfriend cheating by contacting the guy she's cheating with:

I asked for one as proof, acting as the "sister's boyfriend", "because I was very good friends with her real boyfriend(me), so I would like to help him save some heartache". Sure enough, I received a text of her naked in our apartment where she has lived for only the length of our relationship. It was proven to me then.

Some of the commenters question his tactics, which leads to drama:

[OP argues that his actions are necessary for going "up against a narcissist."](http://np.reddit.com/r/relationships/comments/38ifir/update_i_25m_suspect_my_24f_girlfriend_of_6/crvhpwf?context=3) but others disagree. 

[Narcissism comes up again, but this time the main slapfight is over the legal aspects of sharing nude pictures](http://np.reddit.com/r/relationships/comments/38ifir/update_i_25m_suspect_my_24f_girlfriend_of_6/crvh1qx?context=3)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fake meat leads to real meaty drama in /r/futurology </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 22:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I wouldn't call that Ramen." A hot, salty drama broth cooks up in /r/food </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 05:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drama is swimming upstream to spawn in /r/food </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 19:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eyebrows raise in /r/tinder when someone writes "maybe she's not trying to impress your insecure ass." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 17:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guy takes on makeup in /r/funny </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 14:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is he cheating with a hitchhiker? Tune in to /r/relationships and find out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 01:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Transplant staff drop a donor heart on the ground </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 21:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Long slapfight cum biology lesson in /r/funny about Caitlyn Jenner, pronouns and gender identity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 23:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drama in /r/relationships about how OP's boyfriend might have gotten cut. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 20:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Commenters in /r/facepalm tackle the good old incest debate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 16:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone in /r/skyrim writes "I hate mods," and salty comebacks ensue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 07:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beef over beef in /r/india </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 21:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buttery (or should it be creamy?) Alfredo sauce drama in /r/cooking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 23:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Context: OP makes a post questioning the common use of cream in Alfredo sauce. Original post can be seen [here](http://np.reddit.com/r/Cooking/comments/37twab/the_alfredo_cream_conspiracy/)

["in the 21st century, an alfredo sauce is expected to be creamy..."](http://np.reddit.com/r/Cooking/comments/37twab/the_alfredo_cream_conspiracy/crpv7iu?context=3)

[Argument over the convenience of creamy Alfredo in restaurant kitchens](http://np.reddit.com/r/Cooking/comments/37twab/the_alfredo_cream_conspiracy/crptnkx?context=3)

["While I agree with your reasoning, it's still wrong."](http://np.reddit.com/r/Cooking/comments/37twab/the_alfredo_cream_conspiracy/crpxbwf?context=3) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Commenter in AdviceAnimals states that "everyone cheats." Everyone disagrees. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 15:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Butter spills in AskReddit over whether or not Led Zeppelin kidnapped a 14-year-old. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 06:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Missy Suicide does an AMA, leading to an extensive debate about how much art is worth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 19:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FPH drama hits r/CrazyIdeas when someone posts about about a verification system. Accusations of brigading and personal insults abound throughout. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 22:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Context: Someone posted to CrazyIdeas that "fatpeoplehate should have a verification system like gonewild to make sure it's users are fit like they claim." This leads to a number of arguments and lots of downvoting and upvoting. 

[Someone brings up medical issues](http://np.reddit.com/r/CrazyIdeas/comments/37bo4i/rfatpeoplehate_should_have_a_verification_system/crlft2g?context=3)

[Someone brings up the burden to society](http://np.reddit.com/r/CrazyIdeas/comments/37bo4i/rfatpeoplehate_should_have_a_verification_system/crlh0z8?context=3)

[Things get personal](http://np.reddit.com/r/CrazyIdeas/comments/37bo4i/rfatpeoplehate_should_have_a_verification_system/crlmxut?context=3) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Debate about beer and party etiquette in Advice Animals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 21:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Small but satisfying portion of sushi drama in /r/food </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 21:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/relationships debates "unrealistic standards" and "settling." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 17:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Frustrated weather man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 06:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drama in /r/nofap over a Bible quote. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 02:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My SO's birthday gets overshadowed by Christmas, so I made him a surprise "half-birthday" cake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 16:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My SO's birthday gets overshadowed by Christmas, so I made him a surprise "half-birthday" cake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 16:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that McDonald's in New Zealand serves a "Kiwiburger" that tops a beef patty with a fried egg and a slice of beet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 07:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chicago food drama in manages to cover both hotdogs and pizza with remarkable efficiency in /r/food </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 18:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Very uncomfortable stage hypnosis show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 01:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sparks fly in /r/tinder over what will get you laid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 21:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harvesting Geoduck Clams </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 18:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Welcome to The Jungle--meat processing drama in /r/WTF </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 01:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alanis Morissette's 1991 single "Walk Away." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 05:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Announcement: Clarifying Rules Regarding Circlebroke titles/posts, Meta posts, and Posts Containing Suicidal Statements </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 00:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **What is "Circlebroke"?**

Circlebroke is a sub dedicated to complaining about Reddit--it's about annoying trends and bad behavior. This is distinct from drama--posts in SRD should highlight the petty Internet fights that entertain us all. They should *not* be links to circlejerks or links to nondramatic chicanery to which you personally object. For example, a FPH-themed post with 50 "found the fatty" comments isn't drama. Similarly, long comment chains featuring fairly civil disagreements do not qualify as drama (regardless of whether or not you, personally, find it abhorrent). 


**What is a "Circlebroke title"?**

A Circlebroke title speaks more to the trend than it does to the actual drama. For example (I made these up, but I hope they illustrate the point):

"JusticePorn is totally not being racist again."

"Guess who shows up to defend the wage gap in /r/politics?"

"A post in Seattle subreddit about public transportation leads to an interesting conclusion: 'Black culture' is responsible." 

"Askmen has a problem with women: Exhibit J"

Circlebroke titles and posts will be removed with a corresponding explanation. If you are unsure about your title or post, you can ask us through modmail. 


**Is there a "meta" sub for SRD?**

Yes, for discussion or posts about SRD within the context of the metasphere, check out /r/MetaSubredditDrama 


**Announcement about submissions featuring suicidal people**

Submissions featuring suicidal comments will be removed. SRD is a fun place--the drama is supposed to be a source of entertainment. Suicidal statements are to be treated seriously and not to be used as a source for our posts. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some skepticism about James Randi leads to drama in TIL. "Show us on this Voodoo Doll where he touched you." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 03:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comment in /r/AdviceAnimals gets downvoted, commenter proceeded to pick on others' usernames </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 21:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Things come to a boil in this lobster thread, so get your drawn butter ready. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 20:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lax drama Lox down /r/FoodPorn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 09:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woman allegedly killed her fianc by tampering with his kayak and then updated her social media status </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 10:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OP in OkCupid states it's "woefully ignorant" to only date college graduates--not everyone is on board </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 22:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
