<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2159</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 17:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure what internet ads have to do with games but I'll play ball. Non invasive ads are perfectly fine and yes, they have to make money somehow. 

That said, don't drink and reddit. Just some advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 17:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you guys think it was simply coincidence that this game is releasing at the time as Overwatch? Even if the game is really good (and from what I've seen, it is good), competing with a Blizzard release of a similar genre seems like a shit business strategy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 17:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the swooning of all the women in the area from Geralt's presence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 17:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like some people sub consciously choose not to enjoy things. I understand people have different tastes and all, but really? How can you think TW3 is boring? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 17:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Downvote and move on for this stuff, tbh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 17:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you talking about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 17:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean you can take them on a case by case basis. A lot of ftp games have excellent micro transactions and of course they have to make money somehow. Micro Transactions are not "evil " by default but they can definitely be done wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 15:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Girls existing is definitely sexist then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 14:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People call women existing sexist at this point. I don't think I know what sexism is even supposed to mean anymore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 14:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't recommend SOMA enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 14:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome FTP games are a big part of PC gaming. Not sure what you find not good about them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 13:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good call. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 13:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My immersion just went up at least 8 points tbh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 13:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you gotten to play the new Zao torps shima yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 13:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember getting downvoted for saying all this stuff whe n radar was a new thing and everyone was crying about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 13:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Complete bullshit m8. Try maybe 4+. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 03:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Andrew Lewis - Voco Loco](https://soundcloud.com/alexanderjlewis/voco-loco-krne-x-lewis-x-brasstracks-1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 00:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Card seems a tad OP imho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 21:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Warspite isn't the best for brawling since the turrets are much slower, there are less guns, and it can actually be citadeled unlike the NM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 20:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New Mexico is probably the most indestructible ship for her tier in the game. Only ship you really can just charge right at them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 19:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wasn't speculating though, he made a statement sounding factual. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 19:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like something you should do for every game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 19:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean I was just curious what the reload rate was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 17:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the reload rate by default?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 16:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carry weight is crazy low. I played it a couple weeks ago and I would drink water before going out and be thirsty by the time I got anywhere for a hefty debug to stamina. But really though, the saving is just far too limiting. I had to use a sleeping bag MOD just to make it remotely playable. Especially since the firefights in survival mode still have an exuberant amount of enemies who all basically one or two shot you. Frustrating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 16:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have they balanced Survival Mode more since the beta? It had a lot of interesting ideas but I found it to be overall a frustrating and imbalanced mode as it was in the beta. The game was clearly not designed around such features.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 21:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't really a serious question, more a good ole chivalry meme. :D Can't wait for the kickstarter though. I hope they get the appropriate advertising they need because the game looks awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 20:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can take hits, just not early in the windup. Poise increases hyper armor in DS3. The playstyle is not invalidated as is clear by the ability to use the weapons.

And did you just criticize me for being good about a game that the entire premise is to git gud? You funny man.

it is not about the player being good

Funny shit

Edit - all these down votes yet no replies telling me how I'm wrong. Salty dogs ITT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 20:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mordhau when </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 19:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went through the whole game with the Guts style Ultra Greatsword. One of the slowest weapons in the game. Couldn't use it in PVP very easily but that's just because it's so easy to dodge but in PVE it wrecked face. Only time the lack of poise bothered me was when I let enemies surround me which is my fault. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 19:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But just running around hit trading everything is not very interactive. Poise and hyper armor are fine imho. At least for pve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 17:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope this is the case. Aldrich is this hugely feared lord who DEVOURES GODS and his fight was like eh, whatevs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 03:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted to see him turn off the torch after it had all melted. Can never end too late. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 23:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's called [projection](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Psychological_projection). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 23:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just planning on wearing the Dancer's armor set and if anyone questioned me I would just whoop out the Estoc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 22:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure she only does appearance and not gender. Would love to be wrong about that though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 21:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you change gender in DS3? I thought you couldn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 13:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played some of the survival mode and it was clear that the game was not balanced around it. Consistently frustrating and needs a complete game rework. Chances are, Bethesda won't put in this kind of effort, but that's okay because mods will do the work for them and there will be a survival mode overhaul in a few months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 18:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything about this frame is irregularly shaped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 17:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't played any of it, but I've seen a lot of gameplay and it looks fun. Too bad for them they have to compete with a Blizzard release of a similar genre. I have doubts that'll go well for them, even if it is a good game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 21:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's worth pointing out that the EU has almost triple the playerbase that NA has. Which explains why these bundle deals are more targeted towards new players. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 21:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gonna have to disagree with you there, but I guess it is more a difference in playstyle. When I play these open world RPGs, I am all about that immersion. I'm the kinda guy who won't even sprint anywhere because I'm like "why would my character be sprinting right now?" So I'll just slow walk and take it all in. So, for me, the openness of Skellige was nothing but pure blissful immersion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 21:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree that TW3 was pretty easy and it's basically my main gripe with the game (which also ties into the lack of depth in the combat). But, TW2 was not any harder imo. The only reason TW2 was more difficult was because it was all around clunkier and you were fighting with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 20:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair points. Not sure what you got against Skellige though. That place was my favorite part of the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 20:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet a lot of people would stop playing this game when it's constantly flooded with scrubs playing their T8 ships they bought after having the game a week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 20:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, I find the frequent rerelease of "rare" ships to be rather scummy and I'm glad NA is making people's mouths froth at the idea of owning one (as I'm sure is also part of their plan). Wargaming NA is a business and if they thought selling the Warspite every other weekend was a good business strategy they would do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 19:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious, what made Witcher 2 good that you didn't like in 3?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 19:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A+ conversation contribution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 19:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've already gotten what you've purchased with your money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 18:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? I don't understand your mentality at all. They've always advertised those ships as "rare" ships. If they want to put them on sale again that's up to them but I fail to comprehend why you feel "unappreciated" by them not going on sale. Tirpitz will probably drop again when the German BBs come out, like the Kutuzov did with the Russian CLs.

Wargaming doesn't owe you shit and for you guys to bitch and moan about this stuff when they've been constantly releasing quality content, balance, and bug fixes for their free game is kinda childish and insulting, imho.

Edit - I think Reddit should have a new karma system called butthurt points. Whenever you downvote something and don't leave a reply, you get a butthurt point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 17:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a shitter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 17:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All this mass hyperbole doesn't help anyone. You people blow the bundles out of proportion. The only one that was really wack was the Tirpitz, everything else has been very reasonable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 13:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I don't think it's too unreasonable for a company to play around like this for social media. If it was real I'd be all about them BIC pens tbh.

Edit - a word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 02:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah well I guess you just can see everything behind your really expensive cameras or is that just a prop and really you're checking out a kaleidoscope of 90s boy bands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 01:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but Atlanta doesn't count because US ships are only half as good as IJN so 16 / 2 = 8. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 01:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's try this to be sure. Let's get everyone to sell T10 that way nobody will ever get put into T10 matches. I'm pretty sure about it though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 01:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amagi has 10 guns, Yamato only has 9. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 01:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially while playing BBs, I often ignore enemies that I put to low HP if I think a teammate will be able to finish them off. My damage potential is better put elsewhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 00:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would just sell all your T10 ships. MM only gives you T10 games if you have T10 in your port. It does this to encourage you to play them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 20:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every video! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 15:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The detection on the Chap is much better which helps the playstyle a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 14:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You like the Chappy but dislike the Schors because of the maneuverability? The Chappy has considerably worse rudder shift and turning radius. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 20:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's delusional.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 20:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see a couple deleted comments is what I see.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 20:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His ego was my favourite part!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 20:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shoot that was my favorite part! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 19:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the guy who admitted to cheating so that's why it didn't work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 19:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lost an Amagi game I had 8 kills in. 

http://i.imgur.com/I7w8oAP.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 19:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know you probably don't care and probably won't believe me, but as a fellow human I feel obligated to let you know that you're a fucking moron.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 19:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am personally of the opinion that respect is earned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 19:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's sad that you can't participate in constructive discussion because of what I assume is a deep rooted narcissism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 18:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's un-American about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 17:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man I remember when these things first released and how my friend stayed up all night to get it with his dad. I got to play it at his house that day and I didn't have to stay up all night. :D 

Good times and good memories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 16:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sequel improvement number 1 would be 60fps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 16:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Modifying the game affects the multiplayer balance. Simple as that. The game doesn't recognize the extent of your modifications and the use of such mods online, so the game simply doesn't allow it at all. If you expect otherwise you are sorely disconnected with reality and I question whether you've ever actually played a PC game before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 15:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're allowed to modify but not if you want to play online. Should you be allowed to aimbot in a shooter because modifying the game is a staple of PC gaming? You're a fucking moron. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 15:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clan battles when.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 15:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The faster it's going the less time you have to react. The worse detection on IJN torps is often offset by the added speed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 14:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The DPM will change when because the torp reloads are changing, as well as having Zao torps. The speed of the torps matter a lot on how good their detection is too, but that's still the least important factor. IJN torps do more damage and travel faster. That's what's important.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 13:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> USN clearly do not have the best torps. Not only do IJN get significantly more options in torps, the IJN torps are doing more damage and are way faster on average.

Edit - holy shit people actually think USN are better torp boats than IJN? Holy fucking shit guys come on this is embarrassing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 12:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can tell it's a meta by the way that it is. Pretty neat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 23:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> alls I'm sayin is if I saw that on overwatch I'd be like yeahhhhhhhhhhhh nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 21:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've told him this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 20:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah wasn't him. But it was probably this post that inspired it. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 20:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where so, I need to know if this is him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 20:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You beautiful bastard. Is this you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 19:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does that include the post coitus cuddle? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 19:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I charge $50 an hour for my hard carrying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 19:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it wasn't T7 I'd probably play it, but I'm gonna need more rewards than that if you're gonna get me to put myself through all that frustration.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 19:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I know, but Harry didn't know that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 19:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way I use this behemoth, it wasn't a typo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which one of you did it!? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 18:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I got my friend playing Dark Souls 3. Let's call him Dirty Harry. It is Harry's first ever Souls game and he went in dry and lonely. Let me preface this by saying he knows nothing about the games, especially about any deeper mechanics such as the one he had the (un)fortunate pleasure of slapping him in the face. 

So Harry made it to the High Wall of Lothric. Nice job Harry, it only took you about 4 hours. Upon his exploration Harry struggles against fire breathing monsters and multiple pathways, he really just needs some friendly guidance in his dark journey because it's all too much for Dirty Harry. And then, an angel in a knight's clothing and a purple name. A friend!? Harry's new helper helps clear out those tough mobs and reveals hidden secrets and items. Just when Harry thought there was nothing but frustrations and violence this angel has showed companionship and guidance in this dark world. 

And that's when these two travelers happen upon a chest. A chest all by itself. The angel points towards it and Harry doesn't think twice. Only when the mimic's jaws fastened down on Dirty Harry did he fully start to understand the world he is a part of. Maybe one day he can look back at this and appreciate just how special a moment he experienced, but until then, I hope whoever did this to him recorded it. 

"Dude this fucking NPC set me up" - Dirty Harry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 16:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My GS (Guts style ultra greatsword) has like 640+ attack right now, but that's a str/sex weapon. My str is 45 and dex 40. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 15:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the one hand, I regret buying a PS4 a few months back just to play misc exclusives. On the other hand, I bought it knowing what it's capabilities were at the time so I can't really complain about Sony wanting to upgrade the system after I've got the crap version. On the third hand fuck exclusives this shit is dumb just give me everything in pc please for fucks sake you're acting like your console is a pc now anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 23:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I guess Johnny Depp never saw this ad" comment from 11 months ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 05:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he enjoyed it actually.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My first impression of the Chapayev </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 16:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm typing this on my phone (slow work day) so please excuse any typos or poor formatting. 

So this ship is a bit of a mixed bag. I have over 100 games played in the Mikhail Kutuzov and even though the ships may seem similar, they require a pretty different playstyle in a lot of ways. For starters, the maneuverability on the Chapayev is abysmal (7.7 second rudder shift: 890m radius) and it's one of the main things keeping the ship from being a powerhouse. This radically changes how well the ship can perform fighting vs BBs and dodging torps as the turning radius exceeds most BBs. The Chapayev is unforgiving in this regard, especially when compared to the very agile Kutuzov. Combined with the large citadel, low HP pool, and paper thin armor, I am much less confident in my ability to tango vs BBs than I was in the Kutuzov with smoke screens. Mistakes are easy to make and get punished very hard. Instagib style.

However, things aren't all bad. I run concealment expert on the Chapayev (which is a must have for every cruiser, imo) and this drops the detection down to 10.2km which is a big help. Huge, even. Not only does this give you a nice safety net to disappear when things start getting froggy and/or you need to reposition, this ship gets the most useful stealth firing capability of all the T8 cruisers so far. Being able to shoot from 14.2km without being seen is actually starting to get close enough to ideal. For most other cruisers, the range is either too far or too narrow a margin to be reliable. While 14.2km is still not close enough for your firepower to be entirely efficient, the option is there for your use. That said stealth firing itself is not a mechanic you can rely on as more often than not there's going to be something to spot you like planes or a DD. Having 10.2km concealment also synergies well with another strength of the ship: radar.

The new Radar ability is DEVASTATING to enemy DDs when you give it a little bit of teamwork. By yourself, you probably can't kill the DD in the short 20 seconds it is active as you will realistically get only 2 salvos before it ends. I play in divisions very frequently however, and if we get another cruiser or DD (or both) ready for the ability to activate, that DD is good as dead more times than not. And even if the DD manages to survive, they will have escaped very banged up and with your whole team knowing their last known location. Most importantly the CV. I know that most DDs aren't actively playing around this ability yet, so I'm not going to jump on the "it's completely broken" bandwagon yet, but the ability is as strong as it is situational. It can easily be wasted and the cooldown is very long. The ability extends past your detection range, so if you're detected by something, you know you can use radar to find them.

AA is super strong. Not the strongest, but still good enough to rekt.

At the risk of being too long winded, I'll leave it at that. My overall impression is that this ship is incredibly strong with proper teamwork, but its poor maneuverability keeps the ship from being independently difficult to deal with. Mistakes get punished without mercy. For this reason, I imagine it'll be a difficult ship for a lot of people to play without divs in randoms.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two for one special! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 19:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do I not get a Devastating Strike? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 04:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cruisers vs. The World (Atago match - 175k damage) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 15:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I guess I'll call it a night. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 06:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cruisers Counter Destroyers!? (Atago Commentary) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 20:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My first commentary! Playing Support. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 20:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Be careful of your ship's roll. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 20:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ideally, should your amp match your headphones sound signature? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 15:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been researching a lot of amps lately for my HE-400i, and I haven't been able to find any kind of answer to this question. What I mean is that if your headphones' sound is slightly warm, should your amp also be slightly warm? Would a slightly bright amp make the headphones more neutral, or just work against the headphone's strengths?

Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazing Screenshots from my most recent playthrough at 2560x1440. HUGE SPOILERS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 21:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Owners of the Tirpitz, what are your thoughts on it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 15:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the game's release a few days out and therefore the release of the Tirpitz, I would like to know if the ship can actually hold its own against other ships of its tier. Owners of the Tirpitz, do you think the ship is worth it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MM thought this was okay. Just might be the worst MM I've been in. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 02:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aim small, miss small. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 06:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How good has Wargaming been in the past about game balancing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 20:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all! I've just recently gotten into the game of boats and I'm loving it way more than I thought I would. I was hooked after just one match and my friends and I are eagerly awaiting clan battles. But one thing concerns me, balance. I've been in the situation before where the developers just seem to not understand how their game is played so they make the wrong changes or simply never change anything. And having played this game of boats a little bit now and seeing the recent discussion on this subreddit, there are definitely areas that deserve some assessment. 

*See title of post*

Since I didn't play WoT, I figured I'd ask (this is my first Wargaming game). As far as I'm aware, that game sill has a thriving competitive scene, yeah? That's gotta be a good sign. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Showcase of Gecco's 1/6th Guts figure! I can't wait! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 16:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> how2spear </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> *Count Reuven's Treasure Spoilers* The Butcher of Novigrad (Combat footage) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 19:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My 1/6th Scale Raiden Figure arrived! (Made by Gecco) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 23:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just received in the mail! New 1/6th scale Big Boss figure by Gecco. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 00:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2v1 courtesy of mercs mod </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 20:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
