<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1423</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 10:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah... Sure...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 06:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree that it's possible. A good example of misleading events is Jojen's greendreams which come true in unexpected ways.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 06:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like blackfish and his personal sigil </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 06:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "you know nothing, Jon Snow" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me, obviously...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's actually one of the better spin-off ideas I've heard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tyrion lannister, obviously </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 12:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TheMountain or TheHound or even KingInTheNorth,  my personal suggestions at least.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 07:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's some top quality twirling I must say... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The likeness is uncanny, well done. He's also my favourite character, he just can't help being so awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The chimer were those that left the Altmer to follow Veloth. Seeing as they travelled all over it is most likely that it would affect their physical appearance. In saying so I believe the chimer had darker skin then the Altmer. Apart from this I think they're quite similar, if not identical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks pretty good, well done </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After the death of their first child Cersei rarely had sex with Robert, if ever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Divath Fyr (Morrowind) vs Neloth (dragonborn DLC) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 17:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An even playing field, they can bring whatever equipment they wish (in the field of reason), however staffs aren't permitted. An open field battle, strictly magic (however, the type is their choice).

Make it fair, so if one gets an item give a reasonable substitute to the other as well. That's really the only rule for equipment, so go nuts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kronos (Greek mythology) vs Vivec (Elder Scrolls) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 12:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Empty field, one on one, they can use anything they wish (armour, weapons magic).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 12:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What style did you use? It's quite pixie looking, not bad though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 05:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Tyrion died, I'd probably still watch it but I'd have to grimace at every episode without him. He really livens the show up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 03:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 03:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BURN THEM! BURN THEM ALL!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how it says family, duty, honour. Well done </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds awesome, I would personally love to, unfortunately I don't have the time. But I've played several story's with a group of friends (usually not all that serious, to the DMs sadness), if you won't any help with anything I have a decent amount of experience, just PM me anything you need help with. Great idea though, GoT D D would be awesome, hope it works out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doubtless they did...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 11:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, obviously, I thought it went without saying...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 11:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tyrion, by far my favourite, he's funny, and quite witty. He's also a pretty good guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 10:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well... He's insanely bad at politics  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 09:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This got real dark real quick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree to a truce, I really can't be bothered either </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *wink wink* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your entire argument is an error, every word you type is an error. In answer to the second 'example', maybe you should learn english, this is quite easy to decipher.


"Hey ya big dummy dumb dumb" - are you 4 years old or just really bad at using words? 

"How many errors I'm making?" - Um, what? 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you feeling alright, I stated that it was the next comment. Maybe you should be giving it a break, seeing how many errors you're making </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You did, in the next comment, you really have to keep track or people might even accuse you of stupidity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read it the way it was written </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ALL HAIL THE NIGHT KING!! (until of cause Dany and her dragons destroy them...)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you should read what you wrote, I have no idea how that couldn't be seen as condescending, ignorant of a thing to say, just saying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing this is true, what the hell is your problem with a simple question, I think, in this case that I'm not the one that's stupid here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's usually due to poor optimisation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, no need to be a dick about it, it's not my fault you bought a Nintendo Switch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That guy should be *kart*ed away...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that a switch I spot?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, of course. Damned memory of mine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why though? He was given oathkeeper, it's 'brother'. Just seems odd that he would use it in stead of oathkeeper  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "in [his] own bed, with a belly full of wine and a maiden's mouth around [his] cock, at the age of eighty," </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 00:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out. Out now!...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 00:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 00:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, after he burned Shireen, I was happy he *died*, he did show remorse especially after his wife **killed** herself. But that really took away all my sympathy for him  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 00:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes... The man who went to the queen and divulged that he knew she was screwing Jaime and her kids were born of incest... Dude was as sane as they get...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, maybe you should get to the cloud district more often... I hear it helps you be a better self-justified ass, just rumours though...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EVERYTHING] What's your favourite house, group? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can be any house of Westeros/Free cities, or none if that's your thing. If you're more of a religious fanatic that's fine, I won't judge (to you're face...). Anything goes really, house, organisation, religious group. Who do you most connect with. And no, DRAGON! is not a house... All said and done I would choose house Targaryen, mostly cause I love dragons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Ah. What am I saying. Of course you don't" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What house do you support, and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting, I like the implications, but it just seems lacking for some reason. Would be cool for sure though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Explains why most people are dicks to you even if you save Nirn  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was kind of what I was going for with it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EVERYTHING] is lightbringer Valyrian steel? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It occurred to me that it's quite possible. Azor Ahai took a lot of time to forge the final iteration of the legendary sword, plunging it into his wife's heart. Both Valyrian steel and lightbringer were forged with magic and blood, is this a coincidence or because they are both the same? What I'm wondering is, is lightbringer Valyrian steel? Is this confirmed?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is light bringer made of valyrian steel? I always wondered, I read some stuff and it seems possible, just like lightbringer valyrian swords require blood and magic to be forged, is this confirmed?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 12:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I know, but for the first two seasons he's only just coming into his story, it's mostly just him despairing about his legs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 07:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Painting?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 07:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :'( I will buddy, I will...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 07:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's when you gotta play games like the witcher, has an abundance of both. But seriously I had this exact same situation when I my sister played the witcher 3. Fair enough though, first like 10mins and there was already a naked women so...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can just imagine one of the worker's day. 

Bank goer: "**why won't you fit**"

Worker:"how can I help you? "

Bank goer:"the bloody coin machine's broken"

Worker: "what coin machine? "

Bank goer: "you know, the one full of paper"

Worker: "um, sir, that's a printer"

Bank goer: *mumbles something* 

walks away </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait! Ice in a hot chocolate! Hmm... Never seen that one before </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, by taking away everyone's money you make everyone richer... Wait. That doesn't sound right...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've bean there...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sad, would've been a great title </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A book is always better when you take it slow, ponder the words and really get enthralled by the story. I like to take it slow when reading so I can just soak in everything before I get overwhelmed. I mean, what's the point in reading 52 books in a year if you didn't fully become immersed in them, one well read book is worth a dozen hurriedly read books in my opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you made chicken tonight?...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gorgeous, just gorgeous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asking him to prove it by doing several things, such as teleport to a beach, change the weather and then something else. Once I have proof I see what's going on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, pretty funny, needs a bit of formatting for ease of read though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, gold...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So basically a windlance from LotR, seems plausible I guess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> House Targaryen is a shadow of it's former self, it was once great but must now rebuild from the bottom of the wheel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I saw, he said sometimes, and, sometimes look at them in the bigger picture. But to get the truth we must loom at them both ways first </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What has this got to do with anything? Also, when you consider a place like Tamriel, only a fool takes titles literally. Again, how is the simple answer a civil war, that doesn't make much sense now does it? Why would the tower be tied to some civil war, and how could the tower be an entire country? Doesn't make sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In elder scrolls nothing is *just* something, believe me on that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm... Bigger again, how about Wun Wun plus the mountain and the hound fought all three dragons...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who would win, The mountain or Wun Wun? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whatever weapons and armour they choose. Takes place at noon in an open (and empty) field. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wun Wun and the mountain, now *that* would be interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah I see then... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't the *king* refer to Alduin, who was sundered atop the throat. Alduin, was the king of dragons (in a way), the Nords challenged his reign there. They both destroyed him, and sundered time (as we know weird time stuff is going on their). Bleeding, most likely refers to the broken time there, kind of like it's seeping out, seeing as it's called the time *wound* this somewhat substantiates this notion. All in all, I think it quite clearly represents the throat of the world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hear me Roar!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has his flaws, but don't we all? He's much preferable than his brother, and he shows far more compassion. And his adventure with Arya gives a new meaning to his character, a softer gentler side.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks awesome, I like the scale of it too, like 10 time bigger then the iron throne :') but seriously, looks great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that a mac...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's funny, many people spend their whole lives striving for one thing. But when they get it, they don't know what to do with it. I know that he's a pretty cunning guy, but I don't think ***he*** knows what he's gonna do with all that juicy power.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're really starting to push my buttons!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes a lot of sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can only assume you'd be keeping him in your garage right?...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK Tyrion...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same, it's my compulsive need to finish all chapters and not miss anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 11:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's just hope they haven't been LED astray. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EVERYTHING] if you could have any creature/animal what would it be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 11:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything that is shown, or at least mentioned (either books or show) is acceptable, whether extinct or not is irrelevant. Nothing of human qualities (no no giants). Other then this go wild. I'd also like to know if you have any colour preferences of their skin/fur/scales. 


Personally I would probably choose a white and gold dragon (primarily white with golden highlights)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 11:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jew...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 11:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really marble at your puns. Can I call you Mason, because you've shaped my life...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you call a thief that isn't black? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 11:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 11:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, life is tuff but we have to be hard as stone if we wanna make it through.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 10:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They say when you've hit rock bottom that there's only one way to go, up. You just gotta rock it and be, because win the end, Wad can you do about it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 10:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose that's understandable, I personally found that Bran's early story was boring, in fact I never really found it interesting. But that's because of different people having different tastes, not everything can cater to just one person's wants. It's got to have a nice balance, and if you don't find it interesting, just skip it, you'll probably regret later on but meh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 10:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's wrong with Dany? It allows us to contrast different people and their experiences and views on things. And to be fair, they all have their own huge stories (apart from Ned). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 10:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a chip off the old granite block aren't ya?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 09:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry, the later episodes there won't be anywhere near as many people to have to remember...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favourite is roasted...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really rocked my world...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "not today" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You gotta control yourself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sharing is caring.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am.... Appeased... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Littlefinger's motives - power, power, power with a side order of power dipped in a nice power sauce  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
