<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3288</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 19:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My problem with the paradox games is the lack of combat. Looking at a map is no fun. However, if they can get eugen systems to do the combat, and make the map global, ........ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 19:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ruse was by no means as realistic as the wargames are, and wayy more forgivving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 19:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aoa failed because it wasnt wargame and because it didn`t get enough promo. (And because it`s expensive). Besides, I think most of the eugen fans are history fans, so a fictional fantasy setting had less apeal to many fans. Myself included. WW2 is popular with everybody, and if they make it a wargame game / :) / they will most likely reach a wide audience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 17:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonder how they will implement Weapons like the V- series of rockets,  and some of the advanced weaponry that the germans made "wunderwaffen". Most of those were never completed, but weapons like the goliath tracked mine could be used by infatry, and the precision guided rocket Frits x. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 17:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guess who's back, back again
(Shady) Hitler's back, tell a friend
Guess who's back,
guess who's back,
guess who's back,
guess who's back
guess who's back
Guess who's back...
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YVkUvmDQ3HY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 17:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eugen systems have already said that strategic bombers and paratroopers will not be implemented in their games, because paratroopers and bombers were used BEFORE a bettle begun, most to secure or disaple strategic locations. Using the in the midst of battle would be suicide. That said, the less advanced weaondry of ww2 could mean that we might yet seem them in a game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 15:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good range though. Kil knock out a T-34 at 1600 m range, while the t-34 had to be closer than 700m to damage the tiger. So even a tracked ticker will pose a serious threat, if if it only reaches the front lines before the engine bursts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 15:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was by no means any lack of technologies in ww2, and a ww2 game would not be simpkified at all. I think (if they really ARE making a ww2 game) they might be on to a winning formlua. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it seems I can`t argue agains that opinion... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 13:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What u talking bout? I know that the germans are not some kind of super army winning everything. Has it come to this then, everybody who plays as the germans are "wherboo" (Whatever that is) ??
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 12:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YEEEES! Tiger, Me-262, Newbelwerfers..... beautiful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 12:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ww2 game comming? YEEEES. Been dreaming of that for ages. Can`t wat to go all blitzkrieg on people, use  newbelwerfers, and few tigers and my beloved me-262!
Bring it on, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 12:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What, Wargame announced a ww2 game?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 11:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, leave rome out of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 11:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can`t wait, Egypt setting has me pumped! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 10:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doubt it. They can`t sell all sorts f crazy stuff the way the do in gta 5. Maybe a unque horse, a hat or something, but nothing like gta. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 10:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Last good game"? More like the only good game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 12:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or, eberybody starts alive and weel and go on about their buisness, but instead of respawning as humans they spawn as zombies? EH!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 17:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it seems we will be getting zombies soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 15:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At first I thought "No, cod does it". Then I heard the noices and thougth "YES!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zombie mode incoming? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 15:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 15:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dunno. The honor system kinda worked for John, seing as he was a repentive criminal trying to live a better life, so he could be either good or bad. If however our protagonist in rdr2 is a marshal or some kind of good guy they might use another system. Still, good or bad choices can be made by anyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 19:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because games have been delayed before doens`t mean Rdr 2 will be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 17:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, they are legends. The music fits the game like a hand in a glove. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 11:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don`t know where all the "it`s getting delayed" posts are coming from. There is no reasen at all to assume it will be delayed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dead end alley - the western feeling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 14:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 16:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make it open from the start or don`t make it at all. I expect to be able to roam around form the get go. No blocks. No nothing stopping me from exploring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 16:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None of these plots seems very likely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good chance that we will see a deeper economy in rdr 2. We`ll just have to wait and see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta beware us sneaky Scandinavians when we go all crazy and live in the forest! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 16:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there are some newer ones as well, from 2014 I think. Shows native americans and other stuff. Could be from rdr2.
http://www.gamezone.com/news/rumor-red-dead-3-concept-art-leaked-3440323 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 16:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the failed robbery where John was shot involved a steamboat or boat of some kind. I think the "God" figure mentions it. And besides, the fact that there are so mant buffalo/bison alive in the trailer suggest an earlier setting than 1906, and the fact that all the towns and stagecoaches are freshly painted and nowhere nearly as old and "used" as what we see in rdr. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 15:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly, nothing new. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give how fantastic the music form the teaser was I feel confident that the soundtrack in Rdr2 will be epic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 21:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not my video, I just subscribe. I also think a lot of the info sounds like BS but he has many good points as well. Worth a watch imo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rdr possibly close to finish (?) and focus on native americans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 12:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe we`ll see Salladhor Saan have sexy time with the queen?? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sam has it in oldtown.
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Rchj4oOG4KE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> White walkers would be gone in a week (napal, incendiary rounds, nukes). Without knowing the reason for the invasion I don`t know how they would interract with the seven kingdoms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
