<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3065</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 03:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is another question.  Say you are teleported to that Galaxy, would you be able to see things that are 13.2 billion light years beyond that point in space? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 01:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe get a small child feeding one?  Try to capture the child's reactions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 18:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ad is definately a joke but the frustration appears genuine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 01:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe have someone there for YOUR protection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 01:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The link is not working...there is no climate change here... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 00:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice pic!  Looks like he's shaving a piece of aluminum down because of how much material and how deep the tool is.  I see he is not wearing OSHA approved safety glasses, no side shield.  Also wearing a long sleeve shirt is usually not a good idea when working around rotating machinery but I'm willing to bet he's been doing this for a while.  It would be cool to maybe have some of the machinists tools layed out on a workbench for a little foreground interest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 01:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm all for eliminating drug use, now we need to ship him some ammo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 01:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice sunset colors!  I like the old barn but the part of the house on the left is distracting and not adding anything to the pic.  The foreground has nothing of interest and is under exposed and that will will always happen with such a high contrast scene unless you either use a graduated filter on the bright part of the scene or use HDR. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 01:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definately like the first pic better, the bush on the left is too much.  Have fun with your new lens! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 00:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man I would love to be there!  The lake is perfectly smooth and the mountain top has some snow.  The low cloud is cool, you can see the rocks under water and the reflection of the mountain is just right.  I honestly don't know how I would be able to make this shot "better".  Awesome job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 23:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been getting back into film photography and have visited my local labs that still develop film here in Fort Worth.  At first I googled 1 hour photo places...needless to say I didn't find any, it's been a long time.  Anyway, after visiting these places and seeing what they have to offer I have been going through my old slides and negatives to see if any are worth being scanned and adjusted in Photoshop.  I have found several where the exposure wasn't just right or the color balance was weird and I might be able turn them into something worth printing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 23:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should check out r/photocritique!  You can post single pics and ask for advise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 17:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to live in Fairbanks Alaska and the light there was awesome.  I was only able to get a few good shots of the way the light looked during the 4 years I was there, it is very hard to get it right.  I like your shot of the guy training for cross country skiing!  You can tell he is going all out because of the steam coming off from him, it's great!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 17:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the tips! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 16:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for thinking about my photo!  If it helps this is a ring gear from a locomotive axle.  Do you think it would be better for me to explain the pic when posting? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 16:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was experimenting with composition and isolating an industrial type of subject to make an interesting photo.  I was actually bored at work last night and thought it might look cool.  I have no plans to print it, although it might look good in someone's mancave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 16:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea that's a hard scene to capture because of the high contrast between the sky with the mist and the relatively dark foreground with the hill and tree detail.  Unless you do an HDR shot or if using film some Kodak Ektar 100 might get good results.  Also next time maybe try to get more of the sky in the shot and less of the foreground, that will help emphasize the sunrise.  I really like the pine trees on the left, maybe try getting more of them.  Good luck and thanks for posting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 06:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps you should have exposed for the trees and bushes, I bet there was some nice foreground interest in the bottom half of the image but I can't tell because it's all black. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 06:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An awesome sunset would be sweet.  Or maybe a bad looking storm with a lightning bolt.  You could use a flash to light the house so it's not blacked out by the background.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gear </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 05:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 05:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true, there are a lot of people who have been doing this a lot longer than myself.  Also there are some pros that get paid to go around and get awesome shots.  Like this guy:  http://www.marcadamus.com  I want his job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 04:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it's a little disheartening to look at all of those awesome landscape photos because none of mine come close. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 02:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You will find what you are looking for at www.photo.net </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 02:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know of any one stop source of info for what you are looking for.  The period you are talking about is the point in history where warfare changed from guys marching around in actual formations and each side standing in a field firing at each other with muskets all the way to the first nuclear bomb being dropped.  There is a lot going on in that time frame with evolving technology, such as the invention of the machine gun, which forced a change in tactics.  It may be easier to concentrate on separate wars and the tactics used and what weapons were in use during those wars.  Wikipedia has a bunch of info to get you started.  Look at "infantry tactics", looks like it starts at the beginning.    https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Military_strategy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 04:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to bomb the downhill sections and I always stay clipped in.  The only time I unclip is usually going slow around a sharp corner...I don't like bashing my knees into rocks if I fall over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 04:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was a woman in the shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 04:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only thing I can think of to make this scene better would be either rain or snow just to emphasize how much these guys are out there getting stuff done.  I like it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 04:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use time z pedals...its a clip in pedal with a platform for when things get sketchy and I might have to bail which isn't very often.  So I say both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 02:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going back to film vs blowing a ton of money on a new DSLR.  Just got a Minolta SRT 101 from ebay a couple weeks ago, it was made in the 60's and still works.  I did have a Canon G11 until it broke, maybe lasted 3 or 4 years.  For now I'm done with fragile plastic cameras. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 02:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice fall colors!  Not sure what he is taking a pic of though with that long lens?  Is there one without the guy in it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 02:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you go through Glacier NP you can also hit up Banff NP in Canada and check out the West Edmonton Mall if you're into that kind of stuff.  If you plan on camping in the Youkon don't forget they have bears there so bring bear mace and practice food safety. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 01:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a book called the milepost, it details every store and gas station along the way along with operating hours.  Also don't rely on your cellphone map, or the ability to make phone calls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 01:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definately Glacier </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 01:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I try to ask myself what if I were there taking the pic and how could I make it "better".  After all this is personal opinion.  So to me this kind of shot needs the right light and this isn't it.  I would have either gotten up early or stayed later to get the sunrise/sunset.  Looks like you were facing the sun on this shot which makes for too much contrast between the sky and the ground and you have to choose which one you want to expose for or use a graduated filter on the sky to even out the contrast between the two.  My 2 cents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 22:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm back at work... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 02:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My opinion is it changes with your age or responsibility level.  If your a kid and don't have much to actually worry about then you can lay around and watch YouTube videos all day and you should be fine.  Kids used to lay around and watch TV all day and for the most part they are fine.  As an adult you will need to support yourself somehow.  After you get that part done then back to the Internet if that's what you like to do with your spare time.  It's a free country after all so do what you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 02:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hard to remember what I did before we had kids.  One thing I do remember is when going someplace like to the store takes way longer now.  Used to just roll out to the car and do it up.  Now gotta round everyone up, make sure they are wearing clothes (first thing my boy does is a shuck off his shoes and pants when he gets home).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 01:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Door knob is always a good one.  If someone farts without calling safety before they fart the other person is entitled to punch the shit out of him until he can touch a door knob.  Drinking more is always a good choice.  Used to drive around drunk but that is always a bad idea.  Go to the club and mess with hoes is always fun.  Make a potato gun before hand and once you get drunk see what you can find to shoot out of it.  A machete throwing contest is fun.  Grill some steaks and play corn hole.  Fishing.  Black out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 01:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm at work so I want to go home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 01:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dickbutt three way circle jerk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 01:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh, if the Internet is not working I go do something else.  If my car isn't working I go fix it cause I need to go places. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 06:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea there are people that have bumper stickers that say "secede".  Pretty sure they are the Texas militia card holders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 06:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm staying in Texas, all ya'll traitors can run off to fantasy island if you want to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 05:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw something the other day that said we have a 1 to 1 ratio of cells and bacteria in our body. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 02:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jack Bauer is a bad ass!  He killed 267 people in the first 24 hours! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 01:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell yea!  I rode my (imaginary) dirt bike to school every day on the school bus and jumped everything and shredded every yard along the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 01:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend killed himself.  I was hanging out with him the day before and he seemed fine and the next day they found him dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 01:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least they didn't go to work and start shooting people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 01:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Star Wars...all of them.  Even when the first one came out on HBO when I was a kid didn't interest me.  I haven't even watched the last few because it doesn't make sense from a fantasy perspective to have things that happened in the past be better (as far as cinematography and effects go) than things that happened later.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 05:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EVERYBODY FORGETS THE FIRING PIN CAN BE TRACED AS WELL!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 04:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's for kids with limited internet time, this way they can go straight to the good stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 02:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rock root thing in the bottom left corner is distracting and the whole left side above it adds nothing.  I zoomed in a little to get the rock and left side out and also some blank sky at the top and it looked way better to me.  https://i.imgur.com/H2N2xNd.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Machine from the past </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 01:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Machine of the past </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 01:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 00:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought they suspended her bow hunting liscense lol! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 00:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be a porno. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 06:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried to get the most ridiculous pic of myself, my kids liked it :)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 05:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watching ridiculousness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 05:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Auschwitz.  It was a Nazi extermination camp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 05:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unplanned road trip, just wing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 05:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posses the dad strength, anything is possible! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 05:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A-ha!  The motive behind the question has been revealed!  Looks like we have a Nazi grammar hater. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 05:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't call them faggots anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 05:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pong, I'm old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 05:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like you took the pic in the setting sunlight and that's always nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 05:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was called the three story beer bong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 05:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://imgur.com/a/PCE1W </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 05:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm with you.  Ketchup or nothing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 05:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lower back is good also </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 05:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in the military and stationed in Alaska then got orders to go to Louisiana.  They gave us the option of driving and they would pay us for 11 days of traveling and staying at hotels.  We stayed the previous night in Calgary Canada, drove through the park and kept going.  I forget where we stayed that night but it was far from the park. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 04:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> During a baptism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 04:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never been to Yosemite but it looks nice.  My favorite is Denali if I had to pick one.  Me and a friend rode our bikes about 70 miles into the park in one day and camped out at a lake.  It was awesome weather and we could see the mountain the whole day which is rare.  But as far as pure beauty goes I am sticking with Glacier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 04:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the best way to enjoy a bad movie.  (Jk lol) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 04:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some blurred background would be cool.  I can tell that is some type of bmw in the background and it's distracting.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 04:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I joined the military and they told me what I was going to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 04:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was the boss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 04:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glacier national park. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 04:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most country music:  https://www.google.com/amp/digg.com/video/think-country-music-sounds-the-same-youre-absolutely-right%3famp=true?client=safari </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 04:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ear gages.  There are going to be a bunch of people with old wrinkly and flappy ear ear holes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 04:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, if they don't want to come down at all or are a general pain in the ass just walk away and go somewhere else.  Different dealerships have different sales strategies.  Some will try to squeeze out the most from you while others will sell low but move a lot of cars.  Hint: find one of the latter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 04:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found after a while everything looks the same and you leave good friends behind whenever you go.  Also you can never go back and things be the same, some things are better left as memories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 04:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Puffer fish that wasn't prepared right so it would kill me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 04:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey everybody look at Mr Obvious here, he's a real funny guy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 04:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm at work so...keep working </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 04:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't drink that stuff!  Energy drinks are the new smoking...you will see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 04:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TRUMP IS A LOSER AND HE WILL DESTROY THIS COUNTRY IF HE IS ELECTED!!!!  HILLARY IS A LYING MURDEROUS BITCH AND SHE WILL DESTROY THIS COUNTRY IF SHE IS ELECTED!!! (How was that?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 03:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taco Bell...it worked for us and we have been married for 19 years now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 03:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should do the dog shadow puppet on your dog </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 02:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You almost perfectly nailed the thirds composition "rule".  So it looks like you used some kind of graduated filter to make the top half of the sky artificially dark and a polarizer to make the clouds look like they do.  That or it's HDR.  Other than the background the colors look washed out...seems like the ocean should be more blue and the foreground should be brighter since it is sunny out.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 02:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe next time get everyone in the shade because the direct sunlight on some but not others throws off the exposure.  Also try using the biggest aperture opening (smallest number) so the background is more out of focus while keeping the people in the front in focus.  Also it looks there is a random tree island floating in the pool, try not including that next time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 02:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At first when I opened the pic I thought it was an advertisement for 500px!  I agree, great composition but the light is flat.  Hopefully you can go back and get more! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 01:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe try getting closer to the rock, like 20 feet away and don't get the sign in the shot but keep the upper color in the trees in it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 01:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ass in the background is distracting.  Maybe used a little higher shutter speed to keep her hand from blurring.  Exposure is good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 01:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To me it looks like the main subject, the building, is under exposed.  If you relied on your cameras meter settings the (relatively) bright lights tricked it into underexposing everything else.  If your camera has exposure compensation you can adjust for this.  Nice composition though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 01:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like you got the exposure right!  The black background is solid and not washed out looking so that is a plus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 01:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice car!  The weeds in the foreground are a little distracting.  The building in the background looks interesting, maybe include more of that.  Also do you use a polarizer?  If not it would help get rid of the glare on the car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 00:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just described one of the fight scenes on the movie Hero. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 06:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We didn't have electricity from the grid until I was 5.  My dad had rigged up an old engine and an army surplus generator which he used to charge car batteries inside our trailer.  Once they were charged he would hook them up to an inverter to run the TV and lights.  We had one of those old little black and white tv's and when the batteries would start going dead the picture would get smaller and smaller until it went out which meant it was time for bed.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 06:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like you found yourself a nice keen kutter ax!  I'd like to have that one hanging on my wall next to my double bit ax and hatchet.  They all have good handles too, good finds! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 04:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No...and you've had enough to drink tonight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 02:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While your at it look up how many people are on Mars right now...zero.  I'll believe it when I see it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
