<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3788</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 16:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's where an agent come in. You can find stuff regarding what you should look for like low taxes, good school ratings, recent trends, etc. I would suggest doing some driving around before you go and talk with a real estate agent, that way you have a good idea of where and can then focus on the what. If you are pre-approved take that value and just search [Zillow](www.zillow.com) for houses in your range in the area you want; if you see one, contact an agent to go check it out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 16:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well more reason to go to a dealership, maybe the engine will be under warranty. You never know how those dealerships will diagnose it, maybe they find some seal within the engine led to the engine seizing up...you never know. I would say it's worth a look, the engine had 31,000 miles and was within the 12 year time frame.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 04:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, but remember you have two types of conditions so the timeline won't be the same. When your doing MC make sure you can tell whether it is a Condition Precedent or Condition Subsequent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 02:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There isn't really a difference, just a slight connection. 

A condition will trigger a duty owed. Whether you have a condition precedent/ subsequent that event must occur for the contractual duty to arise. If the condition is not fulfilled, the duty does not arise, and therefore the parties are not contractually obligated to follow through with the prospective duty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 02:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife and I pay everything with our CC because of the cash back offer. We just pay everything off monthly. We get extra % back for certain purchases like gas and groceries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 23:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude no offense but think bigger. How often is that helicopter mechanic job going to be open with your city? If I was you I would do something you will enjoy both while in and then is marketable when out. 

Remember they are going to pay for your education/training while you are in. Then they are going to pay for your education while you are out. I would pick something you could piggyback off of when your out in the private sector. 

Not trying to mention politics, but I think engineering is going to be in high demand in the future because of trumps infrastructure goals. Plus you can't go wrong making $50k plus when your out. 

Think big dude, many don't, be different.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 23:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huge, huge, HUGE! If they won't give you one or they give you some bs 1yr it might be a used engine they bought at a junkyard or salvage yard they got super cheap. It's paramount you get a new OEM engine from the manufacturer and they instal it...anything else you might as well go point at a car on the yard and say put that engine in. Get the manufacturer warranty if you can. Possibly go to a dealership as well and price them out. Usually the small work is priced up and the large "heavy" work is priced reasonable...then at least your getting it serviced at a dealership.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 22:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your in a pickle. You could make this interesting, but I strongly suggest speaking with an attorney versed in real property law in your jurisdiction. 

Ok, you are both liable for the loan 100%, even if the other does not pay. That being said, I would approach this individual and offer to assume their portion of the loan. By assuming their portion you are taking over the entire liability and releasing them from further contributions. BUT, in exchange for this assumption they must convey their 50% interest in the property to you by issuing a new deed. You MUST go to the mortgage company and inform them of this because it WILL trigger the acceleration clause in the contract you signed with them. 

What this would do is, in exchange for taking on the burden of the entire loan and risk of foreclosure, give you 100% ownership of the home and after you sell it 100% of the profits. You have to go talk to a real estate attorney, I couldn't suggest that enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 22:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say if you can replace the engine and everything else needs to get that car to point where you have a "new used" car, then do it. There is no point really to take on that much debt for something new if you can repair something 1/3 which would get you in the same position really. Either way your going to end up with a "new car" of sorts. 

I would also try and shop them, go to another spot and say I need this, I was quoted X price, could you do it for less. Biggest thing would be getting a warranty on the work done. You MUST negotiate some type of warranty that spans at least 3 years IMO. Don't be afraid to tell them no, and don't be afraid to negotiate with them on price and warranty. 

Good luck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 22:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit, you need to speak with an attorney for legal advise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 22:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could easily go get it set up by an attorney for the same price; just shop around a bit. Plus, if you begin the business you can write off the legal fees as start up business expenses; so why not talk with a professional?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 20:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha! That's awesome use for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 20:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good, that is glad to hear. I have a co-worker who we just worked through this process actually; she was upside down though. 

In your situation you should have no problem getting the car refinanced. When you refinance something you are basically taking the equity you have in the good and using it to get a more favorable loan term. 

To figure out your equity take the FMV of the vehicle you read on Kelly Blue Book and subtract it from the balance of your loan, that will give you, roughly, the equity you have in your vehicle. I say roughly because car are very difficult to find a solid price on, rather then homes where there are more factors that go into computing the value. 

So, like I said before you can go to a national or regional bank, or you can go to a local credit union as well. I suggest starting out at a local credit union because they will, typically, have more favorable interest rates as opposed to national banks. They may require you to open up a bank account, which isn't a problem ask them what the lowest amount is required to hold an account with them and open one. 

Just be honest with them and tell them you want to apply for the loan in order to remove you off the current loan you have associated with the vehicle. Don't be afraid to "have your dad or brother" take a look at the specifics (insert whatever line you want) and just shop around for a low interest rate. 

What you want to do is get the new loan for the 30-day pay off amount of the current loan on the vehicle. The bank/credit union will usually work with you on making that payment to the current loan holder and it sometimes moves faster because it is a certified payment instead of a personal check. 

Then, you just continue to make payments on the new loan and forget about the old. Over time you should pay less for the vehicle for a few reasons, one you were making extra payments which saved you money on interest and by refinancing you are getting a lower interest rate which will lower the amount of interest accrued each month.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 20:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't looked, there is still a lot of variables in the scenario. If they do their credit in house they will probably use the account receivables as a basis of factoring in the restructuring process. Your fine, you have nothing to worry about. Plus, as soon as they filed for Bankruptcy they had to stop everything associated with their business, excluding formalities and other business expenses. It's called the automatic stay, it's basically a halt on everything so the bankruptcy trustee can discern the timelines of when and what their powers extend too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 19:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, cars suck. They are a few things that go into this. If you are upside down on the car then it may not be the best route. You should research the current value of the vehicle, go to Kelly Blue Book [Kelly Blue Book] and determine the value. If you owe more then what it's worth, your "upside down/under water." 

If she doesn't care and wants to keep the car, that's her business, and you should make the grown up decision to get far away from it. 

When you refinance something you are looking to take the equity you have in the good and use it to get a lower interest rate. The interest rate is really what your looking to get the lowest, that will determine your payment, and how much you pay over the loan period. I don't know the specific rate your at now, but tell her to shop for a lower rate. You can go to banks, credit unions, etc. I would suggest a credit union, they usually have lower rates as opposed to national chain banks.

If they don't give you a solid rate, then you have some thinking to do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 18:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are a national chain that sells clothing,  so I could image they have a large amount of credit accounts with high balances. Usually in a bankruptcy proceeding those outstanding credit accounts are sold at a discount to another company. 

Also, it will depend on what type of bankruptcy proceeding they are seeking. They could go straight liquidation (Ch 7) or re-organization (Ch 11)--it will depend on a lot of factors.  

There are a lot of things at play. I would suggest calling the number on the back and cancel your account. Looks like you can log on to your account at their website, maybe they have a way to close there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 18:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The loan is technically in your name. As a co-signer you are liable for the outstanding balance of the loan if the principal borrower of the loan fails to pay on the loan. If she stops paying, they will look to you for payment. Your sister needs to refi the loan, basically getting a new loan, but without you as a cosigner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 18:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like your mother's identity has been compromised. I would report it to every account you have before they make some larger purchases.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 17:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before: 0%

After: 100% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 17:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough. My wife asks me all the time what to look for, and I just tell her, you know when you see it. After awhile of doing this, it just comes to you really; it's like mental-muscle memory.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 16:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love same day flips! Good job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 16:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I look for vintage "the Simpsons" shirts; found one for $0.25 and sold it for $35.00 on eBay. I have a stack of old Levi's in a cedar chest stashed away for a rainy day. I have bought several older hats before but nothing came of them, really just broke even. 

I'm aware of older vintage brands, but have never really came across anything worth purchasing. I'm not into fur, so I always pass on that. Are there specific brands you look for? Specific eras?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 16:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beautiful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 16:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol...they don't give two shits about your stuff. I swear they run the trucks over every package.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 16:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if it just gets sucked up in a black hole as some alien street sweeper floats by...smh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 15:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My lucky number is 3, What does it mean!? What do you do for a living?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 15:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How fast is Voyager 1 traveling?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 15:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you look for in clothes? I search for vintage jeans (Levi's) but not much else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 14:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your input, I never thought of looking at it that way. Do you have business cards you hand out?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 03:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, your technically seeking legal advice. It's frowned upon, and I think against the subs policy. My response wasn't legal advice, btw; just a friendly encouragement. If anything else occurs don't be afraid to go talk to an attorney who offers a free consultation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 02:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha! I like to be conspicuous with my look ups. I looked up a watch one time while holding a conversation with the owner, bought it for $1.00, and sold it for $35.00 the same day. I think the iPad is a little obvious, they know your a pro.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tools of the trade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 02:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I primarily use my iPhone (eBay app) when I'm out prospecting. I saw a fellow flipper using an iPad and got jealous. Do you have any tools you use?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 02:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the time...it's rough being a flipper, but also a collector at the same time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 02:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well this is obviously still developing, but your on the right path. Keep all the information you have in connection to your loans. Document when you call them, who you talk to, etc. They shouldn't be coming after you now that the government has taken action. I would keep your payments current and on the payment plan you negotiated with them. Your good, don't let this bullshit get you down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 02:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are all the otters at? Pics or it didn't happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 01:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Etsy is calling your frames dude...make like 5-10 of them and sell them for like $50...boom you got your side hustle going!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 22:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya no worries, shoot me a PM. I'm out of Michigan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 22:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are you located? My brain works the same way, I just graduated from law school with a concentration in business transactions and real estate law.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 21:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a big commitment. Get a pre-approval letter before reaching out to a real estate agent; you don't want to waste the agent's time. Get a 30yr FIXED rate loans; interest rates are beginning to rise try and get the best deal you can--don't be afraid to shop around for a loan. When you look at houses, look at A LOT of homes to get a great sense of exactly what you want; when you know you know. Get a good reputable agent, and don't be afraid to reach out to an Attorney for a free consultation if you feel you are getting screwed with. I would strongly suggest getting an inspection, you can usually find a good inspector for $300. If you are buying a home with land I would also get a survey to determine the exact corners of the land. Do you have any questions? Ask as many as you need...now is the time to do so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 20:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, congrats on finding it! I use to work at a car dealership and we would do the hose thing all the time with leaks. You can go to any auto store and get some seals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think flat fees will lead to a better relationship with the client and increase the chance to upsell them on other products/services you offer. ABC.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's going to be difficult for many older attorneys to keep up with the pace, your right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see the impact, great point. I'm not completely sure if it paid off for the firm, but they ran the ad on several radio stations leading up to New Years...and then afterwards I never heard anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 18:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing insight, thank you for sharing. It all really does make sense when put into the same conversation. I had not even thought about the Uber thing. A local law firm advertised for New Years they would comp everyone's Uber bill up to $25/30 if you submitted the receipt before the 7th. I thought that was interesting marketing move.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you come up with documents you can sell at a set rate, knowing exactly what you have in the document preparation? I'm in the process of considering going that route.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could sell those. Just curious, how long did it take?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as you disclose that all warranties are removed and your selling the vehicle as is, so long as the purchaser reasonably inspects the vehicle, they have no standing to claim warranty. 

Edit: There are a lot of consumer protection laws that effect vehicle sales; that's why the window sticker says in big bold black font " SOLD AS IS," and  unequivocally notifies the consumer. 

Now, if you sell it as it, but also make representations as to condition of the vehicle (ex. No flood damage), if the purchaser later finds out the car was in fact damaged because of a flood--they would have standing to file a legal suit based on contractual misrepresentation. 

Warranties and contractual defenses are two completely separate issues.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. It could possibly be the seals around the trunk and/or windows. Also, I know in my car (2008 Ford Focus) there are two 2'' inch holes behind both the driver and passenger seats. When it would rain hard the carpet would soak up some of the water as I drove through puddles. You could also start by testing it yourself with a water garden hose, just play around with areas and see if they leak as you spray them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you kidding? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could speak with an attorney before you write this off as a loss. The quicker you speak with one the better. Even though you bought the car with no warranties, you could possibly get out of the contract on contractual misrepresentations...it's going to be determined based on the facts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's beautiful. Great job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 15:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I just downloaded the Reddit App and I'm still getting accustomed to it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 15:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, and very well put. I see two things happening: (1) The Attorney-Client experience/ relationship will become more valuable; and (2) as more go the online route, legal issues will increase because of their DIY attempts gone wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 15:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha. Love the candor, nicely put.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 04:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to go onto the FAFSA website. Follow their prompts. I would try to get some scholarships too; go to your school's website they should have a page dedicated to them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 03:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bullshit. You can invest in property without a conventional loan. Find someone who owns their home, willing to sell, and buy that shit owner financed. You more or less have a job, keep making money, and live there while you fix up the place with the $10,000 you have stashed. Be creative, guy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 03:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would go after those grad school loans you have incurred, but only if they are higher interest rate then your undergrad. Those are ALL good ideas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 03:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best loan doesn't exist, pay cash and get scholarships if you can. 

If you can't, Federal backed loans have the most flexibility. If you sign up with FAFSA, later when your finished with school you have a grace period before your first payment is due. If you can't begin paying or some other life event happens, you can put your loans in forbearance. Forbearance is basically a pause on you paying for a determined period of time. 

Once you accept the loan your loan will begin to accrue interest at the rate set for your loan. 

NOW...that's Federal...if you go with a commercial loan, you are locked in and required to pay. There are no grace periods, no forbearance, etc. 

Commercial loans/lenders are out to make money. Student loans are NON-dishchargable in bankruptcy so you are required to pay them off. Commercial loans also DO NOT have Forgiveness programs like the Federal loans DO.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 02:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Real Estate at a fixed interest rate before the interest rates get hiked up. **you don't need a conventional loan people, be creative... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 02:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I can see how AI can/will be implemented more, but I think there will always be a need for someone to put in the right inputs, proof the output, and present the findings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Condition of the Legal Market </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Current/recent graduates, do you have any concerns as to the current/future conditions of the legal market. 

Do you see commoditized legal services, such as legalzoom, as a positive or negative? How will you be creative to excel in the future?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Condition of The Legal Market </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I'm seeing is how the legal market is transforming into a commoditized field of products, rather then the practice and advisement of the law. 

What are y'all doing to combat or conform to the current/future condition of the legal market? 

(Specifically, as a hopeful solo, services like legalzoom and the like worry me as direct competition.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 18:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely epic...great piece.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 22:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha! The mind reader would have an edge, they would be able to see the future before or at the same time the future observer observes the future; would they be simultaneous observations? That's trippy concept! Could they fight each other out of their own mind, like in Harry Potter? Lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 15:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, thanks for the input. I have time on my side; I'm 28 years old and just became an Attorney. I don't care if it takes me 20 years (I'd be 48, with plenty of career left), I just want to have a solid base and do it the right way. I'm willing to work hard to obtain my goals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 15:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, I was always good in science based classes. I just read through a Fundamental of Chemistry book and decided to jump over to math because I know most chem. and physics are rooted heavily in mathematical calculations. 

Funny story actually, in one of my law school classes another classmate was trying to be a smartass and quoted the wrong equation for velocity. I raised my hand and said "your wrong, velocity takes not just distance and speed into consideration, but direction as well. The scientific equation for speed and velocity are often misused..." Everyone in the class just stared at my with their mouths wide open, haha.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 15:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will do, thanks again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 15:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Statistics and linear algebra are listed on the course plan as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 02:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally! Haha, my wife thinks I'm crazy. I ask her questions all the time, she is a wizard, but hates school. All of my family are professional mathematicians on some level...except me, I'm the damn lawyer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 02:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect. Sorry, I searched, but did not find anything like this. I wasn't looking for a list per se, but this will help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 01:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your time. I want to know the basics and I had a family friend tell me to start back with Algebra because that is where most math is based. Should I jump back a little and start somewhere else? I must admit, I only started with algebra because I found a free book at a garage sale. Fractions are something I never understood, I can say that with certainty. Thank you again for your time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 01:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Easements and LL+ T are must knows.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 01:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what level, if I had to guess, very low. I am currently working through a book called: *Painless Algebra* By Lynette Long, Ph.D. 

The book has eight chapters, I'm currently on CH3: 

CH1: Basics
CH2: Integers
CH3: Solving Equations w/ One Variable
CH4: Solving Inequalities
CH5: Exponents
CH6: Roots and Radicals
CH7: Quadratic Equations 
CH8: Solving Systems of Equations

For a EE BA, I am going to have to work my way all the way up to Geometry, Calculus, and Differential Equations. You have to understand, I don't care if it takes me twenty years to get to that point, I want to get to that level. Is there a course of action you think would be best? I don't care if it's going back to counting from 1-10; I want to know the best way of getting to my goal. I appreciate all the help. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always hated these; always wanted to say assumption of risk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michigan's Unauthorized Practice of Law Statute.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ALGEBRA Practice, where do I find it for free? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 23:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did not care about school when I was in high school (hs). I graduated HS with pre-algebra as my math level (yes, laugh). I'm now a law school graduate, nothing like I use to be, and smacking myself (literally) for not applying myself. In a nutshell, I'm teaching myself Algebra and need a lot to practice; any ideas? I'm free to chit-chat as well; I'm planning to obtain an Electrical Engineering BA so I can practice Intellectual Property Law (yea, I changed my life around).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 23:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always say: " Go google, MCL 600.916...lemme know what you find." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 23:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting, thank you. I just am trying to think of creative ways to make money over here in the US because our legal market is evolving quickly.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 23:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You really should go ask a Real Estate Attorney in your jurisdiction.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 22:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Write something. I had under 5min for my last essay; literally knew the law, wrote all the law bullet style, got a 7/10 on the essay. Keep your time wisely.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 22:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am making an argument for this because my state requires me to take a licensing test and 30hr course. Brokers are allowed to represent both the Buyer/Seller if the instance comes up. I understand ethical limitations in representing the Buyer/Seller in the same transaction, that isn't my concern.

My underlying question is based on little to nothing is done about unauthorized practice of law in the real estate industry; why can't attorneys capitalize on an industry they have the right to be in?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 02:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to put a disclaimer on this post: I am not an attorney and you should go and talk to one before you set things up. First, when you go talk to an attorney about setting up a business, so long as you actually start that business, those fees associated with the counsel can be deducted under the start-up-business deduction. Second, the main and most important difference between a C and S Corp is the way the taxes are implemented. For a C-Corp there is the traditional double-layer of taxes, once at the corp. level and then second at the shareholder level. Your going to pay taxes at the corp. level depending on the yearly gross income, and then each shareholder will be taxes at their own respective rate based on their bracket. Now for a S-Corp. there is only one level of taxation. Taking a S-election turns the Corp. into a flow-through entity and removes the double taxation, which allows the shareholder to only be taxed once on the dividend they receive at their respective bracket. Third, you have to remember a few things, a) S-Election allows you to deduct a lot more of the costs associated with running the corp. and b) Shareholders are the owners of the corporation by way of the stock certificates.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 02:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you could really turn this into something. Extremely well written. Great imagination, very vivid.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 00:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha. First thing to come to mind was the Crazy Cow level in Diablo 2.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 16:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would go for it then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 20:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Secured covers Article 9 of the UCC...fyi. Sales goes through A3+4. lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 20:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sales is a must. You get a very nice review of contracts, and you go through Article 3 + 4 of the UCC...both of which could show up on the Bar. Secured is a good class, but Sales will help with both MC and Essay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 17:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long have you been a member? Do you offer services other than what your listed as?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 21:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand what your saying, at what point do you scale? And when you scale, do you just add one or two areas? (Obviously I know "It depends") I'm trying to mentally implement this strategy in my head and its difficult for me to narrow it down to one area; even when considering the demographic nature of the locality I would be practicing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 20:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No complicated disclosures. I think the process is just slow, then again I don't know. I know about five people who still do not have theirs back either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 20:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also read your article about scaling your practice. Now, it seems counter-productive to only offer one area of the law. I understand and agree with how you can grow into the area you offer, but couldn't you offer a general practice and refer out what you can't do. I am struggling with the idea of what I am going to offer because I'm interested in everything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 20:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was talking with my father-in-law about this the other day. He told me flat out you can't afford to give anyone a break right now, so charge them sticker. haha It's true though, and correlates with what you said: "they would have to pay someone else anyway." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 20:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just read all of your articles on FB and LinkdIn, awesome read. This is such a valuable tool that doesn't cost a whole hell of a lot. I have seen others in the past who have made every mistake you have outlined.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 19:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I've heard of this before; JAG also does free estate planning as well. I'm just trying to capitalize on the network I have in place. Where do you offer free workshops? Coffee Shops, Church's, Retirement Homes, etc? I can see that free is not always the best option, thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 19:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you completely, thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 18:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, now that you say that...it did! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 18:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, PC. I see it under Education-Activities and Societies...it just has this as a hyperlink: "Activities and Societies: Moot Court Honors Council; Health Law Society; Street Law; ACLU." I see it in your volunteer experience, but that is long after first seeing your education. It's not really a huge deal I guess, it may be I'm being to critical; just a thought.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 18:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, maybe just offer pro bono work for my friends that are PD/Fire and let them spread the word? I just figured establishing contacts in their line of work would be good to have; they deal with societies problems and could be a good source of referrals. I don't want to stray from my true motive of showing appreciation for their service; but anyone can see the benefit I would be receiving overall. I was staying away from doing this for just my friends because it would become a PR issue if they then went out and handed out my info; they could be construed as my agent/solicitation issue...I'm just brainstorming on the best way to jump start business with good PR.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 18:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, that is cool. I would elaborate on that because "Street Law" to me looks slightly unprofessional when read without that context.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 16:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go into the history of Halloween and how Mexico celebrates Day of the Dead. Then compare how main-stream America has stolen the holiday and used it as a marketing tool to push the candy industry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 16:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Curious, what is Street Law?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 16:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go out and "get business" or else. Edit: B/c no one liked my first post. haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Free services to build base/network, good idea? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 16:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am currently formulating my business plan. I have multiple ties to both local and state law enforcement. I had the idea to offer free estate planning to law enforcement, fire, and military (both current and retired). I planned to offer free review of what they currently have in place, and if nothing is in place, put together an estate plan for them. Do you think this is a good idea? I think it would jump start my business and get my name out there in a positive light.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
