<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3297</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't need to go to Church. It's good since it provides community, charity, and unity with the religion, but the only requirement is to trust in Jesus and God.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the idea of treating your neighbors with respect and understanding would be a good idea to catch on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 22:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy Scarlet Witches </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 22:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the strange thing is that you can be Christian, and not like the organization of the religion of Christian. As long as you're OK with the teachings of the Bible you can still consider yourself a Christian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 22:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought someone of your reputation would be a bit.....older. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 22:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Name?"

"Johnny Bravo!"

"Occupation?"

"Johnny Bravo!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, not Kruger, Keifer's long lost brother, but Keifer was certainly better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally preferred Civil War over Winter Soldier (both are great). I just found the personal story of Cap in Civil War far more fascinating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved the story, characters and actors. I thought Eric Johnson had a good performance as Fisher although I wish they would have shaved off a few years on Sam so that his voice could have matched up with his visage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really liked the script, but that's just me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally loved the characters and story, and even people I thought I'd hate (Charlie) turned out to be great additions to the series.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked Eric Johnson's performance, but I think there's also a separate problem where they needs not only a voice actor but also have that actor do the physical performance.

Conviction mo-caped physical performances look a little weird for the traditionally animated faces because they wanted to bring back Ironside for one last story. Ironside probably isn't physically able to do all the physical performances.

I don't mind that they switched out actors for iconic characters, if he performance is good. For instance, I thought Keifer Sutherland was better than David Hayter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MY BRAND! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with most of your assessment. However, I disagree with the Spider-man film critique. I've liked-to-loved every Spider-man film, save for Spider-man 3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 12:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, of course. I'm not talking about the individual artistic achievements with the previous Spiderman films, but more of the fact that I really did like the amazing Spiderman one and two which included the road again. Sony seems just up a creek in terms of getting its productions under way. They had more than 20 different spider-man properties in production at one point after The Amazing Spider-man 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> J.J. Abrams' "mystery box" taken to the next level </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like some of his writing. He isn't actually attached to this movie as of right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This sounds completely pointless and confusing.

Well, that sounds completely like a SONY move. Just look at the Ghostbusters remake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't say blame Snyder. He's a decent director who doesn't exactly have a keen appreciation for writing and narratives. For Man of Steel and BvS, I more blame Terrio and Goyer (aka "the luckiest son of a bitch working in Hollywood"). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally loved both TASM movies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But......isn't Venom EXPLICITLY tied to the Spider-man mythos? For almost any other character you can get away with shifting the backstory. Look at Quicksilver and Scarlet Witch in Age of Ultron. But this seems like a step too far.

I loved the Agent Venom and Anti-Venom stories, but they're directly tied to Spider-man in the comics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not only that, but he had the fucking testicular fortitude to claim that Edios Montreal had a development team full of racists because they were comprised of white people talking about oppression. Manveer Heir is a despicable little human being. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked Mass Effect 3, but I admit that the plot portion of ME3 ending was a bit weak (even after the extended ending that made it "alright"). I really dig Dragon Age Inquisition.

I thought it was Casey Hudson's decision and not Walters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved Mass Effect 3 and Dragon Age Inquisition, but I'm getting worried about this game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Ah, yes, "EA". We have dismissed those claims." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Democracy is non-negotiable!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For myself, I have really liked to loved every multiplayer component in a halo game (first person shooter ones) , So for me, the really big indicator of a quality Halo game is the campaign as the deciding mark. For myself, I thought halo four was brilliant, and I hold it among my favorite video game stories ever made, which none of the other Halo games manage to do (even though I love the rest of the games). Halo fives storyline had some interesting moments and nice character bits here and there, but the overall narrative was just a mess, and they didn't really know what to do with bringing back Cortana. I don't think Brian Reed is a terrible writer, but I definitely think he shouldn't have been in charge of writing halo five. I hope they bring back Chris Schlerf for Halo 6. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So, is "Into the Badlands" good? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interested in seeing it and I just wanted to know if anyone would recommend it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "They do exist!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Greg, we talked about this." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree that you choose whatever gaming device you want, and don't be a jackass about it. Most modern platforms these days have a lot of variety and options to their games. 

The only real problem I'd add with PC is spotty optimization. And if we're talking about Steam, we're also talking about one of the worst customer service a company has ever offered with a marketplace that's as unorganized and ugly as it is mired in asset-flips and rush-to-market crap games. I mean, I don't think SONY or Microsoft has great options for Indie devs, but at least there's a process for approval and people can RATE the damn things. 

I also have a particular bee in my bonnet concerning PC and Piracy, but I won't get into that minefield.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Halo 4 was incredible, and I really liked Halo 5. Gears of War 4 was also a great addition to the franchise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, that's actually more akin to "PeopleOfWalMart.com" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not even green screened. Just Andy Serkis in a Scooby Doo Halloween costume. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You shut the hell up! Freddy Prine Jr. is a gift to the world! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it possible to learn this senate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fernand Mondego in The Count of Monte Cristo (2002).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually felt bad for him a little bit when he sees that Faramir is alive and has that small moment of recognizing his son still lives.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You came to the ~~wrong~~ right neighborhood, motherfucker." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has expanded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 23:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOVE that movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steve Buschemi as Ellie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's funny in it, but I wouldn't call it a great performance. It's still his wheelhouse of acting, in which he plays a sleazy detective. He can either play stoic or sleazy. If he pulls something off like Tim Roth in Reservoir Dogs, then I'd reconsider. But for now, he's just "fine" in my eyes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The Bible tacitly allows pedophilia, 

[Uh, no it doesn't.](https://carm.org/is-pedophilia-wrong)

"The whole history of the Church"?  You mean including the parts of advancing science, providing for the poor (Catholic church being the largest charity organization in the World), and helping build the bedrock of Western civilization? 

And if you invoke the Crusades, I suggest you actually look up the history in that it was a response to Muslim expansionism into Europe. Say what you will about Christianity, but actually acknowledge it's role in history rather than just a evil entity you vilify because you disagree with their beliefs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch out, we have an edge lord over here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my point of view as a Christian, God is perfect, people are flawed confused creatures. ANY organization that has more than one person is going to find conflict SOMEWHERE.

As a Catholic, I want a hard line Pope that says "absolutely not" and Ex-communicates every priest convicted of sexual assault and child molestation, and turns over those accused of molesting children back to their countries of origin. There's no damn room in the church for that or merely ignoring those transgressors (even though it's an incredibly small number of the clergy, there must be a blanket stance against everyone in the organization who sexually molests children). 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Pitch Black

* Lord of the Rings trilogy

* Captain America: Civil War

* The Count of Monte Cristo (2002)

* His Girl Friday

* Sanjuro

* Hot Fuzz

* Rush Hour 2

* Casablanca

* Nashville

* Gattaca

* Jurassic Park

* Die Hard

* True Romance

* Snatch

* The Matrix

* Inception

* Dumb and Dumber

* O, Brother Where Art Thou?

* North by Northwest

* Cabin in the Woods </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked the human elements, but that's just me. I liked how the people were finally shaken out of their apathy and started to work for a life worth living. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe the Axiom was generating enough gravity for the...tachyon particles which made the.....nanobites make the fire extinguisher particles....uh.....yeah, I have no idea how they did that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it was about a man during world war 2 suffering from a disability in a play-like setting for the majority of the film. It has "Oscar buzzwords" all over it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ryan Gosling, for myself. He's fine, but there hasn't been a single role which he's had that I would consider to be brilliant. For me, his best roles were in "Drive" and "Gangster Squad".

Post-edit: I said the man was fine! I didn't say he was Sam Worthington level of bland or anything. I just don't personally think he's brilliant but has had a lot of "solid" roles without really stretching himself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked the show, but I just thought that the first two seasons were unnecessarily slow, and I hated how the show incorporated the characters of Walt Jr. and Marie (God, I hate Marie. "Oh, Marie's shoplifting again!" Who cares?! Walt is getting shot at in the other scene!!!!).

I think it's an incredibly well-made show, but I don't think it's perfect. There are very few shows (even excluding ones I love) that I would consider to be masterpieces from beginning to end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention the "Jack and the Bounty Hunters" episode with that ending </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that's apart of the show's charm - taking time with loving shots on the environment and characters in them to establish setting and tone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 14:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know about that.

"No, Loki."

Odin told that son of a gun and Loki still tried, and failed, to be king over the Earth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 19:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You're gonna love my nuts." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 19:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if a fall from this height would kill me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 19:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> REX gonna give it ya </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 17:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved how much fun he had as Rhino. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 01:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched his special on G4TV show "Icons" and e-mailed him after seeing it. He wrote back thanking me for the e-mail and he seemed like a nice guy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 01:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't seen the most recent episode, but it's a very well-made show. For myself, I'd still say that daredevil is the best superhero show ever made, and still currently on. Not only do we have the Golden age of television going on right now, but we have the Golden age of superhero television shows going on with the marvel Netflix shows as well as the DC CW shows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Us: "No....stop....come back....." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? Which laws or institutions are persecuting Muslims? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Like how there are some idiot guys who can't handle female Ghostbusters.

Good God, Superman can't make that leap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, [this](http://m.huffpost.com/us/entry/13652002) is actual Christian discrimination. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, that was actually a response to Muslim invasions into Europe. I suggest reading Rodney Stark's book on the Crusades as a fascinating read </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To say that Christian persecution in the world isn't a thing is downright ignorant. In fact, Christians face some of the worst [discrimination in the Middle East](http://m.huffpost.com/us/entry/13652002). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, there actually is Christian discrimination in the world, moreso in countries outside of the US: [link](http://m.huffpost.com/us/entry/13652002) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no need to be a jackass to the guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're John117, I assume you're fighting with the Didact right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 09:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you a Duke, or a Dimwit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gotcha! I do really think Remedy houses fantastic developers. I liked Max Payne, and REALLY liked Alan Wake, but I LOVE Quantum Break. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very similar in terms of how they use the protagonist in the narrative (throwing him against impossible forces and slowly coming to grips with the situation). 

In my opinion, Quantum Break is better than Alan Wake by a good margin, especially in narrative experimentation with a time-travel plot. I'd compare to CD Projekt Red's jump in quality of writing from Witcher 2 to Witcher 3. Apparently, the PC port is a bit poo-poo, but I can attest to the XONE version of the game being awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 19:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They hinted at it in quantum break.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 19:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is the line between freedom of religious expression and forcing someone to go against their religious beliefs for the sake of another person is damn close to infringing on the Freedom of Religion. In the case of a judge however, they really should just preside within the law as they're not a business or something outside of the judicial system  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 19:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A judge who can't separate their personal feelings from their duty to uphold the law should absolutely be removed from the bench. 

But the problem is that many times in presiding over a case, their own interpretation of law and punishment with particular rulings comes down to personal interpretation on their part.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 19:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know. This seemed to have more actual story than RWBY. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "What kind of monster are you?!"

"The Wolverine." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm eating." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "For the present your friend, tomorrow your host, for the short time formality stands between us, the Count of Monte Cristo." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> James Cromwell is brilliant! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loved it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is that the book wouldn't really make an interesting story. Most of the conflicts and such in the novel are really just logic puzzles and there really isn't much in terms of character and overall plot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a damn good film. I think a lot of the hate is because it had the name "I, Robot" and except for some well-integrated references, it's not really the source material.

It's one of the better sci-fi films of the nought decade and still holds up. I LOVE how the movie plays with the unspoken "black-man-vs-white-man" mentality of trying to make Bruce Greenwood's corporate head as the bad guy. Everything from the design of everything, to the action (I adore how overpowering the NS5 robots actually are in combat), and it's an excellent character study of a man who burdens himself with self-hating guilt (Spooner). 

I do wish it would get more love, especially that FANTASTIC [interrogation scene](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=05bGPiyM4jg)!

"Do you ever have a normal day?"

"Yeah. Once. It was a Thursday." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's terrible. Unfortunately, it sounds like senior management will be responsible for the cut-back, not you. All you can do right now is what you think is the right course of action. I think it's important to highlight (in the nicest way possible, of course) that senior management doesn't understand what your team does; it might be a good idea to present that.

I've never been the head of a team in the arena of business, so I have no experience here, but I wish you all the best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 07:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  im a massive fan of "this is 40" too.

I hated that movie. If you didn't know what the Hell "LOST" is, you'll have zero idea what the hell 40% of the jokes they attempt are about. I genuinely can't believe Paul Rudd's character is an adult and makes such a TERRIBLE business decision as a supposedly seasoned professional in his career when he has a family to look out for (not to mention that it's not a "new family", as he already has multiple kids and a long-term wife and he should know better than to gamble away his family's future for something he takes no research to understand, which I found completely idiotic despite the film's attempt to try and convince me that this is a reflection of real life). I also didn't see what the point was of Leslie Mann and Megan Fox off dancing in a club for no reason than to waste time and have MORE unnecessary celebrity cameos.

 Like its done in a way where the jokes have literally no impact on the scenes, you can tell they changed things out as they used different jokes for the trailer then when they released. i dnno i feel just find it weird that you hate the man child archetype when thats literally what Deadpool is, he just also breaks the fourth wall, doesnt smoke weed and is a super hero

I disagree. Wade is shown to be uncaring to the world (and unlike most of Apatow's films, it's not trying to say that the world they live in is OUR world, especially with the stylistic sensibilities. A lot of the jokes are not interchangeable, especially in context to how they're used like with pre and post Deadpool transformation as the backbone to the character's sanity. Wade is a thug for hire, and only seems happy when he's with someone who shares his libido, style of humor, and quick wit. Scenes like the Zamboni death reveal, the cutting off the hand moment, the shock of Francis' escape, and so many other moments of visual comedy working in sync with Renolds acting and physical performances is just great (even BEFORE becoming Deadpool). 

 .. but then i accept that its a reddit meme'd movie that everyone goes out to bat for.

Much like you with "This is 40", I don't love Deadpool because of what other people said about it on Reddit. I love the movie because I love how the narrative is structured, how it smartly uses fourth wall breaking, makes the characters emotionally resonant by combining the drama and the humor flawlessly, has excellent action, utilizes every cast member so incredibly well, and quite frankly put so many movies in 2016 to shame in terms of how much care and effort went into everything which includes the editing and audio design and terrifically balancing the tone of the story.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 07:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You took my words out of context man, that's dishonest.

You put your words out, and I referenced them in context. That's just wrong.

 but what I don't get is the awkward stalls in responds whenever they are in a romantic conversation. 

Because David is an awkward man, who has had seriously emotionally complicated relationships in the past as is inhibited by his fears going forward with a new relationship. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be careful with that joke, it's an antique </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well to be fair, there's also the discussion of graphical fidelity when it comes to presentation and whether or not devs are willing to sacrifice it for frame rates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do hope they'll change the core thematic content of "violence and revenge" being the center point of the narrative. The previous game betrayed the heart of the source material in that bloodlust and vengeance are poisonous things, but Shadow of Mordor embraced it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Junk food cinema. A terrific look at forgotten gems and B-movie goodness that's without irony. One of them is the man who wrote Doctor Strange and they gave great insight and humor about these films. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  AAAAAAAYYYYYYYYYYEEEEEEE

Must be the money! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Check yo-self, fool!"

"Oh, shit! It's Big N!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scalebound also looked terrific

Post-edit: The Hell? All I said was that I am sad that Scalebound was cancelled and that it looked like an interesting game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. I personally thought Funny People was a mess, and not just from the fragmented macro narrative. """""""jokes"""""" like making fun of that one German guys accent for an entire scene just strike me as disturbingly unfunny. Not to mention that the editing and cinematography is so pedestrian that I genuinely thought this was rushed to the theaters. The argument scene between Jonah Hill and Seth Rogen is one of the most terribly timed big-budget movie releases I can recall in YEARS. 

I thought Knocked Up was just....awful. Once again, if you have zero understanding of the pop culture references they keep spouting out, you're lost. Not to mention we have a huge amount of shock value jokes (again, in dialog only) with the doorman scene or the "spelled coming wrong" moment. 

Also, I'm just so incredibly god damn tired of the man-child archetype FOR EVERY FUCKING JUDD APATOW MOVIE! There isn't a single man in these films with one iota of understanding what the Hell responsibility or maturity is. Yeah, I can enjoy it every once in a while, but not every damn film!

Also, for Deadpool, that "Did I leave the stove on" moment (regardless of whether or not you thought it was funny, which I did) is supposed to blend together and cement Deadpool's mentality of not taking things seriously during incredibly dramatic moments while also breaking the artifice of the film and the fourth wall. 

Look at how Tarantino does comedy in his films. He actually uses the film itself to accentuate and create a funny moment. Look at how he uses a zoom and a whoosing sound effect in Django Unchained to create humor after the sudden and dramatic death of [Calvin Candie](#spoiler). Here's the scene: [link](https://youtu.be/weKNVNSG-vk?t=22s)

I haven't even the slightest understanding from Apatow in terms of making a """""comedy""""" outside of people speaking dialog (and usually terrible dialog at that). 

Not to mention this video that perfectly analyzes what Edgar Wright does so....uh....right, and what sooo many comedy film directors get wrong these days: [link](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3FOzD4Sfgag) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "600 leaves? That's about two specs of dirt." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "What's that, Lassie?"

"ARE YOU SMOKING YET?!?!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ""PC load letter"? What the fuck does that mean?!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. American comedy has never been the same since we were graced with that piece of cinematic glory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Nice Shot!

Chat disabled for 1 second. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really didn't like No Country for Old Men. That third act non-ending completely spoiled the rest of the enjoyment I had for that film. I'd put Hot Fuzz and Eastern Promises into the "masterpiece" category, personally. 3:10 to Yuma is SO damn good. 

Post-edit: I guess "screw me" for having a personal opinion on the matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's British comedy, which is far, far superior (at least I think so).

If you're JUST comparing British comedy these days to most American comedies, I agree....mostly. 

Deadpool, Tropic Thunder, The Nice Guys, Zombieland, Black Dynamite, Cabin in the Woods, Tucker and Dale vs. Evil, and Horrible Bosses are fantastic (not to mention a lot of great animated films from Pixar/Disney), and are among my favorite comedies ever made, but these days, Judd Apatow and his ilk during the naught decade and 2010s (in directing, writing, and producing) have replaced well made comedies with cheaply shat out snooze-fests that substitute making great jokes with the artifice of the medium for pop culture references with a shelf life of a piece of moldy bread, random celebrities cameos that are as distracting as they are unnecessary, and incessantly using shock value to generate an awkward laugh. 

In my opinion, standards and competition for American blockbusters these days have never been higher, whereas American comedies are absolutely floundering, for the most part.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 05:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anakin, my allegiance is to the Republic! To sand!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  GRRM loves shades of grey, with the except of maybe Ramses. Dumbledore would not be completely good, and Voldemort would not be completely evil. Harry himself would probably be completely different.

That's one thing I do criticize against Martin. He claims that there really aren't good vs evil people in the world and Tolkien's "simplistic" view of morality, then has characters who are just wholly despicable people with no or very little redeeming value as characters, like Joffrey, Ramsey, Walder Frey, Cersei, etc. and have completely honorable good people like Jon, Ned, Brienne, Pod, Sam, etc. Tolkien ALSO had morally gray characters (moreso in the Jackson film adaptations) with characters like Boromir, Smeagul, Elrond, Denethor, Isildur, and Wormtongue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 14:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I really dig about this show is how much of a mystery David still is, especially in terms of whether or not he can be trusted (or even if he can trust himself). Having the perspective of him flip back and forth between sympathetic and dangerous makes for a fascinating dynamic. 

Close-ups are "big budget Marvel"? I don't get that criticism, especially when close-ups are mostly used in this series for the OPPOSITE effect of how it's usually used in providing extreme discomfort even with characters we know and like. The romantic scenes (which don't always utilize music and warm lights, like when David is sleeping next to Syd) are the only ones that maintain consistent "normalcy" in the entire show. Everything else is underlined by the schizophrenic mentality of style reflecting David's mind. Following eye movement with shaky cam is evocative of the instability faced by characters in the show while showing them trying to maintain a small amount of mental stability.

I think the casting is good and I think the sound design is PHENOMENAL! 

I haven't seen Gotham since the first season, but I much prefer this show. I really liked the actual "COP" portion of the show, but whenever they actually try to tie the show into future Batman villains or Bruce Wayne plot lines that won't pay off until he's an adult, it gets downright infuriating because they're all just winks, nods, and foreshadowing to things that won't be in the show in either the immediate or distant future of this series. Bruce Wayne does NOT need to be in Gotham, and often they cram him into episodes where he has absolutely no reason to be there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 07:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Daredevil
* Cowboy Bebop
* Trigun
* Jericho
* Prison Break
* Band of Brothers
* LOST
* The Expanse
* LOST
* The West Wing
* Twin Peaks
* Samurai Jack
* Legion
* Riverdale
* Firefly
* Arrested Development
* Clone High
* The Young Pope
* Deadwood
* Profit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 07:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Samurai Jack is the equivalent of an average anime.

I would actually say it's more equivalent to Ozu, Mizogucchi, and Kurosawa in terms of cinematic sensibilities. It's more "traditional Japanese cinema" than most anime these days, even ones like Samurai Champloo, especially in terms of how much it lovingly focuses on environments and diagetic sounds.

The show is excellent, especially in the artistry of its visuals. I am SOOOOOOOOO deliriously happy the show is getting one last season to go out on.

I wouldn't call it average at all. It's surface-level "all ages" friendly content hide the amount of craftsmanship and care that makes it so damn brilliant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 06:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way that one questioning guy says "rRRRRRUUUUbies?!" on the boat always makes me laugh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 06:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it still just episodic, or are they willing to go more with the Clone Wars route in having mini-arcs within a season? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 06:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peter Parker from "The Spectacular Spider-man" - A normal guy trying to do right, make ends meet, make his family proud, has a good assortment of social issues with his friends and romantic interests in his life, and struggles with understanding what it means to a responsible person. That may not "count" since Peter Parker is from a comic book, but if James Bond can be considered a movie character even though he came from novels, than I thought it could count. I don't have any of his smarts or charm, but I do think I can really relate to his struggles as a regular joe just trying to keep his head on straight in a crazy chaotic world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 06:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the show a lot (mostly in how well it uses the visual and auditory elements of screen-media), however it's still (for me) just "very good" that hasn't QUITE nudged over into "fully great" territory. Maybe it will be one of those shows that will need to be able to have the entire season behind it before showcasing me realizing how terrific it is (which has happened in the past). The trippy genre-and-style blending they do is great, but in terms of the narrative and characters, I haven't been given something to really chew on, like I could with Daredevil, The Wolverine, Captain America: Civil War, The Amazing Spider-man 2, Deadpool, X-men, Luke Cage, Doctor Strange, or a lot of other screen-media Marvel adaptations. 

I won't deny that's it's absolutely BEAUTIFUL in terms of cinematography and editing, but I just need a little touch more in the characters and overall plot before I come down on the side of "YOU MUST WATCH THIS SHOW" immediately, like I feel with stuff that's on right now such as The Expanse, Mr. Robot, The Americans, or Riverdale (I know, the show surprised the Hell out of me). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 06:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you just look at the show's overall plot, it might seem a bit underwhelming. However, I would argue that it's how the show is PRESENTED (sound design, editing, cinematography, composition, art design, etc.) in telling the story through visuals which gives it the appeal (which is the television/film's main appealing aspect of its medium.

It's a building mystery and fleshing the universe through bits and pieces seen through a fractured lens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 05:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please, Oscar Isaac WISHES he could be as awesome as Ivan Ooze.

"Not to mention I've had a Charlie horse since the renaissance." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
