<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3247</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 21:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Mmmmmmmm](http://33.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_m4jtbw9L161rnc2zr.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 21:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Mmmmmmmm](http://33.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_m4jtbw9L161rnc2zr.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 05:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, that is the plan. A more detailed narrative, less loose ends, lots of other changes, and overall longer than here. 

Traditional publishing house. Or that is the plan right now. 

Happy Thanksgiving! 

( *this comment not endorsed by Mother.* )  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 21:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've decided to go into the Shoe making business. You may now call MHE "Master Of The Shoes" and I am "The Cobblers Cat". 


Happy Thanksgiving from u/_9Mother9Horse9Eyes9 and u/subject3247 ! 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giant Pyrosome and Salps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 06:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To Trip or Not To Trip. Trip Like I Do.......*cue up The Crystal Method for Vince* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 06:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 23:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seem like the one doing the threatening right now. Very full of malice.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 23:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? Isn't this behaviour of yours what lead me create r/transpass when there was a user who was downright hateful to other transwomen? 

Try being a little more supportive. I only sit on the sub out of respect for the conversations u/CedarWolf and I had during that ordeal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 22:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THANK YOU!

Posting so when I build my PC next year I come back here.... 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A transgender Marine comes out, tests military's new policy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 05:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Final NASA Eagleworks Paper Confirms Promising EmDrive Results, Proposes Theoretical Model </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 08:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 18:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Touchy Touchy? 

No Touchy Touchy! 

Touchy Touchy now?

No Touchy Touchy Touchy!

Too bad...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 10:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not like they can tell the whale no......  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two Kayakers Lifted Out of the Water by Whales </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 22:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 04:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Links to the stores listed here, and a few more:

_______________________________________________________________

 nbsp;

[Dolls Kill](http://www.dollskill.com/)


[Kill Star](https://us.killstar.com)


[Plastic Land](http://www.shopplasticland.com/)


[Blame Betty](https://blamebetty.com/)


[Sinister Souls](http://www.sinistersoles.com/)


[Tragic Beautiful](http://www.tragicbeautiful.com/)


[Redemption Klothing](http://www.redemptionklothing.com/)

[The Violet Vixen](http://thevioletvixen.com/)

[House of Widow](http://www.houseofwidow.com/)

[Rivethead](https://www.rivithead.com/)

[BlackCraft Cult](http://www.blackcraftcult.com/)

[Black Hope Curse](http://blackhopecurse.com/)

[Sourpuss](https://www.sourpussclothing.com/)

[The Mission Boutique](http://themissionboutique.com/)

[Dark In Closet](http://www.darkincloset.com/)

[The Gothic Shop](http://www.the-gothic-shop.co.uk/)

[Maya Jewlery](http://www.mayajewelry.com/)

[Victorian Foundry](https://victorianfoundry.com/)  

 nbsp;

---------------------------------------------------------------- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 04:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're just not that smart, or well read. 

[Proof 1](https://spaceflightnow.com/2016/05/25/spacex-on-track-to-launch-astronauts-in-late-2017/)

[Proof 2](http://io9.gizmodo.com/these-astronauts-will-be-the-first-to-launch-with-space-1717036938)

Also, not even an American! What a worthless little troll life you have! 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well.... considering I was in cryptology. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 20:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, I'm 48, and it's not my first election. I liked Bush (mostly) and Mitt, and McCain. 

I don't like Trump at all. Nothing about him can I get behind. If I were still in the NAVY I would be anxiously waiting to get out so he is not my CIC.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 19:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have two similar in my basement, and a Philco I bought this summer that was made in 1943. I haven't started restoration yet on any of them. After my friends aren't living here I will.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 01:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least *someone* got it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dammit Barry! Fix this so Lex Luthor isn't President! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 19:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 14:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad you enjoyed it! 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 19:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I voted!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 19:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shortly after Polls close. Expect to see some information around 8pm NYC and 11PM LA.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This baby boy likes to visit my Dad. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 17:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 06:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess we just have to disagree.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 06:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah. Anyone who goes to a poling place with a gun on their hip and confronts a woman with her child and then blocks their exit way is the asshole.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 04:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He confronted her, and then he blocked her and her son when trying to leave. He has a clearly visible gun and acting in a unstable manner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 04:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. I was one of this kids with friends who had guy friends with guns in the trucks. The guys showing up late or leaving early to go hunting. My Dad and Uncles all having gun racks and a pistol in the glove compartment. I'm very comfortable around guns, even in open carry like here in GA. 

However, at this point it is a matter of respect. Respect your fellow citizens who are not comfortable and don't bring them to polling stations. Respect others and don't bring assault rifles into a mall or place families eat. I don't care if you conceal carry, I'm all for it. 

Respect others. Respect their feelings of fear of a person at a polling station who views it as a threat. Respect the fear of a mother with child wondering if you are going to kill her in front of her child because you have a gun at a polling station and behave in a confrontational manner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 22:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So we agree this man at the polling station with a gun on his hip confronting a woman with child in tow is a shitty person? 

If he had acted politely and not had a gun..... he's just another person. 

And yeah, if he had been black he would have been treated different.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 20:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know. To me he was clearly intimidating her before she voted and after when she was leaving as he blocked her with a gun on his hip.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 20:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So why do the White Nationalist and Neo-Nazi's want to go to Black polling stations? Nobody asked them to come into their community? The black people aren't going into theirs. 

How would the public react if the black people armed themselves against people coming into their neighborhoods armed and with intent to harass them into not voting? Or if black people went to white polling stations and were armed? 

No matter what, it is just setting a bad example in the eyes of the world as to what American politics has become in this election because of the actions of one man telling them to do this. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 15:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hes like, Who are you going to vote for, crooked Hillary? And I was like, thats really none of your business, Cotti said, adding that the man was standing in the sidewalk outside of the office when they left and blocking their path. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 15:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know. My friends used to bring them and I took gun safety along with them, along with a simple survival course. I grew up hunting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 08:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to read what I wrote again, and use critical thinking. And Google "Threatening and intimidating".

Woman - I had to explain to my 9-year-old why a man with a 357 magnum is standing outside the polling station, she told the Huffington Post. I felt intimidated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 07:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Old man with visible gun in holster confronts woman with child - "Who are you going to vote for, crooked Hillary?"

Woman - "That's really none of your business."

Woman and others feel intimidated by this "Old man with a gun" so they report it, after they are safely away from this person. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 07:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He confronted her. It says that in the article too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 07:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The question you should ask is why do they feel the need to open carry and confront someone who declines their sample ballot? Wouldn't you be intimidated if you were a woman with her child in this situation? 

I've been around a lot of open carry people here in GA. Doesn't bother me in the least. If one did confront me at a polling station I would confront them back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 07:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are right. 

However, just having the gun is enough for some people. It doesn't need to be pointed at anyone. Having it on your person and visible and then acting in a threatening manner ("Voting for Crooked Hillary?)  towards someone is intimidation. Many people are less likely to tell someone to go fuck themselves in such a situation. 

This should not be what is happening. We are better than this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 06:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because [History proves differently](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/New_Black_Panther_Party_voter_intimidation_case), and would again if it was a black man at the polls with a gun confronting a woman and child in the manner this man did recently. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 06:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Georgia here. 

[History is *always* relevant](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/New_Black_Panther_Party_voter_intimidation_case).

And now you have [White nationalists plot Election Day show of force - KKK, neo-Nazis and militias plan to monitor urban polling places and suppress the black vote.](http://www.politico.com/story/2016/11/suppress-black-vote-trump-campaign-230616). 

The man in the photo is a *white male* with a gun at a polling station. What do you think would have happened if it was a black male? Who intimidated a woman and child?



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 06:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are still avoiding the question; What if it was armed black men and women? 

I hope you know your history on this one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 06:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is within his rights, but it doesn't make it right. 

He's an asshole. It's clear intimidation with the gun. How many people are going to be afraid of someone like that when they confront them outside the polling station? 

How about a bunch of black men in Philly armed outside the polling station for when Trumps Neo-Nazi's come to "monitor" the stations?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 05:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad you are a fellow vet, and I'm glad you are voting. Nice to meet you! 

I was the one attached by a Trump supporter. For being a female and veteran (Combat Action, JMS, AFE) and supporting Hillary. Because I dared to speak up my opinion and not be afraid of him. I even shook his hand afterwards when he calmed down. 

But I do stand behind my comment that it is not normal for a person to be at the polling station with a gun. What image is he setting for America's election? For the children that see him? Is this who we are now? I don't care if he was there with sample ballots. That's fine. But don't give anyone grief when they refuse one, no matter who you are supporting. 

The admirable, respectable, thing for him to do would to have gone and placed the gun in his vehicle, and properly secured.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 05:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read what you said. I understand what you said. 

The fact is it is not a normal thing for a person to be at a polling station with a *gun*. 

I've already had a run-in with a Trump supporter who couldn't believe a veteran is voting for Hillary. He literally got so mad he could hardly talk. 

No, when/if I see one of these assholes when I vote Tuesday and they have the gall to talk/confront me at anytime they are most certainly getting an earful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 01:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Covered Up? You can literally see it in the photo, with the sample ballots](http://img.huffingtonpost.com/asset/crop_5_197_535_535,scalefit_630_noupscale/581cfa38150000b700531cd7.jpeg) 

Personally, when I go vote on Tuesday if one of these fucknuggets is there I'll tell them to go to Hell.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help open a chat room for /r/shruglifesyndicate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 00:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 00:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Added to side bar. Now need 4 more people to click on it. 

Enjoy. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From a Million Miles Away, NASA Camera Shows Moon Crossing Face of Earth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 21:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 18:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will be a physical format when released. At least that is what he is aiming for at this time. 

If that falls through there are other plans I've made to help. I know a small publisher, and Amazon eBook is another fall back. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 18:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't confirm that. Sorry :( 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 03:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mmmmmmm hmmmmmmm Vince. 

Smoking is still smoking.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 20:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me show you Half Life 3 ... now there is a screwed up ending. My head and heart still hurt. One of the few games to make me cry and hold my cat. 

So thankful for the 3 DLCs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 23:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The The - Giant 

 nbsp; 

---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------


The sun is high and I'm surrounded by sand

For as far as my eyes can see

I'm strapped into a rockin' chair

With a blanket over my knees

'I' am a stranger to myself

And nobody knows I'm here

When I looked into my eyes

It wasn't myself I'd seen

But who I've tried to be

I'm thinking of things I'd hoped to forget.

I'm choking to death in a sun that never sets.

I clogged up my mind with perpetual greed

And turned all of my friends into enemies.

And now the past has returned to haunt me.

I'm scared of god - and scared of hell

And I'm caving in upon myself

How can anyone know me

When I don't even know myself

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> THE THE - GIANT </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 23:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 21:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You Don't Know How It Feels"

 nbsp;

 nbsp;


__________________________________________________________________________________________



Let me run with you tonight

I'll take you on a moonlight ride

There's someone I used to see

But she don't give a damn for me

 nbsp;


But let me get to the point, let's roll another joint

And turn the radio loud, I'm too alone to be proud

You don't know how it feels

You don't know how it feels to be me

 nbsp;


People come, people go

Some grow young, some grow cold

I woke up in between

A memory and a dream

 nbsp;


So let's get to the point, let's roll another joint

Let's head on down the road

There's somewhere I gotta go

And you don't know how it feels

You don't know how it feels to be me

 nbsp;

My old man was born to rock

He's still tryin' to beat the clock

Think of me what you will

I've got a little space to fill

 nbsp;


So let's get to the point, let's roll another joint

And let's head on down the road

There's somewhere I got to go

And you don't know how it feels

No, you don't know how it feels to be me

 nbsp;

____________________________________________________________________

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TOM PETTY - YOU DON'T KNOW HOW IT FEELS (VIDEO VERSION) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 21:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 06:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The book is on schedule. Should be finished in December, then a cleaning up/revision/etc.

We were actually discussing tonight about posting. I'm working on my own project and MHE encourages me often. 

Anything major comes up we will let you all know. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 04:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's coming along nicely. Still on schedule. 

We appreciate everyone's patience. Believe it or not, we are watching the sub still, reviewing old posts, and MHE is working hard. 

I am also working (real work- as in career) a lot lately. 

Just keep your eyes open.....

~ Gabbi ~  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 00:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shenanigans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 06:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u/_9mother9horse9eyes9 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cubs beat Dodgers to clinch spot in World Series, end 70-year drought </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 05:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cubs beat Dodgers to clinch spot in World Series, end 70-year drought </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 04:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 06:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm that it was "fun". I was there and my ship is decommissioned.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 02:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Just check out the link. 

Best of luck and have fun if you get hired!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 05:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> remove </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Athene Artemisia by Isaac Mills / Mugwort Designs (2010) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 05:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 06:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Carl Rove had a better program](http://www.pensitoreview.com/2015/03/18/flashback-rove-erases-22-million-white-house-emails-on-private-server-at-height-of-u-s-attorney-scandal-media-yawns/)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stranger Things season 2 is now casting extras in Atlanta, Georgia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 17:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stranger Things season 2 is now casting extras in Atlanta, Georgia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 17:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 04:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Yeah...ok](http://www.cbsnews.com/news/more-unearthed-footage-trump-says-of-10-year-old-i-am-going-to-be-dating-her-in-10-years/?ftag=CNM-00-10aab7e linkId=29868172)

......

[Sure](http://www.nytimes.com/2016/10/13/us/politics/donald-trump-women.html). 

Still voting for Hillary. Anyone who ass kisses Putin and has Russia make cyber attacks is never going to be trusted, along with his being a rapist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 23:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such a great movie! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 23:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are right on several points. And I don't know of anyone except a few Republican Politicians who have made comments, and that judge recently who let the guy off with only 6 months, and...and. 

Point being - It is very indicative of *some*  people in that party to brush off certain behaviour. 

This lady in the article, she has done something wonderful. To belittle her experience and determination to bring it to light should not be dismissed as simply "A lot of people are raped". 

I don't want to ramble. I just don't want it belittled either. 

I don't support Trump, but I respect others right to support him. 

Thanks for engaging me in conversation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 22:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then how do they feel about his sexual assault of women? I mean, he's clearly grabbing them by the pussy, making unwanted sexual moves on them, and rumored to have raped a 13 year old girl.

What is needed for people to stop backing him?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pussy Riot - Full Frontal with Samantha Bee. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 17:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Is The Way Of The Flesh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 15:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 18:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Re-write and new content started 66 days after end. A single story line was increased from 5k words to 21k words. 

It is a MHE Production. I just help at times, when needed/asked. 

There is a tentative book deal, and if it falls apart I have a small publishing house lined up for an initial limited run. I'd like great artwork, including some from here, to be included, but that is just my frog to throw until it sticks. If it sticks. I think it has wings this time. 

My writing will be under another name. We both write under other names recently, usually in r/nosleep. 

MHE calls my writing "A subject3247 Joint" and is my advisor, editor, and all around best friend (more often then he'd admit probably). 

Go forth and look around now. Might find a breadcrumb or three that leads to a sandwich. 

Love </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I call this her "Belly Rub Trap" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 17:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Belly Rub Trap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 17:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 23:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep.... currently in that predicament!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 14:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only translate what you have. Do not worry about the rewrite. It is for publishing in a novel form, hopefully physical. It is not expected to be translated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 04:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonderful artists and writers have created many things to enjoy. Just follow the links on the sidebar. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 04:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Angelica had a kitten that died.....

I leave it up to your imagination ..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 22:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh.. oh Gods. Winters are awesome in older vehicles here in the South. That hard ass blower motor pulling heat off the engine and cooling system right down on your legs. Take the top off and go....

Sigh....Bet they don't have that in a self-driver. Probably just a moon/sun-roof. Ugh. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 22:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah... that is why I bought a New Daily. Saves on Gas, fun to drive, has everything I wanted for getting around ATL and further. 

Save the other two for cruising   camping... and it makes men want to talk to me. So I have that going for me too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 21:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has been posted......enjoy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 21:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has been posted. The one sent to me. Enjoy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There was once a little girl who was very merry and very cruel. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 21:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 19:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking about it... only two extra stories. Kinda secret too. 


Sigh. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 19:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right there with you! 

I'd love to be buried in either of them, but they are such awesome vehicles that one year I will have to figure out who to leave them to in my will. 

And I miss riding motorcycles too. Sigh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 18:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in a city also (Near ATL) and have had similar happen in the rain. A person lost it in a curve and ended up in the wall on I-285. It was raining, I had two options; Hit them, or brake hard and get pray I made it behind another vehicle that was to my right. 

Point is - I'd rather control my own fate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 18:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok .. so, in the country, on back roads, people who know each other sometimes stop in the road to talk for a bit. They happened to stop in a curve and left me three options: Run over the side of the ridge (very large hill/mountain) on the right, run into them at a decent speed (35-40) or swerve left into a gully (side of mountain). 

With the self driving car not knowing there is a very steep drop off to the right, but a decent and safe gully to the left, what would it have choosen? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 17:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh.. once I was on an icy road to my parents home in the mountains. I came around a bend and I had to choose between hitting two cars (neighbors talking) stopped. I had to choose between the gully in the left side or the ridge drop on the right. Knowing the ridge was there and I was on the right I choose the left gully and didn't hit anyone. 

What would the self driving car choose? It doesn't know the area.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 15:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1981 Jeep CJ8 Scrambler and 1970 Chevelle. I've never purchased a NEW car (off the lot new) until two years ago. 

I can very much see them take away ownership and make it so they are lease/rent only if they were to take off. 

Personally I will never trust a self-driving car over my own instinct. At some point that car might decide my life is worth less than whatever situation it will be driving in and I might see a better driving reaction/path than it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 15:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. As the owner of two classic vehicles and one more going to be paid off in a few years I will not be upgrading to anything self driving for a very long time. I enjoy driving, especially in my Jeep. 

I will not buy a self-driving car until I am too old to drive safely.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 06:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ant-Man and The Wasp.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 06:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Still thinking on it.....* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 06:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sound advice! I'd really hate selling my PFR stock, even if it is currently losing GBP. 

After November Election I am expecting a wild market ride.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Memberries vs Pepperidge Farm Remembers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 05:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buy, Sell or Hold? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 05:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And he thinks he can make all the large corporations bring their money back and pay taxes, and give them tax breaks at the same time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 17:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually.... there are two secret stories...small ones. We are debating on releasing them. I'll ask tonight. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 17:19:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is coming along nicely. We are discussing another venture and have a few ideas. A few private subs have been created. Our synergy is still going strong. It is a lot of fun to bounce ideas around and settle on things for after this venture (This was a MHE Production, where as mine are a subject3247 Joint). 

There will be a lot of expanded content in the revision, probably far more than 60%. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 05:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is actually pretty good. I can imagine how it would fit in, but I would really like if they remade Man-Thing. 

I couldn't find a discussion about it in a couple of Subs so I took a chance here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 16:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> () </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 06:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 Love it! Love you! 3  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 15:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard they can be gay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 21:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [One Past - Chinese Man live feat. Mr Raf](https://youtu.be/C0H6WlogsXM) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 18:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As you wish......... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I...Eye... I...A finger in my I am to be or cease to be Eye for I am Eye forever more cried the Raven in the Moonlight. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 05:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "And why do you think it is changing shape?" the grin asked. 

"it's the fault of the news media - Television is influencing our image of the world! They keep telling us that the world is changing - and more and more people keep believing it."

 nbsp;

___________________________________________________________________

 nbsp;

Believe not what your I views, nor what your Eye witnesses. Believe in what you see. And shift until your I is what you want to be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 04:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it is not......... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 21:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are old writing tropes. Even Stranger Things mentions Stephen King. 

Plus a lot of it is common conspiracy knowledge stuff. MKULTRA and LSD, etc. 

There are far more differences between the two shows than similarities. Their *flesh interface* isn't even flesh (coming from a living being turned into a portal). 

But both are great and I am glad you enjoyed theirs and ours.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CSS Suggestions Go Here </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 07:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CSS Suggestions go here. 

This is all I have the energy for right now...sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 21:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Effin' cats, man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 21:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We will not reach 7k anytime soon. We are currently losing subscribers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 23:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll delete! Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 21:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorta... but full rejection. Uses his own tech. We finally have the smart Pete we deserve.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 21:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless he rejects Stark. Personally I'd love to see that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 23:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 22:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are. And a super secret private club house sub too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 21:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll make you a MOD at /r/9M9H9E9. 

You don't have to be *here* Sarah.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 19:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> comment replyOnce Upon a Mid-Summer Eve .........
from TheAmericanPharaoh [+2] via /r/DigitalCartel sent 13 minutes ago
show parent
I remove. I don't delete. Most of you will be removed for sure.

There is your answer /u/xvvhiteboy  right [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/DigitalCartel/comments/4xum93/once_upon_a_midsummer_eve/d6ik0ny) as he shows his true colors. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 19:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then why aren't you killing us all? Remove us all, if you have the balls. Delete our posts. Go against your own beliefs again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 19:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I go where my friends are.

You are not a friend. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 19:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh... see. I do like u/Dart200. Despite his meltdown. He is a kid. 

I don't need to speak for anyone. Your actions speak to everyone. 

I can take or leave you Anthony. Your little playground doesn't matter to me, same as you do not matter to me. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Once Upon a Mid-Summer Eve ......... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 19:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All Hell broke loose and ***Digital Cartel -*** ***Dramapalooza of Summer of 2016*** went into full swing with a Coup of the Senior MOD.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 19:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, I already proved I can fuck you up. Everyone here knows it. 

Super simple. I create, you destroy. 

You proved that when you changed the CSS. You have no imagination, you simply bitch and whine and can't create anything, so you envy those who can. 

I'd rather protect and learn from them. It's been a long time since I embraced my creative side. I have MHE to thank for that, not you. Vince encourages me. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 18:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deflector shields at full because you are not part of something and want to play head games with people not in the know. 

Nice. 

Pussy move.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
