<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2997</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 06:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Shit year to be a Jew in Europe, but also the peak year for global Jewish population so far

Those two things seem seem like they're strongly related. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazon, iTunes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 01:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LoT's season finale is on April 4th though, so there's still two weeks where none of them are on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 01:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except that basket interference call was completely correct.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 00:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would guess money </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The only convicted doper in the 2013 top 10 is Valverde

Note that I said

 his main competition consisted mainly of convicted dopers *or people who were riding for convicted dopers*

so  that includes Nibali and Roche (who were riding for Vino and Riis respectively), though I guess technically not Purito since I forgot that Azevedo wasn't running Katusha yet in 2013 and that neither him nor Ekimov had actually been convicted.

 Talking about someone in a comment chain about them is not singling them out

The comment I was initially responding to was 

 everyone in my circles kinda roll the eyes or joke "yeah that vuelta".

which is definitely singling Horner out compared to other Vuelta winners.

 sorry that you stumbled upon a comment chain that hurt your feelings

I'm not Horner, people talking shit about him doesn't hurt my feelings. I'm just trying to understand the seeming double standard between how he's viewed compared with how other dopers are viewed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 08:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not yet, the CBI best-of-three championship starts on Monday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 06:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's telling that's his only top 15 in a GT as well.

[Not quite](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/2010_Tour_de_France). I mean yeah, his Vuelta win is certainly not without suspicion (though he was the only one of the main GC contenders there who was on his first GT of the year), but he's hardly the only sketchy Vuelta winner in recent history. Sure there's a good chance he was doping, but then his main competition consisted mainly of convicted dopers or people who were riding for convicted dopers, so singling him out seems odd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 03:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Gonzaga has miraculously avoided having to play Villanova, Duke, **or Arizona**. 

[Uhhh...](http://www.espn.com/mens-college-basketball/game?gameId=400915547)

And if the likes of Villanova and Duke wanted a shot a taking down Gonzaga, maybe they should have made it past the round of 32. You can only beat the teams you play, and it's not Gonzaga's fault that other 'elite' teams didn't last long enough to meet them in the tourney. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 03:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  AMC is a channel that basically doesn't exist outside of Breaking Bad and Walking Dead.

Longmire was on A E, not AMC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 01:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  it doesn't make sense when they don't include a segment of their own walled gardens in those ratings.

It absolutely makes sense; why would they reveal their own proprietary numbers when they can just cite Nielsen's ratings that are already public? Networks have no incentive whatsoever to reveal all their data when making PR announcements; the reasons they give in public for renewing/cancelling shows need not be the same the as their actual internal reasons for those decisions. 

Again, the idea that networks are making decisions without considering the money they're making from sources besides their linear channel is completely absurd. Network executives don't always make the best decisions but they're certainly not all ignorant dinosaurs who are oblivious to things that are obvious to the average redditor.

  Viewing habits have changed a lot in the decade since it was last seriously looked at, and profits aside, the networks should catch up to those changes.

And how do know they haven't caught up with those changes? 

  What does it hurt at this point to include all legal viewers of their programs in the overall ratings results from Nielsen?

What does it hurt to *not* include all legal viewers of their programs in the overall ratings results from Nielsen, *provided those viewers are still counted*? You're incredibly hung-up on the idea of Nielsen counting certain viewers, when all that really matters is that they are counted. Networks use Nielsen to measure viewership on their linear channel and use other methods to measure viewership on other platforms, and like every other business they don't reveal any more data to the public than is necessary (Netflix and other streaming services don't reveal their numbers to the public, why would you expect networks to reveal their streaming numbers?).

Edit: also, remember that a show's competition for renewal are the other shows on the same network. If one show gets terrible ratings compared to another show on the same network, it's quite likely that its streaming numbers are also terrible compared to the other show. Streaming, DVR, etc, apply to all shows, not just certain ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do views being "ignored, insofar as Nielsen ratings go" matter if they're still being counted? All that ultimately means is that networks use different metrics to sell ads and gauge viewership on their linear channel versus their streaming service. Networks make decisions based on money; if Nielsen ratings are a more important factor than streaming number it's because they're making more money from their linear channel than their streaming service; the idea that networks are just ignoring the money their making from their own streaming service is completely absurd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But you can monetize views that are online

And networks do. Those numbers are just not publicly released so people apparently think that networks don't count them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They are essentially ignoring some of their own viewers

How are they ignoring those viewers? Just because they're not included in Nielsen ratings doesn't mean networks aren't counting those views. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 22:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Barry already looked for him:

 No Cisco Ramon, no Harrison Wells, no Caitlin Snow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 22:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there are any speedsters on Supergirl's Earth they're not operating in public as superheroes. Supergirl was just the second public superhero on her Earth, and E1 Barry was the first speedster people on Supergirl's Earth had encountered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 22:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  grade 3

That terminology is used in some Commonwealth countries (Canada for example) but not Britain itself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The whole season is often shot and edited before any of it airs.

Not for broadcast shows that air in the fall </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 18:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whisky  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 18:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Is this a more recent development in television, or have I just never noticed it before?

It's been like this for decades, so you must just not have noticed it before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 18:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Everyone seems to be waiting for his 2013 Vuelta win to be revealed as doping; everyone in my circles kinda roll the eyes or joke "yeah that vuelta".

Singling out 2013 seems a bit odd when you consider that half of the last 10 Vueltas (including the ones immediately before and after 2013) were won by known dopers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 03:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not the reason (despite how many times it might be repeated on this sub). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 03:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  it doesn't help that Rahul is now going to Supergirl 

Just for a guest spot, and after iZombie had wrapped filming for season 3. It has no affect on his commitment to iZombie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 07:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smallville never saw a significant increase in viewers year-to-year; Supernatural increased its viewers from season 7 to season 9. But Supernatural is the exception, not the norm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 07:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's just Fox being Fox.

This really is the best explanation for many of the things Fox does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 06:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arrow's competition for renewal is the other shows on the CW, so that's the comparison that really matters. While allowances should be made for timeslots and timeslot competition (and other factors like lead-ins) when comparing two shows on the same network, directly comparing Arrow against other networks' shows in its timeslot doesn't mean much. Sure Arrow's timeslot competition from the Big 4 networks typically kick its ass in terms of ratings, but that happens to every CW show so it's pretty much moot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 06:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I think ratings will go back up.

Ratings hardly ever go back up; at this point just hope they don't drop further. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 06:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've both dropped, but Arrow has dropped by a larger percentage:

* Flash: down 21% this season compared to last season (on average), down at most 25% from this season's premiere to the most recent episode (down 29% from season premiere to last week's series low)

* Arrow: down 31% this season compared to last season (on average), down 31% from this season's premiere to the most recent episode (series low). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 06:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  John Barrowman is the most experienced of the lot

Victor Garber was performing on broadway when Barrowman was still a child. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 06:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  can Marvel?

[Marvel already did](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Fpv4g5WgOfo) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 03:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I don't subscribe to Hulu... but I own Buffy on DVD so I'm good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 03:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a hell of a game (Last possession aside) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> H50's ratings are up 5% from last season and Blue Bloods is only own 4%; every other returning scripted show on the network besides NCIS:LA is down by double-digit percentages (as are most returning shows on other networks). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Contador, Valverde, and Purito are notorious for not getting along all that well with each other, so that wouldn't surprise me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kreisberg is one of the creators of the show, along with Berlanti and Adler (check IMDb or wikipedia if you don't believe me). He's been heavily involved since day one; he did a bunch of promotion for the show last year as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kreisberg was heavily involved last season as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazon, iTunes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is not on broadcast TV

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Generally when people quit a show that's pretty much it, they move on and don't come back. So this season being better than last isn't going to reverse the damage that S4 did to the show's ratings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah I get that, and it's and important distinction. I was just clarifying since Live+3 are a class of ratings but they're not what you were actually talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  advertisers only pay for Live+3 (that +3 being people that actually DVR and watch the ads).

That's the C3 ratings. Live+3 ratings count people who skipped ads (and thus are mostly irrelevant). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   it's easier to stream it than to run and catch it live.

This applies to all the shows, so it's a moot point when comparing two CW shows.

 CW tried to salvage it on the assumption that storylines produced by the other three shows can keep viewers interested,

What are basing that off of? None of the storylines on Supergirl this season have come from the other shows. And Supergirl is still performing better than every other CW show besides the Flash.

  Flash needs Arrow because this speedster vs speedster format just isn't working

It's working well enough that Flash remains the most popular show on the CW by a significant margin. Whether you personally like it is moot.

 crossovers are the one thing everyone is hinging on 

Crossovers are like 1-2 episodes a year. If a show can't sustain itself, the crossovers aren't going to save it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well what really matters is how it performs compared to other shows on the CW. For that live ratings are a pretty decent metric, since it's likely that total numbers (i.e. including DVR and streaming) are highly correlated to live numbers among CW shows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If Arrow ends, the platform to which Flash, Supergirl, and LoT are built would shatter and the entire sub-franchise would fall.

You're vastly overestimating the importance of Arrow to the other DC shows. Flash was spun off of Arrow but it doesn't need Arrow. Flash has been significantly more popular than Arrow since it premiered, and the Flash/Arrow crossovers only saw a bump in Arrow's ratings, not Flash's. And Arrow characters could still appear occasionally on Flash even if Arrow were cancelled. Supergirl isn't a spinoff and mostly just interacts with Flash of the other shows; cancelling Arrow wouldn't really affect it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CEG should be safe for a 4th season, the CW doesn't have enough CBS shows to get rid of it just yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its ratings are in the 1.0-1.1 range which is plenty good for Fridays. Plus it seems to be helping CBS's other Friday shows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is not on broadcast TV </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Black Sails isn't on broadcast TV </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The CW has already cancelled two shows this season and is guaranteed to cancel two more (and possibly a third). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It adjusted up to a 1.0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  IIRC, it was announced 1 year ago that number 5 it was Elementary's last season.

It wasn't announced as a final season, [its status is currently in limbo](http://deadline.com/2017/03/elementary-2-broke-girls-criminal-minds-amazing-race-bubble-no-early-renewals-1202049290/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Preliminary unrounded rating is a 0.48, down 0.03 from last week and a new series low. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The vast majority of the article was just about one show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ABC promoted the shit out of WWR. 

But it's still just one show, it flopping in ratings could be for any number of reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 17:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   The last 3 have been 0.56, 0.51 and 0.50 respectively

Technically we don't have the unrounded number for yesterday yet, could be anywhere from 0.45 to 0.55 (but probably on the lower end seeing how total viewers dropped from last week). tvseriesfinale lists them to two decimal places but it's always _._0 to start with, they update with the actual unrounded value the week after.

Edit: preliminary unrounded rating for yesterday is a 0.48 (per RJK on spottedratings) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 17:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A lot of people like to say "ah it's the networks third or fourth most watched show, they won't cancel it". Which is probably true. But the context beyond that is that it's been around for a long time, the budget is likely much higher than most of the other shows, it's surrounded by much more popular shows that are of the same universe, most of the cast are up for contract evaluations next year etc...

Yeah as a more expensive older show it's probably safe while it stays in the top 4 or so spots, but if it slips out of that then it's likely in real danger. Just look at TVD: two years ago it was the 4th-highest rated on the CW, the next year it was pushed to Fridays midseason despite still being around the CW median at the time, then it was renewed but for a shortened and terminal season. At this point I could easily see Arrow following a similar trajectory and ending after a [possibly shortened] 7th season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People bring that up *all the time* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 07:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to Harry there are an infinite number of universes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If not when Barry was first on her Earth last year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 04:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kara has presumably told Barry about Superman, but they haven't met. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 04:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah she specifically asked to not have many singing lines in that episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it doesn't say the country assume it's the US, since this is an American site and Netflix is an American company. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you don't already pay for CBS All-Access, you pay for CBS's main network. Paying a company for one service does not entitle you to all their services. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's had some good form in recent years, just not with much consistency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He just needs to summon his 2014 form </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent news </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  making cord cutting cost just as much, or more, than cable.

If you want all the content why would you expect it to cost much less just because you're accessing it differently? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah they aired on The WB (though Buffy moved to UPN for its last two seasons). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buffy and Angel were both produced by Fox. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Is there anywhere to see these without spending money on buying the whole season?

Not legally </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The ESPN bracket is the same](http://a.espncdn.com/i/ncaa/basketball/ncaatourney17/ncaam_bracket.pdf). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ??

You don't need to be concerned about a network pulling their shows from Netflix to put on their own in-house streaming service if you're in a country where the network doesn't operate. How the US streaming rights to CW shows are handled is a separate issue from the how streaming rights to the shows are handled in other countries. /u/1033149 didn't forget that not everyone is in US, rather the matter being discussed only pertained to US viewers in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The CW doesn't operate outside of the US, international rights are a separate discussion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait so which is it: are you comparing to season 1 of Supergirl or not?

You said Supergirl drop 55% in the demo from 2x01 to 2x16, which I have shown was false. Now Supergirl has dropped 53% on average from season 1 to season 2 (don't know where you got 55%), but I have already addressed why that isn't relevant to the original comment that started this discussion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 08:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DVR is counted. The numbers that matter the most to networks are the C3 and C7 ratings which include all views within 3 and 7 days respectively where the commercials weren't skipped. However these ratings are rarely released to the public, so the closest we usually have to go on are the Live + Same Day ratings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 08:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's nowhere to watch all of season 3 that's legal and free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 07:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's smoking the speed weed, duh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 05:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well Twitter isn't a particularly reliable indicator of viewership; its numbers can be useful but you typically have to dig into them rather than just look at stuff like what's trending (also Twitter has a problem with bots).

I would expect that live and app viewership is pretty strongly correlated among CW shows; Riverdale's position in live ratings of below the DC shows and Supernatural but above everything else is probably about where it is in streaming numbers as well. But what we don't know is what percentage of the CW's total audience watches on the app vs live and how that's changed from last season, which would be key in seeing how the network is doing overall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 05:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, okay, that was disturbing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 05:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They built this up as something amazing akin to the Buffy musical and yet they totally boned it.

Everyone should have known this wasn't going to measure up to *Once More, With Feeling*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 05:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It is almost as if the writers and producers don't ~~think their audience has~~ have critical thinking skills. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well broadcast ratings have been steadily declining for decades so it's natural for most shows to drop and somewhat regularly set new lows. The CW ratings have dropped by more than average this year but it's hard to say exactly why. Could be reversion to the mean after many of their top shows didn't drop that much last year, could be their increased promotion of their app (which for the record is not new) has led to more viewers shifting to streaming; in the case of the DC shows it could be oversaturation of the genre (or of Berlanti's style in particular) causing people to lose interest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Demographics aren't always the most correct and usually give a huge age range.

The demo numbers that get released to the public have a huge age range, but those are just a small fraction of the data Nielsen provides networks; as always the data that really matters isn't just given away for free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But the president of the cw (im pretty sure it was the president) came out and said that sometimes you let award winning tv go on, even though its ratings might not be doing well. 

And the ABC president has repeatedly insisted that Conviction isn't cancelled. Don't take everything network execs say at face value, they're constantly playing the PR game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They do care about critical reception as associating your brand with a toxic tv show isn't a recipe for success.

That matters but only in pretty extreme situations, it's rare for shows to become so toxic that they drives advertisers away.

As for media presence I think you're conflating what networks want and what advertisers want. Networks care about the trajectory and future of individual shows; advertisers get what they paid for even if an individual show tanks. And social media is not an accurate way to measure viewership; it does have useful information for advertisers but at the end of the day prices aren't benchmarked to social media numbers. Meanwhile networks care about it because it's PR for their shows and can provide information they can use to improve/maintain viewership. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  While all businesses want to make money, the CW has been shown to take critical acclaim over the nielsen ratings

Lol you think the CW isn't in this to make money? Yeah they have lower viewership than the big 4, they deal with that by running lower (likely negative) initial margins and having lower-budget shows. And how much they actually value critical acclaim is up for debate; their recent renewals of low-rated but critically acclaimed shows can also be explained by the CBS-WB dynamic of the CW. For example, CEG got renewed for a third season with very low ratings. But cancelling it would mean cancelling 3 of the 4 CBS shows on the network (NT had even worse ratings when not airing behind new Flash episdoes while Reign has equally poor ratings, is presumably more expensive, and has reached the 70-episode threshold that the CW seems to have for its low rated veterans), which CBS would likely not approve of.

As for the rest, that's just your speculation as to what the CW might do in the future, not the situation the CW is currently in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Advertisers care about four main factors, media presence, nielsen ratings, critical reception, and streamed ratings.

Advetisers care about how many people (and which people) are exposed to their ads. When buying commercial time on TV networks they use Nielsen ratings to determine that and thus set the price for the commercial time. The same goes for streaming ads; they pay based on who watches the ad. The show itself is pretty much just a billboard to them, they don't care about other things related to the show like awards, social media, etc (they do care about their own social media presence but that's a separate matter). 

As for No Tomorrow and Frequency, all we the public can do is guess what their streaming numbers were. Now they were likely not very good, but the biggest reason why we can guess that is because we know their live ratings weren't very good and it's reasonable to assume that live and streaming numbers are strongly correlated within shows on the same network.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The CW's situation is not very different from that of the other main broadcast networks (though I will applaud their PR team for convincing people otherwise).

 Unlike major networks that puts Hulu and Netflix above their own streaming services and limits what content is on their streaming service, the CW has a platform that is pretty much "free Hulu".

All the networks have their shows on their own service; how much access they give varies by network but is overly pretty similar:

* CW: Last 5 episodes are available to stream without any login
* Fox: all episodes of current seasons are available to stream, with only the most recent episode sometimes requiring a cable login to watch (varies by show)
* ABC: Last 5 episodes are available to stream, with only the most recent requiring a cable login just for the first week after it originally aired (upon further investigation it looks like for some shows the rest of the current season is available to stream with a cable login)
* NBC: Last 5 episodes are available to stream without login, rest of current season available to stream with cable login (though a few shows don't require this)
* CBS: Last 5 episodes are available to stream without login, rest of current season available to stream with subscription to All-Access.

(These are for streaming from the networks' websites. Cross-referencing with the apps on my 3rd gen Apple TV yields only a few slight differences which go both ways for NBC, ABC, and FOX, while the CBS app is only for All-Access and the CW app isn't available. I'm guessing the apps will vary slightly across other platforms as well)

As for Hulu, it's owned by NBC, FOX, and ABC (30% each, with WB owning the remaining 10%), so those networks selling streaming rights to Hulu is still somewhat in-house. And CBS has it's own subscription streaming service (All-Access).

 Cutting ties with netflix or hulu is something the major networks will not do for the foreseeable future. 

The CW recently ditched Hulu but at the same time strengthened its ties to Netflix. Meanwhile 3 of the big 4 have no reason to cut ties with Hulu because they own it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Episode 2x01 - 1.09 in 18-49 demo

Episode 2x16 - 0.62 in 18-49 demo

(1.09 - 0.62)/1.09 * 100% = **43% drop**

Edit: just for good measure, doing the 18-34 demo as well because the CW cares about that (I don't have unrounded numbers there though)

Episode 2x01 - 0.9 in 18-49 demo

Episode 2x16 - 0.5 in 18-49 demo

44% drop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 02:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Supergirl has dropped by 55% this season.

Compared to last season, when it wasn't a CW show; if we're comparing ratings of CW DC shows that excludes season 1 of Supergirl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 01:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It didn't say "compare this season of Supergirl to *this season of* other CW/DC shows.

But if we're doing that, LoT losing 33% of its demo audience from 2x11 to 2x014 is probably more concerning to the CW than anything Supergirl's ratings have done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 00:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This claim

 SG has lost viewers faster than any other CW/DC show. 

didn't restrict to just this season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 00:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not everyone on this sub still watches the show; it's pretty easy to shitpost and whatnot just by following this sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 00:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nelison ratings aren't for judging overall popularity, they're for pricing the sale of commercials. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 23:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But the recent decade has made that increase more exponential

Disregarding that "more exponential" doesn't really mean anything, the rate at which broadcast ratings have been falling has been pretty consistent.

  Its not the fact they are doing it but that they are put into a unique situation that can dictate the future of the network. 

The CW's situation is by definition not unique if the other networks are in the same situation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 23:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  More over, compare this season of Supergirl to other CW/DC shows and you'll all see that SG has lost viewers faster than any other CW/DC show.

Nope, LoT went from a 1.23 to a 0.59 last season; this season Supergirl has gone from a 1.09 to a 0.62.

 Make no mistake, Supergirl's ratings dropping are a problem.

But it's not a problem specific to Supergirl. All the Berlanti DC shows are down this year (as are nearly all the CW's other shows), and Supergirl's ratings are still higher than every other show on the network besides The Flash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 23:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The unprecedented factor is how now more than ever, the ways in which we can view shows have been increasing. 

The ways in which we can view shows have been increasing for decades, streaming is just the latest evolution of that.

 The CW app is something that is unique in terms that if they play their cards right, they could use to their benefit.

It's not unique if all the networks are doing it, which they are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 23:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  CW does a piss poor job at promoting the show.

The CW airs promos for Supergirl all the time (both on the CW and other networks); it and the other superhero shows are all pretty well-promoted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 23:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Broadcast ratings have been going straight down for decades, this isn't unprecedented.

Also the major networks have their own apps, the CW isn't doing anything unique there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For (1), Kryptonian naming convention is for women to take their father's full name as their last name; that's how it's been in the comics and other media for decades. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still maintain that Zor-Allen is the best name for this ship </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're not surprised, just disappointed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  wonder if many fans will be pissed off this time

Supergirl's viewership went down compared to last week, so I'm guessing not many Flash-only fans bothered with it this time (which makes sense, they weren't heavily promoting it as a crossover like they did last time). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oberyn was handily beating the Mountain in that match but blew it because he was more focused on getting the Mountain to confess than just killing him. I'm assuming that in this it'll be a straight fight without the extra baggage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "is a *lesbian* cop" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 08:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course, but it would still be worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 08:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP specified Trial by Combat Rules, so per Beric's own interpretation of those killing him once is sufficient to win even if he's revived immediately after.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 08:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oberyn could beat her but it would take him both hands to do it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
