<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3787</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 23:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes months.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's some of my artwork. I LIVE to make art. Let me know what you think. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 22:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 22:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took his art camp one summer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 22:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 22:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way we've done it is that we've built up to a climax and then right about the peek after having already been having sex, we've both taken a big hit of dmt. The experience is extraordinary. It amplifies the sensation dramatically. I have lost my erection almost every time but it is still a powerful physical sensation. The experience has been totally physical, instead of visual. She has said that these experiences have been the most powerful sexual experiences of her life. We have also done this with oral sex alone, with me on her, and her on me. I'll wait to describe our individual experiences in greater depth and see if she'll want to contribute as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 22:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's something I discovered through my interest in Robert Venosa's work and he learned it from the great Max Ernst. You can do it by rubbing sheets of plastic or saran wrap on thin wet paint.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 22:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://subject3787.bigcartel.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 22:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 24x36 inches. The heart is done with mischetechnique, hatching white over glazes of oil color.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 21:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll check it out, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 21:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tool is one of my favorite bands ever, what can I say? ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 21:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love psytrance and I'm not ashamed to say it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 21:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not Miley Cirus btw but my friend Shelby who is a painter and fashion designer and modeled live for that portrait. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 21:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Tool. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 21:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I think it's pretty common to have an artists picture at the top of an article about them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 21:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of it is through a process called pareidolia where I create random stains or patterns (through a process called decalcomania) and then look at it and paint in what I see. It's a bit like a Rorshach test. Anyone can do it and its a great way to free up creativity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 21:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not in Vienna but I've taken workshops with Andrew 4 or 5 times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 21:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's cool, I appreciate it. Ultimately I'm doing the best I can and trusting in my own taste even if it doesn't appeal to everyone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 21:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ozora because it was small and chill. My girlfriend got really sick at Boom so we couldn't have much fun together. It was also really hot and getting there literally right after Ozora was a bit of a drag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 21:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hung out with my girlfriend naked in Sasha's Shulgins' lab once. There is pictorial evidence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 21:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've taken pretty much everything in both the tryptamine and phenylethamine form. I've drinken ayahuasca and smoked dmt many times and they've been important experiences for me. Ultimately though my real spiritual practice is just living life. The dmt state shows me about the workings of perception, that beneath it all there is the timeless witness, consciousness. And that's all I can say for certain, that there is experience, that something is going on right now. I'm not really on so much anymore about getting to some really high state or getting some kind of clear message, I'm more about resting in the uncertainty of it all, taking what life gives me, and rolling with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 21:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've drinken ayahuasca and smoked dmt many times and they've been important experiences for me. Ultimately though my real spiritual practice is just living life. The dmt state shows me about the workings of perception, that beneath it all there is the timeless witness, consciousness. And that's all I can say for certain, that there is experience, that something is going on right now. I'm not really on so much anymore about getting to some really high state or getting some kind of clear message, I'm more about resting in the uncertainty of it all, taking what life gives me, and rolling with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 21:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I've made cover art for Mumukshu, Numinous, Obsidian Tongue, Beat Conscious, Neuroceptor, Sixx, and a few others.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 21:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://instagram.com/subject3787 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 21:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Patience, practice, and dedication.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 21:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did you think of the non digital work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 21:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went last year! It was great. If you look up the RadiOzora soundcloud there is an interview that I did with them on there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 11:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently in San Francisco, CA - born here too - but a bit nomatic. So many influences but I love Ernst Fuchs, Odd Nerdrum, Beksinski, Alex Grey, and Robert Venosa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 09:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have some friends that teach great painting workshops in Colorado. Look them up: David Heskin, Philip Rubinov Jacobson, and Amanda Sage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 09:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bi-girls are crazy about me. ;)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
