<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1811</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 18:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a fus ro dah version? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drunk arab sneezes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 10:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 09:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, good, yes yes yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 08:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately it's big 2 only..  



I'm sorry, but I'm depressed right now... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drunk men try to bring stump home </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 16:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stephen Curry Tries To Bear Hug LeBron James, but LeBron Has None Of It </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 14:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drunk woman fell in shit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 18:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 14:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But did it dieded? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 19:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bon appetit at the end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 09:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That laugh tho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 09:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Daamn, that's nasty! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This 3D glasses question on Amazon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 13:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whys is the rum gone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 11:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 10:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget your camera's crop factor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 10:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jfigg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 20:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What it's like when the beat is about to drop.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 18:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I explained this to other guy, and since you asked similar question I'll copy paste.

**Light Frames**  
Are the images that contains the real information: images of galaxies, nebula...
This is what you want to stack.  

**Dark frames**  
Removes dark signal from your image (stuff you don't want to see) it's easy to take dark frames. After you take your light frames (the object you were photographing) put the lens cap on the lens and shoot between 15 or 100 images with the same settings, don't change nothing, don't move your setup, shoot in the same place right after your light frames, because temperature is important for dark frames.  

**Bias/Offset frames**  
I'm not sure if they really improve the quality of the final image that much, but they also remove some stuff that shouldn't be there, also you don't have to take them after each set, you can take them once and use them for half a year or so, of course the ISO is important for those frames and let's say if you take light frames with 1600 ISO one day and you only have Bias frames that are 800 ISO, you then have to create library for Bias frames, if you are changing the ISO frequently you should have Bias frame library that you can choose from to match the ISO of your light frames. To take Bias frames is very easy, temperature is not important, put the lens cap on, change your shutter speed to fastest possible (1/4000s, 1/8000s) and shoot between 15 and 100 of them.  

**Flat frames**   
I'm a beginner too so I haven't figured out the proper way how to take flats, but from what I read is that you drape a clean white t-shirt over your lens and shine a flashlight perpendicular to the lens, of course not too close to the lens, and you take also between 15 and 100 of them. The flat frames should be created with the ISO speed of the light frames. The temperature is not important, and shoot in Av mode.  

P.S. If you have taken 20 light frames and you then take 100 dark frames that doesn't make sense so, take less of those frames than your lights. Of course if you take 500 lights you can take 200-400 darks if you have time ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 11:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I curious how fast they were going? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 16:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can shake my eyeballs fast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 15:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is possible with the 200mm you just have to take a lot of images of the object and then stack them in Deep sky stacker, remember the rule of 500 (500/your focal length = maximum exposure of your image without visible star trails) also keep in mind your camera's crop factor, for my camera it's 1.6x so it would be 500/(2001.6)
And if you want better image quality you also need to take dark, flat and bias frames. If you have questions please ask.  
Edit: if you want longer exposures of your images you can try increasing the rule to maybe 550 or 600 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 15:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to know what it is as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 08:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you achieve 4 point stars? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 08:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not important at all to maintain the alignment, you just have to keep what you want to see in frame, for example deep sky object moves a bit after several shots, I adjust the angle of the camera a bit, take more shots, adjust again, so it's not important at all, the deep sky stacker will automatically align and stack your images. Of course if you have a stationary foreground in your image (city, mountains, some landscape) the deep sky stacker will mess it up, and you have to manually take that foreground shot and later add it to your post processed sky image. And my advice is to not process the image in the DSS after it has been stacked, when it's done stacking just save the image to .tif integer 32-bit and you're good to go to other processing programs (I usually first go to Photoshop and then later to lightroom). Hope that helps. If you have more questions please ask. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 19:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Canon 70D + Tamron 70-300mm @ 300mm + 1.6x crop factor = 480mm + tripod  
300x1s lights @ f5.6 ISO 3200 (5min)  
100x1s darks @ f5.6 ISO 3200  
95x1/8000s Offset/Bias  

Stacked with DSS, Processed with photoshop and lightroom (levels, curves, histogram, color balance, vibrance, saturation, highlights, shadows, etc..)

[TIF Link](https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B9y8ylhe9rpoNXh5ZFIxYnRkZ00/view?usp=sharing)  
I would love to see how other people would process my image differently and what results they'd achieve, if you are willing to help me improve my post processing, please describe briefly what steps you went through processing the image. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First attempt at M45 Pleiades, your processed image is more than welcome </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 19:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 19:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm new to astrophotography too, but I think your exposure time is a little bit too long, generally you want to have rule of 500 in mind (500/focal length=longest exposure of your image without experiencing star trails) also keep in mind your camera's crop factor, if it has one, my example is I often shoot at 300mm and my camera crop factor is 1.6x so that's 480mm focal length 500/480= roughly 1s maximum of exposure for single image. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stop comparing them and just accept the greatness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 00:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 17:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the answer, so what I understood, that it is best to take darks and flats after each **set**, but I still don't know the proper way how to take flats. What I read is that you drape a clean white t-shirt on the lens and shine a flashlight, if so, how far should a flashlight be from the lens? And does the light need to be perpendicular to the lens?  
Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 13:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I stack images from two different days? Also will the dark frames be good from the first day for the second, or do I need to take dark frames after each set of lights </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 07:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome man, I'm still trying to figure out what's the best way to process an image, anyways, thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 22:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, I would love to see how other people would process my image  
[TIF Link](https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B9y8ylhe9rpoT1BwdmU0YXFRMTg/view?usp=sharing) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 21:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very cool image, how did you achieve such a good color and black sky background contrast, and how did you remove the noise considering you shot at 12800 iso </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 21:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Canon 70D + Tamron 70-300mm @ 300mm + 1.6x crop factor = 480mm + tripod  
360x1s lights @ f5.6 ISO 3200 (6min)  
100x1s darks @ f5.6 ISO 3200  
95x1/8000s Offset/Bias  

Stacked with DSS, Processed with photoshop and lightroom (levels, curves, histogram, color balance, vibrance, saturation, highlights, shadows, etc..)  

Edit: [Unedited TIF Link](https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B9y8ylhe9rpoT1BwdmU0YXFRMTg/view?usp=sharing) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I know it's posted a lot, but here's my first attempt at orion nebula </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 21:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 22:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's about 5ft 3/4" of bananas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 15:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stolen video </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 15:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stupid brains... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 07:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You win!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 12:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. How many dark frames for a DSLR on a tripod?  

2. How many bias frames for a DSLR on a tripod?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 08:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need this camera ASAP! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 12:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never really laugh that much on reddit, but this has to be the funniest and truest thing I've ever seen here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 20:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow you're fast! I guess I'm really bad at math :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 20:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes you are right, but in this case I calculated the observable universe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 20:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this is not a composition of 2 photos, how did that person managed to stay perfectly still for 30 seconds? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I may be wrong, but I did some calculations and compared how far the Voyager 1 has gone from earth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 20:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If earth is the whole universe and you are Voyager 1, then it's equivalent of walking roughly 3 meters from your house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 17:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Guys what do you think would be possible with this equipment?**  

[Opteka 650mm-1300mm + 2x converter + Canon x1.6 crop factor = 4160mm](http://www.amazon.co.uk/Opteka-650-2600mm-Definition-Telephoto-Digital/dp/B001NMR23M/ref=sr_1_9?ie=UTF8 qid=1449741564 sr=8-9 keywords=opteka+for+canon)  
And a tripod of course  
I guess the f16 would be really bad... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 16:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **1.** Is it true that you only need to take bias frames once or twice a year?  


**2.** What shutter speed for flat frames? In one place I read 0.5 to 2.5s, in other place it said 1/80s is good, so what's the ideal speed?  


**3.** After stacking images in DSS I get the red hue image, do I process it in the program right away or do I save the image and go on to CS6 or Lightroom? And then how do I remove that red hue, how do I know what is the right color/temperature for the picture?  


**4.** What kind of adjustments should I do in photoshop or lightroom? How you usually adjust your image after stacking it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 19:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah ISO really high even for a Canon,  maybe he meant 1200 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 08:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [How is this not mentioned?](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g__xyd9v2tc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 08:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG!!! Yes it is!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 08:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm late, is there any way I can rewatch it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 08:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I'm kind of a Lebron fan, more than I am a specific team fan, I don't care on what team he's on I just want him to be successful, I'm not from US btw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 15:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I may be weird, but I really don't want them to break LeBron's 27 game winning streak.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 14:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great pic.  
[This is my first attempt](http://i.imgur.com/m9HSYt9.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 10:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> de_rats2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 08:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Also, would you be able to share your RAW files for this image? I'd see what I can do with them.  

Sure, I've included this picture files and my try on Pleiades  
[link](https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B9y8ylhe9rpoVjA2dTV4NnNqbk0/view)  

I'm really curious about those star trails at 1s exposure. I may have an idea what may cause it. I found an article that says IS may cause moving objects to blur, here's an extract:  
Before getting into the nitty-gritty of the subject, its important to clarify a common misconception about image stabilization, which is that it enables you to freeze fast-moving objects at slower shutter speeds. This is totally false. Image stabilization only allows you the ability to capture sharp images of static subjects at slower speeds. Moving objects will be equally blurry or streakyand in some casesblurrier or shakierwith the IS turned on.  

And the other idea would be to weigh down some weight on the tripod hook. So yeah, learning every day.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 20:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Are you using remote shutter?    

Kind of, I connect my smartphone with the EOS remote app.  
Also why when I save my image after stacking in DSS it comes out all red, and it is way less sharp than what I could squeeze out of one image in lightroom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 19:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for giving such an insight.  
I still have a lot to learn, I still don't fully understand what are those dark, flat, light, offset/bias files and how to take them, I know that they are important to the quality. As you said, I did a mistake by first processing all the images in lightroom, then stacked them in DSS.  
Also I recently tried to capture Pleiades at 300mm and I could only get the stars with no trails at 1/10s I think my tripod is sturdy enough and I'm shooting from my home window so there is no high wind.  
And I wanted to know what is your process of processing the exposures? Do you first stack them in DSS or you use some other program? Do you then process the result image in lightroom or photoshop?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 14:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I know about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 14:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And one more question.  
Am I right about this?  
The longer the exposure of the object the better image is going to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 11:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing that brightest dot is the orion nebula right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guys what do you think would be possible with this equipment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 11:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 10:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, amazing, I wish I could photograph in such a quality one day... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 10:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm very new to astrophotography, I only have Canon 70D, 18-55mm kit lens, Tamron SP 70-300mm f/4-5.6 Di VC USD lens and a tripod, is there anything interesting in the sky that I could photograph with this equipment. I need as much knowledge from you guys as I can get. How could I improve my astrophotography. Right now I'm not planning on buying any telescopes or EQ mounts, I want to know what I could get out of my current equipment. Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 10:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Camera: Canon 70D  
Lens: 18-55mm kit lens @ 55mm f5.6 ISO 1000  
Exposure: 20x4s  
Processed in Lightroom and Photoshop CS6  
Stacked in DeepSkyStacker  
[Uncompressed image link](http://www86.zippyshare.com/v/lr0RVklj/file.html
) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My first ever attempt at anything </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 10:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 09:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you took those images without moving the tripod nor the camera?
And then you aligned and stacked them right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 20:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you track the object in the sky? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 08:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just watched the latest episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 10:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CLOAK ENGAGED </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That's it I'm done with this show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 08:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With each episode this show has gone more and more stupid, the characters are the most annoying part of the show, Carol the most annoying stupid little fucker in this show, I waited so many episodes for someone to shut her ass up and she kept getting more crazy, Tandy the most pretentious annoying idiot who can't be himself, it's like he follows the stupidity from Carol, always trying to be more disturbing to everyone, Melissa, arrogant, ignorant, contributes no value to the show, the other characters are only passive to the show. The only character that has any value and is somewhat reasonable and interesting is Todd, honest, genuine person.   

I don't really understand what people love about this show, it continuosly gets more and more frustrating to watch, the characters are dumb as f*ck and it gets worse and worse with every episode.
I only started to watch this show because how interesting and good the first few episodes were, then it somehow progressively got boring and predictable...  

I really feel like I'm the only person in this sub who sees this show the way it is and I hope I'm not the only one in the world who sees it such way...  

The downvotes are fine, as long as I express my opinion on the internet.  

Bye bye show, On to the next one.  

Edit: **Haha so butthurt for a mediocre show..** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ricchi e Poveri - Bello l'amore [Pop] (1981) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 19:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 17:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are more balls in the world than men </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 17:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to see how it ends </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remote tribe in Papua New Guinea meets white man for the first time in their lives </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 17:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 14:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Focus, fire a gun, we need someone to lean on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 19:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always wondered what they do after dropping, do they just lie there all day? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 19:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't there a 8 sec violation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 17:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Humans are explorers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 17:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Bob Marley, it just lifts my spirit up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 11:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a subreddit for these types of gif recipes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 18:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't, I have a phobia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guy escapes from prison by pretending to be a jogger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 10:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 18:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That has to be a winner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 07:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously wtf is wrong with this team........... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 15:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [You forgot to add this](https://youtu.be/DuT9GqUzJLY) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 12:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No he's not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 07:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=azIh8gsXVRg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 16:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This is the best and most genuine footage of grey alien available](https://youtu.be/d_uqAZW5YF0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 14:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bob Marley  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 12:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously? No Walking Dead mentioned? SERIOUSLY?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 12:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually there are tons of material on the internet, youtube videos of people sharing their experiences, articles on various websites, etc..  
To me the most interesting ones to watch are atheist experiences when they go back to their bodies having experienced NDE and realizing they were wrong about themselves.  
If you're interested here's couple to start off.  
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oRk9_dK7Quo  
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=V-GHrsSqcNw  
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=q3adbayvKWA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 10:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to be short, just because I know, what I would say, would mean nothing to you.  

Blind woman goes to surgery, dies, leaves body, sees everything, colors, instruments, herself, table, doctors, when came back to her body she's frightened, because she saw first time in her life, and she told doctors everything she saw, what exactly they were doing to her, how things looked, and where they were. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 20:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Bob Marley - Stir it up](https://youtu.be/bKbqrKtoTY0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 15:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I've seen too many NDE's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 13:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds crazy, but even Kim Jong Un is loved by Jesus, Jesus loves every person.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just found this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 17:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 17:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would suggest to buy a rare golden coin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 17:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm shy and I have social anxiety, I would be really nervous if a girl approached to me.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 16:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fleshlight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 16:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Become the president of the United States  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 16:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was the best thing I've ever saw in a while, Klove so funny haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 13:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest, I'd rather have the greatest 3-pt shooter of all time on our team than Joe Harris..  
Just my opinion.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you think Ray Allen is possible to have on our team? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 07:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that he appeared in the Uncle Drew movie, it got me really interested if he's planning to do something in this city, I would really love to have him on our team, such a great guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 11:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saying there's no other life in the universe it's the same thing as taking a tea spoon of water from the ocean and saying there's no whales in the ocean.  

Edit: Sorry for not reading the title entirely, this is not inappropriate, but gets my point perfectly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two crackheads decide to sit on a crossing, didn't go well for them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 21:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buddy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 17:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 14:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this a thing now?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 10:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relax, it's just a meteor.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 20:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [You stupid](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=t97R3jxbl6E) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 16:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's sad that I have to deal with this thing too, but I get up in the morning and download the game without watching the news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 19:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading out loud in class, I have a really bad phobia of that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 17:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry guys, he's wearing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 14:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's an after life, it's just difficult for  people who live their lives based on what scientists know about us and our universe to understand that there might be some other place, some other dimension or spirutual existence that hasn't been discovered or observed. If there's no evidence for something, that doesn't mean you have to immediately disprove it, sometimes you just have to believe it no matter when most of the society is telling you not to because the scientists don't know about it. What do you loose by believing something unearthly, nothing, and you dont know what you might loose when you die, so believing in higher power costs you nothing.  
  
I'm okay with downvotes, it's all good as long as I share my opinion on the internet. People will eventually start to think differently about God and after life in the near future as we will start to discover and study our spiritual sides. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The chair appeared out of nowhere </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 21:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 21:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [High quality, for phones](http://i.imgur.com/PHSHqA5.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 17:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [He's enjoying it](http://i.imgur.com/G6ZoIBD.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 18:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trotl trotl trotl, long long, power power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 07:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why all the 360 videos have such a bad quality? Just asking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 07:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snoop dogg? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have no words to describe this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 09:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cruise ship seven nation army </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 09:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 14:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect loops.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quick few questions about the console </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 18:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Can I store my videos, music in PS4 hard drive?  
2. Can PS4 play 4K video? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 11:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This is better](https://youtu.be/EZ7Fjsr6Ebk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am completely new in the console world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 09:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never had a console, never really played on a console, well maybe few times, I've always been the PC guy, I always played games on the mid-end PC. The reason I've never been in to consoles is because I've never had the money to buy it, or if I had, there were more important things for me to buy. And now the time has come for me to finally buy the frickin' console and I decided to go with PS4, but now I'm considering about the games, should I buy discs or digital? One reason I don't want to buy discs is because I would have to insert them every time I want to play a game, on the other hand what I heard about the digital version is that some accounts are getting banned for no reason, so I'm kind of stuck between two options.  
Can you help me decide?

**Edit:** It is done, I just bought PS4 Ultimate Player 1TB edition and couple of games (GTA V and NBA 2K16) (physical)  

A few more questions came in to mind.  
**1.** Will I be able to store my videos, music in PS4 hard drive?  
**2.** Can PS4 play 4K videos? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 08:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's spinning wheels </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 06:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the hell happened?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 21:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pirate bay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
