<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject366</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 15:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can get the surface quality up to the level of nJoy toys there might be a chance.  My advice would be to first find a single shape that really resonates with people, get the surface finish up to the highest standards, and contact me.  My email is tom at priveco dot com.  
Here is a link to the 6 nJoy pieces we sell.  The photos are not manipulated either.  We shoot them in house and their finish is THAT GOOD.
http://www.vibrators.com/nsearch.html?catalog=vibrators-dot-com x=0 y=0 query=njoy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 15:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't sell cat food, yarn balls, litter boxes, or that sort of thing.  Do you think that the cats could live on edible lubricant and play with a feather tickler? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 06:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few important things:
1.  We have never had an email newsletter.  Never.  So once you shop with us we just ship your parcel and then never bother you again.  I think that is the most important thing.  
2.  We do all of our own shipping in house.  Other sex toy stores use drop shippers and thus share your information.  We keep all of your data under one roof where I can be sure it is confidential. 
3.  We use plain brown shipping boxes and ultra secure tape (but a lot of sites do that).
4.  We offer a service called Double Layer privacy.  For $0.99 more we heat seal the contents of your order in a black plastic bag and then put that inside your secure package.  That way if someone gets nosey and opens the box, they still won't know what is up.  
5.  We make shopping on the site quick and easy.  We filter through all of the products in our industry and only sell the best, that way you can shop quickly and be sure that you'll get a great product.  

Here's a little video that sums it all up.  BTW our company is called subject366 (like private and company squashed together).  It is a big focus for us.  
http://www.vibrators.com/adques.html

Thanks for asking.  If anything, the privacy of the site is my life's work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 06:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vibrators.com really isn't the place for those consumers.  We are sort of a friendly, understandable shop for women.  Our customers don't seem as interested in size as they are power.  

Here is an example of a HUGE vibrator.  It is called the Great American Challenge (people have posted about it on REDDIT before)  http://www.vibrators.com/world-s-biggest-vibrator.html  We sold only around 50 of them last year.  

This is our most slender vibrator.  It is barely thicker than a AA battery and was designed to be as slim as possible.  We sold hundreds of these.  http://www.vibrators.com/oasis-intimates-slim-vibe.html

Our customers like powerful toys though regardless of the toy's size they like power.  The best way to predict if a toy is going to be successful on our site is to measure how strongly it vibrates, so we do.  .  We sell a bunch of Hitachi Magic Wands and Sybians which are really, really powerful.

Great question.  I'm glad you asked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 05:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over the years people have introduced some really strange products into our industry.  I have to admit that some of the folks in the sex toys business are a bit weird (probably myself included) but these products seem to really take weird to a whole new level.  Here is a short list:

Beer Flavored Lubricant - Yup, personal lubricant that was flavored like different kind of beer.  It smelled an tasted like the morning after a frat party.  Ick!  Here's a photo from Flickr http://www.flickr.com/photos/thebookpolice/3265291763/

Hommemystere - Women's underwear for men.  The website is priceless:  http://hommemystere.com/

The Cock Pipe - A device that contains burning stuff that you strap to your penis.  http://cockpipe.xxx/

A stripper shoe with a pocket pussy build into the platform, and all sorts of other stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 05:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone in the office once said "I've measured so many dongs that if a flasher every exposed himself to me I could tell the cops "It was 6 3/8" long with a circumference of 2.75"". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 05:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People in the office were talking about this product today.  It's supposed to boost your testosterone.  http://www.shopinprivate.com/on-testosterone-cream.html

We are looking to find the next pill.  So far we have only found duds.  In the 14 years I've been selling these items, there have been a number of FDA crackdowns on different pills.  What happens is that after the crackdown all of the pills stop working for a while, then a few months later they will suddenly and mysteriously start becoming more effective.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 05:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We used to offer a "no invoice" service but not for that reason.  It was popular among international customers so that they could avoid paying import taxes on the merchandise they ordered.  

Eventually we stopped when we realized that people could use it for the wrong reason.  It got too murky for us.  Sending anonymous sex toys to people seemed a little too close to harrassment.  

We want to offer a really private service and we offer a few things that no one else offers, but that process had to stop.  Here is one thing we do to ensure privacy.  It's called Double Layer Privacy and we invented in our company.  http://www.vibrators.com/ulprivdel.html

Thats me in the videos (the dude).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 05:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One thing that sometimes brightens my day is that our lead customer service guy sits outside my office and I can hear what he says if I pay attention.  He is quite charming in a sorta blunt way that I enjoy.  One day he was talking to someone and he said.  "Well, technically its not the largest vibrator, we have others but that is the largest one a human being would use."  That cracked me up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 05:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup.  Unfortunately, they usually work by cheating.  Although the package will usually say they contain things like Ginseng or Ginger root, the companies that make them "spike" them with synthetic ingredients like generic viagra.  Here is a recent FDA notice about a pill called Rock It Man.  The FDA visited our office over it.  They wanted to know who made it and how to contact them.  We cooperated with the process and had to destroy our inventory of the pills.  http://www.fda.gov/Drugs/ResourcesForYou/Consumers/BuyingUsingMedicineSafely/MedicationHealthFraud/ucm344806.htm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 05:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We sell a bunch of different anal bleaching creams on ShopInPrivate.com and the reviews are positive.  The same products have been used to treat liver-spots and skin blemishes for decades.  

Are they safe?  Many of the products use Hydroquinone, which the FDA says is OK but some European countries do not allow.  If you want to avoid Hydroquinone, this is the best choice:
http://www.shopinprivate.com/dr-pinks-anal-bleaching-cream.html
The same product is sold in "spa packaging" under the name Biofade and made by the same company but if you buy the Biofade brand it costs $20 more.  Check it out here: http://www.shopinprivate.com/biofade-anal-nipple-vulva-bleach.html  

I'm happy to answer the question, but I think I just outed myself as an expert on anal bleaching creams.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 04:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People say funny things to me to:  I worked a trade show where our company was looking for partner websites where we could advertise. While speaking to one group of women, I mentioned that I run Bachelorette.com, ShopInPrivate.com and I said "I also run Vibrators.com, I guess someone has to, at least I do so professionally." to which one of the women said "I thought you'd be shorter." Ha ha ha... That cracked me up because I'm not tall, but I might be the tallest person in my industry.  All of the guys are vertically challenged.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 04:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of the humor in our office is word play.  A few weeks ago were were testing out boner pills to see if they actually do anything.  We were looking for volunteer employees to try them at home.  One guy said "I'm petrified of those things" to which another person said "My wood is petrified from these things."  I love working here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 04:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny Stories:
I apologize that these will be responses to questions that no one has asked but I'm sitting here in my office with nothing to do.  I'll post them as replies to this message.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 04:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are very welcome.  I've read a few of these where it seemed a little sketchy.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 04:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a small one, so you are correct, better for a beginner.  It is a strapless strap-on.  It is worn internally by the woman and she can thrust with it that way.  You can also use it manually if you want.  Another good choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 04:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I may have misinterpreted the question, if you were looking for something that the woman can use to penetrate a man, we have those too.  They are called "strap-ons" and we have sorted through a bunch of them to find the best.  This is a great choice as it vibrates strongly, fits securely, and is priced modestly.  http://www.vibrators.com/love-rider-strap-on-system.html

By the way, the process of a woman penetrating a man with a strap-on is called "Pegging".   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 04:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has a badass locking function which can be used to either ensure it doesn't start vibrating in your luggage or to make sure it doesn't inadvertently wake you up from your "victory slumber" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 04:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are lots of sex toys for couples.  I think I remember seeing a study that said 30-40% of sex toy use was done with a partner.  Typically the toy is worn by the man to turn him into a vibrator, but there are other options.  The We-Vibe is a vibrator that a woman wears both internally and externally (half of it goes inside, the other half rests upon her pubic bone) and is enjoyed by both partners.  

The company that makes it has been making continuous improvements over the last few years and version 3 is pretty awesome.  It includes a remote control so that she can get what she wants and then turn off the power when the task is complete.  It is here:  http://www.vibrators.com/we-vibe.html

If the price is a little steep, you should try a vibrating penis ring.  Cock rings make your erection harder and last longer and the vibration turns your penis into a vibrator.  Here is a good one to start with:  http://www.vibrators.com/mg017.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 04:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't mess around, I use this:  http://www.vibrators.com/lelo-bo-vibrating-ring.html
If a woman is going to use something that is vibrating for her pleasure, I'm going to make sure it is me.  You would too if you were a straight male.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 04:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> High end products are usually made from silicone of which their are different grades.  Platinum-grade and medical-grade are terms that are thrown around a lot.  High end products tend to be rechargeable and rechargeable vibrators are usually quieter too.  This is because much of the sound a vibrator makes is from the batteries shaking around inside them.  Higher end products can be more powerful, but some are not. Nicer vibrators can be splashproof or even submergible. These are all things customers like.   Finally, as price increases so do the amount of luxury touches, many high end toys come in boxes that resemble iphone packaging with nice inner partitions and materials.  It is not uncommon for people to spend $150-$250 on a sex toy.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 04:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> California buys the most toys but it buys the most everything.  Let me answer the question you really want to ask.  What states buy the most toys per capita?  For us it is Colorado, but at times Utah shows up!  I'd like to know if anyone has any theories on that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 03:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted to become an automotive engineer, which I eventually did.  I actually loved the automotive business, but one day I started this weird company...  It's been a strange ride.  I never would have suspected it and I doubt anyone who knew me when I was a teenager would have either.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
