<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2423</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 07:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #**IS THIS NOT THE DEFINITION OF NOSTALGIA?!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 06:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pepperidge Farm remembers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 06:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's about the size of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 05:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your not the target demographic. I bet Cosmo and Wanda annoyed the shit out of people 15 years your senior when they first popped up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 05:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I did.

Stealth only requires the use of the drones. You can literally sit behind a wall outside the base and use the drone to do a recon, then drive the "COME AT ME BRO!" RC car and download things in most cases. It's not hard, and most times you won't be detected by the dumb AI. It's like playing in god mode, how easy it is. If you have to go in, the stun gun has ridiculous range, so whatever stragglers remain can be easily picked off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 03:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This appeals to me because I am an adult who used to watch these tv shows, except for the two furries, and I am now reminded of a simpler time when cartoon breasts gave me a prepubescent stiffy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 03:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I quit watching a month ago. Damn, looks like I missed the titular Taboo in action by that much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 02:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This game is too easy with those stupid drones. No risk, all reward, makes Jack a dull boy.

Also, the story blows. There's no real reason for these annoying characters to be doing this shit other than their "fuck the system" mantra. I never felt invested in their stories. Also the final mission is weak.

And back to those shitty memelord characters gah, fuck them, especially Wrench and his shitty fucking mask.

I'd say it's even more half assed than the first one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 02:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think she will win t either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 02:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand? What's up with musicians and this show? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 02:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did he finally fuck his sister? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 02:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the kind of deal Walter White should have worked out, except with whatever game was hot back when the show is set. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 01:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Suicide Squad. 

They all should have died instead of mechanically lumber toward success.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 01:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's from the Skleero arc where the X-Men visit an ancient island by Costa Rica and a new mutant transfigures the shape of Colossus' face. It's an older arc, but it checks out all right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 01:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/subredditsashashtags </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 01:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No he's not. I believe he's taking the minimum he has to take for an appearance there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 18:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, all figures I have on that body have an issue with the gummy joints. Daredevil, Deadpool,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 05:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should watch Game of Thrones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 04:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe the first one in The Flash's first season Blu-Ray didn't include the Arrow half, but the second season did include the Arrow half, because otherwise it wouldn't make sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 04:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. I haven't got much faith in his new one. The one where Ryan Gosling will actually be playing a literal mute.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 04:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yes, Refn's only good film.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 04:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It looks like some shitty Ubisoft basic bitch game."

-r/PS4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 23:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [That's a recipe for death.](http://www.livescience.com/41839-gamers-thrombosis.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 23:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the world feels REALLY empty.

Maybe cuz everything disappears all the time. Cars, NPCs, Cops! Freaking cops! Sometimes I can't start up a decent fire fight cuz no cops will spawn! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like they made every character a different aspect of r/funny. I fucking hated them. Especially goddamn Wrench with his fucking shitty mask. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who is your daddy and what does he do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 06:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think of all the passive aggressive lyrics we would get though. And the passive aggressive guitar one upsmanship. So dope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 05:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At long last Connie Britton's free to work on actual good shows again! 

I can't help but think that she was ecstatic when ABC cancelled this shit show, and then bummed the fuck out when shitty network, CMT, picked it up for another season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 04:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, which is why I prefaced with "I know it wasn't." I watched those earlier seasons as a teenager so the societal issues at the time where lost on me, besides 9/11 and terrorism. This probably wouldn't have bothered me as much if we had a different President, cuz they probably wouldn't be pushing a blatantly bigoted agenda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 02:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :')

That is all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 02:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it wasn't, but this season feels like it was tailor made to play into Trumps anti-Muslim ban. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 01:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say you're about to piss off the majority of this sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 01:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> May gosh have mercy on your collection  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 00:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are all owners of this cyclops on this blessed day. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did you do to piss her off an make her threaten you like this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 05:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even that would still be PG-13. Only way they'd get an R for that is if we see some blood and gore.

 I really don't see Sony releasing an R rated Uncharted. It's very likely that they'll cut it to PG-13 anyway. Sony's film division desperately needs the money.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 05:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joe Carnahan is the writer not the director.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 05:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cold blooded! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 05:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/phillyman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't buy them when they first release, they get price drops pretty quick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 01:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aces! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 23:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe heat them up with hot water, and then cool them down with cold water? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess it's biased if you don't think that spreading hate and harassing people online is shitty thing to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being an all around asshole who "joked" about pedophillia being a-okay in his book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 05:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just pics of the boxes, no figures mandatory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 04:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He'll die 20 minutes into the movie, and Millie Bobby Brown's dull older brother will save the day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 04:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just graduated last December, from what I could tell my peers never stopped being pretentious. NEVER. A contributing reason to why I wasn't very open in class. Too interested in being the next Tarantino or coming up with edgy, and "deep" ideas or liking weird shit like Berberian Sound Studio, cuz it's not a mainstream blockbuster.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen some of his videos and the dude complains about some of the strangest things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [niggas creepin](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Kp7eSUU9oy8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 21:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mario Kart 8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 21:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the problem? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 20:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only stuff that interests me on the Marvel Legends front is the MJ/ANAD Spider-Man pack, the two Fantastic 4 figures, and depending on what's included the Phoenix/Bald Head Cyclops pack. Those, along with the current Cyclops and Wolverine are gonna be my only ML purchases of the year, it looks like.

DC Icons has the Superman Doomsday pack, and Supergirl and Nightwing figures. Not sure if I'll get Jon and Robin. 

The Batman Animated line has nothing of interest for me since there weren't any TNBA figures. Might just get Animated Superman to go along with my TNBA Batman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beautiful Scene from Glorious Anchorman 2- Ode to Doby  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 17:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 07:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In The Americans, I don't believe Elizabeth has met face to face with the head of the Russian Consulate, and the Jennings never met Nina. That show could probably fill this whole thread with a list of major players that haven't met. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 03:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [just order one off amazon] (https://smile.amazon.com/Marvel-Spider-Man-6-inch-Legends-Symbiote/dp/B01D11DYRK/ref=sr_1_2?s=toys-and-games ie=UTF8 qid=1487643939 sr=1-2 keywords=marvel+legends0)

Hurry while it's still at retail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, I wonder who's gonna be the lone survivor*? /s

*does not include Jacob Tremblay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll check tomorrow when I pick up Hacksaw Ridge on Blu-Ray. I've never had great luck when it comes to finding new things while collecting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, okay. So on hand is what's on the shelves then. I guess that makes sense then. I checked it when I woke up, and it said that one of them had 22 on hand. Now, it's only 12. I guess some one bought the case, and maybe 2 other figures. The one closest to me looks like a dead zone then. It's been at 14 since Friday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 17:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does brickseek work? Is the saleable column whats on shelves and the on hand what's in the back? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It looks like a generic Ubisoft game," said r/ps4. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 04:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You think Full Frontal is pretty perfect? Where were you in that thread from a couple of days ago, where damn near every post was shitting on it?!

Feels like this subreddit is pretty anti-female late night comedy host. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 03:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like The Amazing Spider-Man movies for what they do right. But deep down (not that deep, actually) I know that the second one is a mess of a film. The first film is better, but it's held back by having to redo the origin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I call the other one "Cyclops with the good hair." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 00:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought this was r/tifu not r/humblebrag </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 21:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They probably just didn't push it down to show off the effect on the hair in one shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 21:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> comic MJ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Toy Fair 2017 - Marvel Legends 6" TRU Exclusive Dark Phoenix and Bald Head Cyclops 2-Pack - Figures </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 18:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 05:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hoping to find at least a Cyclops when I go buy Hacksaw Ridge on Tuesday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 05:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just saw your other thread, lol. Congrats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mary Jane looks like Emma Stone to you guys too, right? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 05:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 01:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #**NECA**
 
**"We only work on Predators and Aliens!** ^^^^^^And ^^^^^^sometimes ^^^^^^some ^^^^^^other ^^^^^^shit." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 23:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well DO something about it, you spineless prick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 21:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last time that happened was the Sandman wave.  POs or straight up orders should be dropping any day now. 

And when they do, I'd appreciate an amazon link to Cyclops and Logan! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 18:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [DC Collectibles Icons/ Bombshells/ BTAS figures pics](http://news.toyark.com/2017/02/18/toy-fair-2017-dc-collectibles-action-figures-241059) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 07:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'd go over his head. No way he understands this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 05:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fucking dark dude... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 05:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grace went out the window 9 years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 05:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would they change Ryan Gosling's name? Real missed opportunity there to remind the world that his name is indicative of a young goose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 04:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm serious btw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 04:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, the Trumptards are out in full force. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 04:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #JUST SELL THE DC UNIVERSE TO KEVIN FEIGE ALREADY! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 04:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smart move, he probably didn't want to be involved with a project that sounds like it'll be a massive pain in the ass to work on. It's like Warner Bros is permanently stuck in "FOX Fant4stic" mode.
Honestly, this just makes me even more hesitant to get remotely excited for Wonder Woman, the only DCEU film this year that has a shot at being good.
They just wanna pump out rush jobs to make a quick buck, and it's gonna hurt them in the long run.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 04:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smart move, he probably didn't want to be involved with a project that sounds like it'll be a massive pain in the ass to work on. It's like Warner Bros is permanently stuck in "FOX Fant4stic" mode.

Honestly, this just makes me even more hesitant to get remotely excited for Wonder Woman, the only DCEU film this year that has a shot at being good. 

They just wanna pump out rush jobs to make a quick buck, and it's gonna hurt them in the long run. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 04:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was way faster than I thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 03:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This movie was not made with a Donald Trump presidency in mind. He'd start sending in bombs the minute they landed. He'd be that one soldier in the movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 00:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone have the links to the Cyclops and Logan figures on Amazon? I can't find them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 19:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you think of the head sculpt?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, classic Rebelscum attitude on display there. Those guys are never happy about anything Hasbro does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 06:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This show is like a slightly shittier version of You're the Worst. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not even a great joke. I'm surprised this guy's skin isn't in shambles, seeing how thin it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 02:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hated these characters so much. They were sooooo annoying. It's like they personified different aspects of the r/funny family into characters. 

I wound up skipping the Dedsec videos cuz they were gaudy as hell, and full of annoying quirks.

These characters made me miss the utter blandness of Aiden Pearce. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 02:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~r/cummingonfigurines~~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who the fuck are the arctic monkeys? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cuz this guy goes through jobs faster than an alcoholic goes through bottles at a bar.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FAKE NEWS! SAD! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found Shia LaBeouf's reddit account! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 04:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He must be a real asshole to work with cuz this guy goes through jobs faster than an alcoholic goes through bottles at a bar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 03:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean during the general election. I don't think he'd protest vote, or support Trump. So he'd pick Hilary, and "Bwah!" his way through the act of voting for her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #**This guy goes through jobs faster than an alcoholic goes through bottles at a bar.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 01:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like in the end, he'd be a closeted Clinton supporter, but he'd be cringing about it the whole time. I can't see him getting on the Trump train, or putting things on Cruz control. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 01:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy goes through jobs faster than an alcoholic goes through bottles at a bar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox Plants Trump-Putin Fake News Story to Promote New Movie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox Plants Trump-Putin Fake News Story to Promote New Movie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After this photo was taken, a kid ran up to the figures, said, "YOINK!" and ran off with them. Reuters reports that OP's balls are bluer than Yondu. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol Kermit.

Also what's up with the pelvic thrust most people put their figures in?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice Gobots! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 18:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You give him too much credit. I doubt he knows anything about Jackson besides him being on the $20 bill and being President. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Venom over Green Goblin?

For shame, r/SpiderMan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 07:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you use it pretty frequently, you should definitely keep it. They only charge $50 while you're on Amazon Student Prime or whatever they call it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 07:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think a lot of the people who thing we're supposed to be like the gang are the ones who have lost interest. You see, to them stuff like making Mac openly gay, or the Gang Turns Black, is the show getting cucked by a political agenda, so they started to lash out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 07:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was there a point when NCIS was considered good TV? That shit is some of the blandest, most derivative crap around. Kudos to the writers though, for maintaining cushy jobs like that though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 04:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have sleeper cells in every subreddit ready to attack anything remotely anti-Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 04:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @realDonaldTrump agrees. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 03:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are seriously talented dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #**SNARF SNARF** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 09:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wins by default cuz I got to see Cecily get Marlyn Monroe'd by Sean Spicer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flashback Saturday: Someone farted during cold open (right as Leslie Jones saids, "And I'm going to Spain!")  /r/LiveFromNewYork </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 08:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 06:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they do like 20 a season and the 2016 half was really front loaded, it felt like. I think we got like 11 shows and 2 1 week breaks.

I'm expecting 2 shows a month until May. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 05:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I guess I'm staying up tonight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 05:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got some bad news for you... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
