<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1499</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 10:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For future reference how are injuries at school delt with? I had once attended a high school fair in CA and had fallen off something akin to a inflatable bounce house, the fall was around 6ft body height + 2 ft, where I had landed back of head first onto concrete and received a concussion. What were the legal implications ( I pretty much was sent to the nurse and sent walking home after 4 hours I was in a great deal of pain lasting around 8 hours before subsiding) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 10:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quick question how fast would it be to reach a dispatcher? Last time I called 911 due to being involved in a 10 car accident it took 15 min to reach anyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 10:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dam I hate all these gutted government agencies  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 09:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could be a scam </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 09:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some cops can be quite screwed up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 09:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like this is just rubbing it in OP's face... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 08:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most stop light now days are timed with the speed limit l so no reason to speed for the odd mistimed light. (Though I often fail this advice bc there is one light near me that feels like they screwed up as avg. time waitingi noted is 5 freaken minutes regardless if cars are on the other sides or not) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 08:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't chain of command recognize those underneath them? Such as a sergeant recognizing his soilders underneath him? Also if conscription was active they would be just shoved right back in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 08:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was this giant army not too far from their border led by a hawk that was later fired for insubordination. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 08:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps the whole Cuba thing was to get US nukes out of turkey? After all the secret agreement afterwards pretty much led to turkey and Cuba nukes being removed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 08:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could never really see the point of Cuba if ICBMs could reach anywhere on the globe. ICBMs really can be realistically intercepted close after launch. The only reason I would see reason to do so is for a first strike launch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 08:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After the breakup of USSR it turned out the solviet installations in Cuba were much more closer to completion than it was thought in Cold War times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 08:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya'll don't know, I reck'n </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 11:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you rear end someone generally you are in most cases considered at fault. Unless your insurance is the type that covers damage to your car even if you are at fault, I would say there is nothing to gain from filing out a report. 

I would assume that the other guy in question would file a report after he views and understands his damage, but if he didn't have his insurance maybe he wouldn't want the law involved.
 
Just from my experience from car accidents, but I am not versed in law of any form. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 07:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stalin killed people to purge Russia from dissent and rebellion. Unfortunately the man was very very paranoid and saw enemies everywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 07:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> USSR mechanized infantry and armor corps (and no the air force was not anything special) was in shambles pre-op Barbarossa, and for a good portion of the war it continued to be in shambles. The infantry was the main force by far.

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mechanized_infantry#World_War_II </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Each flu vaccine vaccinates against multiple strands of the flu. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have had a few, Bird flu was pretty wide spread but over they are toned down by modern medicine and vaccination that can vaccinate against multiple diseases in one shot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4 but still 2 main ones  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The details is there apparently 2 'main' branches of the flu. The first branch you come into contact with is the flu your body gears its response to; while the body does respond to the other branch, it uses the response that it would show to the first branch which is improper, rather it would be better if the body chalked up a new response to the scene branch. 

Some generations predominantly encountered one branch while other generations encountered the other branch, leading to some flus being more deadly among different generations. In the case of the Spanish flu the older generation were exposed to the branch that the Spanish flu came from, while the younger generation was exposed to the other branch first in their life. This lead to the younger generation having a weaker and more inefficient defense versus the Spanish flu compared to the older generation.

Edit: link https://www.cdc.gov/flu/about/viruses/types.htm

TLDR: Flu has 2 branches, older generation was resistant to the branch Spanish flu came from. Younger generation was weaker to that branch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe a different name? You know... how all the defenders committed sucidal and all that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 08:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The American army didn't really bother defending it tooth and nail do to its bad location </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying and trying to find something on this and I gotta say, it most likely not a real thing, even in real life the only time it would happen is possibly at graduation, and even then in my personal experience it didn't happen (expect for the 4-5 clueless people who happen to throw their hat, though one time 1/3 threw) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok had to dig around for awhile but I couldn't find a few articles I read about the theater in Middle East. Before 1800s there was theater in the Middle East among other entertainment forms. A lot of poets had produced works and etc. I also dug around creating google searches more and more detailed, until I got frustrated to find further reading for you (I don't know why I just did so) 

https://books.google.com/books?id=KZcohRpc4OsC pg=PT124 lpg=PT124 dq=1600s+middle+east+theater+-war+-london source=bl ots=TRn4w3Odm4 sig=h1VErptC8asU79V2o99c_2FD76s hl=en sa=X ved=0ahUKEwjRhPzW6cXSAhXHh1QKHaMvDVoQ6AEIOjAI#v=onepage q=1600s%20middle%20east%20theater%20-war%20-london f=false </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it? One sec </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some researchers managed to find out a few reasons why it was so particularly deadly among youths. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His prison was more akin to house arrest. But on a island. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ai unless the empire was established by this time (I don't think it was though) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't imagine Kennedy a hero </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That being said I think a lot of armies had trouble engaging. Anecdotes tell of how Caesar in order to get his army to fight took the banner of a unit and tossed it over to the enemy and told his soldiers to get the banner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can jokingly  imagine a conversation among warriors resting after a skirmish. "Bob those guys coming down that hill aren't our guys, let's kill them." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 09:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I never played XIII I heard Snow's theme and thought it to be pretty bad ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 08:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or CHARGE. Ram that bayonet into their hollow dead eyes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 08:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well at least it gave the AA gunner something to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 08:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it really was to appease wary states. In the war of 1812 the capitol was burned so it was not at a easily defended location. The swamp was terrible many early presidents and congressmen complained about the hot, humid climate. Economically? Possible I don't have much knowledge off the top of my head of the economic implications of D.C. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 08:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think the gas did anything more than psychological at most, I can't imagine simply being exposed to mustard gas causing permanent profound physiological changes. (Unless it's the kind of exposure that leads to death or disability, but I don't think hitler was disabled)

But maybe his psyche was already so messed up that exposure was just adding more damage on top. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 08:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will you end up killing your characters? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 11:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ancient Greece (Aristotle's time) and Rome thought the earth was round. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 10:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy was who I was talking about https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eratosthenes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 10:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ancient Egypt when some mathematician figured out the earth was round and it's circumference (he was surprisingly almost right on the spot) but many coastal communities would have that idea that the earth is round (ships would sail forth, you would see the ship "sink" over the horizon.) 

Edit: spelling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 10:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nancy Reagan was thought to be the brains of the White House when the brains of Ronald failed. (Sentence sounds harsh) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 10:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He kept calling it India for a while... he would have time to correct his mistake, realize his logs and miles traveled didn't add up... but then I remember he thought the earth was smaller than it really was... despite the more common consensus that it was big (at least bigger than what Columbus thought) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was checking to make sure someone commented this. Russia was getting stronger each day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 23:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't that... the same link? Minus an M </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 23:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 09:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Suprisingly often in some countries, while some for pranks, most thefts happen to sell for scrap. Wiki showed that in 1 city in India 2004 10,000 were stolen over 2 months 

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Manhole_cover_theft </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 08:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is your occupation and what advice would you give? (My major is electrical engineering and would love some advice) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 08:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love the very simple yet precise answer to a potentially complicated answer  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 08:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he got caught, he was just better at surviving and had more points in luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 08:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was worse? The pacific or the eastern front in WW2? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 07:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few of my teachers were quite open of their experience with alcohol. I.e. " after drinking a few beers with teacher B we ..." but this is CA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 07:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I respect your belief but would appreciate if you looked further into forementioned belief </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 04:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it pretty much jammed a lot with potential if misassembled (plausible, the gun was just a tad stiffer when misassembled, adding on to field conditions which were probably horrible) to injure the shooter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 04:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do you aim? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 04:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well I respect your belief but I think more good then bad has come out of the Bible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 04:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stoped chaining Dustia when I get to around lv 45... and then I start chaining stronger monsters so... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 03:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? Does this apply in all states? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 02:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like it's going to potentially escalate the situation. Why not first talk it out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 02:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly I don't like the idea of ever talking to a cop before a lawyer  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 02:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russian numbers are also similar, aden 1, dva 2, trree 3, shaterre 4, paat 5, shest 6, sem 7.

It's hard trying to reproduce some sounds in English. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 02:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And by 'evil' I mean messed up from today's point of view. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 02:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While a good deal of the popes were quite 'evil' I think they were more of a backstab and poison evil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 02:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Careful what you label propaganda, wouldn't the Bible be closer to a guide to life? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 02:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I compare it to American intervention in Central America. They don't want a hostile state right by them. (Slightly off topic: Do you think that is one major reason Chechnya did not achieve independence?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 02:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I compare it to American intervention in Central America. They don't want a hostile state right by them. (Slightly off topic: Do you think that is one major reason Chechnya did not achieve independence?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 02:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's all MAD, they are all MAD, the world is MAD! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 02:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's all MAD, they are all MAD, the world is MAD! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 02:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's all MAD, they are all MAD, the world is MAD! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 02:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's all MAD, they are all MAD, the world is MAD! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 02:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's all MAD, they are all MAD, the world is MAD! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 02:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I compare it to American intervention in Central America. They don't want a hostile state right by them. (Slightly off topic: Do you think that is one major reason Chechnya did not achieve independence?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 01:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's all MAD, they are all MAD, the world is MAD! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 01:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was I at 198 or 188? Better do 50 more to be safe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 01:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never really had a problem with the early hunts but then again I am the kinda of guy who chains Dustia at the beginning of the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 01:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First time fighting them, I attack with a heavily farmed Auron, and then O.O karma hit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 00:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about the monks on the mountain? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 00:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The calm lands' one got me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 00:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about XII where buffs and debuffs matter but if it seems tedious to continue to apply them you can have a gambit for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 00:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has a great well done story, the battles are more strategic and some grinding is required unless you are some god at strategy 

But even then the grinding and customizing your character's jobs and abilities is pretty fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 00:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me ANY mage BSB please, I have 4+ heal BSB, 9+ physical BSB, but I only have around 4-5 mage SB total... even though I have sheepsong but not shout... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 00:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do thief abilities stack with breakdown as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another question, when did the US start using dog tags on military personal and what is the story behind their adoption? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the atomic bomb tests and the subsequent bombings in Japan, how much thought was given to radiation exposure and how much did the US know about its effects at the time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 05:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> X, in those days I had no internet so those trials were a pain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still like them.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 11:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically is Black Mages considered as a composer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 11:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe he was talking about the other spheres such as return sphere? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 10:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried but it was just not my type I guess? First DS game I played and I couldn't beat the first boss. Took me around 20 tries to get him to half health only for him to morph into a nope monster. Around 60+ attempts I figured hey I am a pyromancer let's run around in circles and burn him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 10:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I might as well check it out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 09:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What part? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 08:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mountain lion would be scared off, Black bear scared off unless he is really hungry, grizzly bear will kill you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 04:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only time I don't cringe at Irgot on my team is if he is mid vs Zed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 23:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reinforcement bar under the bumper (might not be the official name) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 05:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prius, Camry is plastic I'm pretty sure. Others not sure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 02:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a noble he didn't like, talked too much he was known to roll up a metal plate like one would roll up a paper. If they didn't shut up, he would knock them out by punching him. Note Peter had the strength to roll up a metal plate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pardon me I think I am misunderstanding you, are you insisting that because the data is flawed, the forced sterilization in large numbers of Native Americans never happened? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How hard is it to distinguish between civilian and enemy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 10:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think sucidal thoughts are fairly common, but by how much? And how many lead to sucidal attempts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 10:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Similarly the USSR break-up was speeded up by miscommunication with various leaders of prefects and the USSR head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 10:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh those Egyptian dynasties, not to say Europe didnt have their own very inbred families  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
