<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2240</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 22:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool! Where on LI are you from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 22:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very much so. Everywhere is a bringer though so it's unavoidable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 16:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh so you're familiar with long-form - awesome! So you would be down for learning more of and experimenting with some long-form? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 15:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally understandable. I recommend it, it's fun and supportive there. NYC is where it gets a bit more intense, but Govs and Brokerage are super fun. So what's your improv knowledge? Mostly watching Whose Line? or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 15:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never hit up Govs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 14:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where on LI are you, if you don't mind me asking? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 07:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am one of them. I'm just searching for them in hopes perhaps we can meet up on LI and not have to commute to NYC all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any Long Island-based improvisers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 03:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry if this is the wrong place for this, but: are there any LI-based improvisers that would want to practice/perform long-form (preferably) or short-form? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 09:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 04:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what DAE stands for, but: I still love The Simpsons. Perhaps the quality isn't as consistently good, but I still think that they produce some amazing and very quotable episodes, as always. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 03:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An excellent point. Sometimes when I copy and paste the story to Reddit the formatting gets a little off. I'll try and fix that now, and hopefully that helps. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Demands Sanders Show Birth Certificate To Show No Relation To The Colonel [Onion-style article] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 05:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NEW YORK, NY  Business mogul and 2016 Republican Presidential candidate Donald Trump is calling out Vermont Senator and Democratic Presidential candidate Bernie Sanders on a seeming nonissue. Trump is demanding Senator Sanders reveal his birth certificate in order to dispel rumors he started that the Senator is related to Kentucky Fried Chickens founder and mascot, Colonel Sanders.
	
We cant immediately prove it to be true, and we cant immediately prove it to be not true. Therefore, Im gonna say it! exclaimed a fiery Trump. Does it make sense? No. Is it relevant? No. Its the perfect notion for me to make a big deal about for two weeks! finished Trump.
	
However, it doesnt seem like we will see the end of this in only two weeks. Trumps cockamamie theory has started a trending topic on Twitter (#ChickenSocialist) as well as Not My Chicken, Not My President, a Facebook page that has already garnered over three million likes. While 72% of Americans see this as just a moronic way of Trump getting himself in the headlines, Trump sees things differently. I couldnt be happier, he began, this is the American people sticking up for American values. This country is failing! We suck! I can help us not suck anymore, and clearly my brilliant realization is the first step on that road. This social media activity is a uge step in the right direction for America, Trump finished.
	
At press time, Trump stood by his words and encouraged more Americans to join in this seemingly pointless fight. Additionally, when supporters of Bernie Sanders asked Trump to show his birth certificate to see if there is any relation to the CEO of the four-time bankrupted Trump Organization, he called them idiots and stormed away.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Confederate Flag's Feelings Hurt Following Removal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 04:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MONTGOMERY, AL  Earl, the long-flying Confederate flag located on the Alabama Capitol grounds, was taken down, as per Governor Robert Bentleys orders. This comes after the tragic shooting in Charleston, an event that sent fear down the spines of everyone in the Confederate flag community. I can kind of understand it, said Earl, but I have a family to support! Money doesnt grow on trees; my family needs this job to get by. I dont know what well do nowthank goodness Obamacare was upheld in the Supreme Court. Thatll be a big help for us. 
Earl isnt alone in this situation  Confederate flags around the country have banded together to form CERCF, or Committee for Equal Rights for Confederate Flags. We understand the backlash against our kind, but we demand rights, too! said Billy, the President of CERCF. Just because people use us as an excuse to do horrible things, doesnt mean we can just be discarded! We demand to be memorialized in museums or some other fashion! barked Billy. 
We asked average Americans about the missions of CERCF, and their responses largely did not align with Billys. The Confederate flag represents a blemish on our history and should be removed and never praised, said Molly Shanahan, of Vermont. The Confederate flag being hailed disgusts me, and the time for its removal was, oh, I dont know, 60 years ago! exclaimed Hannah Jones, of Colorado. Im confused  flags can talk? Ian Smith of Arizona scintillatingly asked. However, we did find one man who sided with CERCF. Dale Williams, a 59-year-old man from Arkansas, stood by the flag. Yeah, slavery and oppression were bad but the flag is more dan that  the flag represents our history! History is like my wife  it aint always pretty, but I stand by it, he lovingly described. 
The general consensus against the Confederate flag wont stop the organization. Well become a big ol lobby and fight for our rights! yelled Billy. Earl aint alone! Weve got a bunch of members like Earl! And I wont rest until all our flags have some sort of protection! continued CERCF President Billy. Earl added, Well take this case to the Supreme Court! We want Obama to hear us, too! Following Earls wishes, President Obama released a statement to the organization. This is stupid, began the Commander-In-Chief, the Confederate flag is horrendous and its removal is late, if anything. We will not entertain any demands of the flags. With the Presidential elections in 2016 quickly approaching, the story to watch will certainly be the CERCF lobby fighting for the rights of the antiquated, racist remembrances of history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man Who Loves Being Trampled Disappointed With Black Friday Safety </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 02:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ST. LOUIS, MO  Roger Powers, 32, was one of countless Americans taking advantage of the incredible sales this Black Friday. However, Powers had an ulterior motive for shopping on this busy day. I love being trampled to the brink of death. Its just such a rush! I figured this could be my opportunity for a thrill, but I was dead wrong. By the way, I kind of intended the pun on that one.
	Powers said he figured to best store to carry out his plan in would be the local Wal-Mart. Anytime they show Black Friday crowds, its ALWAYS at Wal-Mart! Powers stated. Upon entering the store, Powers dreams were soon dashed. Police waited at the entrance, only letting in groups of 75 or so at a time. When you were in the store, officers were there patrolling to keep peace. What the hell kind of crap is that?! he finished.
	Powers sadness could not be placated, despite having good reason to be. Yeah, I got a 50 inch, flat-screen, 3D, LCD TV for 80% off, but thats material goods. The trampling is a soul-warming desire that cant be substituted for with objects.
	At press time, Powers was seen purchasing a ticket to Pamplona, Spain, in order to fulfill his desires at the Running of the Bulls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study: Maury Lied About 88% Of Paternity Tests Just Because </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 04:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> STAMFORD, CT  You are the father! an emotional Maury Povich would shout to potential fathers on his program, The Maury Show. Reactions from the shows guests and audiences would vary, but a new study claims that the reactions are based in inaccuracies. A study conducted by the Statler Research Center concluded that 88% of men who were told they were the father on the show were, in fact, not the actual fathers.
	Its an appalling find, said the studys head researcher, Dr. Glenda Waldorf. We have a lot of free time, so we tested it over and over again, just to get the same results. When you think about the money, and time, and stress caused by all of this, itsits almost horrifying. Mr. Povich felt otherwise.
	Horrifying? Haha, is she serious? Dude, its hilarious. Tell that buzzkill to chill! Mr. Povich began. The host felt no remorse for his deplorable actions. The people watching arent the only ones who need entertainment! So, I see the inside says that the guy isnt the dad, and I throw caution to the wind! Plus, isnt it good if the kid has a father figure, even if its not, like, their real one?
	Dr. Waldorf tackled this question quite bluntly. Its not good. Its actually quite terrible. A childs psyche is a very sensitive place, and having a parent around who shows no interest in them can be quite detrimental. A child may be better off raised by a single, loving parent than a caring parent and an obligated one.
	But the children arent the only ones affected by this. We spoke to Dmitri Hawkins, one of the men on the show who was lied to, and he expressed similar sentiments. It was a lie?! What?! Ive put my time and effort into raising a kid that isnt even mine?! Not to mention this kid sucks! His name is KeithKeith! Thats a sign that hes a terrible person. I mean, mentallyfinancially...Im ruined! Ruined! Povich felt no shame for his actions after hearing Dmitris story, merely commenting, Heh, what a noob.
	At press time, Povich had decided to follow through with Does Someone Love You? Week, and he plans to lie straight to their dumb, loveless faces! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Demands Sanders Show Birth Certificate To Show No Relation To The Colonel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 03:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NEW YORK, NY  Business mogul and 2016 Republican Presidential candidate Donald Trump is calling out Vermont Senator and Democratic Presidential candidate Bernie Sanders on a seeming nonissue. Trump is demanding Senator Sanders reveal his birth certificate in order to dispel rumors he started that the Senator is related to Kentucky Fried Chickens founder and mascot, Colonel Sanders.
	We cant immediately prove it to be true, and we cant immediately prove it to be not true. Therefore, Im gonna say it! exclaimed a fiery Trump. Does it make sense? No. Is it relevant? No. Its the perfect notion for me to make a big deal about for two weeks! finished Trump.
	However, it doesnt seem like we will see the end of this in only two weeks. Trumps cockamamie theory has started a trending topic on Twitter (#ChickenSocialist) as well as Not My Chicken, Not My President, a Facebook page that has already garnered over three million likes. While 72% of Americans see this as just a moronic way of Trump getting himself in the headlines, Trump sees things differently. I couldnt be happier, he began, this is the American people sticking up for American values. This country is failing! We suck! I can help us not suck anymore, and clearly my brilliant realization is the first step on that road. This social media activity a uge step in the right direction for America, Trump finished.
	At press time, Trump stood by his words and encouraged more Americans to join in this seemingly pointless fight. Additionally, when supporters of Bernie Sanders asked Trump to show his birth certificate to see if there is any relation to the CEO of the four-time bankrupted Trump Organization, he called them idiots and stormed away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Squirrel Preparing For Hibernation Already Tired Of Nuts Jokes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 06:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CENTRAL PARK, NY  As the cold weather approaches, Clancy, a beloved squirrel in New York Citys illustrious Central Park, has begun gathering food for his upcoming hibernation. As usual, the food gathering brings about societys shallow jokes.
	Ive been collecting nuts for less than a week, and Im already hearing it, said a disgruntled Clancy. You all go food shopping and no one laughs. I go food shopping and everyone has a field day. Real freakin funny! he finished.
	Less than a week into collecting is a short time for a squirrel to start feeling hostility towards joke makers, but Clancy is known around the squirrel community for his short fuse. Oh, yeah, hes a dangerous one, said Clancys best friend, Tom. Tom continued, detailing Clancys run-in with the law. A tourist from Toronto made one of those nuts-in-cheeks jokes, and Clancy wasnt having it, said Tom. He made fun of the tourists accent, then bit him three times. It was badreal bad, he finished.
	So what does the future hold for Clancy? Im working on controlling my anger, he said, but I cant make promises. All of Clancys neighbors, including tourists, seem to be giving him his space, making 2015 the smoothest preparation period yet.
	At press time, Clancy, following in the wake of Pizza Rat, had collected three slices of pizza, prompting other squirrels to make obesity jokes. Clancy has a court date where he will most likely serve two months community service. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
