<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3183</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 05:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, AI mode covers a lot of the learning map things and you still get to play a game to work on other fundamentals. So that's kind of weak. Stuff like stats i hear but everything is accessible when you're picking the hero, like talents and stuff.  
  
All your points are fair to a degree. They are urgent. It's easy to look at a UX and say we can improve here and here. To an extent though. The interface, in the bigger picture is pretty solid and well put together. Works well and is overall intuitive.  
  
I think we'll see chat improvements with the guilds and stuff. I don't think there's a dire need for changes though. Still fair points. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 04:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah it's crazy how much resemblance you have to her. great job. nailed it, really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 23:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah this and staying on top of xp. to rank up you need to learn to turn bad decisions into good ones/wins. Fighting 4v5? or 3v4? make it an even fight or advantageous fight, maybe it is a 3v3 camp invade turn it into a 4v3. Are they fighting over obj down a talent tier? make it a win.  
   
amd soak soaksoak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 19:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> honestly a large portion of suggested reworks, talents changes, and etc are ludicrous and 1. either not well thought out or 2. have that "lack-of-understanding the game" perspective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 07:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone should be havingfun o matter what they're playing. They should also be taking it seriously. Not because it's this mode or that. Because you should want to win and be good at what it is you're doing. Learning good habits and applying them will allow you to carry them over to other game modes and just get better.  
  
But have fun. Have fun in every game mode or don't play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 23:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fair point. as an ad it certainly works though. and to some extent that's absolutely spot on but on the other hand it's addressing or setting up a subset of people being alone on a day when everyone is supposed to be together.  
  
it's not so much encouraging being alone in order to watch porn, it's that you are alone on xmas so cheer it up by watching some porn  
  
either way, good point. and ads are often what's perceived more than anything else. with that consideration it's prolly on the fence how people are perceiving it and taking it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 23:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lotta people get told that in their lives. you don't get to the top without taking some risks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 22:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> are they otu of their f'en minds i efeel like that is so forward heavy just any day now
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 21:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> actually im not im specifically highlighting differences between the characters. vaguely defending it because 'they should do everything' and 'they should be equal in doing everything' and they're 'assassins it's their job' is all over the place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 10:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol clever chaps. 
  
but to some extent they nailed it. you know sex sells...but making sex sell and relatable, in that we all do it kinda way. At least as an American.  
  
Unfortunately asking for a PornHub account/premium isn't exactly xmas gift material. But it wouldn't make a bad gift for a couple to themselves.
  
why do i keep getting spellchecked on relatable? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 09:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's some cruel irony there for sure. 
  
Often brain cancers sometimes are hard to catch too till they're inoperable. Like he could have thought some forgetfulness, fatigue, and small neuro deficits were his age at first. You never know. Shitty stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 09:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but in real life he doesn't second guess the shit he hears every two seconds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 09:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i remember that monche and styles track from back in the day. so dope, still dope.  
  
yeah mental health wont get any recognition here till it's more recognized nationally. in general it's stigmatized. can't expect a sub genere that oversexualizes, overmasculinzes, overindulges and glorifies substance abuse to get on board with a positive mental health message when the rest of the country looks down and punishes you for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 09:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> listening to wayne gets me too creative.  
  
lol, i start writing shit and getting clever and playing around with words, making words up, and bending definitions till they break. legit did it twice, edited for way longer than i had to on one paper. on the other the teacher appreciated the loose use of the english language but wouldnt recommend doing it again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 09:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u can throw the orb careful ltimed as a line or u throw it when the waves kiss to the side.  
   
ahhh dude no shit that's my point. your arguments are vague, for all assassins...they're assassins...like no shit.   
  
i didnt say they nerfed his team fight. they nerfed his single target dmg. ming's reset make her kit fundamentally a hero killer one. 
  
because she still 1. has some form of waveclear. and 2. is that much better as killing people, and when she kills one she probably kills two, at least. 
   
like look at like this kt/jaina are a 7/10 on killing but ming is  a 9/10. so ming is a 5/10 on waveclear and kt and jaina are 9 and 8 respectively  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 07:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  [Port Alberni](https://www.google.com/imgres?imgurl=http://edelweissbb.ca/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/port-alberni-background.jpg imgrefurl=http://edelweissbb.ca/ h=2112 w=2816 tbnid=2fGlkQOlLJFSVM: vet=1 tbnh=160 tbnw=213 docid=DUT2c0szs-8C6M itg=1 usg=__xAhAr-y2oIPtfDBTWAqgN7o74lQ= sa=X ved=0ahUKEwjfz4G99uPQAhVCMyYKHcvtBkAQ_B0IezAO)

legit has one stoplight in the picture. def could have missed the second one i guess...4 lane road though, i'm impressed. must have squeezed your budget for that. or the local mining/industry needed wider road to go through town. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 06:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ahh you're missing the point. ming was built to to team fight. the resets, the cornerstone to her character, is built around her kills.  plus im sure it was considered, nerfing the dmg. she can solo but it's one ability rotation plus some to 100-0 someone. and she can still waveclear, which you really haven't addressed. an orb to the side of the  wave. nor does it stop her ability to lane because her poke is so strong she still will do fine in lane.
  
kt's sun kings fury was giving him crazy single target 100-0 blow up potential. so they took it away because it made him too strong and do *everything* too well. you could argue, more so than waveclear, being able to kill someone is a fundamental part of the game. doesn't mean it wasn't needed.  
  
lol it's okay to disagree.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 04:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus man, you're reaching.  
  
THe point is, yeah, Jaina and KT are great in team fights and solid burst damage. But they aren't picked over ming, barely. if at all. Ming's nature in team fights is so strong you need to make it more of an option. 
  
eh w/e man i guess, i dont see the point in holding onto or defending onto one aspect of ming's talent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 03:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol alright, she does a majority of the shit you'd want a hero to do. and she does it well. her team fight alone is enough to carry her as a pick with the resets. and it didn't totally nerf her waveclear. it certainly took a big chunk of it but a well placed orb is syill effevr.her pick rates over jaina and kt spoke for itself.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 18:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a cultural thing because they started a television channel and it took off. 
   
And to be fair, we tried it in America too, GTV or G4TV and it didn't take off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 18:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People forget PTR isn't matched near relevant skill. Chromie, Varian, Zarya...the PTR 'impressions' were way off. PTR is imo to make sure he doesn't have any crazy bugs that need to be addressed *right now* that they missed.   
  
We'll see, shield increased, maybe bring the cd down again or who knows, really need to see how he plays with everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 18:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah alot of that is numbers tweaking though.  I still feel like they moved him more to that bruisery kind of role he always fit into. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 18:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but the fact they're working on him show's it'll actually be soon. Just about every rework they've touched up in the following patch when needed. THe initial rework release doesn't close the book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 18:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sigh man, no one needs to complain about it.  
  
Alright man, You still have addressed, fundamentally, why it isn't good for a hero to do everything and how that overshadows when drafting other picks.  
  
You make good points, they just don't really justify having one mage picked over the other two constantly. It was just like KT when he was in the position ming was. You could pick him to cover all these things and no one else ever got picked. Plus you always had decent waveclear with Ming with a good orb placed to the side of the wave.  
  
I'd bet she's still picked over the other two the majority of the time but instead of 9/10 times or 10/10 it's closer to 6/10 or 7/10 times.  
  
And that's where we'll disagree, it isn't good design having heroes do everything. Absolutely not. And no they didn't lose KT's waveclear, they nerfed his single target blow up potential. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 18:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's not randomly gimped and this is the core of what people are getting at. You could always waveclear with a well placed orb.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 09:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> e r that's what makes heroes unique in HotS. On the same note some heroes are going to be similar i ncertain ways. Particularly when it comes to draft. You're going to draft one of those three KT, Jaina, o r Ming. So you do need to make the comparable in a sense. If one of them does everything better than all of them, there's no decision on who to pick. Currently that's the case. When we pick a mage Ranged carry mage we pick ming over KT or jaina, almost everytime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 08:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i find it hard to imagine people are pushing back against the calamity change. her wave clear puts her in the same spot as  KT was when he was OP OP. 
   
And what is it exactly? You don't want heroes taht can do it all. They can't check all the boxes. Good hero dmg, good team fight, ranged burst carry, good laning/rotations, good poke, wave clear. It covers too many bases, especially with the nature of draft.  
  
So of all those things they could have changed with calamity they removed part of her pve and wave clear. It could have been reduction in damage overall and talented into 150% vs minions on calamity.  
  
Mcintyre in his review of the patch notes, rather the PTR patch notes, on noting Tyrael's santification nerf from 80 sec to 100 and Li Ming's calamity nerf said they shouldnt be nerfing these heroes but buffing other heroes. 
   
Now there's a point to that, to an extent. If we buff Jaina and KT to match Ming, they both have super short cd's. KT would be the problem he was. Nor would they feel as unique. Tyrael's nerf is trying to keep sanctification on a similar or slightly longer cd than a lot other heroics, powerful ones. So this prevents the dynamic of having Sanc ready to go every time without concern. 
  
On the other hand Diablo, Artanis, and a few others did get buffs. There's a give and take. You don't want a hero, in draft, to satisfy all the marks. It's what makes a hero OP, competitively. At least dominant. And it shows in her pick rate.  
  
as for your direct question, their cd's are much higher. And they're more balanced. Feel like people forget how powerful KT was back then. Should we go back to that? Like this isn't...Ming is picked primarily for her teamfight and reset potential. And that's what she should be focused on. You're talenting into the wave clear as much as you're talenting into a finisher for her combo, so that's kind of a weak argument. Whenever there's the option for a mage between ming, kt, and jaina you take ming everytime. Because she checks all those boxes.  
  
Overall I'm just shocked people are even arguing this. She's still going to be a teamfight animal. Still can reset through a whole team and be ridiculously strong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 04:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah  i was gonna say the league would be more demanding imo. with playing against team regularly, prepping for them *weekly* in a dynamic meta.  
  
I think it more has to do with the circumstances around which they say they're 'retiring.' Aka getting snubbed or feeling so, underachieving/non making expectations with performance, stuff like that (removed from roster/disgagreement w/ leadership).  
  
edit: in general eSports tends to publicly not show the best of professionalism. Not that it isn't in every industry and job just eSports worlds tend to put it on blast for some god forsaken reason.   
   
...For all our pleasure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 23:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why not...usar...

^_- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 19:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> don't hate the player, hate the game.  
  
if your shit is valuable, contact an appraiser and put it to auction or private sale. if you don't give a fuck, want quick cash, or just are being a lil silly, go to a pawn shop but don't expect to get what it's 'worth.' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 18:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eh adaptation actually looks like it's in a good spot right now with those changes. 
   
my initial reaction was uggh, brush inc speed? come on that's crazy. Then I thought back to one time i accidentally took that talent on cursed hollow. Dehaka is picked for his global. This will enable to engage on a team a bit more effectively after using his global.  
   
I also think this will be a lot more effective than we think it will be. Obviously we'll have to see, and there's a good chance it's every bit as bad as I and everyone initially thought it was. He's picked for his global, that won't entirely change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 18:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eh yes and no. part of what's going on is taht u can either use the charge to engage or use taunt to engage. or using them combo'ed is a decent length of cc that should result in a kill. 
   
people get a lil tunnel visioned on one  talent sometimes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 21:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eh i dont know man, losing that baggage prolly gives a better representation of you mmr today, rather than over all time. which in game mmr is trying to do. just because an mmr reset is a bad idea in game doesn't mean it doesn't work for hotslogs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 21:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, there's a few things i think going on in noblesse's head.  
   
if they only though illidan was in there, it's a bit of a gamble though. he can be hard to kill and they don't know where anyone else is. he had to think he was getting more than one or it's too risky. 
  
without MVPM's bottom camp going blue, they were anticipating an invade imo.  
  
the point still is, one person in there and a solo stun is potentially a big mistake, possibly a bait.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 19:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> def responded to the wrong comment i think.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 17:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 40% reference? leisure? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 07:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> jo's a solid carry in bronze silver. jo, a good dmg dealer, and bwing. besides going for a spec/xp thing. which you can do with good waveclear on an assassin or tank too. 
  
66% win rate on valla 58% on ming atm. bronze 4 lolol.  
  
placed silver 3 just going to have to wait till next season. i used to say bronze was easy to get out of but this season it's extra crummy. part of carrying in B/S is that, you need to be good enough to win fights 4v5, win obj's 4v5, win fights down lvls and talent tiers, win fights without or with a bad tank, win fights without cleanse or peels. 
  
You have to be able to not go clear that lane, risk losing the keep, turn a bad fight/decision into a good one then go do what you're 'supposed' to. it's difficult to carry and win down here. i'm not saying people aren't where they belong, most are, trust me. there's def some people who know what's going on. most that do though do rank up.  
   
edit: one bad losing streak and you're bronze 4 though...lolol /shrug </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 02:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey, it's a fine line considering the lengths your country went to persecute people. so it comes with the territory. we're not even 100 years out from it.  
  
are their concerns with immigration? of course there. but there's little you'll do to actually stop it. focusing on integrating them rather than resisting it will surely bring a better way forward. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 02:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's actually oddly accurate. once in a while i get lucky on down in long island </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 00:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you guys sound way too sheltered. and a bit nationalistic. not that there's anything wrong with a bit of pride, hell i'm american, but i'm also from nyc and the reaction you're having to some people with color in their skin...seems juvenile at best and downright immature and irresponsible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 00:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to be fair, being a criminal and an addict isn't exclusive. lotta criminals do have drug problems and a lot of addicts commit some crimes.  
  
generally though, their record is mostly relatedd irectly to the possession and consumption of the drug. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 01:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actualyl was going to pitch an article to somewhere, and if you wanted to follow up with a part 2, it'd probably appropriate. Not sure if it's yours or an editorial call, regardless.  
  
I think a large part of it is $$ and lack thereof in a young, growing scene.  
   
That said, the role of a coach in HotS is even more critical. That's due in part to a combination of things. It comes mostly down to the fast paced nature of the game, combined and driving, the nature of shotcalling in HotS. Being in game can cloud your judgment, either with a tunnel vision, short nearsightedness, or too long a view. 
  
Shotcalling is what differentiates HotS really. Despite what some people have said, without ever making a clear argument against it (or for similarities in other games), there's rarely a 100% correct thing to do in HotS. Whether it's choosing to take the obj, both obj's, push structures then obj, take a camp, invade a camp or something simpler, is this the fight we take? is it the fight we have to take?  
   
Granted, we all see this, at least those with a keen eye, in our everyday games without recourse. On the pro level, it is everything though. While your shotcaller fulfills this role in game, in training having someone outside the game to help guide that decision making will help in training you to be a better shotcaller in tournament matches.   
  
A good example was a game from...the summer championship where one team, on Sky Temple, went Tyrael/Morales/Raynor cheese. They got the keep and the team who was at risk of being cored took the wipe opportunity, all ~30ish seconds of it to boss. Then hearth back, defend, the core was knocked to 60% and proceeded to base race. The added damage from the boss, the boss taking the keep(!), and the pressure it created, the decision as a whole was critical to winning the game against the cheese. Their window to do that was minuscule at best and the risk was great.

Watching top tier abathur play shows it too. At what point he goes from soaking/clearing a lane to hopping in and committing to the 5 man team fight with evolution. These are simpler but more relatable examples for the average viewer. The more games I watch as a caster though, related the decisions I thought and think a team is going to do, vs what they, arguably, should do and what they ultimately do, predicted or not and for better or worst have really brought this point to fruition. As the meta evolves alongside the dynamic map pool this hand in hand will continue to drive HotS as a shotcalling or coaches game.    
  
Now as for whether the coaches are allowed on comms is another discussion. Some places I think allowed it during their last season (Korea, iirc?). The fact that this has already been broached, granted in a region that values coaches, is telling. Korea being the top region, also strengthens the point of HotS being a coaches/shotcallers game. 

Often people make comparisons to other sports. The top comment here even does on the importance of coaching. There's a saying that defense wins championships and coaches build legacies. I don't think it's any coincidence the first legacy of HotS was MVP Black's 40+ game win streak nor is the Korean region's dominance accidental. The nature of HotS as a coaches game adds to that resolve. A final note is to examine the speed and efficiency KR teams make their in game decisions and commit to them. Rarely is there a moment that they are 'deciding' what to do and never does a caster suggest they aren't sure.  
  
This resolve and unity alone, can give them the edge to win even when making the wrong decisions. It certainly speaks to the strength of good coaching which in turn imparts the shotcaller with excellent, quick, decisive, judgment. 

Anywho, that's my two cents. Sorry I'm tight for time, casting Heroes Hype tonight 9PM EST at twitch.tv/Heroes_hype with /u/halorin (@ (lol self plug! tweet it out!),  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 11:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i smoke daily and still look 10 years younger, after smoking for ten years. my mom and dad both also smoked for forever and look great for their age so, meh, genetics. and i'm just not sure how i'm going to rapidly change that. then again  guess accumulatively it'll catch up.  
   
anyway, trying to quit but fuck it's hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 10:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when i was...20...9  years ago...lol that can't be right. 
    
anyway, i thought i'd live fast and like fuck it, what i looked like at 30, 40, whatever. and it was so easy to look at someone that did that much more than i did, not looking wrinkled up till at least 60+. like x still looks good and he did y for 10 years. 
   
anyway, i do age well. but half of it is like, feels like it's in your head. then again if i woke up every morning and thought i was old, because i looked old, i'd actually freak out.  
   
that said, when the day comes and over the course of a couple months it all goes to shit, i won't have forgotten the hell i put myself through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 06:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well they're not. they're planning, from my understanding along with other trends w/ their products, to utilize it primarily for business. 
   
a few more things add to that argument, particularly that it has everything, from hosting a hangout and video to not needing it to communicate w/ someone.  
  
my best bet would be it'd be monetized for businesses, or altogether. so get grandfathered in? lol nah im playen. but i don't think it's going anywhere. it's also been around the longest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 06:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just use hangouts... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 08:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to    be fair everyone has an offseason. this tourney kind of came out of the blue and everyone just prepped really hard for blizzcon. so deciding to take a couple days or weeks isn't unreasonable. 
  
i phrased that wrong but you can approach something more like a friendly than a league matchh. or exhbition.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 20:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> see when those reviews came out, they were legit critiques coming fomr LoL and DotA. Now that the game is fleshed out more, we see that those aspects are actually it's strengths. In the sense it's fast paced, obj based, different maps do add variety.  
  
So I don't fault people for that initial reaction but def should keep an open mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 20:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> exactly, there's zarya, samuro, guldan, auriel. 
   
and some i'm prolly forgetting. and the nature of the bully changed too. it wasn't just zagara and thrall to counter. which is all like related obviously. 
   
so yeah, and this is what their reworks are about. sonya still sees some competitive play and some HL she's not totally out of it. just not top pick, dominant like she was and certainly as fallen a bit behind.  
  
i personally think she handles peeling samuro really well because she heals off the three images. if her speed boost was a bit more for her chase it'd might help too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 20:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol i mean i doubt we'd actually get it separately and a healer/dps multiclass would be stupid unique and cool.     
  
but personally, i think it'd work better separately. and since velen was on that leak list he's holy through and through iirc. 
   
 so i wouldn't be surprised to see a holy and then a disc...(am i remembering that correctly?)
    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 19:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eh we're getting 'faster' animation but i think that's because they're just getting better at developing the heroes more than anything.  
  
that said, someone like varian negates sonya big time imo. samuro too to some extent. and i don't know if that's because 'their faster' as much more dynamic kits that do what she does better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 18:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i think we'll see a light and shadow desperately. i dont remember priests much from wow so...i'm not going to say anything more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 18:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> iirc somewhere i saw something about him.  
  
i'm pulling hard for velen myself. plus the dranei link makes a lot of sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 18:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dmg kara is big over there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 18:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did they?  i wouldnt be surprised is a lot of people, 1. coming from blizzcon took some time off and 2. came into this playing those teams on their home turf as a crazy hard uphill anyway.  
   
and wanted a bit of time off so are just like going into it as meh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 18:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah and dig did show up they played well and they played well against the KR teams. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 03:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah the instant abilities are super frustrating. i can switch something else off qc but those... 
   
my boo was sonya but i can't stutter with w anymore. even when i'm not stuttering to sorta happens of o attack moved anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 03:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> noticed it on sonya's w. what kills me is it's instant cast ability. i don't use qc universally and have been transitioning to using it more n more. this has certainly made me think twice about what to switch over.  
   
that said, i wonder what pros think? or if they're having issues. we move fast on our best heroes but they move fast constantly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 17:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah but he does need something. And it probably isn't just raw health. Hit kit is dynamic and, as we saw, it's easy to put him over the edge to OPdom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 15:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to be fair we had a queue like that but it was 4 or 5 in the morning.   
  
TL can throw ya a 400, 500 second queue even at peak times sometimes, but 600+ is usually in off peak hours, way off peaks hours.  
  
ALso need to put into context we played the same team 3 games in a row before getting a new one. Generally though, that's not my experience.  
  
It's also with mixed mmr teams from silver--plat/dia/gm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 09:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CN played the dmg build :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 09:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it's hard to point at one hero and say x! Definitely. Especially because if you throw in the comp and add a tass to Valla, or even Butch for that matter, it changes. A friend was telling me Valla stats solo isn't a great win rate but w/ tass or duo supp she shoots up to 90% or some insane win rate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 09:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they run 3 warr in KR too. They look toward Arthas a lot over there.  
   
Sometimes what works for a team and how they use heroes is unique and cool. Sometimes it's indicative of a shift in the meta. But good job, congrats, and was cool seeing three 3 warrior comp out of the West. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 08:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i do tend to recall a few pretty english teachers too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 06:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asking History would make such a better name.   
  
Although i like that one, it grew on me after initial dislike. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 00:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> would it be comparable to certain developing areas, in like India, that have sewage rivers still, and lack of plumbing/running water? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 00:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i lost it there, told my gf both laughing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 23:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> got mine with 5k miles. buy used, cert pre owned, off lease. esp around a place like nyc where someone thought they needed acar and never drove it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 10:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol or maybe just both, to like emphasize the point. like he's responding to both of us and being doubly wrong rather than we each prove our point to him.  
  
i'm synergizing points here dude. get with it,  come on. lolol jp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 06:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol dude i find it a stretch to say 'self casting R is intuitive' when the actual ability gives no indication to be a self casted ability.  
  
that's be like me selfcasting  blizzard or something. sure i might try it eventually but it's def not 'intuitive' or the first thing i'd try to do with it, by far. that's really a stretch.  
  
and i get it man, i'm on of those devil advocate argue for the sake of feeling out the argument but sometimes...lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 06:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah def, to be fair, if it's picked up on it's also fine if they did say something at the time. but it shouldn't be punished for not doing it in the moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 06:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, in light of that the HGC set up I think is really positive. It opens up competition directly between pro-am teams and pro.  
  
 I cast and I casted a match...I can't recall what it was for but it was a sort of amateur championship that had a couple pro/semi pro teams on their way to regionals using it as warm up I think. Totally allowed to be there and everything though, they weren't like pro pro yet.  
   
Anyway, they went up against what was, at the time, and it was a little bit ago so people weren't as good as they are now, a top NA amateur team. The ammy team got crushed and the skill gap was so apparent. Not totally crushed for a best of three but it was one sided for the two matches.   
   
So, hopefully there will be solid communication now and door's opening for these guys to scrim and stuff, and rotate into the HGC.  
   
That said, on top of the 5v5 teamwork, and what role the inhibit within it, flex, carry, support, tank, pseudo support, bruiser, melee plays a factor into it. And many pros can do all those roles on the HL/casual level.   
  
Most importantly I think. And this is really where things get brought a step up, the way they look at the game and it comes together is just...different. It's super impressive watching them see things develop and adapt and overcome them, punish, capitalize or correct themselves on in the fast paced nature of HotS. That's really where, imo, pro's become a step up on everyone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 06:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They made the correct ruling for sure here. That said, the zera thing is banned now that we know about it because they aren't sure. So in that situation, when you're not sure you have to rule on the side of caution, allow it for the situation it was used in and then ban it from future use now that you know about it.  
   
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 05:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to be fair it's built from a game where this might not be an issue. sc2. Also, as a game designer, this just wouldn't be something I anticipated. Granted, in a more globalized world it's definitely a convenience but, from the jump, not something I'd consider a priority.  
  
That's not to say, especially that there's demand, that it's something we shouldn't have. Just that being how the game was developed and in light of the circumstances, I can understand why it'd seem like a big hurdle. And, consequently, while there is demand, it's very possible that it's a vocal but small minority of demand. Probably very small. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 18:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> def send out a couple tweets reminding people they'd make cool xmas gifts!! ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 18:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha and part of me almost feels this request comes out of a "lore realism" kind of thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 08:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And super decisive no less. Well, technically he can hop over the sides of a VP but not the center...like wtf? get a grip.    
     
II  even has the thought today when a kerr spike grabbed me mid air and we were on comms and I was like ahh that's bullshit I should be able to hop over that. 
  
The reality is,  while it wasn''tt absolutely needed at the time in  hindsight it showwed  how hard it was to grab a kill on  him. It's still hard just now he doesn't slip out last second, sit out for 10 seconds and come back in full  hhealth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 07:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> infernal shrines is 40 minions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 03:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hmm yeah the host being made yes?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 03:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorrrrrrrry!  
  
Sometimes i'm just so overcome wiht excitement if i didn't catch it right there I'm all like "LEEEEEEEEROY JEEEEEEEEEEEEEENKINS!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 03:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HBO def has a history of doing things like this. That said, it's possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He's building Theresa isn't he?!? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 02:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When he has Bernard kill Theresa it'd be pretty weird if she just went MIA. He can't say it happened 'accidentally' in the park because --- shitshow.  
  
While we're down there the machine is building a host while those events are going down! 
   
Anyway, stuff is posted here a lot and sometimes you miss something, my bad if this is out there already.   
  
Also, big credit to mi novia, my girlfriend, Meghan. Who prefers her name be said like Meg (normal) HAN (like Hans, the german name).  
   
Also, props to all of us saying Ford was the evil genius behind to all. But to what end and what else is going on?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 20:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's actually why i stopped played sonya.    
   
and then i took w off quickcast and it worked better. thought i wasn't quickcasting w right...lolol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 20:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he was a journalist for 25 years. how do you think you would ghostwrite a book? I'd take notes, religiously, about my subject and spin it in a positive light, write it in his 'voice.' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 08:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> true that, my bad. to be fair i should have added that. Except that claim came from Trump. Who is unreliable with facts. It was actually the other way around. Think about it too. Why would Trump turn him down? They both made millions off that book. 
   
That said, coming from a reporters perspective, and putting 20 years between it, and throw in reporter's books and notes...It's probably a pretty accurate take, any past discrepancies put aside.  
  
i'll take it as a pretty accurate account of the day to day of someone.  
  
i mean to be fair, everyone made some money, so why not do # 2? And really man, look up the stuff you're about to say. Like there's 0 accounts of proof that Trump rejected him for a second book. And Trump was even asked to provide proof, and declined to do so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 01:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eh to be fair man, a guy who worked with him 20 years ago giving his account is just that. There's not much that can be subjectively manipulated with  quotes. 
  
It's going to inherently have a bias depending on if the experience and work relationship were negative or positive. If the guy came forward and his experience was a great one the article would have been written anyway.  
    
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 01:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nah not really. I've been meaning to because i generally have heard positive things. It does a good job of a straight up slasher kind of show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 00:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yall being a little hard on keurig's. and it isn't burnt. it's usually more watered down then burnt.   
   
that said you may have a bad or old machine too. and it's just so damn convenient.  
   
the ninja shits on the keurig thoug h and you can make full pots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 22:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that sort of might be me.  
  
i kind of know im bad with it and a dick though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 19:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> anyone who met him in the last two years, even maybe 3-4 got a politician version.  
  
there's a good new yorker article about him from his ghostwriter... 
    
here's teh article: http://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2016/07/25/donald-trumps-ghostwriter-tells-all  
   
imo it's pretty telling. you get a much better feel for someone after you're around them a bit and they let their guard down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 18:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm interested in your forest fire fighting over there and geology and terrain landscape plays into that?  
   
My father does Emergency Management on the East Coast of a major hospital system. I'm interested in getting into the field. I'm currently a paramedic. Any tips? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 18:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he's solid c list man, it's not out of reach </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 18:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it was for travelling non citizens. 
   
aka exactly the type to be a terrorist. did you even read the article?  
  
 i'm not someone who defends shit like that often but it sounded far from draconian.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 08:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he does ash vs the evil dead... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 00:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> iirc someone mention something about him at some point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 22:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Velen inc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 09:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> git gud.  
  
don't die.  
  
fucking noobs.  
   
nah im playen man. they're two higher skill cap heroes, well after illidan's changes maybe not. But you got to learn when to get in with Illidan, do some damage, and get out before you take any at the beginning of fights. Then learn when the team is low enough for you to really commit do damage, pop your ult, and go to town. 
   
Tyrande, you need to learn her combo, which is hard, Hunter's Mark, Owl, Stun or vice versa. It does pretty decent damage. Learn to hit her stun foremost. Remember if you're marking for your team do it when DPS is around or on what they're attacking.   
  
Tyrande will teach you to have good map awareness because you should be constantly throwing your owl out for vision to find the enemy team.   
  
Check out McIntyre on youtube https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCy2pSbktCNa0P9cR0wfLtwg 
  
and Grubby  
   
https://www.youtube.com/user/FollowGrubby  
  
Watch steamers and amateur/pro games when you can. 
  
Romo#1498 is my battle tag.  
  
Try my girlfriends at HiddenSquid#112616  
  
both be more than happy to teach ya.  
  
You're a long way from ranked play but drafting drafting drafting. Counters and all that.  
   
That other dude gave you a great write up. I didn't want to give you too much. I wanted to keep it focused and a place where you definitely can take away what you want to or need to in order to improve. They might not turn out to be your preferred channels but they are a solid place to start.  
  
edit: granted this is the best melee assassin player in the world, this is Rich on Illidan. It'll give you an idea of the proper playstyle. 
   
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QqIt7SkIr48 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 08:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i could start with a short story and turn it into a novella. 
  
that said, i don't know shit about lore and i'd probably put it on amazon for like 99 cents because it'll take time. Got a lot going on and it'd take from my own writing, that I usually get paid or am trying to get paid for.  
  
So not trying to be that guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 08:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> all you gotta do is get them to d/l and make an account and they'll come back eventually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 08:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well it was blizz's fear too. mostly the q times, along with quality match vs quickly getting into one. it was a double wammy. 
   
works out alright though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 08:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> possible large influx of players combined with the patch being released. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 08:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it'd  be fucking bad though really. essentially the worst fuck anyone's had because it's a guaranteed nastiness spreader.  
  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 08:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this made me chuckle.  
  
and feel slightly better about my procrastination. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 04:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the shitpost went rogue into a normal post hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Varian Day 1 Winrate! OP!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 22:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HotSLogs has his win rate at 28.6% in Quick Match!! Out of control! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 22:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Region: NA

Battle Tag: Romo#1498  
   
Recruit-A-Friend Link: https://battle.net/recruit/KMK5BHFWVV  
   
I prefer HL/Ranked but I play QM and UD plenty too. Love getting parties of 3, 4, 5 stacks for any mode!!  

I'm on a lot!  
  
Also I'll be streaming a bit this week at Twitch.tv/RomoDC   
  
Especially if I get a dedicated partner for the Nexus Challenge would like to steam the whole thing!  
   
Also my gf plays on NA too!  
  
Battle Tag: HiddenSquid#112616
   
Recruit-A-Friend: https://battle.net/recruit/W8S2NNPZR7  
   
Preferred Game Mode: QM/UD/TL/Brawl/AI
  
Availability: Later in the day EST/Night  
   
We both play on the same computer, so when I let her! jpjp! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 21:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in this thread </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 21:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since Westworld has started have you started calling yourself Dr. Ford?  
  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: You can make a wrist pad to use at your computer out of a t-shirt or dish towels. Plus you can wash it too! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 21:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all know using padding for our wrists at the computer can help alleviate some of the stress and pressure that's put onto the nerves when leaning on the desk to type or use the mouse.  
  
I bought a pad for my mouse and keyboard, One wore out over time, got surprisingly dirty, and was retired (the rogue coffee drop and one semi spill) and the other ended up with a couple holes from wear and tear (and beads! beads everywhere!). I kept forgetting to buy a new one when I was at Staples/order it online. I'm young and haven't had any pain or anything. While I do find them comfortable I guess I didn't prioritize it enough but it is something I want for my wrists.  
   
I originally made one out of 3-4 ~~fish~~ dish towels, 6 x 6 or 6 x 8 inches (what? you don't know what a fish towel is?!? *jeez*). I laid them on top of one another and rolled/folded them. Sometimes they required rubber bands on one end or both ends to stay rolled and neat. You def could use glue too I guess, especially if it's going to be permanent. I also figured out (aka was painfully obvious) you could wash these if you did spill something (Dog's ambitious hop to my lap knocked a cup over).
  
I also learned you could use a t-shirt. My rag contaption lasted a while. It's end was still a bit premature but they worked great. Were soft, washable, I could use them as rags if I had to.   
  
I needed something new though. Their eventful end (lol...working late, and tired led to an interesting end for them) found me in need of a new one.  
   
So I did the same thing with a white undershirt that had a stain and was put to the side to become a rag. I took another one that was a little small on me athe moment too.  
  
For the keyboard pad I did cut off the sleeves and the collar so it wasn't so lumpy but play around with it as much or little as you need. Fold it wide/roll it up, throw a rubber band on each end and there you go. Depending on how you fold it you can even make it shorter to for only one wrist if you were gaming and needed space for something else ( I have a bluetooth keyboard also for when I stream and a chromebook nearby too).   
   
Anyway, they make for good makeshift on the spot solution until I get to the store to buy one.   
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 20:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heroes of the Defiance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 20:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so glad this post is here and this answer is too! I was about to make a post right now actually like  
  
Bliiiizzzzzzzz....anyone? Um there's sorta this big tourney that I really want to watch!  
   
p.s. need a caster? have experience w/ Heroes United! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 20:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> peer spite sorta works too. 
   
but my your bro is a dog eh? can't believe that. 
   
**rumor started:** *confirmed* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 20:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> holy fuck how awkward is that. 
  
jesus christ. do people not talk about this first? what makes someone think it's a good idea to ambush someone with marriage?  
   
*marriage* **wtf** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> subborn or dumb. 
  
or just doesn't talk about it before he does it. and that's def the latter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to be fair, it is the dogs. 
  
i don't think i'd have really...that much anger ever to kill someone out of it. Like not much would push me to do something so rash.  
  
The dogs though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, meanwhile you and me are gonna track her down and roll out the plastic! 
  
amirite? yeah? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> giiirl, that ring was a semester of college, take it and ruuuuun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3soooooooooome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, you tell em! You're exciting and interesting too! You special lil' snowflake!  
  
Insecure, probably a bit. But aren't we all? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah and a ton of security works as theatre.  
  
As much as it's a pain in the ass for us right now, at times, *cough TSA* to someone who doesn't understand that they travel through or hear reports taveling through an airport... 
   
hell even at their own airports they see how AMerican security has upped the ante and automatically rule that out asa  possible place to target or repeat of their biggest attack yet.  
  
So this very much worked in a similar way. And I bet these guys got that. As much as people look at this now like, "Yeah, they'd show that shooter!" I bet these people very much understood, hell the two guys sitting there probably had that conversation.   
  
"You think he'll actually come? How would this go down if he did?" 
  
"No, son, he'd drive by, see us sitting here, and drive away. Don't worry. And if shit does it the fan boy, Imma look out for you, ya hear? You gonna make it threw this. I hear your momma maken' meatloaf tonight, and you're gonna be there for that meatloaf." 
  
"But how you'd know that? Mr. WIlliams are you sleeping with my momma while Pa is serving?" 
  
"Listen here boy  
   
Anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> true that. i realized it as soon asi finished typing it but said, 'fuck it' it's the internet and it's time to internet fight!  
  
nah i'm playing my bad. was just too lazy to correct myself at the time.   
  
good day to you sir! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
