<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3428</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 12:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's true....all of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE think that Moon is the Citizen Kane of movies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 06:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 04:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5,849 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 12:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I am OBJECTIVELY better than CDPR"-Todd Howard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here is a picture of the Witcher 3 case. Need I say more (   ) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 07:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 10:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The Witcher 3 is worse than Fallout 4"-Todd Howard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL There once was a man who bought Doom on Consoles. His name... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 07:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 00:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is strange because I no longer have access to online. I looked everywhere to see if it was maybe a free weekend of some sort, but I guess not.  I had it for like an hour went to bed and when I woke up it was gone. \\\_()_/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 21:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Strange free Xbox live </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 20:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On 5/13/2016 at 2 am I was able to play online as if I had Xbox live gold, with any account that had Xbox live silver.  I was playing a few hours before on Dark Souls and it had to start in offline mode, but at 2 am it started in online mode. Currently at 12 pm I can no longer play online. Does anyone know what this was? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 06:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a deck, and was looking for places to buy/play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 23:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will try that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 01:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk my 360 has been running well with every other game and I have more than enough space for the install, doesn't seem to be overheating either(I have the slim). Might be a sign to upgrade to next gen once the PS4 neo and the Xbox One slim come out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 20:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually I am just borrowing the game to see if I want to buy it. I was wondering if it was the game just being glitchy and a bad port or if it was my 360. I will try reinstalling and cleaning it out.

EDIT: Reinstalled and cleaned out the dust and the cutscene ran better but still lagged a ton. Oh well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know why this glitch is caused or if it is fixable. Xbox 360 (Not my video but same problem) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 20:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 20:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What sites do you use to buy online? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 05:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read some yelp reviews about "All About Games" that were saying some pretty bad things about it.  Do you think its a good place to play and buy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yu-Gi-Oh in Boise area </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 00:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone know of a good place to play and buy Yu Gi Oh in the Boise area? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 21:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point,but I just think the show has very inconsistent rules of time travel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 01:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rip is trying to stop Vandal Savage before he takes over the world, if he succeeds he wouldn't have a reason to go back in time an stop him. Paradox. Kronos(aka Mick) shot down the time ship containing Mick which made it crash in 2046 Star City. Paradox.  In 2046 Mick wants to stay but Snart knocks him out which leads to their split and Mick becoming Kronos. Paradox </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 00:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a paradox. Kronos created himself. In the next episode Rip wants to kill a boy who will basically be the next Hitler. So explain to me why Rip can go back in time to kill "future Hitler"(which will change his own timeline immensely) why couldn't they go back and pick up Ray, Kendra, and Sarah?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 00:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of it altered the past because there had to be one timeline in which Kronos didn't fight them so that they didn't crash. Just as there are timelines in which Star is destroyed in 2046 and one where Ray, Sarah, and Kendra didn't get stranded.

EDIT: plus Rip is altering his own timeline in every episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 22:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you kidding me he changed tons of stuff, he shot them down twice. One of which is what led to Mick being betrayed by Snart in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 21:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heatwave shot at himself \_()_/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Xbox 360] Looking for Experienced players to do VOG </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 20:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First time vault of glass raider. Looking for help.

Gamertag: SavedFlipper0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 23:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably not. The show is really cliche and isn't original in the slightest. Not to mention all of the love triangles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 17:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrong clip </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 22:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It isn't because of training.  He most certainly has to let the attacks hit him at the speed he can perceive time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 02:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually traded in 4 DS games to get an Xbox 360 for $15. I like Nintendo games, don't get me wrong, but I feel that if I can get a better game at an equal or lesser price I won't buy another Nintendo game. To each their own I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 02:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I guess that is fine, I just don't like how Nintendo has their games prices go up past the original price instead of down. It has really turned me off of buying Nintendo games because there is no decent time to buy(my personal opinion). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 02:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then let me compare Batman Arkham City to Skyward Sword. Batman Arkham City has a 95.94% and Skyward Sword has a 93.15%. Does THIS mean that Batman Arkham City should cost $30 more than Skyward Sword because it has a 2.79% higher rating than Skyward Sword? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 02:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is what I am saying. Let's say there is someone who likes Uncharted as much as you like Pokemon(they both are very highly rated games). The person who likes Uncharted can get the game for $5 or less, the person who likes Pokemon will have to pay 8 times that amount for a game of equal quality(objectively). Do you think that Nintendo games are over priced?

EDIT: also not saying it is stupid to buy Soul Silver for $40 because that is how much I paid for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 02:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let us go back to Skyrim and Ocarina of Time 3DS. On Gamerankings Skyrim has a 95.15%, OOT 3DS has 93.89%. Does this mean that Skyrim should cost $30 more than OOT 3DS because it is 1.26% higher rated? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 02:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but if you could only get Naughty dog games on the PS3 and uncharted cost 40 dollars because Sony stop printing them it would be considered a classic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 01:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you as the consumer want to pay more money for a Nintendo game then for any other game released by another company. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 01:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it a classic because it is a good game or because it is hard to find at a cheap price. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 01:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But do you think that those games are worth the price when you could get 8 other amazing games for the price of one Nintendo game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 01:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What modern Nintendo games are you talking about specifically? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 01:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is what I am talking about, at other companies when the game sales start to fall they lower the price of the game, but when this happens to Nintendo they stop production. Nintendo is also known for creating artificial scarcity to drive up the price of used games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 01:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
