<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2894</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 34 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Male  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both, it depends on the size of the project and type of work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> German Chocolate  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 05:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks like a tornado drill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm the remaining champ with -15, post still standing. I wasn't even looking to get in the race!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I grew up broke in a poor area. We got treated like trash. I still got treated better than any brown or Asian person in that town. 
Some badly dressed dirty looking lady was racist to my 2 year old step son in a gas station and older guys tell me about their colored friends. 
Now I'm an executive and very few of my peers are not white males. I can go 2-3 months past inspection on my truck and speed while passing officers receiving a friendly wave from the good officer. 
My long term GF is a former D1 soccer player, driven, beautiful and smarter than me. Sometimes people are rude to her for no reason until I walk up and look them in the eyes. I look hard as f until I see the yellow coward scared little soul. Some people will look right at us and I'll speak and they will turn their heads. Luckily for them my girl is smart and nice and I love her because I'm a person that loves a good fight especially when I have something I'm fighting for. She's used to it. I'm not so it's harder for me to just move on.

I'd say I'm on the privileged side.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 13:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. That would make the story less odd though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 06:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was at my friends camp in Delaware I think near the Indian river. We were staying in his grandparents camp. 4 dudes in a trailer shape house but I think it was an actual house they called a camp. We got there at night and I slept on the way down. We were in college at the time. Me and my roommate stayed in one room with two twin beds that were on opposite sides of the room. We all went to bed around 1. We were getting up in the morning for some fishing. 

This is where it gets odd. We were both in our bed with the lights off. I was laying with my eyes open and I started to see a gray smokey like figure above my roommates bed. I didn't say a word and really didn't think much of it until my roommate said "hey *my name* quit f'n around. I remained silent. I stared to get a bit scared. He said my name in a more panicked way and I said "I'm over here dude". He then said "turn on the lights" I said "no way I'm not moving" he then said our friends name and said get the f out of here. This whole time it looked like the smokey figure was kicking at him that was in front of the bed and one was floating above the bed. He jumped out bed and turned on all the lights in the building. He tried to get me to leave right then but I was to tired. We left at 6 am and he didn't enter that room again. I believe he sat in the recliner in the living room all night. I drove home.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 06:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That blows dude. I'd have to think your wife would understand the circumstances but so long as it doesn't eat at you I can see why you don't say anything. This is a good outlet for those thing I guess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 06:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They can get you in the am. You get woke up to someone on you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 06:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prob an x-large t-shirt wearer maybe 2 x. BMI in the 50's would've been my guess. I could have easily got her away from me had I not been completely drunk. She maybe had me by a few lbs I was 180-190 range. I'm guessing she was 5'3-5'5.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We did have a few beers but the guy that was letting us stay wanted to get up early and fish. We had plenty I'm surprised he didn't hit them up or leave me there!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are the only one that didn't get it. Just accept you skimmed and your processes is flawed then move on. I get paid pretty well to write so your judgement falls on deaf ears. Good day, don't be a douche to people that comment on your posts. It's childish.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If that was to me no dude she wasn't but I've consented to worse since... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't describe the details of what she did nor did I say any other people were having sex. I passed out in a room by myself and she came in and did what she did. My buddy came to check up and caught her and pulled her. You are a poor reader my friend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
