<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1497</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fat melts into a sticky mess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ride height looks pretty high? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Semi virgin in that you've only taken it up the arse but not given it? And is what you play a rusty trombone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a shithouse analogy. You're they type that insists on commenting about male circumcision in an FGM discussion. Why must you do this? Are you incapable of sticking to the subject? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm reluctant to say it for sure. Long time since I did those kind of problems. I do remember one question about a propane tank where you had to work out the vapour to liquid ratio. You used a phase diagram to solve it. My thinking is that if there is liquid at the bottom, it requires a certain pressure exerted by the vapour to keep it in the liquid state. So, if you were to draw off some vapour, the liquid level would decrease to maintain a constant pressure with two phases present.

But don't take that for gospel. It could be my imagination and entirely wrong. Perhaps you could reword your question and submit it again? 

I'd like to hear about it once you figure it out, though. I'm slightly embarrassed that I can't tell you the definite answer, sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that's what's going on. I didn't realise that's how it works. Thanks mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 12:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but islam is the worst. And this discussion is about islam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 12:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another islamic triumph!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 12:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're following the koran? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 12:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends if anyone sees. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Witcher 3] Why are many of my potions not available for crafting all of a sudden? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 12:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For example, I just went to make Raffard's and it does not appear on the menu, whether I have the ingredients or not. Gone. WTF? How do I get them back? They just disappeared. I hope this isn't some game ruining bug.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 12:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will the pressure in the tank stay constant, so long as there is some liquid? And then after that the pressure decreases? Can you use a ternary phase diagram for this? I can't remember. And I can't find a nice big TPD for oxygen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 11:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's good to hear. My friends and I were in hospital around a decade before you, judging by your age. Medical progress is staggering. I do take solace in the fact that so many can benefit, even though so many had to die. It's all I can do, really. If I had lots of money I would be trying to help the Starlight Foundation and Make-A-Wish. That kind of thing. That was in it's infancy when I was a kid but now they are huge organisations. It really does help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 11:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Seppo cunts own that now. I am in no debt of gratitude to them. Fuck that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 11:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be happy if fucking Channel 10 would show the support races, instead of interviewing D-grade celebrities while I can hear Carrera Cup in the background but not see it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 10:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw so many things like that at the hospital, it ended up driving me to drink as an adult. I was an alcoholic for years. Shit like that still invades my dreams, clouds my thoughts. I was powerless to help my friends (and not just the two I mentioned  here) and that feeling followed me for a lifetime.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 07:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck the jokes, I'm just gonna go right ahead and fire up the oven. You disgust me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best thing about train to Auschwitz is that there's always plenty of seats left for the ride home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My best mate dying in agony from bone cancer. It went on for a long time. He was riddled with it. We were 8. Had to say goodbye for the last time. Starlight Foundation got him a computer as one last pleasure. But he couldn't even use it.

And then there was the kid who lost one eye to retinoblastoma. He was at Ronald McDonald House and I made friends with him shortly after he had his eye out. It wasn't long before it happened in the other eye. The way a person acts when they know that they will be blinded still troubles me. Makes me fucking sick. I never saw him again. We were only friends for a couple of months. I'm pretty sure it killed him. Imagine that - you just got permanently blinded and you also have a terminal disease. At age 7. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's from an SJW meltdown video. I can't seem to find it, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're an ideas man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do *you* even read? I mentioned nothing about either antlers or tongues. Do you see either in my comment? And yes, I did read the bit about the Chinese people. Hence my comment. So, what the fuck are you even on about, genius? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ZOMG!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He said SA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not arguing economics, at all. Who cares where the money goes? I has to go somewhere - and it won't be into yours or my account. But if you want to play that game, would you like the price of fossil fuels to skyrocket? Stop drilling and that's what happens. You also seem to be willfully disregarding the fact that about 20% of crude oil type products are not used for fuel. And that will increase as the population increases, of course.

We need that shit now. And we need it cheap. How do you expect the world to function without it? People like you would shut down every new drilling operation if they could and then whine because nothing worked anymore. You have this idealistic view that everything would just work out. It won't. Stock markets will crash, economies will be destroyed and so on.

You're just like everyone else - it's not your fault we are in the position we are and it won't be your doing that gets us out of it. But you are happy to use things you don't need, use convenient forms of transport, throw away obsolete technology, etc. Yet somehow, you think you can keep doing this without cheap oil and gas. Please, tell me how?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the charge and what penalty applies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How exactly do you determine what is and what isn't a redhead? There's all shades of red, just like the spectrum of colours in a paint catalogue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to spout some very strong opinions about Chinese people and their culture but I'd probably get banned for it... Another day in /r/worldnews. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, where else do we get lubricants, pharmaceuticals, chemical feed stocks and so on? How do we stop using internal combustion engines by tomorrow? Where do we get fuel to mine the things we need to carry on life as it is? Where do we get asphalt to build new roads?

I'm sure all the people here pissing and moaning are using public transport, paying extra for renewable energy, not using devices dependent on mining rare earth materials, not buying throw away plastic products and industrial fibres and the list goes on and on.

Everyone is happy to whine but no one wants to personally make any sacrifices. I guess those people are responsible for ''the decline of civilization and life on earth''. Fuckin' genius, eh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://cdn.meme.am/cache/instances/folder406/500x/54306406.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TWO! Minutes... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good. The World needs cheap oil and gas. The idea we can stop drilling for that shit is laughable. Maybe we can reduce it as time goes by but right now, we absolutely need it. I'm sure all the people up in arms are doing their best to reduce consumption... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly how it begins. DON'T buy your first packet. Once you do that, it's over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GC/MS means gas chromatograph and mass spectrometer. You cannot hide or mistake anything with these tests. They would literally show any and every drug in your system (if operated by a suitably skilled person). Not only would they be able to differentiate between (say) codeine/morphine/heroin/fentanyl, they could also provide the concentrations extremely accurately.

But doing that shit is fairly expensive. It's used for all sorts of analysis, whether it be compounds in your blood or to work out what compounds you formed in a reaction. 

It might save your arse if you really need it, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not that I know of. Winfield is still (I think) the biggest selling brand in Australia and Victoria Bitter is the best selling piss. I don't care for VB, myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, the value is now going to skyrocket? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers mate. I'll have a look next time I play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then people can't live dangerously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on PC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean why do Americans pronounce it differently to the rest of the English speaking world. Because it's NOT zee. Simple as that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think so. I'll have to check. I thought stuff you couldn't make (because you lack the ingredients) was displayed, anyway. My swallow potions are always replenished. And I have white gull. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Klumpy AF! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hard work and reasonable prices. In Australia, my parents managed to pay off a house loan at ~18%. Now, cunts whine when the interest rate is raised 0.25%. 

Now, we let in foreign investors, negative gearing and all sorts of things that price the average person (like me) far out of range on land/housing in a decent area. People like me have to wait until they inherit a house and land. It's a fucking joke and successive governments have done fuck all about it.

I hope the housing boom falls flat on its face. I want to see foreign and predatory investors lose out, big time. They deserve nothing less. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They manage to load every other page. It's just sheer laziness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not happening for me. I've tried several times and there's nothing there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just shows you ridiculously crap these drug tests are. Demand a GC/MS test. That'll fuck 'em (but they won't pay for it, of course). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that won't kill everyone particularly quickly. That's what I'm saying. This stuff is over exaggerated. It's annoying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno? I thought maybe that's what's happened. Can't make it because it isn't listed. I made it once and now it is not shown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 12:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm reluctant to believe *everyone* would die in a matter of days. There are some pretty remote locations that are nowhere near the targets nuclear weapons would be aimed at. There's huge tracts of land that could and probably would remain OK for a least a little while. Everyone perishing within a day doesn't seem realistic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Witcher 3] Do you lose the ability to make potions if you sell the recipe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 11:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope not. If you do, then I'm fucked. I just went to make White Raffard's and it's no longer in the menu.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 10:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, cheers mate. I got 2013 and it works fine. I just compared the uploaders across the different sites and made a decision based on that. It works perfectly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 07:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was acting like a complete tard, I might add. That band was nowhere as big as he thought it was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 07:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> which one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it hard to use? I've heard of it but I dunno if I have the skills to use it effectively. I was thinking something simple like this for non-technical people:

https://adnauseam.io/

Poison their well and make the data useless.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's pretty good. Last time I got one it was $22 and that was years ago. Fucking great smoke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yawn. They went up and said hello. Complete non-issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What part about I don't want to help advertisers (even if I remain completely and utterly anonymous) don't you get, Jodie? We aren't here to make a buck for you. 

WTF do I get in return for you getting hold of that precious data (that won't be secure, no matter how much you promise it will be)? It's like a fucking self-serve checkout - where's *my* discount? Why should I work for you?

I mean FFS, there's even a banner at the bottom of that page I had to block because it's annoying as fuck. And an autoplay video. If that's what advertisers do, why on Earth would you think anyone wants to help advertising cunts like you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Winfield) Winnie Blues. Commonly consumed with VB:

https://2dbdd5116ffa30a49aa8-c03f075f8191fb4e60e74b907071aee8.ssl.cf1.rackcdn.com/11044657_1462033170.9243_funddescription.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's called 'pleaching'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember when those cunts played at the local RSL and my mate nearly started a fight by pulling his dreadlocks. Hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RYO: 

1. Capstan 

2. Port Royal 

3. Bank 

4. Peter Stuyvesant 

5. Winfield Blue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's fucking garbage. Last week I pressed reload just over 200 times to get anything but a "boo hoo our servers are too busy and we can't be bothered to spend time or money on them" message. And what I got wasn't what I wanted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking to get Microsoft Office but the links on TPB look sort of dodgy... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any other places I should be looking? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks mate. I'm fucking jealous. How much did that work out for each one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of muslims would do well to remember that when in the West. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheap particle board won't stand up to the rigours or war. Jesus, it won't even stand up to every day living. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck's sake. There always has to be one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it does not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marry me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, how I long to be able to afford a miniature turbojet/turbofan engine. Whether it's in a plane or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When it can fly autonomously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell me about it. Why isn't Chechnya a practice target for Sarmat or Topol-M or some variant thereof. You're not getting your own country because your retarded religion demands it. That needs to be nipped in the bud. Immediately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks man. I'm looking to import small quantities of whatever takes my fancy. I tire of the bullshit restrictions here. I want nice packaging and something different, in general. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 12:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got a set of Monster cables that someone gave to me. They fucking suck. They are so tight I've nearly damaged equipment getting the RCA plugs on and off. Absolutely ridiculous. Whoever originally bought them must have discovered the same thing. I mean, there's a firm fit and then there's fucking lunacy. Monster are in the lunacy category. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 11:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dear SMH, what part of DON'T PLAY don't you fucking understand? Autoplaying videos when I ask you not to is a sure way to get me to read your paper or turn off my adblockers.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 11:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And they come in two physical forms:

https://68.media.tumblr.com/830a6d9855abe4dd371d92e2edf3d65f/tumblr_nezmsb8kYv1s04h2ho1_500.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 08:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Level it for a third time? They just don't seem to learn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 08:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They told you not to look... and you fucking looked, didn't you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 03:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but we're talking about muslims. Did you notice? Can you not stick to the subject? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 03:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a retard. You do not know better than medical professionals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did they arrive at the number 1760? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stupid. Annoying. Etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You used my history as the main part of your argument, saying I was wrong in my comment here because I said something else, somewhere else. You're pretty dense. You made the most pathetic of insults possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Wrong. I'm not afraid at all. I just want to see them fail. They are no different than an insect that annoys you. You don't go running inside to hide, you get the fucking spray out. I don't want them to keep treating women like shit. Or non muslims like shit. Or any of the other things inherent to their backwards way of existence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe. But I have bigger dreams than Hitler. Ovens and camps? I could do better than that, given the funds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, you go through my rather uneventful history and that gives you some kind of upper hand in an argument you won't actually take part in? What part of what I say on other subreddits is related to what I say here? Jesus christ. Why don't try and engage in some form of argument, instead of letting your 'research' talk for you? 

You know what sub you're in. Don't try and 'educate' us (fuck I hope you aren't a teacher) on what is appropriate. Fuck off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes, sometimes not. I hate muslims. I'm in no way afraid of them. Why would I be afraid of them? I just don't want to see them get their way. I don't want to see them have their caliphate. I don't want them to be at peace with anyone or anything. They just need to be eradicated, that's all. Like killing a bug that annoys you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, another reddit detective. Nice work, Sherlock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WTF are you even doing in this sub? Shut up and fuck off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let them have hate and division. Let them try and wage war on the powers that be. The Western World will enslave them at best and destroy them, at worst. Bring it on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are you here? Why are you spouting this drivel, especially in this sub? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, what race are muslims, smartarse? Why not call it what it is, instead of lumping it in with other, non related bullshit? And what is this shit doing in this sub? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Contempt is not a phobia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How isn't it? Severe pain requires the administration of (possibly) narcotics. They don't do it for nothing. There's no legal question about it.

This is what you get when you don't believe infants need analgesia:

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pain_in_babies#Late_19th_Century </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I got to that heap of shit of a movie, I'd keep peeling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 11:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the official size of a piece of firewood? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 11:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why am I not surprised? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 10:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You won't hurt me no more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 10:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you ever shower? You've got moss growing up your arm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 10:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://img.memecdn.com/By-your-powers-combined-I-am-captain-planet_o_128937.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 09:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are the lap times reported like that? The first one is +0.128 instead of zero and the second one is an hour and something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 09:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could probly check that out, for a small fee... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 09:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the story with Jane's? Do you need to pay to be able to look at anything good or is there a section where anyone can read detailed reports? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 09:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do the symbols for Italy represent? Nightsticks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 09:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Czech one is cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 09:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We used to play 'run away from the nigger'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 09:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many public pools have you been banned from for creating a giant oil slick the second you jump in? Someone has to clean that shit, man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 09:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Islam in action. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
