<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2069</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rolling stone is better than wikipedia right?

LOL theres different types of action you retard. Resident evil is nothing like bad boys or transformers but all have action in.

28. Days later is first and foremost a horror, with action and sci fi mixed in

Also admit your game idea was shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think rolling stone destroys a wiki list.

Can you admit your survival idea was fucking retarded now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone can edit wikipedia, thats a worthless claim </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rolling stone calling it action surely trumps your little fan edit, as well as an action movie channel on youtube calling it action horror </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rolling stone destroyed your little wikipedia list LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And http://www.rollingstone.com/movies/reviews/28-days-later-20031009 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also 

https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=FW7GalNPl6o </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao isnt wikipedia fan edited? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 28 days is action horror. You mad girl?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao have you seen the movie? The whole last half hour has no dialogue and zombies chasing and fighting soldiers and jim going rambo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Counter this...the entire last hour is action scenes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont need to refute it lol the entire last  half hour is fucking action </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You admit you are wrong and your survival game idea was shit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol this sub is full of cucks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The entire  last half hour is action lmao retarded fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im sorry, youre a spastic with zero iq. Survival game lmao dumbest fuckin idea ive ever heard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said it was action horror, you stupid fuck. Movies arent limited to one genre.

And the whole last half hour was action you fucking moron. Go talk about it being a survival game lololol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clearly you are retarded, the last half hour is all action sequences </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a horror movie with action in it spastic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean wtf do you think scenes of running zombies into mines against a bunch of soldiers with assault rifles is ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Erm I said action horror, retard.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep lol. Survival games are shit bruv </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, 28 days was a fast paced action horror. Slowing down to eat, drink, etc is pretty lame in most games. Thats the last thing a 28 days later game needs.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whats the problem? Its brilliant! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I voted leave and proud! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was actually really good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That too. It doesnt seem to make much sense at the moment.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rip piers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know...but its more the name or association. Its like bad memories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly i dont really regret the purchase based on the sheer amount of fun.  That said, im very forgiving of technical errors and i genuinely got pissed at it a few times, especially freezing and having to reload five minutes each area. So....id say honestly it depends how much technical stuff you can handle. If they patch it up to a better standard then id reccomend it for sure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont think we need yet another survival game tbh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sniper Ghost warrior shoots itself in the foot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im not going to lie, when it actually works, its a lot of fun. In pure gameplay terms, i have enjoyed it far more than say ghost recon wildlands.

But as much as ive enjoyed it a lot, man does it ever try hard to make you hate it.

It takes five minutes to load into each region. Ive never had a game freeze so many times on me, only to have to reload the game adding another five mins loading. Glitches such as most wanted enemies ive killed not counting even though they still show up. Being dead though they are impossible to kill again. 

Its a real love hate experience. If they had ironed out the massive technical errors, and im someone whos quite forgiving usually on that front, it would have reviewed far better.

Gameplay is an 8, but the tech side drags it down to 6. It seems it should have opened with "made despite cry engine" considering how hard thats said to be to use. 

I truly hope the franchise gets another shot, hopefully with a better engine. Theres a damn fun game beneath all the sorry technical messes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still really really doubt that chris would ever have  joined umbrella.
I mean i believe its the real chris, just feels like a betrayal of his character. That name would be posion no matter how hard they tried to redeem itself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 13:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see merkel as a traitor to her own country, the hitler of germany you might say </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 13:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you click the link. Thats not me saying it, its science.

All "races" of people are genetically , biologically equal. Whats less racist than that? Or are you the one pretending that people are different based simply on skin? Whats thats called again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 12:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The EU leaders pass laws that are more sympathetic to criminals , not victims.

As for shady...

http://www.brusselstimes.com/magazine2/2907/5-of-the-largest-eu-scandals-in-our-history

And that was exactly my point, EU cant do jack shit . Yet they still deal with russia. Because thats how reality works, son.  You just have to bite the bullet sometimes and deal with shitty countries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 12:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was great. I wish it had gotten a sequel. It was basically 28 days later the game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 11:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Well we could send them back with known extremist to boot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For one thing, India has already been told no. So there you go.

And shady? You act like the EU hasnt let putin and his chechneya buddies run riot over the gay community anyway. They havent done shit to stop it either. Sometimes life means having to deal with shady folks. And the EU sure as fuck has some shady figures in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoever said it was all going to the NHS? Can you tell me where anyone specifically said that? That wouldnt be logical. You would assume that it would be spread out, including to fund the nhs. But i guess that ruins your little narrative doesnt it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come back in five years and if UK is still around and doing well, you'll look the cretin then, wont you, little billy bitchcakes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You cant be racist when  race does not exist, factually </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.newsweek.com/there-no-such-thing-race-283123


Biological races do not exsist amongst humans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The UK will be fine.  I am perfectly happy if we had stronger ties with Russia, China, India, etc. 

I guarentee it will be fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are bullies because they force laws onto soverign countries, they are bullies because they force immigration quotas onto soverign countries with no regard to culture or size.
They are bullies because if you dont go along with their plan for the reich, you are rail roaded. Look at them replacing greeces democratically elected leader for a pro eu puppet, or look at them forcing ireland to vote a referendum multiple times untill it went their way.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im asking you about the racist remark, dont deflect please, explain how its racist. You do know "latvian" isn't a race, right? Or are you truly ignorant and cannot understand the concept of what race is?


And angry? LOL Im extactic we won!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How was that racist, in any way? Please explain before throwing words you dont understand out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Triss a 6???? BLASPHEMY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a great game sunset was. Sadly underrated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they are allies, who needs enemies? They are bullies . They are not allies, as you can see how they respond to a democratic decision. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL sturgeon couldnt rip a damn fart  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> all that money not being wasted on brussells any more, for a start </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont care if it doesnt, i just wont feel sorry for them when it happens again.  It doesnt need to make a difference, but is a nice little fuck you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brexit was a great move. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well no, but i think they will have a lot more attacks without our help.

Which would just be too bad. A real shame. A tragedy. Etc, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? The eu want to fuck over my country, why should i care about theirs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That racist bloated twat abbott got brutally humiliated and i loved it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we have leverage. Our security is far superior to germany and france at stopping terror attacks. Stop helping them out. Simple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bwahaahahhaahahahah thats a good one. He was a clown  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL yes, miliband sure knew about competency.

Dear god. Read what you're saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And why should we pay?

This is why withholding security info is a valid thing to do in dealing with these eu bullies.

Cosy up to russia, china, saudi arabia, etc.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Labour with these clowns abbott and corbyn will never get my vote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 11:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another fitness routine for me to ignore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 11:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont get the jericho love. Always found him middle of the road, meh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 03:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jrpgs LOL. Shit.

Witcher takes a massive dump on every jrpg in all of creation. 

Only those weird kids who worship japanese culture for no real reason would disagree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically its "the witcher 3 and 99 also rans" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im not encouraging, Im simply saying its not our fight.

Fighting against corrupt regimes has brought nothing but trouble. Look at iraq, libya, etc. True change can only be brought about from within these countries. We insert ourselves and it goes wrong.

And forcing our values and ideals on other countries with extreme differences wont work. 

China is slowly bringing itself around. For example climate change, ivory trade ban. Etc. It has to be natural , not forced and bullied.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You now have a job at the daily mail </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont care what they do . They arent trying to bully us around like the EU and dont interfere with us.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its good if you dont mind the tell tale style game. Less interactive but some cool branching path moments </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What other countries do is none of our business. 

Thats up to their own population to fight against.

Doesnt make it right, but its how it is.

And funny an EU country would call anyone else borderline dictators when they try to bully people who dont toe the line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And ? I think we should have closer ties with Russia, and China actually.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha like you ever had sex </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, lol who cares about karma from sheep? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL its not us planting the bomb, its just up to germany to do their own intelligence and not ask us for help.

Why should we help a country trying to hurt us? Fuck em. They are trying to hurt the UK over a democratically made decision. They are not allies . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some nobody, im sure glad my vote counted for more than yours!

Spoilers...my side won! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to use your best cards. Thats ours. And if EU want to fuck the UK over, then I would have no problem with using security issues as a trump card, so to speak.

Our  intelligence services are the best in Europe. Fuck us over, lose that. Seems fair  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man you guys are lil bitches </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing as UK has had far more success in stopping potential attacks than france and germany, we shouldnt hesitate to use this as a negotiating tactic.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found soma and amnesia disappointing. Keep in mind I only managed to play amnesia when it finally hit ps4. Hasnt aged well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah so youre a pedantic twat. Gotcha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do know it was on ps3 right? Which kinda has a lot to do with playstation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL you remainers act like its the apocalypse.

We will be fine. EU are just bullies , and other countries exsist outside them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 00:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you cant talk about any old sony games? Are some of you nerds that precious? "Omg it HAS to only be ten minutes old!"

Im a nerd too but people like you are just pretentious anal cocks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 00:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mods deleted a perfectly fine thread for no reason that was generating discussion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lol we cant discuss multiplatform games here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scurred of cyborg. LOL . 

Worst champion ever. Not only did she cheat to win with blatent after the bell shots, she was all up for the next fight till cyborgs name came up and she needed surgery for her hand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For sure.  Its brilliant, a true rebirth of the series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha thats exactly how it felt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 08:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im truly sorry for everyone this happens to. We are supposed to protect our vunerable and this is disgusting. Honestly hope it gets overturned </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Singularity is a sadly forgotten gem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 08:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 08:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Started very slow, too many meaningless tasks. But really got into it after a few hours </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 08:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dying light is one of the best games of recent years anad the dlc was even better.

I cant wait for more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 08:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absoloutely loved this game. Dont know wtf they were thinking with the third forogtten game that killed the franchise.

I would love a new wrestling or fighting game with this engine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 11:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mentioned muslims, not me. 

Wow what a racist you are for assuming! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 11:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats fair, because i voted leave and thats all i know about her. I dont really like her though because the english National front are pretty scummy so assume french one is too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep because god knows the french have had no problems with immigrants and a certain religion. Wow it sure is comfortable for my head down here in the sand!

You dont need to like her to understand why some french people would vote for her, and i dislike her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean "pointing out sjw hypocrisy"

For the record, i enjoyed the new gb. Just saying when it doesnt fit your agenda, you sjws sure shut the fuck up fast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where were you sjws when the new ghostbusters made all men out to be retards and shitty people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People are weak. Supporting taliban scum </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poor PC cuck sjw, got destroyed by downvotes lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are retarded lol, everyone downvoted you to oblivion because you are a politically correct cuck weakling! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL Im not trying to get a rise, Im genuinely happy that soldier is free. Justice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL youre getting downvoted cuz youre talking shit and have no idea what context is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol uk, only nation where dopes defend taliban who would muder them in a second </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was in the public interest to take put a terrorist soldier who would never give up his jihad. Good on him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Executed a taliban fighter? Get him a medal! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol notice youre getting rightfully downvoted because your views are idiotic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know horror way more than you, I would bet. It examines the darker side of human nature. And guess fucking what, dummy? Misogyny is one of them. The game makes it absoloutely fucking clear its the position of monsters and is pathetic. Horror shines a light on the darker side of man.

Its a shit review and I wouldnt be surprised if you or a family member wrote it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Show me anywhere that game paints misogyny  as a good thing or something to aspire to, from a regular persons point of view, and you might have a point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edwin, is that you?

Critiquing a horror game for being horrific is absoloutely missing the point of the genre.

The entire review is garbage. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats what melina said </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. Its not portrayed as a good thing at all.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
