<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3191</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cant see cant see a democrat winning here. Steve king could get caught on tape blowing a water buffalo at a satanic orgy and the democrat would still lose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After seeing this, id like to put up a statue of lenin in public places just to see peoples reaction. Most wont know who it is. The responses could be youtube worthy in conservative areas. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The new white house will have Trump stamped on it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. I have no consumer debt. Only debt I have is my house. So the averagw of those with debt is higher.

Alot of that likely includes a car loan which is at a much lower interest rate than credit card debt. They should break this into different buckets. My car is paid off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope the women on here are enjoying the guys cracking jokes about ourselves </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He means he us 30 years old. Lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Debtors prison. Your bill will keep going up in jail too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> im a guy. Sign me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He will be chasing to canada or the arena keague </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds rather homoerotic. Fifty shades of Ezekial here you come </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grabbed the center by the ass pussy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then they should keep doing what they are best at.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Likely has alot of pain, etc that nfl players dn talk about. Michael Strahan showed his crooked fingers last year and said ll long time nfl players are like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 19:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such a jets thing to do. What a waste of cap space. They will suck anyway. So just suck with a cheap and save cap space for the future. This is dumb. If your gonna be shit, be shir on the cheap. Cap space rolls over to the next year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 19:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats right patriots should pay him $25m/year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With all the chaos over Brexit, now would be a good time for Argentina to attempt to take the Maldives again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 23:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What non-politician would make the most fucked up leader of your country and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What world leader has the weirdest sexual fetish and what is it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What us a surefire method for easy comment karma? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Washington Post rips Daniel Snyder callng him a Man Child </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 05:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giants fan: does DJ Fluker totally suck? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 02:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giants had the two worst stsrting tackles last year. They just signed Fluker... Is he total shit?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Askreddit hates the cowboys too. I got alot of upvotes trolling the cowboys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 02:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What non obvious thing is a guaranteed down vote on specific subreddits? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 18:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the difference in responsbilities between GM and team president? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it varies Between organizations. Traditionally, I think the GM manages the scouts, is in charge of the draft board, and in aquiring players and hiring the head coach. I would guess in those cases the president reviews contracts and probably manages the business side.

However, it sounds like team President John Elway handles aquiring talent stuff in Denver. I would bet that Tom Coughlin has final say in picking talent in Jcksonville. 

With the Giants, I never hear the team president mentioned in the press. Its always about the GM picking players. I dont know if that signifies how the team runs internally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Great to be a Giants fan in DC. Redskins fans are shitting themselves </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 06:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Top 2 wrs are gone. QB hates it there and wants a trade. Shitbag own fired the gm and claimed it was because he was a drunk to get out if paying him. The fans want to protest at redskins park.

There misery makes me all tingly inside. Its so much fun to rub it in and make them feel worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which franchise would have the best all time offense or defense </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rules: player has to be very good when he played for you. Preference is given to players who are known fir being on your team.

Example Patriots could use Darrelle Revis since he was great for them. Though preference for guys who were great with a franchise over many years.

Jets cant use Ronnie Lott and the Cardinals cant use Emmit Smith

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Donald Trump declared his shit didn't stink, Sean Spicer would state he keeps a bowl of it in his bedroom due to the refreshing aroma. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know the cap hit on Brandon Marshalls contract? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cant find it on the web. May not be out yet. I doubt its $6m. Likely a big lump non guaranteed piece in year 2. 

The base contract usnt useful to determine cap hit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can you play offensive linemen or defensive tackle and not be a big fat slob? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 06:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a career yoyo dieter, when I am fat and someone says such and such put on wreight, I think he doesnt look that big. When I am skinny I think there are alot of fat people walking around. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 16:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the greatest call or line about your favorite player? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine is from 1988

Lawrence Taylor is a gladiator. If Julius Caesar was here tonight he would cheer him on

Joe Theisman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about new amd chip vs. intel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have built my own pc before. I built my current one 4 years ago. I generally only pay attention pc technology when I want to upgrade. My pc meets my needs so I am not upgrading. I am curious about the new amd chip.

The last time I built my pc the Toms Hardware reviews clearly stated that they recommended intel at all price points. This was before I used reddit. So I asked questions on Toms Hardware. The enthusiasts in there all agreed that I should stay away from amd for gaming. If I want to save money drop down to a cheaper intel cheaper.

Has amd come back? Is it just ryzen that is comparable to intel at given price points for amd or are there ohers? My understanding is that for a while intel was much better than amd for gaming.

the last time I upgraded I really liked the toms hardware builds. They had( havent checked it in a while), a budget build, middle of the road build, and a high end build. I thought their info was interesting. They all said to stay away from amd.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you get bonuses for joining teams? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 23:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I see is you can buy gifts for what looks like real money. It dorsnt even say in game what thry cost or what they do. 

Do teams help with weekly leagues? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do I fall asleep when I read even when I like the book? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How long was full plate armor as seen in fantasy books used on the European battlefields? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just focusing on Europe here. Ill probably ask about other regions in future questions. I am trying to avoid a question that is too vague.

I need to be careful to focus my question and provide context for he experts on here. I know the romans used plates for their body armor, but it was a long way from being full body. I am referring to the full body plate armor that we see in stereotypical movies/fantasy books. I also know alot of the armor is wrong and anachronistic. Such as great helms used by knoghts in full body armor. My understanding is that the great helm was absolete by several hundred years by the time full body plate armor was used. 

My knowledge comes from some youtube channels. They are fun to watch, but I dont know how accurate they are. To name a few metatron, lindybeige, knighterrant, scholargladiaria. There are others.

Those channels mention full body plate armor started after 1420. My understanding is that fire arms started being used heavily on battlefields by the end of the 15th century. That would tell me that the full body plate armor was nit used on the battlefield that long. I think I read that soldiers often used chest plates during the 30 years was in the 1600 hundreds, but that is a long way from full body plate armor.

I am trying to narrow and clarify my question. I understand the people on here are experts and I am trying to avoid asking something that is vague unfocused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Do we really need Their, There, and They're in the English since its obvious what is meant when people mix it up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 00:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm lazy and grammar nazis on reddit periodically think it makes them smart to correct me. I have never seen someone ask me what I meant when I use the wrong one. So it got me wondering. Do we really need all 3? If I was to unilaterally decide to just use "there" in all cases would anyone have trouble understanding me. 

Why do we have all 3? Was there a time when they were necessary? Are these legacy language elements? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Government employees, how has your job changed under Trump? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 02:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there scientific studies about the affect on the gene pool when different ethnic groups have children? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 19:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know Cowboys cap hit trade vs. cut? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 00:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If the giants want to sign JPP they should franchise him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 00:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they cant work out a deal they can always pull the franchise tag. Neither side wants him to play for the 1 year franchise number. This gives the giants leverage. They can sit on the tag until July 15th and then there will be less money under the cap left for JPP. 

There was a post about this on espn. It makes sense. It doesnt mean you want to sign him at the $16m a year number. It keeps him from getting poached by another team quickly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Questions about the IOS incremental Almighty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has some features similiar to Realm Grinder. So... I got all 6 masteries for good and evil. I reincarnated. In realm grinder you then get the option to pick neutral and other things to do.

I still just got good and evil with the same sub choices. Is there anything else to do at this point other than to endlessly grind for karma and get artifact drops ? It doesnt look like there is anything left in the game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hiw much affect have the economic sanctions on Russia had on their economy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These were put in place in response to the Russian invasion of the Crimea and the Ukraine. The price of oil has been low too. Is there a way to seperate out the affect of the sanctions vs. the low oil price? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cutting JT Thomas would saving another $3m </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He spent all of last year on IR. He would only be worth bringing back at the minimum and not guaranteed and that is only if they think he can get back on the field. If he gets hurt and goes on IR , the giants eat his salary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> anyone have an Elona+ download so I can use the game with Elona Custom? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 02:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played a few years ago and I am coming back. I tried using elona custom with version 1.63 and 1.64.  I could make a new character, but if I tried to use existing characters, I get 'illegal version' and the game crashes. 

The links on the website to Elona+ 1.62 download don't work anymore. Anyone have a link to Elona+1.62 or a way to get Elona Custom to work with Elona+1.64 with existing characters?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some Elona+ and Elona custom questions from a returning player. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 22:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played the game extensively a few years ago. I think the latest version was 1.35( not home to check). Got basically to the ed of the main story and ran out of stuff to do. Had every skill, etc...

Thinking about restarting with a gene file so i can have a faster start with less early game grind. I have a few questions.

1. How expensive are deeds of heirship ? Assumw idont have anything to lower costs at first. Not sure how much grinding I need to do to start getting stuff?
2. Any place deeds of heirship drop alot early? I think there is an infinite dungeon called the kitty cave or something. In there ?
3. Does blessing deeds of heirship do anything? Wiki says they give 1-3 stacks.
4. I dont remember what i have, but figure as of several years ago, just about everything. Id have to spend sometimes remembering where stuff is stashed. I figure the first stuff i should get with deeds of heirship is stuff to get alot of gold so i can buy more deeds of heirship. Are blessed stacks of scrolls of oracle the best? Any limit on how big my stacks can be? Anything better that i can aquire quickly. Pretty sure i have large stashes of stuff and i invested alot in shops. Something easy to get. Id like to start over quick.

5. Any recommended items? I dont remember what of stiff does and i dont know all the changes. I dont know what ill play yet. 

6. Any limit on how much stuff you can pass to an heir trunk? 

7. Its everything in your inventory right? Even if i totally overweight. I see on the wiki the list of stuff you cant pass.

8. Can someone help with the mechanic for making a gene? When you get sleepy, you talk to a pet you are married too ( i think i have several) and then there is an option to make a gene? Then i have a gene. So i then quit and there is an option to start with a gene file?

9. I googled elona custom. Latest version says its compatible with elona+ 1.62. The latest elona+ is 1.64. Will it work with that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please recommend your favorite short SF stories and how to find it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 21:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alot of sites review novels, finding reviews for shorter work is rare( unless its Ted Chiang). Please tell me your favorite shorter stories and where I can find them.

If its in a book please say ehich book. If its in a magazine oron a website please say which issue or a link.

Im not looking for author recommendations or magazine recommendations. I am looking for specific shorter works you likes. Up to a novella. 

Alo please say the sub genre and if its like something else that is more well known. I prefer newer works. So maybe back to the 1980s as long as the tech has not been too obsoleted that its obvious this wot work. 

I have broad tastes. SF only. No fantasy. Could be military sf, hard sf, far future, near future, have minority/transgender characters( or just white guys or not matter).

Just looking for stuff that is really good.

In particular, I read a Greg Egan shorter work thst Charles Stross linked to last year. I dont remember the title, but it was aimiliar to Ted Chiangs software objects story. Scientists created AI in a virtual world to test the theory of evolution. Really liked it. So if you know other Egan shorter works please post.

Please no novels. There are lots of places to find novel reviews. Not alot of reviews of individual shorter works.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some questions and suggestions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 18:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am playing the IOS version. The furthest I got was with a samurai to floor 25. I hve played nethack, but never got this far. Some are comments and looking for confirmation.

This is a fun nethack variant. I never liked methack before this. I found it tedious. The effort just to get your pet to follow got me to quit. I like how you made the pets follow better. 

Writing this on an ipad. Likely will have alot of typos. May be hard to read. I will edit from my pc tonight.

Suggestions:

1. Can you please look at stats. I get alot of characters with really low to mediocre stats. I think it says in the updates there is supposed to be weighted chances to a classes prime attributes. If there is a chance its too low. Could you add a base bonus to the most important stats? The only times I got past floor 10 were with good starting attributes.

2. Wizard starts are really dependent on random items. Can you again weight this toward better items. If not you might as well restart.

3. Humans dont seem to ever be a good choice. All other races seem better with every class. If I am wrong please tell me. I think humans need an upgrade. Not sure what.

4. Item destruction. I had two +5 short swords. Next thing I knew they were gone. I think they got destroyed. Can you have a setting where if a monster can destroy weapons, it flashes and if a weapon takes damage it pauses. So we can tell. I died on floor 25 when I had to downgrade.

6. Feature from Cataclysm DDA: this is also from muds. If we get hit with a negstive status like petrifying pause the gamd and make us press ok. And show the status on the screen so we can see it.

7. Keep a log of previous messages we can expand on the main screen. Its too easy to miss stuff. Allow checkboxes for what we want to see. Organize it by floor and monster. Different types. Also please include the time.

8. Wazhack feature: Access maps of other levels we have been too. So we dont have to keep notes for feature locations.

9. Wazhack festure: gem features. Please see wazhack wiki. Some gems have properties. You can embed them onto staffs to makevthem strong. You can drop them on the ground then when something gets close it explodes. Plus 2 gems can be dropped to use for teleporting. This makes moving to shops and back easier. Doesnt work if burdened.

10. Wazhack feature: please see wazhack menus. There are buttons for getting to wands, scrolls, potions instead of having to filter through the whole inventory. This is much easier and more convenient. Especially on portable like IOS.

11. Wimpy feature: common in muds. Can we set the game to pause at different hp thresholds. Like 50% and configure your character to flash or change color when hp gets low. In roguelikes, you cruise then die because you are not careful enough. Its part of the game, but the option to make it more obvious would make the game less frustrating.

12. Wazhack feature: Pet commands. Like stay. In many cellars there are traps. If my pet follows they often die n traps since they get put in traps automatically. Ineed to tell them to stay. I also would like to be able to tell pets to attack or have standing orders to avoid combat. To this point I have used pets mainly to carry stuff and tell bless or cursed.

14. All dog or cat type pets can tell bless cursed. Pitbulls should too. The problem is the types of pets that can dont last long and are not useful farther down. So stronger variants should also. I kniw you tend to get alot of karma and can divine with priests, but it can be many leveks between them.

15. Thrones/graves: the chance for negatives are so high, these are useless. I never use them.

16. Wazhack feature: I dont remember the shop name. Its in the wiki. You can pay an armorer or weaponsmith type shop to enhance weapons and armor. Its expensive. 

17. Wazhack feature: More value for levelling: you get a few skills eventually, hp and mana. Can you add options to buy additional skills with skill points? You get different skills for classes. Please see how wazhack does it.

18. Quick slot: annoying to use magic since you have to stop and open spellbook. Etc. can we have some quick slots.

19 . For IOS/Andriod: range targeting. Its really easy to press in the wring place when you mean to shoot and then move. Ine time I accidently shot a shopkeeper. So if you are targeting a friendly please let us have an option to have an are you sure popup for friendlies. Also can we click on our readied ammo to signify we want to shoot. So if we press the wrong space we dont move. You just get a message that says invalid target?

20. DCSS feature: Autowalk to features i have found on other levels. Game will pause if i hit a trap or a monster comes on screen. Makes the game less tedious. 

21. Close door: i only play on ios. I dont see how to do it. If i cant close a door, then lock is useless. Need this to rest. Later on the spawn is very high. 

22. Monster memory: if a monster did significant damage to me in the past can we have an option for it to flash and then help, i get details. If a monster attack me and it did cold or fire and i dont currently have that equipped can it flash or something to notify me? Its too essy to forget.

23. Quick slot to change weapons: its common to switch from melee to bow. If you have a sword/shield or dual wield you have to open up inventory and switch. This is tedious. Can we designate weapin sets? So can switch with a button. It will still use the turns.

24. Drop all/get all: designate items as no drop. Then drop all. Needed when overweight. Largely resolved with bags, but tedious before you have them. Same with get all. 

25. Divine all at shrines divines stuff in bags. Its tedious to pull out. For 100 karma can we divine stuff that pets carry.

26. Pets follow when invisible. I have not seen a leash. Is there one in the game? I got the invisible talent. Made pets i cant mount useless since cant follow. You should be able to call them so they can follow. Make it a stealth penalty or something. 

27. Polypiling: per update if you already polypiled an item and do it again it will explode. To reduce tediousness can we get a star saying it polypiled? And an are you sure if you accidently do this?

28. Can shops spawn a little more often please? 

29. Speed rest to remove status: can we get a faster rest option if wevhave a negative status? You get a popup. This makes the game run faster if you are just trying to get rid of a bad status. Rest pauses when a mob comes in.

30. Expand religion: this isnt nethack like, but other games like dcss and adom and powder have individual gods.

31. Sokoban: i am terrible at this. I can get past level 1, then i always end up pushing two boulders together or one against a wall. If there is a trap door, i generally dont have levitate potions to get past or some monster gets in the way and i cant push boulder. For a karma penalty can you add a pull boulder option? 

32. Melee characters are too similiar play style. Samurai, caveman, barbarisn, rogue, knight. They are so similiar. Can you make them more unique? Please see my comment about skill points and skills like in wazhack. 

33. More races and please make them more unique. Please consider ones from dcss, angband variants( like poschengband) , and adom, and elona. 

34. Make high skill more meaningful. A whopping +3 for maxxing out a skill? Also please see wazhack. Skills have opposites. As you get good at certain skills you get worse at its opposite

35. Bless not fully implemented. Blessed potions of identify still only identify one item. Blessed weapins dont seem to protect from being destroyed, etc... I dont think bless helps for everything. 

36. Amulet of life saving: i had a blessed amulet of life saving on when my samurai at dungeon level 25. I dont think it brought me back. Its hard to tell, since when you die you immediately go to a new screen and cant see the messages. 

37. If a wand or spell will bounce and kill you can you get a warning? Its a pain to close the game in ios and check the nethack wiki for the range. Same for fireball or if you will hit your pets or a neutral character

38. Can if grease: please add to protect from item destruction

39. If attributes were lowered please change their color so you know when you need to use a potion of restore ability.

40. If you ate a corpse that game a negative affect that you dont have a resistance for or a control, can the game give you an are you sure? I always found having to check the wiki on corpses annoying and on ios, i have to close the app to do this.

41. Quickslot to turn lamps on and off. Its a pain to open inventiry, etc...

Questions:
1. Raising attributes: doesnt look like training with pushing boulders, etc... Works. Any way to raise attributes other than with potions if gain attribute or small chance from magic traps?

2. When would i want to use scrolls of summoning? If i am trying to charm? Any other time? 

3. What branches other than Sokoban are in the game? What other standard areas? Any you are planning to add that are not in now? I have only made it to level 25. 

4. Are there unique bosses? The only thing unique I have run into are my revenants.

5. Any use for hallucination? 

6. Are the class quests in the game? 

7. Wishing: is this implemented? I see posts saying no, but i see mentioned in game that a blessed lamp will get a charmed genie.

8. Ever a reason to dig graves or sit on thrones? The chance of bad is so high i ignore them.

9. Excalibur: this is the only reason to play a valkyrie. Are you going to add it? 

10. Petrifying: does this eventually turn you to stone. I know you take more damage with it. If you do go to stone can we get an icon that shows on screen for how many turns? Helps me decide when i need to take a turn to use my blessed unicorn horn.

11. Do all floors have exactly 9 rooms in the main dungeon? 

12. Are there strategic reasons to real time? Other than some people like it

13. Is beserk ever useful? I attack my pets when i tested it out.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Really good short SF available online for free </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its hard finding good short SF. You have to google around. Then if you find something good you often have to buy a back issue magazine or an entire book of stories. Alot of authors end up giving away their best short SF as samples. Any really good stuff online? Please post a link. Past award winners are good too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From an American, do you have long wait times for medical care? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 03:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When republicans talk about single payer, they talk about how horrible UK single payer is. Do you have long wait times for procedures? 

I saw some republican that said there is an 80 day wait list for most elective surgeries or longer than that. Is any f this true? Are there wait list? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could have a reverse civil war and expel one state/region from your country, what would it be and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most offensive( but non bigotted) Holiday that you could create? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Superbowl Sunday an American Holiday? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When would people stop waiting for Patrick Rothfuss next book? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 23:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If the Falcons dont win, the rest of the country should march to Atlanta and burn the city doen again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 15:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fake stairs that lead out of the dungeon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 15:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hve seen this in 2 games. Downstairs, you use them. Then get a message about escaoe the dungeon or search. I searched in the usual locations. Closts, ed of hallways. Nothing. One level had a teleport trap. Ran through that 10 times in hope of finding the downstairs. Nope.

This is an annoying and stupid feature.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If twitter existed throughout all of human history who would be the greatest tweeters of all time and what would they tweet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 04:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If the world encounters aliens during the Trump administration what do you think would happen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 04:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Melania Trump may never move into White House... Are they headed for divorce? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 02:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump hits 50% disapproval faster than any president in history </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 01:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does Donald Trump remind anyone else of Geder from Daniel Abrahams Dagger and Coin books? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 00:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does karma work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My karma is negative. I didnt check it constantly, but im in sokoban. I looked at the nethack wiki and so e things in sokoban can drive down karma. I cant find anything on the web about what raises and lowers it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does this differ from regular nethack? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 03:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else think Trumps talk about a massive infrasucture project to create jobs is a lie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 04:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was one of the few things democrats agree with Trump on. Trump is going hard right. His cabinet is far right. Republicans in Congress wont support this so he will need every democratic vote. I think he is lying. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could go back in time to 2000, how would you prevent Donald Trump from becoming president without using violence? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 04:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Since Jupiter is 95% hydrogen, could its atmosphere be lit on fire? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 00:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In reference to the Hindenburg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Those of us in the Never Brady/Anyone but New England crowd will burn Atlanta to the ground again if the Falcons lose. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lets all talk about Trumps little dick to bait him into whipping it out on national TV to prove him wrong. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 00:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Adrian Peterson wants to plsy for the giants if minnesota cuts him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is 31. After 31 HoF backs typically fall apart. Go check their stats. 2 ACLs. He was suspended 1 season. At 31 I dont know what he commands. Giants have $30 m cap space and more if they cut Cruz and JT Thimas, but JPP and Hankins are FAs, they desperately need to upgrade at tackle and wide receiver, plus OBJ will want $15m a year after next year. 

If he comes in at around $4m and with little guaranteed after the first year I say yes, but.. I dont know what he commands. The vikings wont pay his nearly $12m due next year. Perkins is a JAG. Not awful but there are guys like him on almost every team. If Peterson can still play and its a team friendly deal, Id do it. 

Its on espn.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Relative newbish questions for IB3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 03:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Picked the game up recently. So Im one of the few newbs. I have played the first 2. I completed the game once. Isa is about level 65 and on awakening 38.  Siris is well behind. Im not very good at defending. Never was. I watch the videos.

1. How do you level low level weapons when you move up awakenings? I have th darkfyre gem, but alot of weapons dont have this slot. 

2. Is there value in completing the game repeatedly? I have been grinding at metius with Isa to grt gold. Spending gold on defensice gems to get max prism gem and on upgrading. 

3. What are the best maps to buy other than darkfyre? I still only have 3 blacksmith upgrade slots. Been saving up chips for the 4th.

4. Is there a way to go up or down awakenings quicker? If its easier, then id like to drop down a bunch to easily level low level weapons then go back up. 

5. Is it worth using a gem for item drops? With dupe weapons, it hasnt seemed worth it. I use a gem to make it more likely to drop gold. Gold is still tight for me, upgrading stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In the last 20 years the giants, steelers, broncos, and patriots have won more superbowls than the cowboys have won playoff games </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 05:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Upvote: Fuck Dallas. I hope Chris Christie is fucking miserable and in pain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 02:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LA fans... How much do you care about the Chargers coming to town? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 18:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conservatives failing to vaccinate their kids is natural selection at its finest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 00:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did ancient and medievil solders wear padding under their helmets? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 17:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you get whacked in the head with a limp of metal.. Whether its a sword or a blunt weapon, I would think it would hurt alot and cause serious damage even if you have a metal helmet on. I would think you wuld want some kind of cushioning under the helmet.

Did they do that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New IVAN development or IVANX? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 20:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IVANX variant had more stuff for a long time. I see some development of the main branch. Is IVANX going to be merged into it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How complete is Caves of Qud? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 18:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are rapidly adding features. Is it a 'complete game' you can finish and they are just adding features?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Throne Room is really tedious please combine options </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 15:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you make it less tedious. Group encounters together? Add an option to have the same answer to the similiar questions. 

Setting so always accept soldiers, always pay people if less than X gold. Always release if say innocent or kill/jail if say guilty. Always buy stuff is less than X. Always pay or force to join, etc...

This is so tedious right now. It ruins the experience for me because I get tired of doing it. Its a big part of getting stronger so if you don't its hard to keep up.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If someone comes to you and says they are hearing voices telling them to murder people what do you do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 22:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The guy who just murdered all those people at a Florida airport went to the FBI and said this. They turned him away. Shouldnt this be seen as an attempt to get help? What would your department do in a case like this?

I dont understand why he was sent to a psychiatric hospital for evaluation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should the Giants replace their OC? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 21:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Offensive tis terrible. Blocking is terrible, but a little better thsn last year. Loss of Shane Vereen is big, but other than that and Pugh gone a few games they have been healthy.

I detest how they use Victor Cruz. He was a pro bowl slot receiver and he cant get open on the outside. Eli doesnt wven look at him.i think he would still be a really good slot receiver. I know they like Shepard in the slot and thry have FINALLY started using Beckham in the slot. They dont rarely go with 2 slot receivers. I think thry should rotate Cruz to the slot and have him run quick slants, but they dont.

McAdoos offense used to be very creative. Now its so generic it doesnt make sense. Other teams gameplan guys open. The Giants used to do that. The redskins dont have a very good defense and they only put up 13 points.

McAdoo calls the plays and he is an offensive guy. So alot of the poor gameplan is on him too. I know the talent is bad. Tackles are terrible, which requires really quick release which doesnt give guys time to get separation. Quick decision making doesnt allow Eli to cycle through receivers and his fear of the rush is leading to bad throws.

I also dont like that the giants rarely help the tackles by chipping the edge rusher. 

I remember week 4 against the redskins. They were down two corners and they didnt bother to target the backups. The Packers had 3 CBs go down and a linebacker. Atleast one CB is definitely  out. They gotta target the backups and the safeties playing CB this week.

Still.. This gameplan is bad. You cant expect the defense to play lights out.

The gameplan was alot more creative the last two years
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How has Okwaru done filling in for JPP? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 20:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He had some big plays against Dallas, then the last two weeks, I dont recall Okwaru being me tioned at all. How has he done? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Isaac's youtube channel elligible for a Hugo award? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 20:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hugo awards are SFF awards given out by Worldcon. It is mostly for print material, but they have TV and movie awards. This should be elligible for best fancast.

I have never seen a youtube channel nominated. To nominate and vote you have to buy an non attending membership to Worldcon which costs $40. I have done this the last few years. It was worth it because authors tend to drop their material in the voter packet. 2 years ago, I got the entire Wheel of Time(since the whole series was nominated) in my voter packet.

Nomination rules have changed due to a couple of slates ruining the nomination process. You can still nominate 5 things in a category, but every addition, item nominated waters down the nomination. If you nominate one thing in a category, its worth one point. 2 and each is worth a half. All 5 and each nomination is only worth 1/5. 

It likely wont take alot of nominations to get this channel nominated if we only make one selection. There are so many different fancasts that it usually does not take many no inations before slating anyway.

Not every author drops their work in the voter packet. For several years all the authors who were nominated for best author have done it. Less the last two years. However, you still get $40 worth of SF material in the voter packet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why can't Quantum Physics be used to explain the very large? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 18:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: If the universe only expands in the vast areas between galaxies where gravitational attraction is weak, how did the universe expand when it was small and it was small and gravitationally attracted to each other? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 18:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WTF is a neckbeard? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 16:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giants going to Green Bay and NE has homefield. Its official Eli is getting his third ring. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 05:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giants going to Green Bay next week and GB may have 3 corners out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 05:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Feature Request: Better Clan search feature </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 13:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Add checkbox for clans I am eligible to join
2. Clan open
3. Rank by highest clan level to lowest
4. Filter by country for people who dont speak english. So you can pick which flags to look for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do aliens draining drops help or hurt? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 19:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do they drain more than you lose ? should you burst them right away or leave them? Its hard to tell. I think they are a net negative.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the hell is there a holding penalty every time ODB returns. Punt? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 18:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok. Exagerrating, there was one return when he ran out of bounds without one. ODB and the staff have got to be getting annoyed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you have a Janoris Jenkins status please post it here </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 21:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump reddit supporter Vanguarde2017 has 40 armed militia and is openly threatening to murder people. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 03:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Frequent the_donald, Vanguarde2017 poster claims to have 40 armed militia and is openly threatening to murder libers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 03:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has the offensive gameplan changed this year? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 23:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eli was really good his first two years in this offense. The line isnt any worse this year than it has been the last two years. Its been bad since McAdoo got here. 

I see people talking about how basic the gameplan has been. I dont recall it being this basic the first two years, but people maupy not have commented on it because they were scoring more points.

McAdoo is the head coach. If the O Coordinator is going to make changes McAdoo had to have OKd it. 

Anyone have a better memory of the last two years? Have they changed alot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: What caused cosmic inflation and then the slowdown in the expansion of the universe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 18:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a few questions related to cosmic inflation.

1. We undrstand the history of the universe down to a short time after the big bang. Is that short time the beginning of cosmic inflation or do we understand the big bang back to before cosmoc inflation?

2. What caused cosmic inflation to start and stop?

3. Since cosmic inflation has the rate of the increase in the expansion of the universe been constant or have there been other periods of cosmic inflation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Is the visible universe expanding or shrinking? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 05:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My understanding is that the expansion of the universe is accelerating and eventually everything outside of our local galaxy cluster will be moving away from us faster than the speed of light and we will never see it again.

Is everything beyond the visible universe already moving away faster than the speed of light? If so that would imply that the visible universe is shrinking. If this is true, does this mean there have always been parts of the universe moving away from us since right after the big bang?

Or has that light just not had time to reach us yet which would imply that the visible universe is still expanding?

Final question: when do scientists think the rest of the universe outside of our local group will be moving away from us faster than the speed of light.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is Eli playing so bad? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 21:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No run game... He hasnt had one in years. 

Blocking is bad. No confidence in his blind side, he was better last year. He hasnt had a good line in years and it was worse last year.

Having to get rid of the ball so fast... Less time to find an open receiver. I know its the gameplan, but they get rid of the ball so fast due to no confidence in the blocking. West coast offense often mix up how long they wait to throw even though its generally faster than other offenses.

Eli is reverting to chuck it deep on third down into double coverage when you need . 3 yards. That is so frustrating. Just move the chains.

Cruz rarely gets separation. He is out of position on the outside and he is r his old self. Sheppard is not getting alot of separation either. Beckham seems to be the only guy to get run after the catch. That is a hallmark of west coast offenses. His guys in stride so they can get run after the catch, but the other guys dont get much separation.

But in spite of this Eli is playing really poorly. Anyone watch game tape and have an idea what is going on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should the Cowboys bench Dak Prescott for Romo? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 06:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mike Pence is the hand of the king. Pence will run the country while Trump Tweets and jerks himself into an early grave. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 21:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you go to preferences- custom themes and uncheck you can down vote the_donald posts in their sub. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 20:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their mods cant permanently disable downvoting. So turn it off and downvote.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How come there are subreddits where you cannot downvote? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 19:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else get the US Department of Justice American Crime Survey Fedex them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 18:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giants fan: question about cowboys injuries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 19:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw a number of guys injured. How many are starters and major contributors? I see Claiborne listed as out. How good is his backup.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Did the universe start at a singularity or was it akways infinite, but everything closer together? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 02:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw someone post in an ELI5 sometime ago, that the universe did not start at a singularity. It is a common misconception. Everything was closer together. If so, how closer? What is meant by the universe being at the planck length if the universe was always infinite? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Upvote if you want to block /r/conspiracy from /r/all . Its a Trumpster Trash haven posting Pizzagate like lies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 21:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Is it possible to transmit power in a form other than electricity? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 16:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We use power plants to generate electricity. Are there other forms of energy we can generate and transmit to homes to power our homes? Why is electricity the only form of energy used?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any LA fans give a shit that the Chargers are coming to LA? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 02:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Are there advantages to learning multiple languages at a young age? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 17:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My understanding is that kids are generically predisposed to learn languages and as we get older its harder to learn languages. I didnt start foreign language until I was in 8th grade. I think in China/India, etc... They learn foreign languages at a very young age. Is this a better approach? Does this help or hurt in anyway learning to read and write your own language. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How did so many Western languages settle on the same alphabet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 17:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My understand is that languages basically morph over time. When groups seperate languages will slowly drift in different directions. Was there a group effort to settle on the current western alphabet to standardize writing? 

I flaired this as culture. I dont see a flair for linguistics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for hard scifi with the most accurate science </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 04:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know its SF is futuristic and fiction... but based on actual science. I read that Dragon Egg is supposed to be very good hard SF.

Less interested in Social SF. I want harder SF. For example Ian Banks is a good writer, but he doesnt provide any scienve behind what he does. I dont want to argue about Banks. I liked his books. Just an example of what I am not looking for.

I am looking for books that are more accurate today. Not books that were 1950s hard SF, but the science changed and we know the science doesnt work.

some stuff I liked

- The Martian ( i know some parts are bullshit science)

- Ted Chiang( Ill take shorter works)

- Greg Egan. I read one of his shorter works I liked.

- Three Body Problem and the sequels.


I have been watching a cool youtube channel by a guy with a physics degree who ties discussions to SF topics and does a reallygood job called Isaac Arthur. He has sparked my interest in more hard SF. Plus I have really gotten into youtube science videos, etc... So when I read SF books, I start calling alot more bullshit on the science. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook/Twitter consider banning Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 02:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [RF]We are contacted by aliens. They threaten to exterminate the human race unless Donald Trump has sex with a pig live on TV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 04:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giants Weeks 1-6 were last in Sacks and Ints. Since then they are first in both. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 23:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Is the cost of Solar Power affected significantly by geography, temperature, and degree of sunlight? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 21:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would think that solar power is most cost effectively in deserts with few clouds and its hot. Is the cost of solar affected by seasons? Days are longer in summers ( as you get farther from the equator). 

Are solar plants able to store energy affectivelt for day and night usage? What about long term affective such as shorter day times in winter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What sexual fetishes does Donald Trump have and why is one of them being a cuckold? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 03:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the easiest way to bait Donald Trump into committing impeachable acts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 03:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dungeon Masters: How long do you prep for games? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 20:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much effort is involved? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should President Trump invade and conquor Canada to solve Americas dependence on foreign? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 04:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: The US had plans to invade Canada and in 1935 built air bases along the Canadian border to support the invasion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 04:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Carolina Governor claimimg voter fraud in an attempt to have the legislature overturn the election. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 23:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Look for Free Encryption software to encrypt personal files before backup to cloud. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 18:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thanksgiving 1982: Lawrence Taylor beats Detroit by himself in spite of only playing in the second half due to injury </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 23:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: The US floats its currency in the free market, does this mean by law countries that do not float their currency, can set their exchange rate against the dollar to whatever they want and there is nothing the US can do about it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 18:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My understanding is US law lets the free markey determine the value of the dollar. However, some countries like China set the value of their currency and do not let it float.  Does this mean US law requires the US to accept whatever value the Chinese government decides to set its exchange rate at? Why would the US government let the dollar float against curtency that is not floating? 

This is economic questions and not a question about politics and using tariffs. Please keep political fights out of this. I am just trying to understand more about currency markets.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Please explain the Indian black money crisis? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 17:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: People who have worked on political campaigns, how do you deal with the job insecurity and what do you do for work between campaigns? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 04:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do they pick the books at the top of the thread? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 23:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 11 missed extra points today and counting. I have seen 4. How many have you seen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 22:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LT remembers Theismann's injury 31 years later </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 16:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NFL Channel Gameday Live reports Tony Romo to be traded after the season and he will have a say in where goes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 16:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Report is that the Cowboys will not trade him to the Browns. He will be able to renegotiate his contract with the team after the season. Romo is eyeing the Broncos.

I just saw the report at 10 AM EST </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everytime you exhale, the CO2 that leaves your body is the by product of energy used to power your body. So most weight leaves your body by exhaling Carbon since yiu inhale O2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 14:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To create energy your body uses chemical reactions to convert food into energy. It uses the oxygen you inhale to do that. The O2 gets converted to CO2 as the by product. The carbon you exhale is how the weight leaves your body.

Note: hyperventillating will just get to pass out. You still have to diet an exercise so you tke in less food and convert more to CO2.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How come the Redskins can franchise Kirk Cousins in back to back years? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 19:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the rule was you cant do it back to back. My understanding is that the Redskins can franchise him again this year. What am I missing about the rule? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumpster Trash caves and settles Trump University lawsuit for $25 million </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 22:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police Officers of Reddit: What is the funniest and/or most bizarre thing someone said to you after being pulled over? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 20:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If a Djinni ever offers you 3 wishes do not ask for money, you will have the IRS crawling up your ass demanding you explain where it came from.... ask for lottery numbers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 20:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: When did the color pink become intertwined with being feminine? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 20:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its kind of arbitrary. Pink is basically just light red. Why not light blue?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you had the power to use the Force, how would you use it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 20:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How will a contract that bars people serving in the administratiom from being lobbyists be enforced and what are the penalties? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 21:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trash talk your most hated teams fans! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 14:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When your team sucks do you still pay attention? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 06:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What position should Sean Murray from Hello Games get in the new Trump administration? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 16:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should Sean Murray get a Position in Trump Administration? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 16:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering how full of shit he is, he should fit right in. 

Secretary of Bullshit?

He could be responsible for building the wall?

Ambassador to Siberia?

Manage The White House Twitter account?

Trumps fluffer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Victor Cruz OUT against Bengals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 22:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get leaving him out if any doubt since we don't want him to get reinjured. We have NO running game so losing any receivers kills. Roger Lewis had a nice TD catch, but also had back to back drops on a drive as well. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OV and JPP Ranked 2nd and third by overthecap.com for Pass Rushers in comparison to their salaries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 22:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Note its only guys who signed contracts this year. We still need them to get there a little faster to actually get some sacks... , but this makes me feel a little better about the pass rush. 

http://overthecap.com/2016-new-contract-tracker-pass-rushing-linemen-week-9/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overthecap.com says the Cowboys will have $19m in dead money if they cut Tony Romo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 21:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://overthecap.com/salary-cap/dallas-cowboys/

Click on 2017 tab. I don't think this is accurate because nothing changes when I change to 'trade' and the other drop downs. They do for 2016. So its not updated. I see that Romo doesn't have a roster bonus so there is no urgency to cut him. Peyton Manning got cut early to avoid a $25m roster bonus. Agents negotiate that to force teams to make a commitment or cut the player as early as possible. 

I don't see the Cowboys keeping Romo as a backup next year at that cap number. Even though Romo is ok with being a backup for now, I doubt he will next year. I would expect his agent to make noise if it looks like he won't start. 

Anyone know the cap situation for Romo with 'cut before June 1/ cut after June 1, or trade ? 

What would your team give up for Romo? I know the Cowboys expect a #1. Only an idiot would do that given his age, salary cap space, and the great possibility he NEVER gets on the field again or if he does, one hit and he is out. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should the Jets go after Tony Romo? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 21:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to overthecap.com , if the Cowboys cut Romo they end up with $19m in dead money. I am not sure this is accurate. When I change the drop downs for 2017 to 'trade' all the numbers stay the same, but for 2016 I see changes. 

http://overthecap.com/salary-cap/dallas-cowboys/

I see that Romo does not have a Roster Bonus. The Roster bonus is what lead to Manning being cut instead of the Colts trying to trade him. So Romo can be kept as they work out a trade. Even given his injury history and his possibility of NEVER getting on the field again, I think somebody will be give up a second round pick for him. Someone might be crazy and stupid enough to give up a one. I know the Cowboys will ask for it. However, I can't see the Cowboys keeping Romo as a backup and he wouldn't want to stay as one anyway. The Jets will have a high Draft pick this year. Would you give up a #2 for Romo even given his injuries? I think a #3 and some other lower pick is a yes for sure as a gamble. 

If they add Romo AND he can actually stay on the field, they are a clear playoff contender. The jets cap situation is bad. They are overthecap next year if they stand pat. So I expect alot of changes (Richardson and Revis are likely gone. Decker will take a big pay cut or he is gone). Ryan Clady's $10m cap hit appears to be a bloated end of contract number that always leads to being cut or renegotiated, so that is big savings there, but alot of teams are WAY under the cap. 

http://overthecap.com/salary-cap/new-york-jets/

What do you think the Jets should do ? Go after Romo? Is he worth a second round pick? You don't know if he will stay on the field so going 'if he stays on the field he is'. We don't know. Odds are he won't play all 16 games ever again. 

Part of Romo's problem is that he always tries to be the hero. He gets hit hard alot making big plays. Alot of the time he hits them, but it just takes 1 hit to end his season or career. He would have to be coached to 'get your damn body down and don't get hurt'. Eli Manning is very good at this. I think its one of the reasons he never gets hurt. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How come the jets won't go to a 4-3 to get Sheldon Richardson in the game more? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 21:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have 4 really good lineman, isn't this a better move than having Richardson standup as a linebacker sometimes?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Westworls vs . TV show Humans? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 18:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have not seen Humans. However, the trailer looks similiar in concept tp Westworld. Robots that become aware. Is it similiar? It cant be as edgy since its not on a pay channel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
