<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2797</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 01:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> because I have been rejected a trillion times in less than a year and Im good looking and athletic... sorry that sounds cocky but come on... its easy to know if youre good looking or not. lets not kid ourselves. as evidence I have been offered (and turned down for many reasons) modeling jobs   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 01:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe if women didnt fucking hate sex so much we would hear less about rape  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> avicularia avicularia as we all know tend to get along when housed together. would an avic avic get along with a versicolor if they were housed together? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 02:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I currently have 1 adult male avic avic in a good sized (tall) enclosure. how would this go? would they fight? crossbreed? or hopefully none of the above ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 19:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks for the reply. I have not studied string theory beyond nambu-goto and polyakov yet. I still have a lot of quantum and relativity to learn. I do not have a bachelors yet or anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 19:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was NOT trying to claim anything grandiose (like him predicting quantum) at all. I was just saying that the quote reminds me of the double slit experiment and how some people interpret it. I suppose you disagree.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> this Nietzsche quote seems to describe the double slit experiment in my opinion. tell me what you think just for kicks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 02:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "That which gives us such an extraordinarily firm faith in causality, is not the rough habit of observing the sequence of processes; but our inability to interpret a phenomenon otherwise than as the result of a design" ... "Question: Is the design the cause of the phenomenon? Or is that also illusion? Is it not the phenomenon itself?"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> is gravity the reason we cant make something hit absolute zero? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 20:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as in maybe gravity affects the length of a string? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 17:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> alright lol I might just not use it anymore. just thought Id give it a try </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> so how exactly are you supposed to use Tinder? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 05:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just got it 4 days ago. im a male in my young 20s. im in shape and not horrible looking. I have 0 matches and its frustrating. also are you supposed to message girls on snapchat when they give their username if you havent matched with them? how the fuck does everyone else know how to do this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 03:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is gold </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 03:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when people say adderall is meth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 05:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> true I have none  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 02:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do you have any good sources per chance? NOTHING is working so far and I just dont understand it. like organic chemistry is literally EASY to me, like a fucking joke of a college class. so how could it possibly be a genetic incapability? I really doubt this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 05:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 05:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the most incredibly strange and frustrating dilemma. I can easily explain what is going on theoretically/conceptually in calculus. and can work out problems. but I just can not perform on tests. I get very nervous and end up failing. and I wouldnt say maths in general no. math might be my favorite subject which is just embarrassing   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 04:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont think struggling in one math is a good reason to not switch but thanks for the input  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> want to switch my efforts to physics but feel like I shouldnt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 20:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am currently studying chemistry at uni and am in my early 20s. I have already switched my major once. I have really taken a liking to the concepts of physics but am struggling with math a.t.m and am terrified of the idea of switching? anyone have practical advice or some shit? thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 08:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> does this make you a bad reader? short answer: no. long answer .... No. and you DID interpret it on your own. you just decided to compare  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 04:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it just seems difficult to understand intuitively. multiple time dimensions feels more plausible but this makes sense  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 04:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> both great explanations thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If the 4th dimension is relativistic rather than spatial, then why is it assumed that the remaining 7 are spatial and not relativistic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 06:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ? Im very new to string theory and know nothing beyond nambu-goto and polyakov so there is no need to be rude por favor  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 05:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fair </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> would you say THC has 7 or 8 resonance structures? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 04:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> correction I think its 8 or 9 Im going with 9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 04:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just looked that up lol I didnt actually know they had that wow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 02:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> by the way the "mirror images" are called enantiomers. just in case my explanation sucked and you wish to research it a little  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 02:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> methamphetamine is methylated amphetamine, so the nitrogen (there is only one nitrogen per molecule) has a methyl (CH3) group attached. the biological activities are different because of this. further, amphetamine and methamphetamine both have NON superimposable mirror images of their RESPECTIVE molecules. some people will say it has a left handed and right handed version of itself. you may have heard of these for amphetamine as levo and dextro amphetamine. the atoms and bonds and everything are the same (remember im talking about levo vs dextro amphetamine at this point). BUT despite this they have different chemical and biological properties. meaning when discussing methamphetamine and amphetamine you really have just mentioned FOUR DIFFERENT molecules all with different biological activity and different chemical properties   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 02:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> literally laughed out loud  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> is anyone else getting unbelievably sick of people saying adderall is literally meth with a brand name? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 02:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> everyone here knows how incredibly far from true this is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 02:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fine ill just delete it all  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 23:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> for the hell of it I was hoping for POLITE comments criticism whatever, just wanted to make sure its a correct statement. its a shame that people who claim they love math love to discourage others from pursuing it. and we wonder why America is so poorly ranked in math   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 23:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh so every single post is written by a genius like yourself? so sorry I am not WORTHY. Christ people on the internet have huge cybermuscles and brains. youre such a cock  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 23:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> never said it was a brilliant discovery I even admitted its kinda stupid, so suck my dick  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 23:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks for the clarity I thought it was "an opinion or conclusion formed on the basis of incomplete information" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 23:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is this how you respond to every conjecture? its a statement sorry to disturb you while youre jerking off into your mouth  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 23:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol I love how much of a cock everyone is, I just started looking into graph theory a few WEEKS ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 20:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> pink toe vs moth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 19:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DVX4VfSAfQ4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 22:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> appreciate it. I have issues with the bass foot and how/when to use it as well, using the high hat confuses me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> having great troubles coordinating my high hat foot while playing jazz. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 21:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> anyone know how to overcome this barrier ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> taking calc 1 for the fourth time any of you math geniuses who flew through it without studying (yes I know you didnt) wanna give me advice on how to not take it a FIFTH time? thanks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 04:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> let me guess a smart ass trolling change your major comment? very clever  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
