<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3944</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 21:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Elemental animals

2. Shit we forgot

3. OP everything

4. Bidoof

5. Gross

6. Does this make me look fat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 18:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it would be a lot more economical if you removed the pictures as well as just left in the super effective moves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 18:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Just breed them. Unless you have a powersave program, there's no way to rename them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 17:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> -The day car man/lad to carry more than one egg at a time

-Special party slots just for eggs. If you're full when they hatch, they to to the PC.

-Remove breeding that required a held item IE Rose Incense

-Implement a system where you could give an item to the Day Care Woman so she could "give" that item to the Pokemon. Ex. Ditto with Destiny Knot breeding with Roserade with Rose Incense that has Modest nature, give the Day Care Woman an Everstone, and she asks which Pokemon you want her to introduce the item to, and you tell her "Roserade".

-Allow the swapping of Pokemon at the daycare, very much like a PC. This would allow you to put items on the Daycare Pokemon without having to take them back from the chatty Daycare Woman. 

-For god's sake can we get a mass release option? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So, hate to ask... But I'm seeking event legendaries. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 08:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know I know, almost impossible to ask for. But I don't care about their legitimacy... I just want to collect them. I don't even use any uber tier pokemon (Talonflame?), I just hate the "???"s in my pokedex... I don't have MUCH, but I have 6IV HA Fletchlings, Froakies, and Goletts.. And Shroomishes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 06:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit I'm Trying to Breed for a Shiny: Box 1-31 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 03:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll poop out phiones all day... Useless pokemon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 01:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just keep them for the lottery.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 01:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5-6IV Goletts (Mixed HA) and a box of 5-6IV Froakies (Mixed HA) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 01:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No shinies or legendaries. No significant HA pokemon either. Sigh. My sister traded 45 pokemon and got a Deoxys and Virizion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 01:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yup, pretty impressive. my luck can't get much better

in case you're too lazy to look, it's like 7 boxes of sheer and utter trubbish. (not literally trubbish, just terrible)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man check out all these beauties I got from wonder trade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 01:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 01:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> of course it takes from the game lol? but you can't make a pokemon with a pentagon, so people will just know you're a cheater and laugh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 00:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can run Night shade and do decent damage if you make it bulky </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 00:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This needs to be stickied or something jesus christ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 00:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can give you one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 23:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a shiny Luxray that I spent days hunting for in the safari... Now he just sits in his box... Ruler of his kingdom of rust. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 22:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clawitzer. Look at it and you'll understand!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 22:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Metagross.


;^) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 22:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol u w0t?

I don't breed many OU pokemon, but I have a full team of 5-6IV shinies.. My favorite is HA Talonflame, HA Greninja, HA Golurk, Mega Gallade, Volcarona, and either Kingdra or Gyarados... They're all high quality shinies. I have a few more I like to switch out or whatever, but just because you see a full team of shinies doesn't mean they cheated. I haven't even battled online because I hate fighting uber teams. So there's most likely a lot more people like me than you know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 21:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is this? I'm confused, yo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 20:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is club nintendo? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 17:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kalos has been my favorite. I literally can't remember a single damn thing about Sinnoh. I'm trying to replay it right now, and it's sooooo slow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
