<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2257</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Married Redditors, what is the worst thing one of your In-laws have ever done to you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 05:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 05:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 05:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Silly bands were definitely a thing like 5-7 years ago. I never got involved in it, but boy did some people get really into it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Imagine there's no religion, countries, or possessions: what would the world look like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 05:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would history be different if every person who ever lived had an ideal childhood? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 05:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 05:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The *wholesome* ones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the worst nightmare you've ever experienced? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 05:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the best memes in the history of Reddit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 05:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If one has a fairly massive object and one needs to transport it a good distance by air, what is the best way to get it from point A to point B? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 05:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would be the one thing that you could do that would surely give an 80-year old woman a heart attack? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 05:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would be the one thing that you could do that would surely give an 80-year old woman a heart attack? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 05:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 04:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On that note, Mick Jenkins is also very good. He is a very relaxed rapper, and his song with badbutnotgood (Drowning) is very good. Also see 'Jazz,' 'Spread Love,' and 'Fall Through.' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 04:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that 95% of the universe is not visible matter, thus making almost all of the simulation unrendered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 04:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The experimentation with outsiders leading major world nations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 19:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peter griffin, have you seen some of the shit he does? Further, just imagine if he had a human instead of some dog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 19:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1349 was the height of the bubonic plague, in which 1/3 of Europe died.

The situation was suboptimal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 18:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Sound of Silence](https://imgur.com/k7ZibS9)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 18:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering he led his answer off with 'you have to be fucking retarded,' yes, I can totally see how he had a stress induced heart attack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 15:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear Caillou is french for *fucking idiot* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I threw a rock into a time travel portal, and it went back 500 years and randomly exited somewhere, how much would the world change? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 02:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What one piece of technology would have you crowned king if you brought it back to the 14th century? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 02:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What one piece of technology, if brought back to the 14th century, would be the most likely to have you burned at the stake? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 02:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what are some of you home improvement horror stories? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 00:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could choose any two people in the world to have a baby together, which two would come the closest to creating a 'superhuman'? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 00:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you were to Reincarnate as any animal after you died, what would it be and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 00:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Financiers of Reddit, how corrupt really is Wall Street? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 00:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What jobs get a lot less credit than they really deserve? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 22:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 18:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These underlying numbers also represent the coefficients for many Maclaurin or Taylor Series, which are ways to approximate any mathematic function using a polynomial. 

For many Maclaurin series, these coefficients are the inverse of the factorial of the exponent, so for a squared term, it would be 1/2, for a cubed term, it would be 1/6, for a quartic term, 1/24. The reason these are what they are is when you take the derivative of that polynomial as many times as the exponent specifies, the coefficient is always 1 when there is no polynomial left to coincide.

For example, the derivative of 1/2 x^2 is 1x, whose derivative is 1.

The derivative of 1/6 x^3 is 1/2 x^2, whose derivative is 1x, whose derivative is 1.

The derivative of 1/24 x^4 is 1/6 x^3, and so on.

Using this, I can guarantee you that the next increment level for your series will be 120, and after that 720, and then after that 5040, which are accordingly the factoriala of 5,6, and 7. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] You just completed yet another successful time travel mission, this one being to Da Vinci's workshop. However, as you step onto the return pad, you realize you left your Cell Phone on Da Vinci's workbench. It's already too late to go back and get it, so you return to a very different world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 17:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 17:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason when I read Jane Seymour, I thought of Jane Goodall, the 82 year old primate expert.

And yes, I would totally go *ape shit* on that pussy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 17:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swear, by saying 'still kicking are you just trying to jinx his death like the  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you were assembling an army of cross-breeds, which two animals(any vertebrate) would you crossbreed in order to create the most successful war machine? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 08:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you had to live for a full week in a zoo enclosure with said animal, which enclosure would you choose and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 08:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 08:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> imagine a stapler dick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you had to augment your genitalia with one household item, which item would you choose and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 08:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With the new year coming up and many people pledging a 'new me,' what is the one most embarrassing memory you would like to leave behind in 2016? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 08:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 07:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was the 43rd president of the United States, I perpetrated the biggest terrorist attack in national history, I made a shit ton of money for my best bud Dick, and I also got a shit ton of Iraqi oil. If I had one thing to say to all my professors at Yale?

*Go fuck youreselves* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could have sex with anyone in the world, but they had to be over the age of 60, who would it be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 07:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I read every page but there was no feature story on Michael Bluth...? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 21:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A German and a Frenchman walk into a bar. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 18:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After buying the German a beer, the Frenchman asks where his is from.

"Auschwitz," the German replies.

"Is it weird living there, especially with its history?" The Frenchman asks.

"Yes, but the services are incredible."

"Oh really?"

"Yes. Cheap gas and free showers." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 18:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello! This is a bot. Any discussion on how Jews are taking over the world, or how they already secretly ran the world must be kept civil. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With Hanukkah upon us, how does a Jewish man prepare his tea? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 18:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hebrews it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 00:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *ron Howard's voice*

"It did not end well for George Michael" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 00:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sounds like he might've literally given his heart to someone this Christmas  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 07:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Money For Nothing by Dire Straits. There's not as much deeper meaning as many of the other songs listed here, but the guitar chords coming out of the intro are just so overwhelmingly powerful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 07:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wish You Were Here is one of the most underappreciated songs of all-time IMO. There's no better song to close all the windows on your car to, and scream the lyrics as loud as you possibly can while nearly shedding a tear because the chords are so beautiful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 06:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so then are their kids your double cousins or how does that work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My brother made a music video for one of his coworker's drunk rap songs. I feel there's a future for his coworker in children's songs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 00:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 09:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well why didn't they just name it the HDVD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 01:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the OP, I ask this, because mine is -113, so I was wondering where that was in relation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your personal record for most downvotes on a single comment/post? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 01:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 01:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well there are two tubes, aren't there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 04:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ironically, through self-goading and thus inflating ones own ego. It may sound really conceited, but knowing I was going to do better in life than the bullies in high school really helped me get through all of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 23:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One time, our young dog had frustrated all of us to the point that we needed some time alone, so we shut the doors to all of our rooms and left her by herself to roam the house. Sensing she has been excluded, she climbed up on the counter, and among other things, picked out my brothers glasses and chewed them up, something she had never done before to any pair of glasses. My entire family thinks she did it out of revenge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 07:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And oil </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 23:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "GUARD! GUARD! I SWEAR THERE'S A SNAIL IN HERE TRYING TO KILL ME. WAIT, NO, I DONT NEED TO GO IN SOLITARY CONFINEMENT!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 07:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> idk why I couldn't help but read every one of these different spelling in an Adam Sandler voice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 22:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cespedes Family Barbecue is high quality. It's a couple of college kids, one who plays baseball for a DIII college, and they talk about professional baseball and have either minor leaguers, former major leaguers, or journalists on every podcast. They were good enough to become correspondents for MLB, despite being two college kids with completely unrelated majors.

5/7 would recommend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 22:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm shocked anyone smiled. No ones smiled since... *the great war*

*violent flashbacks ensue* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 22:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first kid did a much better job of selling it, but if you watch his feet he stands there flat-footed for too long after impact for it to be real </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 04:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I learn that the hard way every time I play GTA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 03:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well shit, why'd you put 26 pounds of force on it? The comment specifically said to put *25 pounds* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 20:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Canadians insist they grew up playing catch, but after watching the Blue Jays, it's very apparent that Jose Bautista did not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 22:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ["And that's why you always keep your arms and legs inside the car at all times"](https://imgur.com/gallery/oIhLH)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 10:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It's all going to work out in the end"

Um... Have you been paying attention *at all* to this year?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 10:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American Pie: there is a different allusion in literally every line </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 17:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was just this year, but someone got someone else an entire calendar filled with pictures of the gift giver. The craziest picture was def the September photo, in which she was a human rocket flying into the World Trade Center. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 22:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Have the balls to stand up for testicular cancer" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 22:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Death](http://fiftiesweb.com/dead/dead-people-2016/) and [taxes.](https://www.donaldjtrump.com/policies/tax-plan)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 09:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I mean, as for her, that's why all of the hints were trying to be fairly subtle, because I swear the last thing I will ever do is put a woman in a situation in which she fears  for her safety as a direct result of my actions. I just haven't been able to get a good read, but it's not looking so good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 09:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like this thread is going to be filled with extremes on both ends of the spectrum, so I'm gonna be coming down the middle. I was doing okay up until yesterday, when last night basically crushed any morale I had built up.

I went to the bar with a friend, we're both in college, and I ended up getting split off there was this one girl I saw there that I had gotten to be pretty good friends and that I thought was pretty cool, so I figured I would try to make a move. I was hanging around with her that night because we were still friends in the first place, but after about 12 subtle attempts later, I'm about to give up, and I see her leave. I think *what purpose do I have here if she's gone* so I decide to follow her out to see if I can get one last shot at even seeing if the feeling is mutual.

She's standing there on the stairwell up to the ground level(the bar was deep underground) and offers me a ride home, and I accept, and she tells me that she has to go back down and get a friend. So as I sit there on the stairwell, 5 cops walk past me, and me, an 18 year old that looks 16, just stood there quietly as they walked by. Sure enough, she gets back, there's an uneventful ride home, I get back to my dorm, and an hour later my friend that I originally went with shows up with an MIP.

So not only did I not get the girl, but I left my friend out to dry, and him being such a nice kid, undeservingly got an MIP. Today, needless to say, has been a shitty day considering the two of those.

Tl;dr: Instead of getting an MIP, I am now a minor in possession of no confidence


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 05:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love it how there was just casually a fireworks mortar used as a domino in this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 18:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, I feel like this question is directly answered by the fact that Donald Trump is president. It's very apparent that these traits are not valued in a large portion of today's America. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 18:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely getting someone 4500 ladybugs for Christmas, and placing them all inside of a 3x3 box. The unsuspecting friend will then experience death by ladybug. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 18:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This doesn't have to do with the rest of the comment, just the initial analogy, but the FBI actually essentially does have a quota on terrorists to capture to make sure they still get [funding](http://mobile.nytimes.com/2012/04/29/opinion/sunday/terrorist-plots-helped-along-by-the-fbi.html)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 05:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see your overall happiness has gone up as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 21:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good thing I just bought a new dick after that tragic forklift accident. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 21:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they're self-conceited. I sent signals to this one girl, and she wasn't interested, but 6 months later she texts me out of nowhere and we end up going on a date. 

Note the 'A' date. On the first date I picked up that she was into herself more than she was into me, and that's all the farther it went. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 20:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump, and inversely, Jeb Bush.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 20:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But when you're a dick to cows, they aren't afraid to start some beef with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to see the Four Corners and the Grand Canyon in one day, and we started at the Four Corners(where Colorado, Utah, New Mexico, and Arizona all meet) and it was okay, but because of the long drive, we were only make it to the Grand Canyon just before sunset.

But let me tell you, witnessing a sunset over the Grand Canyon is absolutely fucking incredible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Soon as I pull up and park the Benz, we get this bitch shaking like Parkinson's."

On Sight // Kanye West </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next Episode by Dre and Snoop is just too much to handle sometimes. Utterly fantastic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The single greatest song ever written, that's what](https://youtu.be/dQw4w9WgXcQ)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 16:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you imagine the people that call this guy every day? He's the head of the *steel union.* Even before the Trump incident, he prob got a death threat every hour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 16:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gravity is just a theory </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 03:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TO THE PLACEEEE 

I BELOOOOOOOOONNNNNNNGGGGGG </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 03:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm from the south KC area, specifically Overland Park([the nicest place to raise a family in 2015 according to Livability ](http://www.livability.com/top-10/families/10-best-cities-families/2015/ut/st.-george) and 250K will probably get you a 3000 sq ft house(including basement) in a nice area on a quarter acre lot. A lot of the houses though that are selling for this price are a little outdated though, like from the 1960's, because almost all of the new houses in OP are selling from 375k-750k </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My RA for my dorm just can up to me and asked me for fantasy advice, and I have never felt more like Pete Eckhart in my life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 02:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 01:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have two brothers who are 16 and 14 years older than me. They both live locally, so I usually see both of them twice or three times a year, and are comfortable enough to text back and forth.

Tbh, because they were half brothers and they lived with their mother, I didn't know they were my brothers until I was like 5. I always figured they were just friends of my dad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 01:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the otter's most likely wet fur is only going to accelerate that smh what a shame </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 21:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it's like telepathy, except instead of using your mind, you use your balls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 18:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I know is that here wasn't a sight of a stain in the morning </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 17:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The female orgasm:

Does it exist? 
How can it be captured?
Is it a myth, much like Bigfoot?
What powers are held by it?
If released, what is its impact? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 17:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would've liked to have seen a ensuing Reign of Terror </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 16:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's the joke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 16:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oakland, because fuck Oakland. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you had to designate one place in the world to put the entire world's supply of nuclear waste, where would you put it and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 16:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 16:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our CAD teacher was great, but undoubtedly he would just yelled "Get back to f'ing work! What the f are you guys doing? Do I need to slap you guys upside the head?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 16:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind of random, but dish washers. My grandmother installed an entry level model in 1997 and it still works to this day, and our family installed a new one, fairly nice, in 2006 and it only lasted 8 years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 16:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Testeskinesis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 16:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's the other joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 16:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a related note, I clean up vomit far more when I'm drunk. However, after doing it both sober and drunk, it is far more bearable cleaning it up while drunk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 16:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, you dodged a big bullet, because at least he didn't become a Raiders fan. Those people are demented. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 16:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lead a violent revolution for the pacifitariat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 19:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Weasel headed fucknugget"
"Mangled apricot hellbeast"
"Utter and complete eejit"
"You bloviating flesh bag"
"Incomprehensible jizztrumpet"
"You Cheeto-faced, ferret wearing shitgibbon" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 18:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would ask for 100 gay friends, just to spite Mike 'a volt a day keeps the gay away' Pence by surrounding him with 1000 gay people for the next four years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 18:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, I'm starting to think the 'Game of Thrones' production team are taking this 'cutting characters' process a little too far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 15:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> life insurance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 15:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not really an item, but seals. Like the aquatic mammal. Especially the ones with yellow bowties. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 01:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and then another 8 weeks off 40 weeks later smh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 00:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> rekt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 00:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *displays warning after video*

Sex Addiction is a real thing. See a doctor for help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 00:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's a fucking tortoise duuuuuuuuuuude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 21:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [When Migos performed 'Hannah Montana' with a symphony orchestra](https://youtu.be/cOxlLKXx5Xg)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 21:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smh you're right: I have a ramp that's on a sharp incline near my house and regularly I get trapped behind a car that going 40 to merge onto a 65 MPH highways. It's hell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 17:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, I never really expected Jordan to be a nice guy. He also seemed very extravagant and intense. On the other hand, I would expect LeBron to be a fairly nice person, Steph to be a little stuck up but still a nice dude, and Kobe to be courteous but very, very intense, which could come off like an ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 16:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, with that band, he might have had the intention to actually bring them back and then he found them all doing cocaine or something.

EDIT: even if OP saw them later, you're pretty much back to normal after an hour on cocaine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When did you meet your heroes and they lived up to everything you hoped they would be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 16:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 16:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Similarly, Jason LaRue(the guy Cardinals fans obsess about because Johnny Cueto ended his career with a kick to his face) is my hero because when I was 8, he caught Alex Rodriguez in a run-down and threw me the ball as he was going back to the dugout. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 22:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 05:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> your mom and aunt were hot dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 03:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The scary part about this is knowing that Ronda Rousey defeated a *professional fighter* in less time than it took her </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friends and I got bored one day this summer and made our own rendition of the Full House intro. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 03:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
