<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject195</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 19:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bruh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 19:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> white guy here. can confirm. It's a meme. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 19:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe it'd be more racist not to post it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 19:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OCpUjERoMKI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 19:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> indubitably  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 19:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mmJEEEEENKINS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 18:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I don't get it. 

Everyone is entitled to their opinions- 

But how can people who've seen the first two seasons of this show honestly still love the show after what it has now become? Arrow used to be an amazing dark/gritty show about a vigilante with awesome action scenes and a plot that made sense. It wasn't perfect. But it was just so good. How can they think these new episodes are "amazing" or "the best episode ever?" 

I mean seriously. They fired one arrow... in a show called Arrow about a super hero named the Green Arrow and Team Arrow.... 

Felicity/Ollicity is hamfisted and shoehorned into so many scenes. She saved the day "again, for the second time." Is there anything she can't do? The Arrow is now "Felicity and Friends" 

The writing feels lazy and hard to follow. Now we have organic corhn and organic shipping ferhns. I still don't understand the main villain's motivations this season other than "I am le evil, humanity needs a reset". It just feels like it was all thrown together last minute. 

There was always some relationship drama but it wasn't the main focus. It was tolerable because the show had an engaging plot and awesome action scenes.  

If it had always been written this way, then maybe I would understand those types of comments but it was just sooo much better before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 18:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My prediction. Honestly with the shitty writing lately I wouldn't be surprised at all if Dahmiehn Dahrhrk actually resurrects him. Then after they kill off dark in the season finale, it turns out Andy was being mind controlled the whole time. And he really is a "good guy" afterall. Oh and Felicity convinces Diggle not to kill him again just for the icing on the cake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 18:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm tired of Felicity's petty ass comments  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 18:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^^^^^and ^^^^^i ^^^^^heard ^^^^^thea. ^^^^^I ^^^^^heard ^^^^^john. ^^^^^I ^^^^^head ^^^^^laurel  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 18:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah but that was before we hated her </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 17:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I don't get it. Why try and take over the city if you are just gonna blow it up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 17:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  jump change

I think you may be thinking of the phrase "chump change" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 17:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that just exemplifies the shitty writing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 17:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember when the show arrow was about a guy that shot arrows? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 11:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you missed these gems. 

Our Organic Felicity organically referencing the organic shipping fern...

Our Strong and Powerful Felicity saying "Don't talk to me like I'm other people" to Olliburr

Oliver saying nothing and knowing his place like the fuckboi that he is. 

Our Shrewd Felicity being a fantastic CEO yet again and spending company resources wisely. 

Our Smart and Talented Felicity being an expert blackjack player. 

Our One True Savior Felicity hitting trained soldiers with a van just in time to rescue Diggle. 

This exchange between Olibbur and Our Light in the Darkness Felicity:
"I was able to repel Dahrks magic." 

"How'd you do it?" 

"I heard your voice in my head" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 10:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> switched to ublock origin several months ago. it's streets ahead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 10:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my biggest problem with her character. How does literally no one on Team Arrow call her on her petty manipulative immature bullshit? And to think she used to be one of my favorite side characters.... Also.. when did Oliver become such a pussy? He never stands up for himself.  He just stands there and looks like a guilty puppy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 10:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do yourself a favor and only watch the first 2 seasons of arrow.
Then just switch to the flash. You will be better off. Trust me.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 10:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I felt like Jessica Jones was just 2 or 3 episodes too long.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 09:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like I'm trapped in an abusive relationship and I can't get out.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 08:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Fucking Guggenheim

\#Guggencancer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 08:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBH That sounded like a felicity line. Why is it so hard to write female characters?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 08:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> \#Guggencancer  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 08:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the hope that kills me.  Every week against my best judgement I still have hope. The hope that it will be better than my expectations. The hope that it will return to its former glory. The hope that Guggencancer will stop destroying the show that I once loved.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 07:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Comic Sans

cmon son </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 06:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know that's right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 22:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so you heard about pluto?? That's messed up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 21:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck, I'm an idiot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 02:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually have pupils that are different sizes. a girlfriend pointed this out to me. Eye Doctor said it's not to uncommon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 08:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comma to the top! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 08:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> woah, was not expecting to get a zero </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 07:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I felt as though the flash was way too cheesy to the point of discomfort in the beginning (especially compared to season 2 of arrow..)  But I liked the universe so I stuck with it. The cheesiness was dialed back a little and it became more charming rather than cringey as they developed the characters though-out season 1. Then season 1 ended very strongly leaving everyone wanting more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 06:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.. you just sound like an insufferable know-it-all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 06:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I gather you were trying to make a joke, but it had too many logic holes to be funny.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 06:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> get over yourself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 06:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> youre' not wrong your just an asswhole.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 22:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  FELICIA QUEEN

idky but I lost it at this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 22:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Mark Waid

is this the author of some of the flash comics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 07:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and his hair </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 07:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fitz would like a word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 02:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too soon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 08:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wut? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 05:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> neat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 05:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why would you put spoiler tags in a comment that describes exactly what happens in the video of the post?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 05:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *harry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 22:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not sure if trolling or serious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 17:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as a lurker of this sub with no 3D Printer I'm with you. haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New here : any thoughts on Garnier pure active intensive charcoal scrub with 2% salicylic acid? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 06:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 04:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Theres like 10 here in Columbus Ohio](http://imgur.com/4D0Qd4T) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 02:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's still the best for sure, the but gap isn't quite as wide. google forced everyone's hand though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 00:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but gmail was insanely better than anything else available at the time  it was released.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 00:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> people in america don't care either mate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 23:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like you don't understand how taxes work or what they are for like at all... You say that taxation is theft. and that governments are trying to steal our money. .. 

If you want to argue about how much we are taxed, or how much say in how our tax dollars are spent, or for more transparency/accountability in where our tax dollars are spent, then I think you can make valid arguments. But it is absolutely idiotic to say that there should be no taxes or that taxation is stealing.  

For example, 

Do you like nature and or enjoy the outdoors? 

* *No taxes would mean no state parks or public parks or playgrounds. No public bike paths or hiking trails.*

Do you enjoy traveling from one part of your city/state/territory/country to another?

* *No taxes would mean no public roads, no road repairs, and no public transportation.*

Do you think that everyone should have access to knowledge and opportunities to learn/receive and education?

* *No taxes would mean no public schools and no public libraries for people to learn*

Do you like to living in a safe place?

* *No taxes would mean no military or police to protect citizens from internal/external threats.* 

How about if there is a fire? 

* *No taxes means no firemen/firetrucks, etc.* 

And so on... Point is, that our society simply would not work without taxes. (*And if want to argue for privatization of these industries, allow me to point out how well Comcast/time Warner handles the cable/internet industry as a counter example.*)

We absolutely need taxes. There are so many things that you use every single day that you don't even think about that are paid for by taxes. So taxes are definitely necessary, but taxes need to be fair and handled responsibly. 

Everyone needs to pay their fair share. [And the rich should have to pay more taxes simply because they benefit more from the system.](http://www.zompist.com/richtax.htm) It's theft for the rich to avoid paying their fair share and yet still benefit fully from the system. The poor and middle classes are subsidizing the lifestyle of the ultra rich while they engage in "tax-dodging." We have every right to be outraged about this. 

No one is holding the rich accountable. The government needs to do this and we the citizens need to make them do it. This is clearly not happening, as we are finding out again and again. Also, governments and elected representatives need to be transparent and accountable with regards to taxation. Citizens have a right to know how their taxes are spent. Citizens should have a say in what taxes are used for. Ideally we try to do this by electing officials that we feel best represent our interests. But it's time we had more say. 


    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's bugging you (if anything) about the Panama papers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 05:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 07:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard it both ways </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 05:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I don't require any assistance from some JUNIOR Minister..." 

I are have become slain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 19:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The scale of this is pretty impressive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 13:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you had to stand next to the first computers and they cost a fortune as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 13:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ctrl f'd 'lips' wondering the same thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 22:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it seems that all I ever encounter is either ignorance or a sort of defeatist apathy. Not desperation and outrage that might lead to some sort of change. None of my friends even know anything about the Panama Papers.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 22:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree. The rest of us are basically subsidizing their lifestyle. They  are getting all of the benefits of programs and infrastructure funded by taxes while contributing nothing to the system. And then we are left to cover their share as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 18:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoyed this whole article and particularly these parts: 
Fitzgerald ... Let me tell you about the very rich. They are different from you and me. They possess and enjoy early, and it does something to them, makes them soft where we are hard, and cynical where we are trustful, in a way that, unless you were born rich, it is very difficult to understand. ***They think, deep in their hearts, that they are better than we are because we had to discover the compensations and refuges of life for ourselves.***

...

 Perhaps the rich still believe they deserve to be rich, and too many of the non-rich believe it too. But their desperate attempts to hide their wealth beneath armies of lawyers and nests of imaginary companies and mailing addresses on distant islands suggest otherwise. *Theyre afraid that the illusion may be crumbling. Theyre afraid that one of these days well figure out how they got that money and decide to take it back.*

How do we take it back though?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 09:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like most people are even handed. Me on the other hand.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 07:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well Gabriel seems like a classy guy. That guy interview him though.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 07:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> agree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 07:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 07:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not very effective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 19:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> huh. I've never not been turned on by boobs before... until now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 07:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well neither the paps nor the writers would have jobs if people didn't eat shit like this up to feel better about their own lives...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 07:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to be fair, I saw that video of ben affleck on reddit a few days ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 02:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 23:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finding Dory* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 00:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is this real? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 03:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ahh good old DeeJayAhmed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 03:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 01:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It never really occurred to me that people could actually enjoy Arrow and "Olicity" in their current states until I saw the people in the comments. Like it truly baffles me. 

Now that I think about it, it's similar to how I feel when I meet someone in real life who actually supports Donald Trump . Like, Oh. Wow. I guess people like you do exist after all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 02:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha sorry, I just thought you looked a bit like Rachael Taylor who plays Trish from Jessica Jones  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 22:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But Muh Freedom Fighters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 22:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> watch out we've got an Edge Lord here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 20:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trish? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 04:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ejecto Seato Cuz
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 02:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/cringe  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 00:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats cause it's a different person </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 02:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was sitting in this diner and the owner invited him back into his closet. now he's here talking to us </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 02:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Barbara Pins </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 10:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saffron </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 10:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it. Not sure where it's going but I'll be along for the ride </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 01:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that was a realla baaad joke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 08:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Night Manager is kickass so far </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 06:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually laughed out loud and said no shit when she said that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 09:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ship it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 11:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> she are is has become felicity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 00:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to me you've been saving that for centuries </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 04:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calm down there ~~Satan~~ George </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 00:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  otherwise intelligent Redditors 

you had me until this.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 12:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Felicity? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 07:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> u/sean_connery_bot has the best pun in response to a PSBattle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 08:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 06:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Season 2 of DC's Legends of Tomorrow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 01:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whats the difference? honestly I'm a pleb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 00:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> JESUS CHRIST MARIE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 23:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It's not a bug, it's a feature..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 23:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But is it Baader Meinhof?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 06:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're like a polite asshole </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 02:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most gifs don't </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 01:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [relevant](http://www.cnn.com/2012/07/22/opinion/greene-olympics-amateurs/)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 00:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hopefully you can forgive my typo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's seems as though many people don't understand this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 00:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 22:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> two right hands is the most realistic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 05:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I imagine that its the popularity of halo. brings out the baddies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 05:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sometimes I wish people WOULD quit early instead of going like 2-15 on team slayer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 04:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mildly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 02:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow this is fantastic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 02:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice save bro
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 02:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Edit 3: LPT Never complain about your inbox blowing up, Reddit will take it as a challenge. I've received way too much love (and hate) in the past 2 hours. My favorite was the recipe for spaghetti someone sent me for absolutely no reason.

lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 01:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think many people would clamor for Lance Armstrong to represent them in anything nowadays.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 01:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is he my girlfriend? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fine Bros Subscriber Ticker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 07:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 01:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, I wouldn't download a car </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When I get out of a toxic relationship </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 22:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 21:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Casey Neistat has some great videos](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCtinbF-Q-fVthA0qrFQTgXQ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite YouTube Channel? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 21:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 21:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Into the Badlands on AMC had some of the best fight scenes I've ever seen on television  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 10:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Panera? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 02:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well, this was from 2013 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 01:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Socratic method is a way to have engaging conversations.

I'm sure Socrates was one of the most annoying people to talk to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 08:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it wouldn't be CW with out triangles  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 01:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was always curious about that. It seemed like she was kind of written out of the show after that happened. Idk maybe it was just coincidence that her character went away just after the fappening  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 23:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
