<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3859</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-29 01:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read this before sleepin and had crazy ass nightmares about people being in my room and ghosts talkin to me. Cant even tell if it was a dream or sleep paralysis... So fuckin tripped out right now  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-26 09:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh the memories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-26 09:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makes me want to cry... And I have the 2011 gt/cs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-25 04:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha will do! Take care  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-24 19:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. Yeah , my professor stresses composition to the fullest, before painting we have to plan and underpaint for like 4 hours, thanks for takin the time to look at this. Recently I have been gettin downvoted for putting up artwork, maybe because its unrecognizable/original?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-24 08:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah only had 3 classes for it, around 6 hours </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-23 12:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 24" x 24" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-23 08:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah I remember them scooter days, that shit happened to me and burst a vein in my foot, couldn't stop bleeding for hours </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-22 18:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the drunk driver, WTFFFF, very sad for the family of the girl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I painted some legs  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-22 17:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anatomy is fun (wip) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-21 05:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-17 22:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> holy bajeeebus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-15 17:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I like how that guy thinks he can talk for the school of the arts, I'm in vcu arts and I really DO give a fuck about vcu basketball. Pissed they lost but what can you do against that last second shot, besides hoping it doesn't go in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-14 22:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yea the colors,but also the texture, you cant see it in the photo,its shitty quality but i used heavy strokes, tried to imitate the style, it was a commission </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-14 13:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/94/Starry_Night_Over_the_Rhone.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "All alone! Whether you like it or not..." -Dr. Seuss [1024x768] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-12 08:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-11 19:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when and where? occupyings my thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-08 01:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fap...Fap Fap  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-01 02:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a junior, still  in school, selling some paintings for commissions and looking for internships, I might double major in art education so I can have a job right out of college while establishing myself as a painter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-31 06:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't taze me bro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-31 06:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-31 06:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rooby rooby rooo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-31 05:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell me about it, Communication Arts here, Vcu. It was tough to convince them. My whole family pretty much talked shit for a while, you know how uncles an aunts are...thinkin their kids are so much better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-29 19:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, you lucky bastard. This things gonna shake the streets, have fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-26 17:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah wasn't thinkin about that, go for it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-26 14:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha that would be pretty funny, but a waste of time. Why not do something productive? People might not even notice, or care  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-26 00:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha man I always sit at the commons all day between classes Mon-Thursday, I have a broken leg so its hard to go back home. Even if my next class is 5 hours away I just sit there an draw etc, if you ever see me say what's up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-24 04:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My hard work that got me talent and skill in art.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-23 05:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah here is an unofficial site I made,  and my blog.


www.Ramandips.moonfruit.com    Clck paintings at the top, drawings also if you wish, sometimes it acts a bit slow, but it's free so hehe

www.noodos.blogspot.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-22 19:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I haven't meditated seriously in a while either , this painting sitting there is gonna change that haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-22 19:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-22 09:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> after reading all the comments   :,( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-22 08:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, your compliment was beautiful and struck a chord also Haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-22 07:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha thank you, means a lot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-22 07:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet, thank you, if you click the top right magnifying glass on the picture itself, it will take you to a higher quality pic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-22 05:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah,sometimes its hard to tell, but I'll take it, thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-22 05:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> are you talking about the painting, or that I put it in the wrong subreddit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Expressive palette knife painting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-22 05:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-22 03:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I say the same thing when I finish and look at the final, it feels great when nights of painting pay off, thanks  for viewing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-22 03:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks for viewing :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-22 02:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I finished , check out the front page of this subreddit if you haven't seen it yet 


I </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-22 02:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I finished , check out the front page of this subreddit if you haven't seen it yet  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-22 02:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for veiwing it, didn't get much love in   /art, I'm glad I was able to show some people on here though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-22 00:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha I just looked at my face and transformed it into rock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-21 23:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-21 23:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is oil paint, I used a palette knife to paint the whole thing so I could have texture. Some parts like the lava are elevated, you can touch them , 4 feet tall, it feels amazing to create somethin like this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-21 22:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THE BEST OF YOUUU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-21 21:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it symbolizes finding inner peace, the big monster face represents inner struggle and anything can distract the mind or trouble it. The monster it about to take over but, the monk is confronting it, its his inner turmoil, and hes going to overcome it and find inner peace, the light is from the monk is shining on the grass and also on the monsters chin area. I wanted to create some tension by the lava about to fall on the monk, but he is not worried. Basically its about keeping a stable state of mind no even when things aren't looking too good for you, sometimes when I meditate I have that problem. The theme is unstable vs stable. Chaos vs peace.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So guys, I finally finished this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-21 21:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shakin off the rust </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-21 02:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-20 06:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea, Haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-19 13:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Holy Hell, just woke in a full sweat from a night terror  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-19 08:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Waking up in my room, except its not my room in the dream, very scattered lighting, more Windows,.black and white....in the dream my door to the hall way is open, I hear somethin coming towards my room, I get up ,have barely any control, falling into the wall, headbutt door to close it and then hit the floor... I cant open my mouth, paralyzed face, can barely make a sound, blurred vision, tryin to yell for my cousin to get up, head butting the wall hoping someone hears, I fall on the floor, crawl back into bed... Look up towards window...looks like someone is standing over top of me...also blurry vision I tell myself its a shadow ..and it keeps moving ...over me, I try to reach out......I smack it.....I feel my face being smacked over an over by rough hands ...it comes closer....a whisper "photos are deceiving,motherfucker"  . I woke up in sweat and in the same place as I was in the dream , same position </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-17 19:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the top comment is a joke about the ninja turtle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-17 01:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realized it when I ran 6 miles and my legs were destroyed for the next few days...I had never been hurt like that. My knees felt worn out and my ankles were dying, took me weeks to gain the heart to run again, happened right when I turned 21. My legs have never been the same again. My knees start Feelin worn out everytime I run too long.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-14 21:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey guys, I painted this to "My December". Sold for 100$ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-14 03:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-12 11:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh lawdy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-11 07:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I first left India I was about 7 years old... I got to the u.s and everythings a blur, there is one strong memory though. Me and my family went to go see pardes in theatres, it was the first movie I had ever seen in my life, before then I had worked on the farm in punjab, it was all I knew. My favorite song was probably Ye dil deewana. When srk is driving away from his life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-11 05:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's sweet... I can get to 18 if i dont GUN it every chance i get...which is really reallly hard. It's like it's made to be floored. When I hit 3000 rpm in 1st gear, a sign comes up tellng me to shift to 4th, it saves a lot of gas, and because of the torque, skipping gears like that isnt a big deal.  6th gear is amazing too, I can be in 6th going 40mph, and the gas meter will have full bars, im guessing the v6 is similar. Compared to my 2000 this has replaced, pretty heavenly, I was getting like 15 hway, I just need to make some money to hook this thing up, have you heard about the ATAK exhaust.. look up the v6 with it on youtube, shakes the ground  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-11 05:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha definitely, A+++ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-10 22:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you go to bodybuilding.com there are catagories and goals sections, find brain and mind health. They have a lot of stuff. I bought this stuff called bodyquick brain quicken, it was said to increase memory upto 30% for a few hours and holy fuck it worked. I took Hindi class last semester and within one week I knew all the alphabets, before the class even knew 5%. I got up to the board and filled them all out, even my teacher was like wtf  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-10 21:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That joints wet, both of em.. I was gonna get the v6 but got the 5.0 cs instead. The v6s look really sweet and gas mileage must be beautiful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-10 06:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Konichiwa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-09 11:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feeling warm inside after watching this, thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-08 20:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There's always a gap between what my work should look like in my mind and what it ends up as, when that gap has become smaller I will repost my work. Failure is never an option, thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-08 20:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6 speed yeah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-08 11:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I call Shotgun. At this point I let my cousin drive it just so I can sit in the passenger seat and feel the torque Haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-08 11:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm pretty much untrained, Im starting a figure painting class in about a week so that should help. I realize my drawing skills have been pretty crappy in the past, I have gotten a lot better but have not put up recent paintings, still unfinished. Thank you I will practice defining the strokes and working on proportion. Thank you for the advice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-08 11:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True words, thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All semester I waited to come home so I could drive this. 3 days after break started, I broke my leg, it's been painful just watching it sit there all winter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-08 00:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-07 23:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I didn't make it from scratch, it was free  and I just stuck with the layout options it already has, when I get better with customizing it I will add left and right arrows,etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-07 22:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I realize I need to reshoot everything, most were taken at slight angle so I could avoid the glare on the oil...and were taken in a rush. I thought I would put up what I have til I reshoot them all, and yeah I don't know why its slow sometimes, someone told me flicker would be a better option. I don't think I would turn this in to anything serious really, I was just trying to have all my work on one page, it gets really hard to keep track after a while. I'll keep in mind the feedback you gave, thank you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-07 20:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I need to do that thank you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-07 18:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they are all working for me,  maybe just reload it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-07 18:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> really? this has happened so many times I thought I fixed it-_- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-07 18:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah I know what you mean, I'm actually in my third year in college right now. I'm a communication arts major at vcu, most of the people in my major work digitally, i feel like I am one of the few that wants to pursue oil painting. There are only two painting classes being offered in my major so it's a little hard, and I definitely feel behind due to the fact that I have not really looked into the old masters and tried to replicate their styles. I don't know why but it never really occurred to me to do that until recently. It is my winter break and I have been reading, looking up videos, anything I can, on rembrandt, titian,van gogh, jmw turner, and a few others. I know that I need to get out of this comfort zone, without knowing the history, it will be difficult to make it. I just never thought I would end up in art, until my senior year in high school, never cared for the history. I just hope I'm not too late, I have two years left, I'm gonna go all out. And yeah I know what your saying about line quality...so everything doesn't look the same, it can carry the eye, but, treat every inch of your canvas equally important? the one painting class I have taken has taught me to work more on the focal point and care less about the rest. Thank you for taking the time to tell me alll this, and I'll be glad to hear any more advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-07 17:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I changed it to something less distracting, thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-07 17:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just incase you didn't know, you could double click and see them bigger, some are actuall high quality </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-07 17:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know most of them are blurry, guess i'll have to reshoot all of them with a better camera. And thanks for the recommendations, will do, I do feel that I need to look at the masters more instead of just trying to do my own thing.. thanks for the feedback </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-07 17:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha it is my own, but I just googled the background, should I change it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Success!! Just finished putting together my portfolio, what do you think reddit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-07 16:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-07 10:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe they're just playing the idiot, maybe they're not playing. I find it hilarious and true Haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-06 12:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best episode ever, made me bawl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-05 12:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell yeah that was me that just got you to 420 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-05 02:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing, usually people fuck up and get terrible  game tattoos, but this, its the perfect image for a tat... The design complexity and the style, the clouds at the bottom,creates a sense of discovery for the viewer. Awesome man  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-05 01:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was listening to ATS in the shower, pretty smacked, and it all made sense, when it got to things building up, wretches and kings, it definitely felt like OWS and also iridescent and the catalyst kind of describe the chaotic vibe/hype of 2012.. i guess we'll see later this year how the messenger plays out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-04 03:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm.....my cousin owns a rot and a '10 subaru wrx, next to him?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-04 03:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On sterl? I'll see it when I go down the street, I  know the guy in sno culdesac with the elise,.never seen the exige though, I drive the silver '11 stang, pretty cool to have another redditor living here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-04 03:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> House with the viper by any chance? Or further? Tryin to think of everyone that's into cars here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-04 00:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neighbor?!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-03 22:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She said he was going through the glove compartment, lookin for somethin and maybe would have driven away if she didn't come and start screaming to get out, she got em out somehow and ran back in the house, I have no idea what he was tryin to do, maybe he was just cold, he was stumbling when I saw him, could have been drunk/on crack, who knows , its pretty bizarre </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-03 17:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She started it and came back into the house, saw him in the driver seat when she went back out, yeah its cold out, hes in a warmer place now  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-03 17:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah its pretty sad, lived here for ten years, never seen random stuff like this happen  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-03 16:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL HAHAHAHA dude shit keeps goin down, broke my leg when i got home and now this shit wtf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-03 16:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha basically man :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-03 16:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's in the picture, I wasn't tryin to be racist, it coulda been any kind of race, still woulda freaked my mom out, she was just screaming that theres a black man sitting in the car, he was around 6 feet, carrying a bag with a Christmas hat, maybe a druggie I don't know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-03 16:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy was walking around tryin to get in all my neighbors houses, he wouldn't give up, called th cops they came an took em away, I live on bonnie mill, next to hoes rd park, I go to vcu so I'm used to crazy shit but my mom, she flipped  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WTF Springfield, woke up to my mom screaming and crying that there's a black man sitting in her car </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-03 16:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-03 15:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha that's after they caught em, when I looked outside he was running and tryin to break inside all my neighbors houses. Atleast 6 houses and stayed on our street long.enough that they got him when they came, I would have whooped his ass but sadly have a broken leg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wtf, just woke up to my mom screaming that there's a black man sitting in her car </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-03 15:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-03 04:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome, I'm in communication arts, hardest department to get into, if you have any questions let me know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-03 02:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Padmapper.com can be a good friend, its how I found my place, filter to your needs  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-03 02:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol at ~four hours in class. Depends on major really...I'm an art major and each class is 2.5-3 hrs....sometimes the day ends up 6-10 hrs, I know gen eds are pretty short though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-03 02:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me know when you make that new subreddit, great idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-02 17:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thinkin about how behind on life I am, and I need to get off my ass to find an internship or somethin to help out my resume... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-02 10:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha damn right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-02 10:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hq, but caught some glare

http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-Xgslxyn77YY/TwFzXInqBNI/AAAAAAAAAS0/tjqobkE7KBI/s1600/Copyright+2011+HIGH+QUALITY+took+a+few+weeks+many.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of my studies on nature,oils </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-02 10:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> a quick study of the Rebel queen of the Sikhs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-02 10:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-30 03:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2011 gt man I feel like the king of the road with this thing...2010 315 HP, 2011 412 ....and 26 to the gallon, amazing suspension. Better then my cousins awd wrx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-29 09:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hilarious, need part 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-28 21:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't smoke jacks. Would thc be considered to mess up healing too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-28 21:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not even in a cast. And have no physical therapy part. I'm on crutches, they basically said I can start walking on it bit by bit and it'll heal on its own. I've felt better almost every day, couldn't even stand at first </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-28 10:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
