<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1239</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 15:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That something is sanitary.

Meat, medical equipment, anything.

Given that I handle both when I'm either cooking or working respectively, I can promise that the amount of skimping on sanitation is far greater a problem than you'd like to think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 15:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lucero's entire 7+ album discography. 

Greatest band ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 23:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an EMT I can attest that 90% of your knowledge doesn't come from the class, it comes from being on the job and gaining experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 13:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you know anything about EMS you'd know it's the last job a special snowflake would take. Almost completely thankless high stress job. My ignorance of the cause of my slimness are hardly cause for saying I'm a snowflake. Regardless I appreciate the advice you gave.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 17:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EMT B is not the same as a paramedic. EMT B is basic life service (BLS) such as stabilizing non critical patients and transporting. Paramedics are far more trained and licensed to use more advanced and invasive machines and procedures such as intubation. They are known as advanced life support (ALS).
I know this because I work EMS myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Starting the ICF 5x5 and need some starter tips </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 04:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I basically would like some pointers on ways to eat right while doing this program. I'm currently working 60+ hours a week as an EMT so my free time and funds aren't exactly abundant. What's an easy way to start eating well so that I can fuel my gains better? I'm looking for building muscle mass and strength rather than looking showy, and I have a high metabolism so I don't really store fat that much at all, so assuming those caveats matter, what's an easy place to start? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 22:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To build his white guilt narrative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 20:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dr. Cox from Scrubs is the best deconstruction of this trope. Half his plot is how it bites him in the ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 20:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boring ass game with lazily done plot twist and cardboard characters. "Uh oh I'm suddenly in the future under water with maybe three killer robots. I am very scared. Guess I'll run around looking for buttons and key cards." Also it's only 30 minutes in but let's drop the big plot twist! Reaction: deadpan "oh well I guess I knew all along now let me wax lyrical about it for two seconds and then stop caring"

Then you spend 5 hours pressing buttons and walking around for key cards.

But there's the typical philosophy Mumbo jumbo about sentient robots that was worn out by Star Trek back in the 80s.

Waste of money, the handful of times you actually encounter an enemy aren't remotely scary. I feel ripped off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 20:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh look, scores of people with only a modicum of "knowledge" (read:rhetoric) ranting about terrorism and the Middle East to fuel their egotistical righteousness. One of the signature shitshows of the Internet since 2001.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 20:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are conveniently unaware of how well educated terrorists are. From 9/11 to San Bernardino terrorists have come from privileged and well educated backgrounds. The idea that these are desperate poor people is a myth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 14:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm an EMT so it's pretty much business as usual. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 00:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Bible. 

Both it and it's sequel The Quran have the most insane fan base too. I don't get it.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 00:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You need to go, my husband/wife will be back soon" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 00:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I already knew but I saw a lot of confusion about it, especially with you tubers who ought know better, so I thought I'd PSA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA: Appraisals mean total ratings, not positive ratings. The symbol on the left determines the overall approval rating. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 19:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure what all the symbols are but if you ever rate a message you'll notice that even a negative increases the appraisal count. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 15:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cue all the people who know tons of Christians and Jews who aren't rigid Old Testament abiders saying this is proof ISIS has no relation to Islam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 15:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can prove free well in a sense. As for God, burden of proof lies upon the person making the claim that there is an existent God, of which no evidence exists. Absence of evidence is evidence of absence. Not to mention if you know anything about religion of mythology and approach the subject honestly, it's utterly inconsistent and mathematically practically impossible, given the thousands of religions both extinct and extant that all claim contrary and incompatible absolute truths. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 15:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PEOPLE ALL OVER THE WORLD

JOIN HANDS

JOIN THE CUCK TRAIN

CUCK TRAIN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 15:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit. A human being that actually loves someone instead of using "I love you" as code for "you benefit me". Are you half unicorn? Where do you people hide? Can you do magic?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 14:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Free will doesn't exist. 

God isn't real.(arguably a good thing)

Love isn't magical and soul mates aren't real.

Hardly anyone, perhaps no one, is truly honest.

The universe doesn't care about you at all.

Happiness is almost exclusively temporary. Even if you get what you want, you will take it for granted.

You can never escape your subjective experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 19:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fine with this, but they should do this for all religious institutions. Religion should be nowhere near any political process. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 02:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an EMT in curious how they loaded two people into an ambulance at once(ambulances are cramped and couldn't hope to fit two stretchers, which in my state you are required to be secured on if you are being transported), let alone why they would do so if your BP was that low as you'd be rushed to the hospital, not left hanging around on this peculiar ambulance. In fact they would be calling ALS paramedics for both of these patients more than likely. Also,  It's a gross HIPPA violation to both share space like that and to actually verbally inform one patient of the details of another patient. This might have to go on r/quityourbullshit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 04:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Already at 130 is the problem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 18:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks anyways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
