<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3415</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So if you have no proof then why believe? I'm interested in your input, I'll probably disagree but I don't mind hearing you out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except according to your book God put the tree of good news evil there for the people to eat and he knew they would so why would he put the tree in the garden knowing they were going to eat of it in the first place. Your God is either a really mean prankster or doesn't make sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God is good why did he allow Hitler to kill all the Jews? If he had the power to stop him and cared surely he would right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is nice and all but do you have any proof of this concept? Where and how did original sin corrupt the world and more importantly what is original sin and why should I believe what you have to say about it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Terraria QOL Change: The Gravity Potion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "In only the Console version, you have the option to turn off "World Flips Upside Down", making it so only the player flips."


I NEED this. I don't use the potion because the screen flip makes my eyes hurt and my stomach feel queasy. I can't even look at a spinning circle without getting an upset stomach so it'd be real nice if this was an option we could get on the PC version.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 13:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a good question. Most games will show the same content regardless of resolution. 

I think in Terraria though this would be an issue graphically. I can see just fine at a high resolution but could you imagine trying to see some of the tiny things in this game at a really low resolution AND zoomed out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 13:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I worked for Wal-Mart for all of about two weeks.

A manager put his hands on me, clasped my shoulder real hard and when I told him not to touch me he slammed his hand down on my shoulder as hard as he could. 

When I asked him what right he thought he had to touch me he told me verbatim that he was manager and could do what he wanted. I even brought this to the store manager, but because this short slimy little fuck was from corporate they decided to just offer me to move positions where I wouldn't have to work with the guy.

I'm a dude and he made me uncomfortable as fuck. He was clearly flirting with the girls on our team and refused to talk to me when I pointed out his touching violated our harassment policy. Management even agreed with me but they wouldn't let us have a face to face meeting. 

I walked out that day letting the head manager know I'm not going to work for a company that won't stand by it's own policies and promote people who abuse their power. 

I suffer from a Generalized Anxiety Disorder and this still makes me cringe and want to cry when I think about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't HAVE to. The Jungle is generally more difficult than other areas, more so in Hard Mode. 

Turtles can kill a player in Molten Armor in just a couple of hits.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, Thieve is the owner. Are you assuming his multiplicity? /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always try to separate the artist from their actions. 

As a big wrestling fan it's hard to go back and watch some of my favorite matches knowing what I now know about some of the bigger names back in the day and how they acted back stage but at some point you just gotta look past the personal stuff for the glory of their art.

Chris Benoit is a prime example. You can't really bring him up without someone mentioning the double murder suicide involving him, his wife, and his kid. Horrible as it may be he still put on some excellent technical matches in his time. I miss him and his art, though he surely suffered backstage. 

Life you know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your tale. I'm tired of all the people I see scoot bootin' around here going over the speed limit with no helmet on and zip zappin' between cars like it's Grand Theft Auto.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like some sort of prophecy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would make an interesting center piece to a garden were it kept properly and trimmed from time to time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/a/iCbY2

What about that? Just went and thickened the houses up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only way to have more actual screen space is to play at a higher resolution. 

Edit: OP, you're a turd. Down voting me for telling you the truth? Sorry but it's the reality of it, the game would be broken if we could zoom out due to the way mobs spawn and other such factors.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A floating mushroom village I'm working on. Any suggestions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually after having another look and zooming in it seems the child's head is cocked to the side. You can make out what looks like eyes and a mouth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can register your old Diablo II key on your Blizzard account and then download a more updated version from there. 

Diablo II recently switched to a more updated platform that allows it to play on Windows 10 systems and the like so older versions from CD's are unable to auto-update through the system. 

Hope this helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is up with the child's face? 

It looks like there is a hand covering it or it's really blurred. 

Kind of creepy looking! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spore Zombies spawn on the surface mushroom biome. 

Lay out some mud and mushroom grass (I usually do around 100-200 blocks worth) and make yourself a Surface Mushroom Biome!

Build a house in this Biome and the Truffle NPC will move in as well. Spore Zombies will spawn in this area. 

Another way to do this if you don't mind losing the surface jungle is to use the Clentiminator and Blue Fluid to turn your Jungle into a Mushroom Forest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That isn't the Lamia tail it's the Genie Pants.

OP is missing the Lamia tail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was so hopeful this was real...oh well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Avoiding the question but sure. Feel justified, it doesn't make it not a dick thing to do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 03:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If your neighbor couldn't stand the smell of BBQ would they be justified in dumping an unwanted substance on your meat to ruin the taste? 

Smells are a hard thing to control.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 03:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very true. It's one of many reason people stick to indoor grows. Safer, better controlled environment, less piggly wigglies snooping around your crop, the list of benefits is endless. If only we could bottle up sunshine... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 23:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weed Pollen is very dusty and can be carried for miles on the wind. Dumping males in any residential area is frowned upon in the growing community because of the potential for the pollen to infect hidden out door grows. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 12:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IMO if you act like that you aren't smart, just a snide idiot. 

I can't speak for myself but there is a wide variation in what qualifies as smart. I doubt most prisoners are smart. Maybe they are a little more wise due to their time but certainly not smart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 12:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let him leave, finish your sandwich. When he comes back, "What sandwich? You must of been seeing things." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 23:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  All so the personal fortune of some ruthless people can increase.

I'd like to point out no one forces anyone to buy cigarettes or choose to smoke. 

People are addicted to all sorts of things, sugar, caffeine, etc. 

Do we blame every corporation that sells these products or the consumer who demands and purchases it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 15:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in ribbons...that was hilarious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 15:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do we allow the most pretentious people in our society to become the most popular? 

These dolts are paid out by big industries that produce their music for them, they have done nothing memorable, and have produced zero classics. 

Why the fuck do you have Nicka Manaj judging people for how they can sing when that woman can't carry a tune or a beat to save her fucking life. She's a loud woman with a big butt...better give her a record deal. 

Hollywood and it's shit makes me sick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 13:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So smart people are too smart to understand simple questions that lead them to reasonable conclusions?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 12:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't one simply stand by the enclosure and if the snake doesn't eat the mouse after a certain time just remove it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 12:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come to Jacksonville, Florida. 

There are tons of strays here as well as a whole line up of dogs who remain constantly chained outside waiting to be "liberated" from their terrible owners. Just go to any hood area and you'll find tons of cats and dogs running around. 

We saw Animal Control come and pick up a massive and gorgeous brown pit who was sweet as a can be. Anyone could of just stopped their car and this pupper would of hopped in for the first dog treat he saw.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 12:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People have seen these kinds of claims before. No one wants to fall for another hokey miracle water device. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
