<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject322</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 00:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will not let me set them as my default playback device.

I think that's a hint as to the problem, how do I find which Audio drivers suit me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All sounds wont go through my headphones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 23:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there. I did a full wipe of my computer and started from scratch, and it's been fantastic getting rid of all that clutter. BUT. Ever since then, plugging in my head phones doesn't make the audio automatically go through them.

In fact, I need to adjust each program manually (And I have no idea how to make audio on Chrome go through them when Skype is on.) In fact, Skype hijacks them completely forcing all other programs to play through my speakers. Which is inconvenient as other sounds come through my speakers while I'm talking to people. I'm sure you can see my issue eh?

What could cause this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 00:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only lived here a year, if you need friends/people to play cards against humanity with. Let me know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 00:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I'll damn well treat a gal like a princess, and I better get treated like a prince. I take you out for a romantic dinner? You take me out on a carriage ride for two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 18:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A good Azmo will tear down any lane with a single viking though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 16:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Falstadd can fly next to and kill any viking,(Maybe not Olaf) even with imediate dash response.

Azmodan can push Erics lane in so hard, the XP stays the same, and the Viking's team is down a lane.

As a Viking main, those are the two characters I hate the most.

Thrall, Greymane and Lunara are also hassels. Illidan can do good work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [HELP] Chrome is always stuck on top, I cannot alt tab, or bring up a new window from the task bar without first minimizing chrome. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 16:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 15:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not gold though. You'd have people spamming for gold.

But maybe you get 10 gold every five commendations you put out? Like. This would encourage you to commend someone every game (Even if it was an enemy for some solid plays because your team was a swinging bag of dicks)

This would now encourage you to play "Just one more game" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 15:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A commendation system, that you could not use on friends, would be great.

With a portrait reward for ten of each different commendation you get. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 14:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right, just look at the shitty apartment Archer grew up in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 14:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If any hero is played right,they seem OP. You ever play against a good viking? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 15:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no set definition for specialist. Azmodan has two wildly different builds, laser for team fight and lane pushing, globe for wave clear and sniping fleeing enemies. 

And he is different from Abathur who has mines(Gank) Hat(Support) and Locus(Lane push)

Who is again wildly different from the Vikings, constant global pressure (As opposed to Abathurs regular global pressure because someone e will call me on it)

Who are different from Gazlowe, amazing at mercs and zoning out fights

Who is different from Slyvanas, highly mobile DPS with abilities for disrupting the enemy team

Who is different from Murky, a lane pushing, pseudo tank, annoyance.

Etc etc.

But none of these people fit into any of the other set roles. One thing they can usually do is push well, but depending on yourself and your build you might be built for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 06:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an Azmo main, yes... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 20:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah mine too. Thy will be done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 20:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah, there are people who expected to get in because they bought Diablo back when the first game came out.

I understand your disappointment, I lived it myself up until this weekend. Who's your favourite hero? I'll play a game for you. I'll even yell a war cry of your choosing followed by "For Slimabob"

I'll die, but I'll do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 20:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is not what I'm saying. I've been applied since the start and I didn't say anything negative. I'm speaking up now, because when I was accepted, I came here to celebrate with people, only to find a torrent of negativity and anger sent after Blizzard.

I shared that piece of information for transparency's sake. And people can be disappointed, sure! People can have frustrations, of course!

But the arguments I continue to see, and the ones I direct this message towards are the "I'm better than these other people who got in the Beta because I actually love Blizzard." These people are the ones who are not trying to look at how Blizzard produces overwatch, but rather feeling victimized for being left out, despite their "Obvious superiority" as a consumer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 19:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're allowed to be disappointed. But I was just using this post to talk about the nasty angry salty "But I spend all the money I ever earn on Blizzard swag, I deserve this!" people, like you mentioned. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 19:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're allowed to be disappointed. I wish it was an Open Beta! But I was just using this post to talk about the nasty angry salty "But I spend all the money I ever earn on Blizzard swag, I deserve this!" people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 19:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> exactly. They don't care so much about you, as they do your region/rig in this case. Those are very unique and valuable metrics for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 17:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not even that, they 100% put some of those people in, like I preordered.

But that's the thing, they want some of everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just because you're loyal you shouldn't get in, they want to test all different types of customer bases, not just the people they know well already. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 17:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got into this beta weekend, and I'm going to enjoy myself, and yes I'm "Loyal" I've been with Blizzard a long time. Since Orcs and Humans. 

But here's the thing, for every "loyal" customer that gets in, they want to test on new generations, old people who might be applying, fans of other shooters, people who have never played a game like this in your life.

I keep seeing people toss around the word "loyal" like they should be entitled to this beta test. Where as the selection process isn't to reward or punish anyone, it's to help make overwatch a well rounded game. Welcoming to new players, but difficult enough to keep the attention of veterans.

I've even seen someone complaining about people getting in who just signed up a few days ago because of the butt themed controversy, and that's a good thing! Blizzard wants to know how band wagoners will react to the game. Will it hold their attention beyond what ever non-troversy brought them in? The beta test is as much a test for gameplay and bugs, as it is for the consumer base. They WANT to succeed, and these are the things they need to do to do it. 

Blizzard doesn't want to punish us as players, they want to do right by us. It's why they're still updating Diablo II and freaking Broodwar. As far as companies go, Blizzard is better than most. 

(Though they seriously need to step up their Europe stuff. ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 17:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a perfect idea! Make them fell orcs though, and you're onto something great.

I'd buy this legend skin in a heart beat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 17:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it is because that is a different incarnation of Diablo with different skills that they are considering for its own hero. They alsobhad the model ore built from diablo 3 cinematics.

The version we have isbcloser to the D2 version. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What evolutions would need to take place for a whale to retain its size, but thrive on land? What might that look like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 16:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 15:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol I posted this in Marvelsrudios as well, and someone commented that. Check my post history to see the thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 13:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The-gutters.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> hrkho jib abah jaju '][bah </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 02:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 02:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was cleared of all charges dick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 01:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy smokes. I wish! That would have made grinding Zera to ten so much easier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 00:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol not sure if that's the best part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ag uhi u nbiur pgyh g'sagok,b </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 22:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 21:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you? I only knew training as a mode you could afk in.

You also cannot lose training matches, which helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 21:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I can AFK in training, and let my bot bodyguards do the killing. This gets my score super high. And getting a high kill count was the whole point of towers of doom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 20:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know how to get live chat, and telephone tells me to go online. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 19:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I often have multiple games running. So maybe that  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 18:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah? How bad are they? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 18:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I may or may not have already gotten the vulture mount. Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 18:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mmhmm... So many hours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 18:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No hack, and I don't play KT. We shall see what we see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 18:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. Haven't touche him since I got him to 5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 18:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think? Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 18:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. I would be skeptical too. But being given the benefit of the doubt by the community helps soften the blow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 17:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry, I haven't touched him in months. You're safe. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 17:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> exactly! I'd at least like to know a time frame for my apparent misdeeds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 17:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I submitted my ticket an hour or two before the post. The post is more about me being desperate for somekinda lead on whats happening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 17:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Made my edit. As vague as you'd expect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 17:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It just tells me to go online. T_T </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 17:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It just tells me to go online. T_T </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 17:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I certainly wont. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 17:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, this is word for word mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 17:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Canada </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 17:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. I love those guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 17:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right? Or at least give me the justification for running off with my money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 16:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 16:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. What a shitty group of people. "He's so much better than us! Get good? No! Flame his shit" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 16:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you think the system is without flaw, that's on you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 16:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried, it tells me to go online. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 16:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. It just tells you to go online. T_T </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 16:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played with him. Followed him around with my low level character while he creamed the high level eneimeies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 16:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I often have other things running in the background. (Mostly games, or media players.) So maybe one of them got flagged? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 16:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't see why I was banned, so I'm going to wait to hear from Blizzard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 16:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll keep doing it, but to think I could get banned for sticking up for people. (If they target me I muteand block them.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 16:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. It's really upsetting. I've owned literally every Blizzard game other than Rock and Roll racing. I've been with them since the stat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 16:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh... Might not be worth 100+ dollars then... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 16:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right? It can just be ripped away from you! I never worried because I don't do bannable things. But now... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 16:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe. I do call people out when they're being bullies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 15:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 15:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could never do that. Haha patience of a saint right here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 15:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah. Right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 15:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. Play the vikings, can confirm, two out of three vikings hit, = no effect on my vision </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 15:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good. I'm glad tobhear that. Thanks for Shari g your story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 15:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fingers crossed we find out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 15:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 15:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played with him. Like, he was max level, and I just followed him while he killed stuff. Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 15:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know. No reason to assume one way or another, you do t know me. I'm just happy people are taking me with the benefit of the doubt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 15:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 15:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus. That must have taken ages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 15:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably, they are good people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 15:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have a support number the 1800 one I found just had a dead dial tone.

I'm k. Canada, does that change thigs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. Because DBro said he wasn't sure if it was bannable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah. I swear, the o lh thing I did was afk in training mode which blizzard already said no bans for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're in the exact same boat as me! I wonder if they did a rolling ban that we got caught in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did it for the vulture but only training. And the smurfs weren't banned, and they got free heroes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt it. I haven't seen any suspicious activity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. Its good to see bans are actually something they do, but... Not from this angle. Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. Never used Linux, I much prefer windows, not because its better persay, just less hastle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First thing I did. Came on here to vent/get clues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww I don't want to leave my guys hanging. But I'm glad you got your stuff fixed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I looked for over an hour and couldn't find the number. I'm in Canada if that makes a difference. Dobyou know it off hand? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope you get it unbanned dude. You didn't hurt anyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably? I'll upload them to hots log and update after work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appealed first, then came here to vent/for clues. I'm sure most people would. Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only been banned from Hots. Still have all the other games. (Literally every Blizzard game except Overwatch at this point) but I cannot bring myself to play them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god. T_T I love this game, but I cannot bring myself to make a new account  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its just a generic "You may have did one of these things" like copy and paste stuff. I'll update after work today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. I appealed before I came here. We'll find out what they say I did. I'll update as we go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah? I'll do just that! Thanks. Its over 100 dollars like I said, which isn't small potatoes when you're a student. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right? They just give me a very broad. "Oh it could mean you did anyone of these things" kinda email. So I'm appealing to at least find out what I'm accused of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. I had a high-level friend grind me to level 70 and haven't touched it since. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never play him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First thing I did before coming here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope so. Fingers crossed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Training mode. No other players were ever involved. I didn't even get dalies or gold from it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing. It just goes into the TOS describing what that particular violation means, which is very broad, without telling me what part of it I am accused of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tonight after work I will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm quite usually positive and encouraging our team not to give up. Haven't even been silenced before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just don't want him to get in trouble. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. Will update when that happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 06:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd delete this comment. One if the things in my ban letter mentions telling other players a out the exploit. I wouldn't want this to happens. To you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 06:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope not! I preorder all of their stuff. But if they ban me I've lost over a hundred dollars and hundreds of hours. I'd not continue being a customer if that happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 05:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah, haven't used him since before the bug anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 05:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too. I will update  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 05:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god I hope the look into it. I spent so much money on this game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 05:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I did it with Zeratul. I love the other two toss, but not him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 05:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even know how to do that. I hope they see that before my chair league game tomorrow.

Thanks for commenting, by the by. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 05:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. I Alt tab in, and que up attacks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 04:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think that's me, but maybe something similar! I hope beyond hope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 04:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh please please let this be the case </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 04:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God no. That's scummy as heck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 04:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't uploaded in ages. I've never been in a party with someone who plays Kael. Jaina and Li Ming are the mages of clutch not. (Chair league team) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 04:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. I mostly came down here to see if anyone e might have recently had a recent story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 04:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe this? But I queue up my hero to move and do things until twenty when I can try out different builds. It must be this. Its the only thing mentioned that I've done anything like. Oh god I hope not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 04:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perma. No idea why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 03:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I literally just tried to go online to buy Azmodunk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 03:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just hope this is a terrible mistake. T_T </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 03:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't touched him in months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Account Bans are a thing that Blizzard does. It just happened too me, and I don't know why. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 03:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EDIT: Thanks to all the support and benefit of the doubt you've been giving me.I know it is easy to say "He is obviously guilty and just whining" but I swear I'm not, and just having all you folks actually giving ideas as to what caused it, and believing me as made this a lot less stressful. I love the HOTS community, and this is why. No pitch forks at blizzard. The worst is people are saying they made a mistake, few pitchforks at me, but that's because I haven't provided all the data on me from the inception of the internet. ;)

Its just a bunch of awesome nerds coming together to try to help one sad guy figure out why his hobby was taken away, and that means a lot. :)

I'll update as I get updates, and make sure you all know what's going on.

Also, go cheer on my teammates tomorrow during their chair league game.10PM EST I know I'll be watching. Go Clutch Bot! END OF EDIT.


I'm really upset and scared right now. I've easily spent over 100 dollars on heroes of the storm, and I came from work so I could play it like I usually do, and I find my account banned.

For "Violation: Exploitation/Abuse of Game Mechanics"

But I've never done anything of the sort. I mean, I don't even use Kael, and he's the abusable one right now. I filed my ticket and I'm awaiting a response. I just want to know, did this happen to anyone else before? What happened? Are there things that might be considered abuse I may have accidentally done? 

edit: To make it worse, I have a chair league game tomorrow!

Edit: Since people are demanding they see thebemail sent too me in full. Formatting might be off because of reddit.


* * * NOTICE OF ACCOUNT CLOSURE * * *

Closure - Heroes of the Storm License 
Violation: Exploitation/Abuse of Game Mechanics

This includes exploiting game design, advertising exploits to other players, automating any aspect of gameplay, or using an unauthorized cheat program (also known as a hack). These programs provide player benefits normally not achievable in Heroes of the Storm. Such benefits include, but are not limited to, increased map visibility, abuse of connection speed, game crashes, etc. These unauthorized programs harm the competitive environment because they offer an unfair advantage over other players and supersede the intended limits of the game.

The above game license has been closed following this violation of our in-game policies. As the account holder, you are responsible for the activity associated with this game license. The abuse that took place was an unacceptable detriment to other players and the quality of our service as a whole. Even if this is the result of account sharing, the account owner is still be held responsible for the penalty because of the impact it had on the game environment.

No compensation has been provided for real money spent on this account. This action includes a permanent ban on Heroes of the Storm access. If you wish to play Heroes of the Storm you may do so only with a new or separate Battle.net account.

We don't take this decision lightly. Our team issued this closure only after a careful review of relevant evidence. Our support staff will not overturn these closures and may not respond to appeals. For information, see our article: http://www.battle.net/support/article/6741

Regards,

Customer Support
Blizzard Entertainment
http://battle.net/support


POSITIVe eDIT: (My keyboard is borken so my e key, among others in the top left, doesn't work, so I am ctrl + ving an e into my texts.)

A blizzard customer service rep, who will remain nameless until I get his permission to post it, has noticed this thread thanks to all of YOU! He's looking into it now and I'll post whether I'm found guilty or not. I don't believe I am, lets hope I their records back me up!

eDIT: Okay guys, so more news. They are asking me about a time when I started and dropped 35 Co-Op games super quick. It's because I was in training mode, and looking for Towers of Doom to see how many hero kills I could get on the board. (It was like 300 and some. My record. I think.)

So we shall see. More updates to come </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 03:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And look how desperately its trying to convince us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 01:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's  spammer who asks for 50 dollars paid online </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kael trying to figure out his bug </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 04:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/beY5Knr.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 16:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said that's what they wanted with her, didn't say they got it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 15:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right? That's what they wanted with Li Ming. If you're good you're good, and it should reflect that. If other people are good they can counter you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 14:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You and I both. The laser buffs are so good because if you take taste for blood, you get one SHAZAM moment, that might shake things up a bit during a team fight, but the laser makes you a consistent threat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The only proper way to play Xul, is a Quick Match Mirror match. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 05:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PsBattle: This happy sloth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 22:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 01:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would, but I don't want to be on your bad side when you shoot up the movie theater </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 22:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a tattoo artist that I love, I want to have working concept art to bring too him before I do though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 22:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the difference? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Working on a tattoo concept, advice on how to make the wording clearer to the artist, or on what additions I could make to the design. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 22:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 06:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nay! For he is a lesser god within my pantheon, and any who worship him, worship me. All gods answer too me, though they may not know it, and their praise is mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 04:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nipplebutter is a lesser diety within my pantheon. To worship him is to worship me. Spread the word my child. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 04:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bless you, for spreading the gospel my child. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 00:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be blessed /u/TastyPigHS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 00:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course! How else could my influence spread?

I /u/keypaw am the high god above all
/u/ScarletF is the Viridian. God of all things green.
You /u/Zamadaga shall be the god of structure, and you and your followers shall add each new god to our pantheon with an appropriate title. So I have decreed! And I have decreed well, for I have faith in you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 00:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I love you, my children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
