<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3901</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Autodesk understands your frustration. Please add your questions to the conversation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 09:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 08:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Twitter thread here: https://twitter.com/ChrisOffner3D/status/839742088564596737 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Autodesk understands your frustration. Please add your questions to the conversation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 08:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 08:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Twitter thread here: https://twitter.com/ChrisOffner3D/status/839742088564596737 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Autodesk understands your frustration. Please add your questions to the conversation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 08:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I keep getting BSODs with my XPS 15 9560. Any ideas why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 07:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep getting blue screens of death with my XPS 15 9560 at least two or three times a day on various occasions. Running Windows 10 on the UHD model.

Is anyone else having such problems, and are there any solutions in sight? I enjoy this machine when it works, but I'm afraid it it feels very unreliable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 07:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also still have an Asus Zenbook UX31A from 2011 and it still works like a charm. Had to replace it this year with an XPS 15 because I need some more powerful for work but I still love the Zenbook. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought I remembered much better CPU utilisation back when I was using Camtasia on a workstation. Is this a driver issue? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does Camtasia utilise my XPS 15 9560's CPU so poorly when encoding H.264? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For many people it *is* a big lifestyle choice though.

I didn't find cutting meat and dairy from my diet particularly tragic but for many people it is a bigger deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House of Cards S04E11 - Beyond marriage. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 10:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 07:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed, he has some great lectures on YouTube - like **[this one](https://deadline.com/2017/01/a-dogs-purpose-peta-boycott-drowning-dog-1201889236/)**. All in German though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 09:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Als wre ich selbst dort gewesen... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 08:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The idea is not to abandon technological progress but to focus it where it will actually improve quality of life in a sustainable manner. And reduce efforts in those areas where it doesn't - like R D on the 500th gadget that enables blind consumerism in a slightly different way.

Not sure who said it but a relevant quote I once read was: *"Today we have many of the smartest and most dedicated engineers in the world working on how they can best get people to click ads on social media sites. That isn't really an efficient use of resources."*

There's certainly a significant reduction in consumption involved in degrowth - but I wouldn't call that primitivist per se. We don't have to go back to the stone age at all, we just need to prioritise better what really matters and what's sustainable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, what? I'm not following. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stephen Colbert to Jon Batiste: "I love hearing from you Jon and I love keeping a dialogue open with you." - is Stephen taking the piss out of Jon Batiste here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Encouraging birth control and improving education and living standards everywhere to the point where birth rates drop voluntarily.

You can see this in all countries: birth rate drops with higher standard of living, education and access to birth control.

Germany and Japan have the lowest birth rates in the world while countries like Democratic Republic of Congo have crazy high birth rates.

The only humane and sustainable way to solve the overpopulation problem is to get people out of poverty, educate them and get them cheap or free access to birth control.

The good news is that birth rates *are* actually in decline around the world thanks to economic development. However, this trend needs to be sped up - because currently world population is still increasing like crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed, The Last Airbender and Legend of Korra are full of Buddhist ideas, concepts and parables. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To anyone interested in what Buddhism is even about - I can highly recommend Princeton University's free online course **[Buddhism and Modern Psychology](https://www.coursera.org/learn/science-of-meditation)** on Coursera as an introduction to (secular) Buddhist philosophy and psychology.

Check out the **[intro video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6N7db2mtT44)** to get a rough idea of what it is about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can highly recommend Princeton University's free online course **[Buddhism and Modern Psychology](https://www.coursera.org/learn/science-of-meditation)** on Coursera as an introduction to (secular) Buddhist philosophy and psychology.

**[Intro video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6N7db2mtT44)** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you like to know more? ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 12:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, technically the Dalai Lama is thought to be a reincarnation of previous Dalai Lamas who, in turn, are the manifestations of Avalokiteshvara, or Chenrezi, the patron saint of Tibet and Bodhisattva of Compassion.

Considering that Buddhism doesn't have a *God* in the same way that Christianity, Islam or Judaism does, calling a buddha or **[bodhisattva](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bodhisattva)** (which anyone can become if they follow the **[Noble Eightfold Path](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Noble_Eightfold_Path#The_Eight_Divisions)**) a God isn't *that* far off I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 11:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But there are varying degrees of unethical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 11:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The author is not saying that it doesn't make a difference!

So whats the answer? **Im not saying that we should all give up, or that we should stop making the small positive decisions we make every day as responsible humans.** And if youre choosing the greener product for health reasons, by all means, do what feels right. But when it comes to combating climate change, pollution, and habitat destruction, what we need to do is take the money, time, and effort we spend making these ultimately inconsequential choices and put it toward something that really matters.

Maybe the most important paragraph:

Beyond making big lifestyle decisions such as choosing to live in a dense urban area with public transportation, cutting red meat out of your diet, and having fewer children (or none at all), there are diminishing returns to the energy you put into avoiding plastic or making sure your old AAs end up in the appropriate receptacle. Globally, were projected to spend $9.32 billion in 2017 on green cleaning products. If we had directed even a third of that pot of money (the typical markup on green cleaning products) toward lobbying our governments to ban the toxic chemicals were so afraid of, we might have made a lot more progress by now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 11:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So whats the answer? **Im not saying that we should all give up, or that we should stop making the small positive decisions we make every day as responsible humans.** And if youre choosing the greener product for health reasons, by all means, do what feels right. But when it comes to combating climate change, pollution, and habitat destruction, what we need to do is take the money, time, and effort we spend making these ultimately inconsequential choices and put it toward something that really matters.

From the article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 10:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Globally, were projected to spend $9.32 billion in 2017 on green cleaning products. If we had directed even a third of that pot of money (the typical markup on green cleaning products) toward lobbying our governments to ban the toxic chemicals were so afraid of, we might have made a lot more progress by now.

Great article, I highly recommend it!

Plug for /r/Degrowth for anyone interested in this topic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conscious consumerism is a lie. Here is what you can really do to save the environment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 10:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 10:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There *are* a bunch of abandoned houses in Berlin. Not too far from me near Ostbahnhof there's one for example. However, they're in a terrible state and it's illegal to live there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To anyone interested in degrowth I highly recommend this book by Germany economics professor Niko Paech: Liberation from Excess </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 10:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'd like to promote /r/Degrowth - a sub about post-growth economy that I believe could use a lot more activity and might be right up many /r/environment users' alley! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 10:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'd like to promote /r/Degrowth - a sub about post-growth economy that I believe could use a lot more activity and might be right up many /r/latestagecapitalism users' alley! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 10:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'd like to promote /r/Degrowth - a sub about post-growth economy that I believe could use a lot more activity and might be right up many /r/anticonsumption users' alley! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 10:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conscious consumerism is a lie. Here is what you can really do to save the environment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 09:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 09:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't consider the consciousness that you have to consume less (not to mention completely excuse yourself from the consumption of many things) as being part of 'conscious consumerism', than you're doing it wrong.

I fully agree but to be fair, *conscious consumerism* as a term is usually used to talk about *what to buy* rather than *how much to buy*.

The vital concept of /r/Degrowth is usually never addressed in these conversations. In that sense I wouldn't say that the author of the article used the term in any misleading way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 09:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're blaming him for deflating your highly romanticised expectation of what it would be like to eat at a Michelin starred restaurant based on his actual experience?

I think the problem is not with the author but maybe with your attachment to this theoretical ideal. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 09:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, nice idea. :D

Although I gather from the trailer that there aren't actually any neighbours, and the house is mostly abandoned? Not sure. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 08:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we stop it with the retarded *us vs. them*?

Whether communism or capitalism kills millions is equally fucked up! No matter the system in place, where it fails (like in this case) there need to be adjustments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 08:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's **not** the right way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China vows to 'make sky blue again' as it drops target for economic growth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 08:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China vows to 'make sky blue again' as it drops target for economic growth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 08:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 07:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finde ich auch.

Nach **Victoria** und nun **Berlin Syndrome** frage ich mich zwar, ob *"innocent expat traveller girl in search for love/belonging goes to Berlin and gets into  trouble with local Berlin guys"* jetzt ein neues Genre wird... ;P

Aber Victoria ist ein groartiger Film, und das hier sieht auch vielversprechend aus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Berlin Syndrome - TRAILER </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 13:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 13:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Teresa Palmer, yeah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Berlin Syndrome - TRAILER </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 12:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Berlin Syndrome - TRAILER </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 12:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trailer: Berlin Syndrome </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 12:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 09:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow... the Brown Hare goes almost as fast as a lion... that's impressive.

I'd be interested to see a comparison of the fastest *land animals*' speed relative to their body size / body length. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 09:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Krita for Sketching, Painting, and Concepting with Wacoms is far superior to Photoshop.

Not really. Krita's performance with large brushes (i.e. on high resolutions) is nowhere close to Photoshop's - even after recent improvements and hacky workarounds. I work in 3D and animation and know a bunch of concept artists who tried to migrate to Krita but had to go back to Photoshop for mostly performance reasons.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 09:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus, Reddit is paranoid. This isn't /r/HailCorporate and I'm in no way affiliated with The Late Show or this comedian whatsoever. I'm just a random dude in Germany who enjoyed this video and shared it on Reddit... apparently in a way that people here found suspicious. I also don't have more than this Reddit account. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 09:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  She told me the other day she could "sleep when she's dead", I replied that I aim to sleep plenty while I'm still alive, which she laughed at. Grim.

Reminds me of this quote by Arthur Schopenhauer:

*"Sleep is the interest we have to pay on the capital which is called in at death; and the higher the rate of interest and the more regularly it is paid, the further the date of redemption is postponed."* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 20:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh?

I just posted it here because I wanted to share it - because watching it I had the reaction expressed in the comment above. Not sure why that's weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 19:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's funny to me how in the US there's this crazy anti-socialist propaganda from cold war times still floating around, where anything 'social' is literally Stalin, and a 'socialist' is the worst thing you can call someone for many people... yet I know of no other country where the communist **[Hero of Labor](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hero_of_Socialist_Labour)** mentality is as strong and alive in the culture as the USA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 19:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ugh, Im So Busy: A Status Symbol for Our Time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 17:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! Best 5-minute set I've seen in a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Late Show: Comedian Mo Amer Shared His Refugee Background With Eric Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 10:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit is a weird one for me...

I had no problems at all getting rid of Facebook, Twitter and other social media since the value proposition was so very clear: the peace of mind I got from not using them significantly outweighed missing out on whatever small benefits they provided.

But with Reddit it's different. I keep coming back to Reddit to get genuinely helpful answers to questions, find tremendous learning resources via truly helpful subreddits (/r/learnprogramming just as one example), etc.

But once I'm back on Reddit for those valuable use cases, I can't help but recede back into also wasting a lot of time on /r/all and other pointless areas of Reddit. :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ugh, Im So Busy: A Status Symbol for Our Time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 10:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ugh, Im So Busy: A Status Symbol for Our Time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 10:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Razer Wants To Build the Best Linux Laptop, And It Needs Your Help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 07:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super, danke! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Earth Awaits - a site that calculates your cost of living around the world according to your lifestyle, family, and housing needs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ist Black Mirror auf Deutsch verfgbar? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrde ein paar Episoden gerne meiner Mutter zeigen, aber sie schaut leider keine englischen O-Ton-Sachen an. Ich selbst habe seit 13 Jahren keine deutsch untertitelten Filme oder Serien mehr geschaut und hab keine Ahnung, wie es sich mit Sachen wie Black Mirror heutzutage hlt.

Ist die Serie auf Deutsch synchronisiert worden? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Sorry, above average isn't good enough.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Max Richter's soundtrack for S03E01 Nosedive beautifully creates and captivates the melancholy of Black Mirror </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "My mommy says you hate foreigners" -- Little girl knights Nigel Farage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Daily Show - Trevor Noah Between the Scenes: That Performance Plus Gerrymandering = Republicans Can Rule Forever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
