<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1989</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: If you shave into the sink, an easy way to brush hair from the counter or off your body and into the sink is to use a shaving brush. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 22:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 21:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well how do you react to eating dairy? I have been dairy free for a few years and my skin almost completely cleared up but meanwhile, I have developed lactose intolerance onto of the allergy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 20:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well isn't that just a more cumbersome way of doing the exact same thing?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 20:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Other than the terms on which the deposit is refundable, the only mention of rent in the lease is the dollar amount, due date, and the prorated part of the partial month.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 19:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't having a rental history make it easier to find a place in the future? What about further down the road when I apply for a home loan?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 19:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a matter of not wanting the burden. It's a matter of not wanting to give that responsibility to any of the roommates. Not myself or either of the other 2.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 19:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My thoughts exactly. As much as I want to trust said roommate, I don't want to have to. But security and trust aside, I wanted to make sure it was legit. It seems kind of sketchy what the landlord is asking for but from what it seems like, it's just a trust thing between the 2 people that are most familiar with each other. The roommate that she was referring to has been there the longest. I and another guy are taking the place of people that have moved out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My landlord wants to receive my rent from my roommate. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 19:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In other words, she said it would be easier for her if all of us gave our share to one person, and she collected in full from that one person. I suggested auto-pay or direct into the landlord's account, for the obvious security reason, but also because I want to build rental history and don't know if that can happen if my roommate is the middleman between me and paying my rent. Am I going about things correctly? 

Edit: The landlord greenlit my idea to set up direct deposit so crisis averted. Thanks for all the input! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OR] I'm reading over a lease for the first time in my life and would love to understand all the statues that it is referencing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 19:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In order of appearance  
OR 90.394  
OR 105.105  
OR 105.168  
OR 90.302(3)(a)  
OR 90.302(7)  
ORS 105.105 through 105.168  
ORS 90.427  
ORS 90.425  
42 U.S.C. 4852d  

Edit: I get it. There is a lot here. I was just looking for a good direction to go in. u/Counsel_for_RBN pointed me toward a Landlord/Tenant Handbook and that was enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Pokemon Go is Nintendo's way of keeping us active, the side quests better be things that help me irl. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 03:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would totally take a hike or meet my neighbors or learn first aid in exchange for Pokemon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT Request: How do I keep my white shoes white? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 19:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 18:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for all of that. Also, does text message count as in writing or is there a formal documentation step that is standard for roommates to draw up?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 08:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> James Spader is awesome, shame on Liz, bad Liz, go to your room and think about what you've done. But seriously, once you are caught up, you'll probably be able to see how the character dynamics have potential to change next season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 06:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't. It has a headache. Maybe tomorrow night.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 05:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking for a comprehensive list and Google's not being very friendly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OR] Very general question about licensing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 04:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beit drivers, wedding, business, or otherwise, what are all the things you need to be licensed for?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 03:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ignorance is bliss  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can one earn scholarship dollars full time as a substitute for a nearly full-time job? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 02:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This might be a question for r/personalfinance or somewhere else altogether but I thought I'd start here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have a place to move into but have not yet seen the lease agreement. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 00:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend is looking for new roommates and I have first dibs but we have only discussed things verbally (and via text message if that counts as in writing.) He is supposed to send me a scanned copy of the one agreement that we all sign onto as well as a renter's application. It will be the first time I have ever put my name on one and among the first I have ever looked at. What details should I pay attention to? What should I be aware of weather or not it shows up in writing? What questions should I be asking that I might not have? I know plenty about the property but not much about the actual contract. It's in a college town too so I don't expect much but it'd be nice to go into things not getting steamrolled or letting anyone pull a fast one over me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 23:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem with the status quo though is that in my silence and my opting to go to the other room, they don't even consider that passive, but consider it my passive aggressive way of saying I'm the democratic black sheep in the family and don't want to hear what they have to say. It be more valuable for me to figure out how to tell them to stop instead of ignoring it because there is no way I can live out the rest of my days opting to walk away from the situation. Like I said, I'm close with my family. Ignoring what they talk about is a luxury I'm seldom afforded.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Me [22M] with my family, on politics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 22:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My family is conservative and loves to talk politics. I've kinda taken a meh approach to the overwhelming majority of the politics of the people in my life but I'm really close with my family for better or for worse. (worse on account of this thing in particular) and would love to find a way to get them to stop shoving it in my face. I can take the kumbaya approach to the points I disagree with them on but they don't give me any breath to form my own opinions or check with my own sources. It's impossible to have a rational conversation with someone about something that is so divisively inflaming as politics, especially with the presidential options we have now. Any ideas? 
   
**tl;dr**: The penis analogy when it comes to political opinions; It's okay to be proud of your own, just don't shove it in people's faces. 

Edit: I wouldn't call myself either liberal, centrist, or conservative. I used to identify as independent/unaffiliated but my views on certain issues evolve and slide along the political spectrum. My views and opinions are besides the point here. I'm the level-headed one in the family who often surprises people whenever anything riles me up. That's one of the hurdles we are jumping here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 21:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I follow your analogy but don't see how something that is fast/big enough to easily  travel from one planet to the next [infecting] would still be too inconceivable small to worry about being crushed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How are bacteria and viruses able to be transmitted through contact instead of being crushed like bugs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 21:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: If I can effortlessly squash a bug on contact, how are bacteria and viruses able to be transmitted via contact with infected surfaces without being squashed themselves? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 19:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 08:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wannabe in my ass   
99 red balloons in my ass  
One time in my ass  
Brass Monkey in my ass  
No one like you in my ass  
Jammin in my ass
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 08:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any *kind* of word counts. What doesn't is Marijuana where the sound the letter makes changes. That doesn't qualify it as silent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is the F.B.I. not 'recommending' charges against Hilary Clinton vs not charging her? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 04:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 11:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll reiterate what some of the others have said but in my own words. The *correct* direction to shave is in the direction your hair is growing. Against the grain will leave your skin smoother for longer but also comes with the associated risks such as ingrown hairs and worse niks. That's at least been my experience.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] My family is pretty conservative and loves to talk politics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 05:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the common denominator of all successful people? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 19:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 07:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see what you did there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone explains to me all the different types of bars? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 09:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Karaoke and sports bars are pretty self-explanatory, but what about sports bars, lounges, dive bars,  gastropubs, cocktail bars, breweries, and 'traditional' bars?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 08:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I...I....I... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 00:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen a lot of videos online of locks being tested with cutters and angle grinders. I just thought the noise of an angle grinder would draw too much attention to the thief.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 00:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chain lube for a lock? Mind explaining that to an idiot? It seems much less counter-intuitive to use WD40 than chain lube.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 20:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is an angle grinder really your preferred method over lock-picking? If that's the case, I feel a lot safer using that lock than I did before. Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did we end up with U.S. presidential elections, leap year, and summer Olympics all on the same 4 year interval? Is it anything other than coincidence? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 20:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 20:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get it, Omega pays for both of those contracts, I just think it's cool. I'm a Bond fan and it's Olympics season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 20:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.olympic.org/sponsors/omega  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Omega, James Bond's preferred brand of watch, is the official timekeeping company of the Olympics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 20:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 20:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WD40, check. I've registered my keys with Kryptonite's key safe program if that counts as writing the codes down. Not having a big enough chain to wear in a way that hurts when I fall, check. And yeah, I'm in Portland.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 19:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link the video please?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thoughts on the kryptonite chain locks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 18:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just bought the Evolution series 4 55 cm chain and am pretty happy with it. The thing I am afraid of (besides the security) is the longevity. The tag that comes with the keys says to not force it into the key hole but I find more often than not that I have to fiddle around with it. It's not as easy as I'd like it to be for the key to go in and out. Especially if I am going to be coming back to my bike at night. What are your experiences?

Edit: Guys, I get it. WD-40 is a bad idea. Its a dead horse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How is an amputee athlete able to keep their prosthesis on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 09:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What word(s) do you intentionally mispronounce in your head to get the spelling right? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 08:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 04:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a fan of Session
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 04:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool. I just didn't know if I was out of the loop or not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does adding to the amount of stuff you are trying to microwave add to microwave time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 00:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand that the electromagnetic waves excite the water molecules but my understanding of it gets hazy beyond that. I would think it wouldn't matter and that if the waves are passing through, it wouldn't matter as much  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My line of work exposes me to small amounts of hazardous materials. How readily available are the tests? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 23:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am mainly concerned with asbestos but also less so with lead and mercury. I take every on-site precaution possible but in case that's not enough, want to add preventative medical care to the mix.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 19:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talking politics with family </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wonder how good business is for door-to-door salesmen of 'No Soliciting' signs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 09:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your favorite local FM stations? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 19:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get to set 6 in my car so throw em at me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 08:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, I'll concede that it might not be terribly outdated. (I'm only in my 20s and born and raised in a migrant home so forgive me for not getting the references from the 70s and 80s. lol) Nonetheless, I think you get the point. Seth definitely throws a lot of himself into Stewie. So much so that it'd be cool to go and review it all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 04:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't Spectre his last or second to last film before his contract is up? I'd expect the studio to be planning far enough ahead.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 04:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good to know because I was just teaching a kid how to do the turn signal with his bicycle. hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the latest on Daniel Craig's successor? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 04:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is your favorite fictional character? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 04:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every time the news is covering something catastrophic, I walk outside, look up, and smile at the sight of the sky not falling. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 04:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 03:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have enough confidence in the market to see it recover fully. I am pretty young and have my money in it for the long run. I am just confused as to how to move my investments around if at all. Not to mention the idea of buying in some more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 03:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have had money invested with a financial adviser for a few years now. I know there are a lot of things that impact the markets but this is the first reference to a singular event that has ever been referenced in an email that has been sent out to clients. My adviser is recommending not to pull out and even invest more where appropriate. Thoughts?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 02:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this common knowledge among motorcyclists?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 02:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where were you reading from?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone seriously needs to start keeping track of all Stewie's outdated pop culture references that fly over the heads of the target audience. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 02:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 20:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah! Thanks! Is finding the time between feeding and business pretty universal or is it going to be a trial and error process?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 19:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The not keeping it caged up all day actually brings up a point that I have wondered about. How will I know weather I am making the right decision or not when it comes to keeping it outside all day or trusting it not to do anything nefarious while I am gone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 09:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rotate slower! It's choppy and i wanna try to hone in on the pattern if not get completely hypnotized by it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 09:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harvard hosts the premiere tournament on the east coast and UC Berkeley on the east coast - both on the same weekend, both prestigious, large, and I've been to UC Berkeley. The Policy is taken very seriously.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 08:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mtter museum in is Philadelphia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 06:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the newer one. The minimalism and sleekness of it matches a lot of other schools.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A guide to Awareness Ribbons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 05:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that, following his death, Einstein's brain was handled both improperly and against his wishes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 04:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite way to stay entertained on road trips? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 01:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 01:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are both of those aforementioned companies completely independent of health insurance companies that deal with people? Could I, for example, call up AARP, GEICO, or any other insurance provider and ask them to start covering my pets too?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 01:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you cleared it up so no worries. And yeah, I am in college right now and am trying to plan ahead for when I get out of college. I'd be looking at a fairly demanding yet regular work schedule, *hopefully* a consistent living situation, and the other factors you pointed out like social life and travel tenancies are completely up in the air because, well, things change.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 01:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fostering a dog? First I have heard of something like that. It definitely sounds like a good idea but how do I even go about that? And don't get me wrong, I haven't romanticized anything about it. I've had pets before... namely caged animals, but still.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 22:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 25 step process for Jack Sparrow. 3 step process for everyone else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 22:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what sort of insurance plans are out there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 20:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> age is something I am undecided on. I understand that a puppy needs to be housebroken but I also see the pros and cons in getting one fully grown. I just haven't made that decision yet. My living situation will change by the time I get around to becoming a dog owner but in my general region, the climate can be good to any kind of dog at the right time of year. I have friends with dogs who all have varying lengths of hair.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 19:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I go beyond the bare bones basics and consider all the other things you mentioned, what kind of budget range are we now looking at? I'm not much of an athletic type so I don't know if I need to budget for sports but I know that dogs need outdoor time, walks, and socialization.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 19:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's times like this that I wish there was a dislike button like people always ask for on Facebook instead of just downvoting. I'm speechless because it's something we just expect from Walmart but at the same time, disapproval, boo Walmart, sorry about your friend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] I am a dog lover but not a dog owner. What are some things I need to know and consider before becoming an owner? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 19:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 18:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to say you are in the wrong sub but maybe get someone from r/personalfinance or r/legaladvice in on the conversation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 08:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is some batshit Texas information!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 02:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not programming languages. lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] Is the email I just got from HonorSociety.org legit or not? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 22:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an acceptance letter but it also asks me to activate my account and be careful with my information. Forgive me for being skeptical but I would expect information like that to come from an @oregonstate.edu email address. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] a type of language. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 22:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I know that a pidgin language is a grammatical simplification of 2 mutually uninteligable language that the speakers organically come up with. But what I am thinking of is when you have a bilingual speaker that adopts the grammatical structure and lion's share of vocabulary from one language and throws the second on in there on occasion.

Edit: Spanglish is an example.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch "Why Humans Run the World | Yuval Noah Harari | TED Talks" on YouTube </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 21:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 21:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Typo. I meant 867-5309 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For sale: baby shoes, never worn - Hemingway ... What's your best 6 word story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 19:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 19:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friends and I tried calling 876-5309 once with a few different area codes and one of them was the voice mail of a man angrily reminding everyone that his name is not Jenny.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lets earn comment karma here </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 19:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/TheoryOfReddit/comments/tx4mz/comment_karmawhoring_101_guide_to_racking_up/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 19:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there any lash-back from the phone company, legal or otherwise, for not using 555 numbers?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 19:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But flappy bird was still banned from the app store and I find that hilarious. Especially because none of the knock-offs were.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are fake numbers in movies and TV shows always 555 numbers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 19:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 18:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can read music fairly well. My goals have changed over time. When I started, I wanted to be an amazing guitarist, but my priorities have since changed and now I only learn songs for friends and family to play on occasion. I also bought a solid body fixer-uper that I want to fix up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 06:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want clarification, not trying to be a prick about it. I mean, do you have a language in mind? I'm pretty sure past tense is universal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 05:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly don't see your point. Anyone who is bilingual enough to be reading jokes on reddit would know well enough how to translate contractions and idioms and such. And father is a religious term.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Actors and actresses are among the only people that get away with going by more than one name. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 19:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some important details of headline stories that people often forget or leave out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 17:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Metallica performed in Antarctica just to break a record and be the first musical act to perform on all 7 continents. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 17:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 08:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To flip your example around, I actually did run into a situation such as my example where the work I was paying for was not done up to snuff. However they did apologize and stay cordial while I was loosing my cool and otherwise being appropriate. It would have been encompassed by professionalism if they had actually done the work well. I'm not going to be a returning customer but not because of how they treated me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 05:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might be so relevent that it's part of the definition of professionalism that I included right below the part you bothered to read.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 05:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The examples I had in mind were the other way around but I guess the shoe fits.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 01:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Workplace etiquette is defined by your organization and communnication skills as well as how you treat people. Professionalism is defined by someone's competence in the skills expected of them in their work environment. Part of your job description might very well include being orderly, kind, and personable, but those things are no replacement for the rest of your job description. Example: I might like my mechanic as a person, but no matter how much he smiles and jokes and no matter how much free coffee I get out of his lobby, if he didn't fix my car, he didn't fix my car.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's a difference. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 00:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 19:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean the confirmed theory that Ron is Dumbledore. And Dumbledore created the Order.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 18:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makes a lot more sense wen you consider Ron technically created it. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 18:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that the cups are never empty is the kind of thing you need to tell your boss. It's one thing to put the crap in yourself but another thing entirely to treat customers like that. We have 1 coffee machine in the breakroom for us and a Keurig and complete serving station in the conference room for customers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit shouldn't impose the mandatory wait time between posts when are attempting to resubmit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 20:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McLaren 12C that I saw on the highway the other day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 19:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McLaren 12C I saw on the highway the other day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 19:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is the O.J. case suddenly everywhere again? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 02:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The O.J. Simpson Story, O.J. made in America, The People vs. O.J. Simpson, and I even think I caught a special that recapped the trial. 22 years later isn't much of an anniversary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am looking for an example in American English of each of the 26 letter being silent and cannot complete the list. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 00:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> F, J, Q, V, and Y are all missing from the list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] What should a comprehensive maintenance schedule include? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 05:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tire rotations, tire preassure check, oil, tuneups, etc. What goes into etc?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoiler] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 18:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone remind me why the password was dashwood.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do we need both 'young' and 'new' if they share the antonym 'old' and that doesn't cause any issues? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 19:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What 'shots fired' post have you seen that actually shut you up or changed your views on an issue? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 06:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 06:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In what world does watching the car behind you suffer the consequences of their own impatience constitute not minding my own business? I'll reiterate for you that I wasn't actively keeping him behind me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 05:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that each subreddits has it's own moderators. I guess what I am getting at is my whole host of questions about the defaults subs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are the default subreddits moderated by Reddit admins or are they just really popular, prestigeous, well-moderated subreddits? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 05:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 05:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't attempting to control anything. I was just minding my own business and minding my follow distance, watching him in my mirrors trying to cut me off. Sometimes space opened up in the other lane and closed right back up but he was too impatient not to try to get in before it closed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you do when a skill of yours starts to atrophy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 03:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 03:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not an asshole. I was going in the fastest lane. And I wasn't so far behind the car in front of me that it made any sense for anyone to cut me off. The asshole was the one that kept trying to slingshot around 1 car only to take his exit earlier than me anyway. I have enough going on between the ears to empathize with why he might want to be going faster, but not to the point where I'm going to allow reckless driving.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What kind of paper are certificates printed on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 18:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE feel a bit of vindication for keeping the driver behind you that keeps trying to cut you off? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 17:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 17:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. It's got about as tall of a cabin space as the b250 though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] Trying to think of the model name of a particular car. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 07:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it's a Mercedes-Benz and a larger one. Not van large. Maybe the same size as an SUV but not part of the G-class. It looks like of like a crossover. Probably a 3-letter model name but I know, I know, with Benzs, that's not very helpful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 07:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://uncyclopedia.wikia.com/wiki/The_Oldest_Trick_in_the_Book  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 19:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  *I think* single issue voters should still have their voices heard. Yes that introduces challenges, and point taken, the test shouldn't alienate anyone or be too rigorous. Would it not be appropriate to draw an analogy to a driving test and calling voting a responsibility as well as a right? Not the impossibly tricky written test but actually driving. I've never written a test before. I'm not going to pretend like I have a grand vision for this. But, like mentioned before in response to earlier comments, I imagine the test drafters would have their work cut out for them.
As to your point on the constitutionality, I would want to see that actually play out in court. Voting rights in a democracy are recognized almost globally as one of the fundamental humans rights but there still are *reasonable* restrictions that disbar non-citizens, convicts, etc. from voting. Those factors are much more black and white than the bar-setting challenge of figuring out who is too "stupid" to make an informed decision but lets not give anyone with agendas the benefit of the doubt. Let's question every standard. I don't think that will be a dead end. I think that'll bring us closer to getting people involved in the democratic process. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite saved post? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 18:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 17:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's like saying everyone who pays taxes and doesn't break the law is also entitled to welfare checks or employee-level security clearance into publicmy funded buildings like prisons, 3 letter agencies, and military bases. We already have reasonable standards and restrictions on exactly who can do exactly what. This is just another one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When do you get what you pay for and when can you get away with being cheap? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 07:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 07:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are other ways to boost voter turnout. And even if there werent, why does voter turnout, as shameful as it is, have to be something we consider when fleshing out the voting proccess?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The plural of anecdote is not data." - Roger Brinner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 06:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 00:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Milk mixing with flour, eggs and sugar react chemically. chemical changes and physical changes are fundamentally different, the dough becomes dough, not a mixture of almost spoiled milk and other ingredients. You are in the clear.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 00:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it went without saying that an educated populous can make an educated decision. That's not taking rights away from anyone, thats incentivizing people to do their due diligence.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 23:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm fully aware of that. I'm just not yet convinced that it is an *unreasonable* obstacle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 23:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moscow Mule Mug is what was on the label when I bought mine and it's so fun to say that I refuse to call it anything else.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 23:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing is in place to stop you or I from voting provided you and I are not fellons, D.C. residents, U.S. non-citizen residents, or someone without and ID. 
P.S. - Did I forget to mention I'm a full time student with 3 jobs? Well, yeah, good for me indeed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 23:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Constituents can place preassure on decision makers in other districts. Especially when it is as royal of a screw up as the voting process. The lead story in flint has cities all over the country looking at their water, Furgeson got people looking at their policing, etc.Even *if* gerrymandering was stopping people from successfully protesting any kind of abuse, news outlets would help put significant preasure on lawmakers to do something.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 23:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not *too* complex. It's just not as simple as passing battons down a track. Overcomplicating it is dumb and oversimplifying it is ignorant. And sure, you can feel responsibple for educational policy, but at the end of the day, the bad teacher is the one accountable of their actions, not the tax payers, the standardized test designers are the ones acountable for the poorly designed questions, not the students, etc. Placing blame on the people that it's easiest to place blame on accomplishes nothing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 23:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, we should educate the stupid, not let them take the country down along with the not-stupid. That chain of command between people and government and education is kind complex (read the other comments) and the bad eggs dont *need* to ruin it for the rest of us. especially just to teach the entire frickin country a lesson that only the select few in charge of educational policy need.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 22:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, gerrymandering is a thing. What does that have to do with voting rights?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 22:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shouldn't the people in charge of the educatonal system be the onces who see the consequences of not doing their job insted of the entire country? I mean sheesh, how does that solve the problem of education? We have a criminal justice system in place. No need to take things out on *everyone* because we only *seemingly* collectively failed at one thing. I'll grant you that education is one hell of an important thing but still.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 22:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, um, history is supposed to be the lesson we learn from. There has been every concievable type of abuse at the polls thoughout world history which is why paper voting is still a good idea over electronic voting (neither here nor there) but the fact is yeah, whenever you are dealing with how political power is allocated, you deal with abuse, corrution, and bad things in general, that doesn't stop us from trying. In the long run, I think it would be a better system than not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 22:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You get to vote for bills in local elections. The electoral college and representative system is a different talk for antoher day but even if you DO that it into consideration, remember that voting on measures is the litnus test that elected representatives use to determine the popularity of their decisions with their constituency. It's not the only factor that goes into their decisions but it is an important enough one that I would sleep beter at night knowing that my representative knew what those of us that put some thought into it know what we are talking about and made an informed decision.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 22:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean like how bias news sources do in the status quo sometimes?  The difference would be that the 'test material' would be tax payer funded, held to a  higher standard, and have bi-partisan oversight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 22:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Potential being the key word though. Does anyone complain about voter information pamphlets being too partisan in the status quo? Not that I have heard of. Also, voting is one of those things where if you want to do it, you will. The last ballot cycle was right before a huge midterm of mine and I voted on test day anyway. You just do what you have to do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 22:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, at the risk of sounding classist, it's not the uneducated demographic whose voices ought not be heard, it's the people who really and I mean *really*) have no idea what they're talking about. The type who you could spot out after having a 5 minute conversation with them about anything and clearly see that they can't make a *rational* decision. Those people are all still allowed to vote.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 22:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it is partisan *enough* to make a difference (because I get it, bias is something that we just cannot get away from, though it is something that we can work away from and do so effetively if implemented correctly) then I think enough peoiple would make a fuss about it that things would change.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CMV: Passing a test on the basic issues and candidates should be a prerequisite to voting in the democratic process. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 19:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand that there are the logistical issues of crafting such a test, let alone the people that are already hard-pressed to find the time to drop ballots off. But I feel like people that truly want to participate in the democratic process (and everyone should be btw) then it's not too much to ask your fellow citizens to prove that they know what they are talking about. I can disagree with you on the issues or on which candidate is better but we can both still walk away understanding that we have made informed decisions, different, but informed nonetheless. Such a test wouldn't be designed to be Partisan or single anyone out, just to make sure there is a fundamental understanding of what bills and officials they are voting for as well as maybe the bill's aim or the candidate's platform. So, basically, it could be thought of as quizzing people on the info inside of a voter information pamphlet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some things that everyone knows but no one says? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 18:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Making a killing and a living mean the same thing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 20:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 02:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> toothpaste mustaches  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some grammar Nazis told me about a seminar they are going to attend about cause and effect. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 08:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're there to affect its effect and it's there for their two affects too.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the black dot campaign is saving lives. [PSA] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 07:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For some period of time, you were the youngest person in the world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 07:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does the arm hair test for blade sharpness exist? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 03:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always been uncomfortable watching people that I trust try it on themselves but when I try it, it doesn't do anything except make me question what the heck I'm doing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What advice have you received that you can attribute most of your success or happiness to? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 18:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 08:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3bxcc3SM_KA  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 06:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a niice comment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 02:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What sets Amway apart is that the pyramids isn't' locked in and the recruited are free to make more money than their recruiter but I'm sure the Pareto Principle 80/20 rule still applies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE go \_()_/ with pets? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 00:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 00:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> proved... o_0
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 21:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'world' is both a synonym for 'planet' and for 'earth'  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 20:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=069y1MpOkQY explains how budget airlines cut costs and all the ways you might have to adapt to if you book with them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shout out to the MinuteEarth video where part of it had the same visuals. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 20:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Omega Olympic Speedmaster is one of the most beautiful things I have ever seen. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 19:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 19:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hypnotizing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sean Bean vs. Stormtroopers would make one hell of an unresolved movie ending. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 18:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 18:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wouldn't the unit cost go down with scale and over time though? It's only (probably) not worth it in the short term. At least as far as I can tell.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 18:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But wouldn't it be excellent PR for someone to say they are spear-heading a change that would leave us better off *despite* the risk and how much it scared them? I understand the tax thing but I don't understand why the option to not give tax-deductible donations is appealing. If you don't make enough money to give any away, sure. But that's different than just deciding one year to not give because you heart isn't in it. Besides the point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do companies give so much to charity yet are not willing to change standard business practices for the better? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 18:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mainly when we want to do something like convert to metric or any of the other examples, often the main thing cited as being the reason we can't is the cost and inconvenience to the markets for those kinds of changes in the short run. But the high rollers that would be impacted are the sake companies that give millions away to non-profits every year so I don't see too much of a difference.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 17:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm good bro. I'm good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Great things are done when men and mountains meet. - William Blake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 17:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.brainyquote.com/quotes_of_the_day.html  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 16:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The yay-sayer rational that you rattled off is great but why you deffend what you do doesn't have much to do with what you say in that deffence. I met good people in this and didn't even wanna even convince myself that *they* were making any kind of mistake but I ultimately walked away. away. Also, correction, I honestly don't know if it was investigative journalism specifically or just journalism. Either way, they were beating a lot of dead horses in their defense of themselves without ever really giving me the depth that you would hope didn't have to be prodded for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Super Hydrophobic Surface and Magnetic Liquid - The Slow Mo Guys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 09:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 06:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a mite on the hair on the wart on the frog on the bump on the log in the hole in the bottom of the sea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WorldWide and Amway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 05:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So for those of you that are already familiar with the pyramid-esque  and legitimate but just barely business practices of Amway's recruitment model, I have a question. The recruiter that got in touch with me was very open to questions and skepticism but reverted back to the same response that most of the speakers at the events come back to and that is that for all the research you could do on Amway and the nay-sayers that all calling them out, people on the internet are simply mean and you can find bad reviews on any company. The more salient point is that the guy I was in touch with specifically pointed out he earned his degree in investigative journalism and made sure to tell me I needed to know my sources were good. So I am here, open minded, and asking anyone who has walked in these shoes before me, what are some *good* *legitimate* *credible* sources that, for lack of a better term, 'expose' Amway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 04:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hxUAntt1z2c  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What subreddit has your favorite flair options? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 04:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Script] College Humor website </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 04:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So there is a musical dots site http://www.collegehumor.com/i/musical-dots and I wanna save what I made. Does anyone know how?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 04:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is with his friends so chances are, if they don't seem like they are going to push him to make a move in front of them, you are going to either hope to run into him without his friends or have to drop bigger hints that you want him to approach you than just smiling back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 03:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a bump on the log in the hole in the bottom of the sea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 01:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> someone get a mod from r/legaladvice over here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 01:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a hole in the bottom of the sea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just published a satirical critique of the Russian government and Putin hasn't sent anyone to kill me yet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 23:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm radiating with joy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 20:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right. All I'm saying is lets not *forget* .... Nice save? ... Nice save... 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: What is so fundamentally different from smart phones and computers that we need 2 unique approaches for so many things? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 19:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: u/GenXClub wants me to be more specific. Why are input methodologies like mice and keyboards seldom (but i'm aware not never) compatible with mobile platforms like tables and phones? Also, why do websites need to be 'mobile friendly'?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 19:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lets not forget KhanAcademy 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 18:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can have eggs, just no milk products. I used almond milk in a banana bread recipe once. It looked black and burnt to all hell but was actually pretty moist and delicious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Experimenting with alternative ingredients </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 18:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do any bakers with allergies have tips and tricks for me? I found my substitutes for butter, milk, sour cream, and cream cheese but I also know how exacting a baking recipe can be. What are your experiences?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What kind of responsibilities do role models have to children with cellphones? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 09:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you know how to say thank you in all these languages? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 08:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 07:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that ransom is the common name for it but I'm like 99% sure that there is also a proper name for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] A specific type of font/typeface. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 07:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe there is a special name for the type of font where each letter is either cut individually from a print source or words are made by combining brand logos that are letters. Example being constructing the word 'my' from the McDonald arch and the YMCA logo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
