<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2840</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 15 guy from Bahrain. I'm into books and games(card and board) and history and politics. subject2840 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leaking from your eyeballs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Throw me to the wolves, I'll return leading the pack with my penis.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never been depressed, quite the obvious actually. I've always been a happy person. I found out that I'm content when I'm consuming something(food, a book, games) and happy when around people. So pick up a book. Go out with your friends instead of browsing Reddit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why we have 69-74 genders. I think that's the latest number. It just blows my mind that people are endorsing this. If I gave you an apple and an orange, you'll call the apple apple and orange orange. I know that some people find this important to them, just never get it. You got balls? Man. You got boobs? Woman.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Few weeks ago I was in turkey. Guy walks up to me (old man, I'm a teenage boy) asks for a cig. Said I don't have. Stands for a minute. Pulls out a pack of cigs. The fuck? Offers one to me. Now I don't smoke, and I wasn't gonna start then and there. He was insisting for a while and I kept saying no no no. He put it in his mouth and started smoking. I took this as a cue to leave. 

In the moment I was so fucking freaked out. I kept thinking he was gonna rape then kill me. My writing doesn't really convey how fucking scared I was. I thought he put something in the cigs so that it looks normal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 15:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bit of back info: I have 2 fantasies, one realistic the other is taking over a small country. I would spend hours making plans and shit for my "invasions" of neighboring countries and it's just so relaxing thinking that I have the power to enact change. The reason I implied that this fantasy is unrealistic is that my country has a monarchy and it's not something I would want to achieve in another country.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 15:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finally someone with a brain :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 15:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nestl is such a horrible company. They sent women who has just given birth in poor Africa nations sample that lasted 6 weeks. Just enough time for them to stop producing breast milk. No breast milk guess I have to buy milk from Nestl now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 15:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey my snap is kufu1796. I'm not from Britain but I was colonized by you so mabye that counts? M15 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 15:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clean air </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 15:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you always will be Handsome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 15:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snowpiercer. Absolute mindfuck. After the climate goes to shit and everything is a frozen wasteland, the remaining humans live on a train that constantly goes around the world. The people on the back of the train are treated like shit, while the ones in the front are treated very well. The entire story is just so beautiful and mind gripping and explains the structure of society so well. The fact that it's so linear, literally and figuratively, was so oddly satisfying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 15:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a long period of my life, I was like that. I was just drifting through life, not taking charge in what I didn't like about myself. As of now, I'm running, and just took a yoga class yesterday actually(the one where your legs feel like they're on fire). I started writing short pieces of topics that truely interest me. My grand plan is to write a book, start a blog of me traveling to Botswana or The DRC for relive and aid. Eventually settle down, probably do events for my books, and running a non-profit while raising a family. 

Everything I'm doing is contributing to the Bigger picture. One of the favorite things I do is traveling. Now I've found a way to do that while helping people. I highly suggest everyone to find something to work towards. It'll greatly improve the quality of your life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 15:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me and my friend discuss politics pretty frequently, like just today we were talking about the revival of the Arabian empire and how much of the world's problems would be solved. Then we were talking about the EU and the EEA and how they're just such a mindfuck and different approach to war then what Europe usually does. 

One thing that I really hate is that this one friend of mine is saying everything is a conspiracy theory. "The Syrian war isn't real, it's just Bashr isn't sucking off America like the rest of the Arabs, he loves his people and he would never chemically bomb them" sure buddy. The guy next to you who LITERALLY MOVED HERE TO RUN AWAY FROM BASHR is also in on it. Bashr is a fucking Saint. These kinds of people make me want to vomit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 15:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> subject2840 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 15:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Running. I go run because I have too, not because I particularly enjoy it. I wanna run long distances without feeling like shit at the beginning and end.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 13:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are quite a few pictures of the Christmas truce between the Germany and British. This was an unofficial truce, where British soldiers and German soldiers randomly decided to chill and exchange gifts on Christmas on no mans land instead of spending it in a wet hole in the ground.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 13:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The current age. We are currently at the most peaceful time, rn most of, if not all, or Europe aren't fighting and are being extermely cooperative with each other( EU, EEA). They've ALWAYS been fighting. Ex: Sweden and Denmark had upwards of 16 wars with each other on a single issue(Norway). Military conflict is also pretty low, they're trying to avoid population centers(sometimes). The most brutal times are in civil wars(Syria) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 13:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a kind of "Cold War" between Saudi Arabia and Iran. Saudi wanted to spread Sunni Islam, and Iran tried to spread Shia Islam. There are two super interesting countries that resulted from this. Bahrain, a Shia majority country with a Sunni Royal family. Oman, the only country in the world that has Ibadi Islam as the most dominant, rather than Shia or Sunni.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> subject2840, send me a snap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listen to the golden age by woodkid, you're gonna lose your mind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1,500$ for a pair of pants somehow this random white girl who lost her entire fortune and is a waitress, now she says for every 500$ she let someone slap her. Worse thing is she got the cash. And didn't get slapped.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
