<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2728</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you from amir valerie HERWITZ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ill go dickless for michael chickless if you upvote me to karma heaven baby! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If a person with an innie belly button hugs someone with an outie belly button, do they have belly button sex? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 03:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How hes depicted in stories or what he actually was? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 03:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine is hank moody from californication because i feel he represents a piece that alot of people have in them. Sort of the asshole with a heart of gold who enjoys women, drinking, smoking, a bit too much and some occasional drug use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is your favorite tv show character and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 03:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 03:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Afraid not :/ i always feel like its never the right time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Havent read any of his books, would you recommend any? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would be trippy af, but if youre esucated in that subject it that would be amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listen to him freestyle as you shared a blunt, doesnt sound too bad lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't think of this one, would be pretty fucking cool although i would have no idea wtf he would be saying half the time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine would be Hunter S Thompson </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could smoke weed with any dead famous person, who would it be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if making a baby required 3 people instead of 2? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 07:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 08:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So am i. I appreciate the advice though, thanks :). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 08:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think women like u may recognize it like that, however i dont think girls my age are ready or mature  enough to see it that way just yet lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 07:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It only suits a very small percentage of people, most people dont look good bald tbh. For a person like me who hates being the centre of attention, i dont want more people lookin at me cause im bald, it also shits in your self confidence. Just sucks that thats my very near future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 07:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, wish i had s choice lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 07:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, 18 and im im right behind you buddy, ill be there soon :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 07:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which is more painful premature baldness or giving birth? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 07:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 06:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its really really difficult to do plus classes arent running whenver you want them to theyre only running at certain times, the ones that i am least motivated to show up to are the 3 hour lectures from 3-6 ducming ridiculous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 05:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive tried all those methods my dis i terest in the subjecy overpowers my motivation and will to get things done lool. Its extremely hard to keep a schedule when u have different classes at different times. I found it much easier to keep a balanced schedule in highschool, wish i was back, i miss it wayy to much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 05:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree they shouls get rid of some old subjects which have no value, or at least add modern courses that teach us the basics of being a fucking adult. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My problem is i have trouble concentrating and end up studying for midterms or doing huge assignments the night before, when i should have started a week ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, and im kind of glad i didnt. That would just increase my stress way too much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The online thing seems like a good idea in context, but then theres people like me who have to be forced to go to school because they hate it so much. If i did all my classes online, i would have procrastinated so hard i would still be in the 3rd grade...lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, im hoping i move in with a couple roomates next semester which will at least takenthe stress of commuting off my shoulders. And to take a minimum 3 more years after this seems like forever when your not enjoying yourself, as well as having the question of  "is this what i wanna do with my life?" Constantly in your head. All while balancing everything else. Shit gets stressful as hell. Forgot to mention, ive always hated school with a extremely deep passion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would you change the education system to make it more efficient and effective? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> University right now. Basically everythings stressful, the hour and a half commute, the pointless courses i have no interest in, midterms and exams worth more than half the course.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
