<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject375</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 05:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might just be disconnection. Happens.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 05:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can leave the game and come back at a later time and still be on the same roll. If you hit the white die, wait for the jackpot to accumulate before continuing to roll. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 00:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hodor" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 04:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this idea! Do you think the series would work better as animated (classically or computer?) or live action? I have a hard time picturing live-action Hork-Bajiir speak through their beaks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 02:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can definitely see how it would be difficult, but movies without clear antagonists have been done before.

https://www.reddit.com/r/movies/comments/296epq/movies_with_no_villain/

Interestingly, the first example is Cast Away, which I had imagined being similar to Ellimist in a way. The long periods of isolation away from civilization and the feeling of being stranded. I think that if they did try to make an Ellimist movie they should take notes from Cast Away on how to tell an engaging story, and convey emotion, with basically one main character.

As for a mini-series, it goes without saying that I would be absolutely for it. I think The Animorphs, if ever brought back to the screen, would need a more serialized format than a movie trilogy. A mini-series would work for that, an actual TV series would work too. But I see the transition between a hypothetical precursor Chronicles mini-series to an Animorphs TV show to be a smoother move than having Chronicles as movies and then pushing an Animorphs TV show.

Maybe this is where the fanboy of me takes over my logic and reason, where I'm just like "Let's get it started and figure out the details later" lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 00:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So if you take the Ellimist from the cover, make him younger initially, and add wings/talons I think he would look decent. Humanoid in the face, while not taking away what made that type of extraterrestrial function.

Edit- Didn't downvote you by the way, not sure who would. Maybe Crayak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
