<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject350</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 19:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plans with Free Unlimited Social Media have been pretty normal in Australia for the last few years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got some amazing pics of the London sky this morning. Images enhanced using Snapseed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-12 01:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 11:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Australian here. The only other confusing and annoying but I found was the Germans charging you a .20 euro cent deposit called "pfand". You're supposed to get this back when you take it back to the recycle centre or something. By the end of my trip I figured I'd have paid about 2 euros towards this. A bit like South Australia, perhaps someone could confirm? Anyway...  We laughed thinking let's do a Kramer and take a truck full to fund some beers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-03 08:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can recommend  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 00:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-01 20:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I'm trying New clothes on, I'd sometimes pretend I'm in an argument and im laying down a kick ass comment to finish the opponent off, with the look and everything. Because apparently looking good is very important when I'm in a row with someone. The funny thing is I rarely ever have arguments with people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-01 20:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My thought process - the dudes a famous singer. Why the fuck is that not a compliment!?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-01 19:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ummm.. I told someone they looked like Meatloaf because they had a ponytail. He wasn't impressed. I didn't get it. I wonder if you are... Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-01 00:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. Everytime I accidentally look at my old Facebook comments.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-01 00:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's incredibly hard I think to hold a mirror to yourself and at the same time be aware of what it is you're actually looking at.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As you grow older - What is the biggest change that you've noticed in your outlook towards life and/or within yourself? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 00:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've noticed that I've started to trust my instincts more, at work or outside.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-27 09:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree. Life is too short to go through all this shit for a deal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-27 08:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've had an amazing 2 days visiting the historic sites and all of them were open including museums and the Berlin Church. Amazing Christmas markets at charlottenburg, hands down the best markets I've ever been to. Great food, crafts. 
Biggest compliment I can say for Berlin is that it's people are so friendly and amazing. We've been helped by strangers, just wanting to make sure we know where we're going when looking confused at a map in my hand. 
Today we're off to the Berlin Wall memorial and then an afternoon/night in kreuzberg.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Haha hilarious. (someone translate for me?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-25 16:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
