<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3240</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 06:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg saaaaame, I hate them so much in the dark. Freaks me the fuck out every single time. I literally cried when I moved into my current house and our closet doors were literally just giant mirrors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 06:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not gonna lie, I totally want a bunch of inflatable dragons now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 06:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's even worse when your whole personality revolves around that one skill. Like everyone knows me for two things: art and writing. I'm glad neither stuck with my sister because she showed potential to be better than me at both. I'm still salty about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 21:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Born and raised in Phoenix here, can confirm that I wear a sweater in anything below 60F (15.5 C)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 02:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course. That's what sucks about irrational phobias, you know they're stupid and don't make sense, but no matter how many times I tell myself that, I still lose my shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 06:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I smoked with my mom and sister recently which was a trip. I suspected my mom had been smoking for years and was surprised when I found out my sister did. Sure enough, things came together and badda boom, badda bing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 03:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if this is really all that weird, but the first and second time I got drunk was at my house, so now I always change clothes when I'm drunk, to keep the legacy going. Every picture of me at a party starts with me in something cute and ends with me in like sweatpants and the weirdest shirt I could find. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
