<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1565</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 22:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I emailed IR today too and got the EXACT same response from Zach as well. Word for word the same email. I suppose that was to be expected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sold...or the seller removes the offer. It is common for traders to put up psychological barriers like this and then pull them before their filled. Not saying that is the case here, but it does happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 03:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got it. Thanks. What if I wasn't being sarcastic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 02:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does that mean? Sorry, I'm new to this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 00:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Analyst ratings are largely horse shit, and are to be taken with a grain of salt. The ratings are driven more by the amount of equity financing and bought deal business the company has brought to the bank than it is the actual direction of the company. It's amazing the number of times a bank has a BUY rating on a stock they have just raised money for. Not trying to be cynical. Just my observations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 00:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my opinion only.....technicals have taken on a much bigger role since the markets have become more and more dominated by computer trading and algorithms. The chart patterns are plotted, and the potential outcomes based on the formation or lack of formation of said patterns are then plugged into the trading instructions. This is why trying to time the market is seemingly more difficult and why the market seems to move so much faster. It's not everything of course, but it's more important now than before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Waaaaaaayyyyyyyy too early for it to mean anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
