<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1120</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 04:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He also directed the video for REMs The One I Love.  Being married also doesn't make him straight, he could be bi or something. God knows my ex husband was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was Morgan Robertson the author of The Wreck of the Titan: Or, Futility (the book that supposedly predicted The Titanic disaster) alive when Titanic went down, did he have anything to say? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 03:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 03:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly thought Alton was gay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eddy Grant- Electric Avenue [Funk] 1983 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 03:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was reading this article (which appears to have been altered from this morning when I read it) and someone in the comments said that Giada de Laurentiis is called "The Blow Job Queen" By Rachel Ray, anyone know the back story to this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 00:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sorry, newbie here. I have a,question about playing this in cpu vs Xbox One </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 20:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to love the Sims on cpu and the old SIM City for PlayStation 1, so I am hoping this game would satisfy a bit of both. I don't know if I should get it for my CPU or Xbox, what have your experience been like? Is there a difference? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You have been visited by the Garlic Bread of death, up vote this or die eventually! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 18:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> garlic bread.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, I used to watch all his videos. There's just something that bothers me about him. I don't know what it is. Nothing specific. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buyer assumes responsibility for the month-to-month tenancy in the upstairs apartment. Occupant has never paid, and no security deposit is being held, but there is a lease in place..buy a house with creepy hermit they said, it's a fun fixer upper they said. And then things got murdery. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How long until the American Civil War will start? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think Trump will declare himself president for life? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like John Green, The Fault in Our Stars was so pretentious. I also don't really like him as a person, I don't know why. He just doesn't sit right with me. 

I have heard he's not writing anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you help promote my favorite YouTube Hellfreezer? He tells a mix of stories has a great voice and and endearing accent, he needs more subs and more patrons! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
