<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1772</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 09:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scam School, DarkMatter2525, MindYourDecisions, EnterTheDojoShow, Taylor Davis, MoeLaddin, Anna Akana, Bryson Andres, Eli the Computer Guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 09:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apply for a loan and spend, spend, spend! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 09:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make every keyboard's spacing different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 09:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kick 'em out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 08:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being able to defend yourself eases your mind so you can live a happier life. You can invest 20 years into a job but outside of that job, you have nothing to show for. When you practice martial arts, you bring it around with you wherever you go.  Greater range of motion is a big self-confidence booster. You feel like you're worth something, and can approach that girl, or that boss. You feel like you're worth something before even learning the first thing about whatever career you decide to pursue. You can teach others how to defend themselves too. It's a party trick you can bring anywhere to get the good kind of attention. Chicks dig a man that can protect her. I enjoy anything creative I can do to express myself. That's drawing, improvising on the piano, singing, programming, writing, sports, yoga, tai chi, etc. For me, even just the exercise aspect makes martial arts worthwhile to me. But there is an aspect of perfection to martial arts which appeals to me, being a perfectionist and all. Any way I can strive for perfection, especially using the body alone, I find very attractive. It's like eating healthy, no matter where you go in life at least you'd be healthy. It's the same with martial arts, no matter where you go in life, at least you'll feel more confident in a bad situation. You don't have to get physical, but if you believe in yourself, being able to defend yourself can have a great impact on your self-confidence in intimidating situations. It's that self-confidence, more than anything, which I feel is the most worthwhile. That or the meditative, internal aspect. Being able to meditate can really calm the mind and make you a happier person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 08:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Monty Python and the Holy Grail </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 08:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dog walking, dog-sitting, babysitting, gardening, tutoring, running errands, photography, waitering, resocking a supermarket, telemarking, secretary, maintenance, and there's laborready for actual labor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 08:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the beach </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 08:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make a buzzing noise like there's a bug in the room while brushing the back of someone's head with a feather. Act suspicious like you're about to pull a prank on someone. When the teacher turns their back, make animal noises, when they turn around act like nothing happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 07:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Between 7 - 9 hours during the weekday and 10 hours during the weekend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 07:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "That I'd get away with it." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 07:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to U.S. statistics, an American woman would kiss an average of 80 men before she gets married. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 07:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'd get classified while the government uses their technology for personal gain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 07:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kill it! kill it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 07:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm tired of being what you want me to be </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 07:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chopin's Funeral march </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 06:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A newspaper </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 06:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Took me half a minute </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 03:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Post it on reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 02:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how 2 spel and gramar property </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 02:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I have a boyfriend" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 23:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Browsing the net late at night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 13:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Add something to my bucket list which isn't on anybody else's so I have that which to answer this question with. (marks off) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 13:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I never loved you." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 13:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 18 and 19 are both teens. 18+ is an adult and allowed to have sex and thus legal. While 13 - 17 are all teens but not legal aka "jailbait. If your question is supposed to be religious or psychologically oriented, some do; some don't. It's their choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 13:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alternative rock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 13:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because 18 and 19 are legal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 13:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assembly. (I don't work lower than C/C++) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 13:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why so serious? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 13:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> David Rockefeller </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 12:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Actually 1 - .999... doesn't equal 0 because there would be an infinitely small remainder. We only pretend it's 0 because we fail to understand infinite precision which exists as shown with pi and trying to find the last digit."  
\*hides from the mathematicians\* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 12:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being out of folgers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 12:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you get Dick from Richard? You ask nicely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 12:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be a picky eater and hate all the food in the house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 12:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well played </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 12:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Passive income. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 11:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Starting off as a billionaire and knowing how to spend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 11:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last airbender, I'd direct it more faithful to the tv series. Pronouncing the names correctly for one. The indian, caucasian, and chinese castings made no sense at all. I'd probably aim more in the japanese direction. I'd also make the movie longer, or break it into two movies. There's a lot of adventures to cover, so it needs more screen time to cover them all.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 11:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the question? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 11:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd choose Genie, would be nice to have 3 wishes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 11:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The great insert my real name. I'd do intentionally failed magic with a bit of humor. Things like making an object disappear under a scarf while discarding it behind my back in an obvious fashion. Then mix in some humor like getting hit in the balls, or tripping on a prop and falling over an assistant while causing a chain reaction of falling props. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 11:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [/r/DebateReligion/](https://www.reddit.com/r/DebateReligion/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 11:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How to spell corectly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 11:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hybrid Theory </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 10:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drink lots of water, and exercise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 10:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 10:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love is something two-way. Unless both people are happy, it is doomed to failure. Knowing when to throw in the towel takes experience and is a sign of maturity as it saves you both time. The more crap you put up with, the more you'll get crapped on. There's certain things a relationship needs to be healthy. If it's one-sided giving, then one person is using the other. Even if one person has an "endless" supply to give, it's an unhealthy relationship. Even in the midst of an infinite flow of giving, the other person won't feel they're giving anything in return and might leave because it's not helping them grow. If you have your eye on someone else, it's also a sign you're not working out with the person you're breaking up with. If you're unable to compliment them, perhaps you don't see anything in them at all. It takes courage to initiate a break up, you should be proud. If you're giving yourself a hard time *how* you broke up, don't worry about it. Just think about how many dudes she's been with before you and how many she'll be with after you. There's no reason to be hard on yourself. "We could have been together longer if only I..." Even if both parties love each other and put in loads of effort, some people live such completely different life styles, that no amount of effort can seal the gap. Things like religion, beliefs, health, these are things which can be hard to seal the gap. If you feel bad about breaking up, you can make you intentions for breaking up clear so they don't hate you. Nobody likes being hated. It's nice to have an extra friend if you need one, but just make it clear it's best if you go separate ways. But if you try to break up in a nice way, remaining "just friends", prepare to get emailed and texted later in life. Whether you want to remain friends or not, both have their pros and cons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 10:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've come to the understanding we don't stop loving loved ones, we just learn to move on when the cons outweigh the pros.If you know anybody which you feel comfortable talking to, they're usually a good place to go. Take it one step at a time. There's other fish in the sea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 09:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably not, there's other fish in the sea. Unless they were just recently ex'd, I might give 'em another chance if I could see a future with them and I didn't have my eye on someone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 09:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because 1999 was 17 years ago and time seems to go by quicker when you get older. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 09:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem with your argument is the assumption that a computer doesn't know or understand while we do. They've done experiments which show electric signals sent to the brain can cause a limb to move. Why can't brain surgery advance to the point they can upload 20 years of education? Does an unconscious or dead person have "knowledge"? Why can't we argue a computer isn't functioning "properly" until it passes the turing test under the same pretext an unconscious human can't lie? Do computers feel pain? (no) What about a "properly" functioning computer? We can program it to act like it does. Do humans feel pain? There's people out there with [congenital analgesia](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Congenital_insensitivity_to_pain) which can't. So a properly functioning human does, maybe a properly functioning computer does too. Losing a limb can suck, but can't a robot also lose a limb and feel the "pain" of trying to function normally? Ah, but a robot you can just repair the lost limb. Yet with humans, stem cell research is nearly at the stage we can replace limbs. No matter how you look at it, we're just a program. A person can be hypnotized and thus reprogrammed to a certain extent. Imagine someone with amnesia so severe, they forgot how to speak, how to make sense of their vision, and even how to breathe. They get hooked up to some machine to help them breathe until their brain heals enough for them to remember how to breathe. Then they relearn how to make sense of 3-dimensional shapes, etc.  
  
So why can't a computer/robot just be programmed to have reasons to lie in certain situations which it "knows" is false? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 08:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> multilingualism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 21:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  have a Ph.D.

usually I see bachelor's degree or equivalent experience </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 18:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They expect web developers to know like 10 languages now to land a decent job when in the past you could find work easy with 1 or 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 17:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand this question at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 09:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The classic upside down plate trick; I'm a picky eater so sue me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 09:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Only you can prevent forest fires."  
"OMG! A talking bear!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 09:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The alphabet backwards in under three seconds." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 09:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A bunch of clothes I bought online which clutters my closet. Such a waste of money, I should be more careful before buying something that might be too thin, too long, or not fit right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 08:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tom's diner </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 08:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can offend people without even trying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 08:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm an introverted, poor, computer geek, I have no friends. (other than family) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 08:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a recent half-serious fight, I used a wing chun-style punch combination but my opponent avoided it, then they tried delivering their own punch but I parried, then they grabbed the hand I blocked with, thus closing the distance, since they were stronger, I responded by kneeing them in the groin. Wasn't the way I expected to win, but they left me an opening, so I took advantage of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 04:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey I just met you  
And this is crazy  
But here's my number  
So call me maybe  
It's hard to look right at you baby  
But here's my number  
So call me maybe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 04:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> drinking too much soda as a kid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 04:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a wrinkly one with a bunch of graffiti on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 01:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> spiders, heights, and elevators </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 01:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Know your audience; make yourself more appealing than your competitor to that audience. To avoid anger issues, humble yourself by admitting to your shortcomings, get a better understanding of the game, and come back stronger.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 09:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About 8 years ago, when I reached significant heights in "meditation", trying to make heads or tails out of the possibility of an infinite past. I didn't realize I was even meditating, at the time I was just trying to reply to some atheist on a message board. I haven't tried re-entering that state again as it was rather scary and I was unprepared. Maybe in another year or two I'll gain the balls to attempt it again when I'm better prepared. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 08:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Discovering my crush at a playground with a cut on her arm, and using my supernatural powers to heal her, pretending it was nothing, then for the first time she notices me. She becomes attached and sits on my lap and we start staring into each other's eyes, NSFW etc... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 08:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 08:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That there's a girl with potential out there for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 08:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That I'm screwed unless I get screwed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 08:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The new zealand caulking deck "advert" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Willy Wonka tribute would make Gene Wilder proud? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 07:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 07:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's a good place to develop your thoughts on many matters, before making a mockery of yourself in public. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 07:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Picking between a racist and a crook is hard, but as I believe in conservatism, I'd sooner see Trump president. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 07:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Move my clock back an hour in the fall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 07:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Replying to the next submitter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 07:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By not giving a fuck. If you're covering up racism, let it out. "Ooooh, you're a racist!?" "I don't give a fuck" Imagine a world where you can just go around offending people. Congrats, you're now a jerk, and the kind of guy most girls actually want when they say they want a "nice guy". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 06:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The most vivid first memory I have is playing street fighter 2 with the neighbor kid over. I know I've played mario brothers on Nintendo before that, but I can't chronologicalize anything before that, even if I do remember. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 06:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My shampoo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 06:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Opened up chrome when I said go to google. (still continues to do it) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 06:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like beer more than chocolate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 06:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> peter banging his knee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 06:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what happens in prison stays in prison </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 06:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take a plane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 04:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Delete 45,000 emails. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 01:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I can list everyone you ever crushed on." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best UML cheatsheet out there that has your back on even the most seldom of class diagram features? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 01:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 00:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice try frank </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 00:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ugly slut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 00:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Programmer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 00:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> imaginary - evanescence </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 00:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see what you did there.  
Well played </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 23:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An oldie, but probably the best version I've heard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What saying that you composed, carries a concept that you feel can inspire others and/or what's the most inspiring quote you've encountered? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 22:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 22:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He said "I don't accept charity from jews" while throwing it back. Due to his choice of wording "from jews", as the exception proves the rule, it appears he accepts charity, just not from jews. Probably similar ideology to the recent rio judo olympics incident now that I think about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 21:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My father </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 21:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Appears to be a CSS rule added to the subreddit here. You can go into your preferences and disable custom themes while browsing askreddit until the joke wears off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 21:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A homeless muslim refusing cash from a jew, throwing it back in his face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 18:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nothing doing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 18:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> their name </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
