<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2746</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why am I frequently required to verify my Microsoft account? Every few days I input the security code and my password. I don't clear my cache. So why doesn't my email account let me in? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 04:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 23:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the words of wisdom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 04:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 68 hives? I'm cautious about maintaining only one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 03:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your post reminds me how much I have to learn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 03:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I'm in Texas, too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Queen excluder: Yes or No? I'm getting mixed messages in my rookie research. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 23:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 14:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I won't actually weep. I'm kidding. But it's certainly frustrating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bluetooth volume drops automatically, and this makes me nigh insane. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 13:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When my 950 connects to Ford Sync, it pushes the volume way down, so I can't even hear an incoming message. This must stop before I break down and weep. Is there a fix or workaround? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 23:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My HD is the sweetest piece of hardware I own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 22:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A red plastic peg to stop biting dogs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Be An Authentic Dungeon Master . . . eh? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 22:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Does your job require you to carry an unusual or interesting piece of gear? My daily kit is simply a boring laptop. What about yours? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 22:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Microsoft is supposedly now bypassing the carriers to roll out updates, why am I not receiving the new firmware on my AT T Lumia 950? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 14:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 15:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I still need a good definition of a "medium" game. I can tell a heavy game from a light game, but medium seems so subjective. Any examples? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fumbled the roll . . . </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 16:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 21:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the difference between Germany's historic secret services, the Gestapo and the SD?  I've never understood the nuances, though I've heard them referenced in film and pop culture many times.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 14:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, that's not the whole point of an online class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 05:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a wonderful post.  Thank you.  Your comprehensive reply means a lot to me.  I appreciate the information and the candor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 17:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the reply! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 00:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an archivist, what were some of your daily tasks?

And thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 21:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. Thanks for this reply. This is all valuable information that will help a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 20:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remarkably competitive? I had no idea . . . I would not have guessed it was so popular a profession. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 18:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Library science sounds like a very good fit for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 18:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hadn't thought about TV. We'll definitely look into this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 18:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the link! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My younger brother is a history major but doesn't know what careers are available to him. Plot twist: he has Asperger's and is a social recluse. Details inside. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 16:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My younger brother is brilliant, having tested out of many basic courses at university.  He has selected history as a major because his only interests in the world (other than his cat) are consuming books on Asian and medieval European history--and playing video games on his PC.  With Asperger's, he sees the world differently, and he wants to interact with other human beings as little as possible, so this eliminates any kind of job teaching history or giving museum tours.  Think of him as extremely introverted.

My research indicated than an "archivist" might be something in which he'd be interested, but I don't know any archivists personally who can explain exactly what they do.  What other fields can my brother and I research that somehow link to his love for history?

He will soon be applying to graduate school, and we all hope he  has a bit of direction before then, otherwise he'll be content to live with our mum and do nothing but read and play PC games all day (now that I mention it, that doesn't sound so bad).

Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 16:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, my OneDrive app hangs when I open it, and the hamburger menu cannot be accessed.  It's a bummer that I can't uninstall the app and reinstall it; now I'm no longer able to access my OneDrive through the app or to auto sync my photos. : ( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is anyone else experiencing problems with OneDrive? My photos won't upload, and the OneDrive app hangs every time I open it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 18:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 18:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crap! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I turn on the front-facing flash on the 950? Does the iris scanner sign-in option need to be turned on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 17:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 05:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 05:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still is. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 15:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Bluetooth not working in all vehicles?  Mine seems to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 15:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, another upvote from me for Zune.  I'm still rockin' my Zune HD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 15:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm. You're right:  when I searched for "Farming Simulator," the results never showed 16, only 14.  I had to click on the publisher's name to pull up the latest version 16. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 22:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 22:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is this weird structure? It's located in a very rural area, with nothing around it for miles in any direction. I've driven by it a dozen times and always wondered about its function. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 15:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 16:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP, I think you crept into my heart and wrote my feelings on the page. Bless you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 20:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your collection makes my heart happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 14:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In RISE, how do I get rope arrows? The Soviet installation tells me that I need them. Have I missed them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 04:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 12:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still using my 920 at this very moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 12:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ben Carson stated his belief that the Pyramids of Giza were originally used to store grain, rather than royal corpses. I've never heard this hypothesis. Is there any archeological evidence to support this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 15:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
