<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2519</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 21:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Republicans are so stupid this will ensure Trump is a one term President  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 20:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah MAK was lead by Bin Laden and Abdullah Azzam but Bin Laden took it in the more radical direction after Azzam was killed (possibly by a Bin Laden supporter) and yeah it was originally just for shipping foreign jihaidsts to Afghan  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 07:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if the Nazi's would be that practical as they hated Slavs and communists  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 01:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't a religion in Germany. Why true Nazi ideology dominated it but most Germans were still Christian which was used by the Nazi's who made it focus on the New Testament and ignore the Jewish parts. The Nazi's would have probably got rid of religion like they do in this show but Christianity was still a large part of Germany.

But yes I agree a lot of Nazi's fled to South America and didn't abandon their ideology and many fascist states still existed in the world including Spain and Argentina  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 06:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think a killer writing 'troll' on a billboard is way more likely than a chipper geek hacker with a strong sense of morality gunning down law enforcement or security guards  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 04:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There no teams at all like Manchester United, Celtic, Bayern Munich, Real Madrid, Barcelona, Benefica-its just a load of nobody teams pumped full of money like PSG and City  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 03:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That what's I thought exactly ! The outfit too  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 00:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speaking of no taste- Overwatch  a game for fucking 12 year old twitch streamers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 00:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Interactive movie'... Witcher 3... I hate to hear what you think Uncharted 4 and Heavy Rain are like as video games </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 00:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There not a proper culture or history aswell which is pretty important  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 23:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol alright you hipster go play WoW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 23:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I don't understand why any footballer at the top of his game would go to China. You being paid way more than nearly anyone on earth and playing for a top club and you want to go to some start up league for money? Depressing footballers are mostly just mercenaries these days  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 23:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh you're hard not liking one of the most critically acclaimed games of all time  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 23:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wretch is a rapper - Wrench is the character my mistake  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 18:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the curse of the Witcher, makes every other game seem inadequate  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 18:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I seriously can't believe that the maker of this show who put so much attention in everything accidentally  put a Soviet sniper from the 1960's-possibly the Nazi's made it but as you said the G3 is more like a German sniper  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 17:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I very much doubt that  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do hackers have to be 'wacky' all of a sudden? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 08:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So when I first saw trailers and such for Watch Dogs 2 I thought they were trying too hard with characters like Wrench and the way they looked. Surprisingly I really like Wrench but I feel WD2 desire to pander to critics and the GTA audience has ruined its tone. I won't spoil anything but there is a moment in the story where everyone should act serious, which they do for about a minute, then go back to being their normal wise cracking selves.

Also when I run into the FBI headquarters on a mission and kill everyone in sight (you can complete the mission like this) it's pretty jarring with Marcus' happy-go-lucky personality.

I guess I feel 'hackers' don't have to be wacky geeks spouting pop culture references every second. I feel Mr Robot and Watch Dogs 1 do a much better job in telling a serious story around hacking and it's seems to fit what being a hacker is. Constantly breaking the law, destroying people's lives, trying to take down corporations isn't really one big joke where you have to be a 'geek'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 03:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah (see other comments) but I don't think he made the Dragunov  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 22:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The difference with what we did to the Japanese and Germans is although we put military bases there we didn't dissolve their government institutions like the Nazi's have done to the US that's the difference. We allowed Japan to keep most of its identity intact, we didn't force them to convert to Christianity or control all information they got form the outside world. In Germany we made them turn away from Nazism but they were pretty free after that. Smith is a traitor because he joined up with the SS when their was still an American resistance movement which contain many people from the army. That is the difference here  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 21:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you talking about Mr Robot?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 20:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This link has all the guns in the show and it's doesn't look like it was inspired by anything German but I take your point about the Stg-44 inspiring the AK. http://www.imfdb.org/wiki/Man_in_the_High_Castle,_The_-_Season_1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually I think Thomas got the the condition from Smith's genes as his brother had the same disease </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like him but he a massive hypocrite in most ways  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nazi weaponry... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay so the Nazi police generally use the MP5 sub machine gun which was of course made in Germany based on the MP-40 and what came after. But the guy who kills the crown prince uses a Dragunov sniper - which is a Soviet Sniper made in the late 50's/60's in our world.

So could it be he has somehow got this weapon from our world?  Or does the Soviet Union still exist in some capacity that they could have created such a weapon?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know how you can watch this show and hate it. The characters alone are amazingly complex and the setting is incredibly well done  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Engels and Marx  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'For them, he must be prepared to give everything... his life...' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 18:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (SPOILERS FOR SEASON 2) So John Smith says this when he is given a eulogy for the family doctor. In the short term he is obviously referring to what he did to protect Thomas. Looking back to the past can we assume family is the only reason he joined the Nazi's? We see Helen is pregnant when the A-bomb drops on D.C. so did he make a choice to join the SS (I think he joined pretty early-1947?) so his family would survive? We know he was deeply troubled by what he and Rudolph had to do and he spent a lot of time in his boat probably trying to forget it - so maybe we can assume he in really a Nazi just doing his job so his family can live a comfortable life ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 03:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have u finished season 2?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 20:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WAITT WHEN DID THIS HAPPEN!??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 19:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think by Queen Victoria's reign was when the limits of a Monarchs power came to be recognised. For example she absolutely loved Disraeli but hated Gladstone who was PM four times during her reign and pretty much did what he wanted in terms of reform without nearly any input from the Queen. She is one of the most loved Monarchs, probably along with Elizabeth I and II, because she oversaw a period where Britain became the most dominant power on the globe. She wasn't merely a figurehead but she was on of the first monarchs to see their old powers really diminish.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 19:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah you have 1.52 not 0.68  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 19:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've studied North Vietnam, Korea, China and USSR and I agree. But these were dictatorships based on the false promise of equality for all and a better life for the workers/peasants. They were brutal but the ideology was inherently evil. Nazism was evil - advocating the purifying of society and weird biological ideas-killed people who were seen as a drag on the state which is evil by the 1930's/40's standards. All the communist countries were instead Nazis a lot more would have died than communist. The Nazi's could have conquered where they did without extermination of minority groups and disabled and that's my point.

I was too thinking what Joe's father says like if we are all united we can do more as humanity but Nazism is not the way - only allowing 'pure blooded' whites to exist is wrong and doesn't make total sense anyway. If you offered all a good standard or living and appealed to them why would you need extermination? Look today at all the Jewish intellects and CEO's - what would be the point in them being killed?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 17:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Connor-because he has my name and a shared passion for brutal axe murder  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 17:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you skipped some cutscenes of course you aren't going to understand you fucking moron </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 17:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SettingsAudioPlaylist turn to off or chill 

Or tune all licensed music off  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 16:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> K/D is absolutely shocking  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 16:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just saying-Juliana's parents don't know anything about what she's been up too. They don't know that she went to the Neutral zone for a couple of days. To keep up the lie she has just not told them anything and acted like it's all normal  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 16:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah the crusades... one word: Pillage!

Pillaging was a way Soldiers supplemented their income although it didn't make it up entirely  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The difference with Romans and Nazis is clear. Romans society was established 2,000+ years ago. They killed people who didn't follow their ideology and religions true but they didn't kill for evil. For example their was no explicit racism in the Roman Empire - they had at least one black emperor and many Africans had high positions. Romans conquered and they felt they had to civilise the world but often left minority groups alone if they romanised themselves.

Now the Nazi's come out of a period where we no many of their beliefs were wrong. People knew anti-Semitism, racism and exterminating minority groups was wrong. People knew experimenting on prisoners was wrong. People knew that the Nazi science of having pure blood or perfect biology was bullshit. The Nazi were the very definition of evil - an ideology that was not a product of its time (even though it did need certain conditions to be popular) and you cannot argue its atrocities had a similar counterpart. Communist states came close but Nazi's were a lot worse. To achieve a better mankind why would it be necessary to exterminate or subjugate all who look different ? How does that actually help the advancement of civilisation ? You could still enforce one ideology without it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (GENERAL SPOILERS) Just watched both season back to back and have never felt so conflicted about TV characters in my life! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 07:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow this show is amazing I have never loved and hated characters at the same. I think Kido and Smith are the best case of this. In the pilot they are just the stereotypical evil villains but by the end of S2 you are actually rooting with them. Both have done horrible things but aren't completely evil men. I was actually coming round to Smith a lot until I found out he was actually in the US army and saw the a-bomb being dropped on DC first hand. How can you then become a Nazi!? I get he had a family but a man like that turning into a fascist!? Maybe his sons death because of the Nazi regime will steer him back towards being a real American? 

Kido I actually respect apart from the fact he killed Franks sister and her kids. He is just a product of his empire and will do anything to see its safety. He's not a traitor like Smith. There are other characters I feel this way about aswell: Helen, Ed, Juliana but feel Smith and Kido represent what the show does so well best. What do you guys think? 

Btw the way Frank and Sara went out was soo badass! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 19:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is soo fucking stupid I hope it's a joke. You'd be killed by the Queens Guard and if captured you'd be put in prison for the rest of your life. The monarchies that remain of European states are mostly connected so there would be another heir to the throne. Not to mention that most of the English royal family don't live in Buckingham Palace. 

Yes there is precedent for the royal line changing (Henry VII) but this was over 500 years ago. Even when Kings are deposed (Charles I James II) someone they were related to usually takes the throne anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 16:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love BF1 but still know Witcher is 10x in quality  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 18:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would you come to a sub on the Witcher and talk about how you don't like it because you only play FPS garbage ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 07:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love lord of the rings - hate Game of Thrones but love Witcher the most!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 06:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck off noob  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 00:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My main problem is that this game is sooo fucking hard. Like I got pretty good at dogfights but didn't understand wtf was going in most of the time and the lack of any clear story of intersection made it even harder  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 19:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wear Geralt's armour, use Kylo Ren's light saber and use lightning - I'm a Witcher/Sith hybrid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 18:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it's the best but in from London and have done that period at university so it was a dream for me. Combat was good, traversal was good, side missions were interesting (Karl Marx, Charles Dickens and Darwin etc) graphics were nice - amazing little details - four different animations for kids playing football! Aswell as all the people working and chatting etc - so much better than unity in that regard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Energy drinks before running </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 18:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 16:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't care what people say AC3 was a beast game. Amazing new mechanics and a great story -may be too slow paced for sum but I thought it was great and really ambitious  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 16:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MW2 spec ops was amazing I still play it to this day - juggernaut favela!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 15:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does big bicep privilege also exist?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 16:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that's a very good point ex-Soviet states have always had it rough including Georgia and Chechnya  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 17:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he was alive I would so have David Carridine as Vesimer  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 17:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dijkstra pick is awful. I love him in Daredevil but no way is he pulling off a dirty northern accent  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 17:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I get that but I did kinda say no jews - I am not talking about minorities in one country but groups in within empires </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 03:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing a couple of distressing comments on this post. 

I absolutely agree that yes if men from a certain group have done attacks like this in the past they should be targeted. French police targeted English football fans at the euros and Russians as they are known for being more prone to violence.

Where I think you have to be careful is basically saying being a rapist or whatever is part of North African culture. Women's rights are way worse in predominantly Muslim countries but doesn't mean all are extreme. In this case study of Germany in particular they have done the right thing but hopefully this doesn't make the rest of Europe target Muslims even more than usual because they are 'rapists'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skyrim SE Xbox One - any there any spells/mods that are similar to using the Force? Namely the standard telekinesis but being able to use it on enemies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 02:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Look how old you've become... (same actor as Lor San Tekka) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 00:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 14:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Waiting for the barman to take your order </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 13:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jedi order he didn't though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did Darth Vader bring balance to the Force because he destroyed the Jedi and Sith orders ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 13:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 21:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Three kingdoms period saw about 1/3 of the population die  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 21:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds more like a communists NYR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 21:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because he is MIA even worse!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 21:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every run is better than no run at all. During realise how true this was until I injured myself recently and can't do any  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 20:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I do understand countries didn't exist as they do today you pretentious dick. But I am talking about regions where countries came to be eg new states after the full of the Soviet Union, Ireland and Northern Ireland. Yes countries are a new concept but the people living in them trace the origins back centuries  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 17:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am talking about other countries not their own population - and I was talking about white Europeans in particular to take things like moors out of the equation. And I strongly disagree some groups have been way more discriminated against than other eg Catholics in the British Commonwealth/Empjre or Sikhs and Muslims in India  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 17:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no my mistake I'm playing there game mode 'survival' which is actually called 'endurance' where you have to survive in a randomly generated world and start off with just a bow-definitely worth a go   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who has been the most oppressed white group in European history? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 14:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I am Anglo-Irish and recently been think about Irish history. The Tudor plantations, the brutal invasion by Cromwell, the conquest of William of Orange and the hardship that followed. That got me thinking: who has been the most oppressed white group in Europe? Ireland is one but how do people feel they compare to groups under Ottoman rule in the Balkans? Or in Greece? How about many of the, now, countries that made up Imperial Russia and the USSR? Would love to hear some input on who had it the worst.


(Edit: obviously the Jews have suffered immense hardship in Europe, whether it be in Germany, Poland, Hungary or Spain - but I am focusing on countries)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 05:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just saying it to make it clear I obviously don't remember what it was like to see episode 1 and understand it properly  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Survival is pretty entertaining! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 05:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely one of the better modes had a really fun experience a moment ago. It was all going well-I had stumbled upon a small village with a couple enemies. I took them out, found a rifle and started a fire. Morning came and I set out. It was foggy but I stumbled across a small camp with more enemies. I silently picked them off one by one. As I was scavenging the camp I see one enemy come charging towards me out of nowhere. I pull out my rifle and shoot but miss. From behind him comes a massive bear charging straight towards me! I take some hits but eventually scramble up a tree all hurt but alas the same guy I missed early shot me out the tree and I died after one day! Great experience so far looking forward to trying again!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was it like to see the Phantom Menace when it first released in cinemas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 05:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I was born in 1995, I apparently did see episode 1 in the cinema but I barely remember it. I don't really remember ever knowing about the Star Wars universe without the prequels. I was rewatching 1 today trying to imagine what it was like (I actually enjoyed myself and the prequels are way better than most action films today) Anyway for Star Wars fans: was it super cool to see the origins of R2-D2 and C3-PO? And to see Yoda and Obi-wan younger and in a different setting? Was it cool to see the emperor as a scheming politician or going back to Tatooine? Or did it all feel like too much fan service? Would really appreciate older SW fans letting me know!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 16:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah thanks for this advice! Yeah well one of the injuries wasn't from running but still get ur point - yeah that's true just need to concentrate on getting back rather than care what others are doing   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 15:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe because I'm English it's just pretty jarring and seems abit like they are trying to hard  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 14:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just cringey - I'm only 21 and just don't believe anyone talks like they do  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 07:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I surprisingly like all the characters individually (apart from Marcus) but today they are so cringey -the constant high fiving, fist bumping, saying dope (okay maybe I just hate Marcus  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Downward spiral and how to get back into running </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 02:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this year has been great for me generally in terms of running. 2016 was the first year I ever did any serious running and I clocked 863km (could have been 1000 if I didn't have injuries) this year and started doing distances of 10km. Obviously this should be great news but I got an injury where I'd didn't run all of October. Then I could only manage 7km's. then I got another injury at the start of this month- a pulled hamstring-so I am completely out of action even now. I know I have put on weight in the last month and I'm just generally feeling shit about running. I want to get back to 10km but it's will be a lot of effort-anyone got a story of how they got back into it properly ? Any tips how to do ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From Rogue One-is this a Wampa variant (looks similar but no horns) with a gas mask and a chain gun? Or another species that looks similar ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 05:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 19:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man you're a maniac  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 18:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did what now!?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 13:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 25 in England  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 13:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is wrong living in a desert planet, leaving that planet and realising you hate sand ? Which is fucking annoying at times  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 13:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I guess but only have to look at George Bush Jr to see how easily a president can be manipulate by a VP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you guys think of President Walker? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 04:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To me he's weak and indecisive and a boyscout - his character essentially serves to be destroyed by Frank but I think him and his wife being uncynical compared to Frank and Claire just shows what it takes to win and you can never take people at face value which the Walkers often do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 04:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know enough but it's too complicated to talk about on Reddit without writing a massive essay and even then you would leave a tonne out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 14:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the most fascinating in itself or whatever but always a good point to look back at and think 'that's how we ended up here'. The Soviet invasion of Afghanistan just after the Iranian revolution really moved the radical Muslim world into action. The MAK (later would spring into al-Qaeda) set up by Bin Laden funnelled foreign jihadists into the country  while the Mujahideen revived weapons and training of the CIA and China.

Fast forward to the mid-90's and the Pakistani backed Taliban won the civil war between the resistance after the soviets were kicked out. The leader of Afghanistan became Mullah Omar who was a friend of Bin Laden. As Al-Qaeda was a floundering organisation he offered them sanctuary in his borders and here is partly where they planned 9/11. After this the war on terror began and Afghan was invaded and occupied. The US then claimed Sadam Hussein had ties to Al-Qaeda (aswell as WMD's) and invaded and occupied them. And here is the context from which ISIS springs out of (a Sunni group who felt oppressed due to the US backing the Shia for govt and armed forces). Again not entirely interesting in itself but I found the overall timeline and knock on affects fascinating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 14:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A man in England fought in the Boer war, WW1 and WW2. By his time in world war 2 he only had one eye and one arm but still shot at Germans hanging off a train while fleeing Europe (one arm!) - truly incredible guy who said he'd actually enjoyed the Wars ! http://www.abroadintheyard.com/veteran-boer-war-ww1-ww2-wounded-9-times/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Steep is great! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 04:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me and my brother just spent two hours playing one ramp course trying to perfect our runs-to get gold was 3000 I eventually got my highest score up to 4444-this is why the game is great-had so much fun doing a single course!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 23:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spanish Inquisition isn't a time period it's an institution  - it existed for hundred of years - the period is actually the reign on Isabella of Castile and Fernando of Aragon in the Iberian Peninsula which was still pretty divided (Spain as an entity didn't really exist) - time period is late 15th early 16th century  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 22:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yes just re-read the booklet - its molding is sterling machine guns which were used to make the original my mistake  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 19:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol a Christmas miracle  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 19:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I was loaded I would but the rebel pilot helmet looked cooler -also full sized R2-D2 for 2000  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 17:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't live in England I'm not sure I'm don't think the guy can ship them legally  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 17:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He won in England so he keeps making them-so I don't know where your getting that info from. The states is a different story  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 15:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It the original mould used for the original trio loft so yeah pretty much the same - only moving part is the detachable magazine  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 13:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep it is ! Won the battle against retaining the rights form Lucas and has his own shop in Twickenham, London  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 13:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah looking forward to playing them both!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 13:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks great for the first couple hours then the paint begins to melt off  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Replica E-11 from the guy who made the originals in England - now I can do battlefront for real! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 13:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 15:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw a mummy preview at the theatre tonight almost walked out, when fucking Tom Cruise. Came on the screen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 14:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I should have mentioned that-I don't want him being an all powerful force god I just like the idea of his character  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 13:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ibra over Kane anyday and Dembele what are you on!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 12:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying bringing him back exactly the same but in some form  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to incorporate Starkiller into Rebels </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 04:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I was recently playing the Force Unleashed and there is a Starkiller skin done in the style of the Clone Wars animated style and it got me thinking how cool it would be to see him in Rebels. I think they could still make him Darth Vader's secret apprentice and he could hunt down the ghost crew.  They could be cool scenes of him killing imperials and Rebels. I think Ezra would be able to connect with him since they are both conflicted Force uses and maybe he would be able to turn him away from Vader since they are a similar age and by the end of it Galen could fly off on his own into the galaxy. Would also be great to see proxy make an appearance ! Does anyone think this could work? 


Edit: I don't want him to appear as some crazy powerful dragon ball Z style Force wielded just as a powerful apprentice probably just as good as Ezra  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 17:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By that logic so is every MARIO game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 16:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah okay thanks ! I was still pretty good at it so was wondering if there were any major changes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Super Mario Run is great! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 16:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I absolutely hate mobile gaming... like loathe it. I hate the controls and I hate the bullshit micro transactions. I was so happy to buy MARIO and just get a full mobile game that has adapted its control scheme to work brilliantly on a mobile. I am happy to pay for quality and while people complain it's short, it's very replayable-great in short bursts whether it's quickly in bed on waiting for a lecture. The only major downside is that it always has to be online which I would love if they made an offline mode and maybe you would have to sync it up after?

I feel a lot of the complaints come from it not being a full MARIO game but you're only paying 7.99 - for a quality game without bullshit micro transactions-pretty good deal to me!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 13:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I do that on an iPhone ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fight Squadron what's changed ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 05:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So today I bought the Rogue One DLC after months of not playing. In the infantry maps I was being killed in ways I'd never seen before I took solace in fighter squadron (Scariff map is beautiful in space) so my question is - have they made any significant changes to fighter squadron since before the release of Death Star until now ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't think I've seen this moment get enough love - Rogue One </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 05:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> {spoilers} 



That last scene with Jyn and Cassian was heartbreaking but so perfect. Just the emotion in their faces really helps you out yourself in their shoes. I love the A-bomb test imagery (in the Pacific). I love it when characters accept their fate like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 05:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favourite is our pound coin which has he White House on fire  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So the DLC is out today-worth picking up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 09:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am about rank 55 but because of BF1 I haven't played Battlefront in ages. Any reason why getting the DLC will be refreshing to play? I love Rogue One so that's he main reason I want to buy it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 01:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I am actually a 'boy' so this doesn't annoy me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 01:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was trolling  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gender is just a social construct I am neither ! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 21:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 19:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't beat Mafia 2 for a Christmas vibe  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 18:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay if your from Holland fair enough you don't know it - should have put it in the post!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
