<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1563</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 20:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That gif just ends slightly too soon and it irritates me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 16:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ed G. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 16:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alcoholism isn't a disease, it's an art. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 02:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's Ser Bronn of the Blackwater to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 14:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if the eroge was the eroge was too much for him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 04:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's something wrong with him I swear. Seems overly sheltered or something. I wouldn't be surprised to find out something really creepy about him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 17:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never got Ornstein's armor. It's pretty much impossible for me to kill Smough first without summons, and even with summons Ornstein almost always dies first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 16:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're able to wear Havel's armor at SL1? Even with Havel's ring I wouldn't think that was possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 15:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've died so many times trying to get to Domnhall of Zena under that stupid bridge by Firelink. It's such an unnecessary jump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 02:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same. Watched every other episode but I couldn't finish it. It was just plain garbage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 02:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> College textbooks. What in the actual fuck. Why would any textbook cost $300?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 02:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This never happens...ever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 02:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're talking about normal rough housing between boys, it is just boys being boys though. Naturally they wanna wrestle and get rough with other boys. Only shitty people can't tell the difference between horsing around and malevolent behavior. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 23:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't parry for shit but I've never had trouble with Gwyn. I either tank him or just dodge his attacks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 23:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel you on that last part there. I kept dying on four kings because I couldn't do enough damage in time. Went on a mission to get my iato to +15 and level up my dex so I could do a lot more. Bought some gold line resin and I went in and whooped ass. Felt awesome. I can't say I was so patient though. Definitely said a word that rhymes with "punt" about 100 times. 

I also don't give up, but it's more fueled by my need to win and avenge all of my losses than my patience.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 03:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant main bosses more or less. Oh yes, I hate TOTG without sunlight maggot. It's horrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which parts of the game do you find most frustrating (non-boss)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 03:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it would be:

1) The rafters in Anor Londo Cathedral

2) Bonewheels right before Pinwheel

3) Trying to open the seal in New Londo ruins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 03:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some are born gud, some need to git gud </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 01:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first character had no trouble with Capra demon. I did a strength/tank character so I could block the first couple hits enough to get up the stairs. This character I'm doing is a fast rolling, rapier wielding weakling with just a target shield. I can't tell you how many times I got trapped by those fucking dogs trying to run to the stairs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 21:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Manus OP a casul </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 16:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buddhism for sure  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 16:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be satisfied </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 16:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Statistically yes it doesn't make a whole lot of sense to be so afraid of terrorism in the U.S., but imagine you were there when a bombing or shooting occured. It would be mortifying. You can't tell me that you wouldn't be afraid if there was a terrorist gunning down people all around you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 15:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah he only slaughtered a bunch of children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 01:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be a much better fight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I think we should expect more from out politicians than pettiness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 08:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thread makes me wanna drink some beer and watch football </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 07:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope that person dies a horrible death completely alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 02:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lucas has a funny way of fucking up royally with great material </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 19:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hardly. I loved the game as a kid but going back to it now, the mechanics are absolute shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 17:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the star wars prequels </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 08:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually did a strength build. Just finished the game for NG+, now I'm on NG++. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 08:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always find that Gwyn is the easiest boss out of all the main bosses.  I guess I just don't like the fact that I can't take my time and try to fight properly with them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 18:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found that rolling to the side sometimes helps to get away from the grab, but I don't think I've ever outrun it. Yes, the spell thing can be blocked, but it takes up all my stamina and it takes more time which leads to more kings. I'm so glad to be done with those bastards. Mostly because I hate running through New Londo Ruins. I've went through so many times that I'm out of transient curses and can't buy any more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hate the four kings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 18:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here are my reasons:



-the grab move is practically impossible to dodge 



-that "spell" they cast at you is nearly impossible to dodge 



-sometimes the two aforementioned attacks are spammed and it becomes impossible to win



-the only way to win (which is actually pretty easy if the two cheap moves aren't used) is to just run up to them and swing away with no blocking or dodging.

This fight has little to do with skill and everything to do with how the kings decide to fight you and how much damage your character can put out. If they aren't cheap, you can just run in and do as much damage as possible as fast as you can. 

On my NG++ I got frustrated trying to block and dodge, getting beat over and over. So I just put my shield away, put on my Giant's armor, two-handed my zweihander +15 and just sprinted right ahead and kept swinging. Beat them on that first try. I just didn't get the feeling I got with most other bosses where I fought intelligently, timing my attacks, dodges, and blocks well and it all paid off. This boss is just a big fuck you to anyone who tries to use normal fighting tactics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 18:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should have checked comment history. Just a troll. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 16:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't make bets if I were you then. I use artorias greatshield in one hand, zwei+15 in the other with black iron set. This sub is usually a great community, but I guess there's always a piece of shit like you in every sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 16:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 60% strength scaling and 26% dex scaling for normal path. Definitely more of a strength weapon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 20:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zweihander weighs 10 and if you're leveling strength, zweihander +15 does a base damage of 325 and scales well with strength. Pancakes most enemies too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 17:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one really should be quite obvious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 17:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Painting guardians on top of rafters in Anor Londo Cathedral or the sorcerers in Oolacile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 03:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean how so, as in what constitutes deserving it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 18:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what 90% of the stories on Reddit would be if people were actually honest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 16:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's all good. I ended up beating O S alone on my very next try.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 16:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How so? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which one of you bastards invaded me before O S? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 23:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just about to summon Solaire and fight Ornstein and Smough, but someone had to invade me. Hit him within an inch of his life, but he hit me with a bunch of fireballs before I could deliver the finishing blow. Well played. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 18:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it wouldn't. At any given moment, that person would be a specific age. The average age would always be increasing, but the average lifespan would never be infinite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 18:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get absolutely furious when my gf's dog does this. I guard my food whenever she is around and my gf gets annoyed other me for being so extreme, but once you've had a dog grab food off your plate, you can't trust it anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 18:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Until you try to fly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 17:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's absolutely pointless. I only care how a person wants to express themselves, but I cannot believe the obsession with gender. Biologically there is male, female and occasionally intersex people (which is a deformity). I don't really care about how people view themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 17:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say it was depression if it was a lasting feeling, but it happens for a little bit, sometimes just a moment and then I just end up being distracted by something else and just go on about with things, feeling content like before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 05:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. I absolutely despise it. First few times I tried to post on this sub I forgot to do that and had to wait. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE get strong, sudden feelings of emptiness and purposelessness completely for no apparent reason? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 04:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: I mean no apparent reason as in everything seems to be fine, you're otherwise happy and nothing traumatic or bad has happened recently. You just go through a mini existential crisis while driving on the highway, feeling like there is really no meaning in anything and start wondering why you are just going through the motions. I don't mean this in a depressed or suicidal way, it's just genuinely baffling as to what existence could possibly mean and I can't seem to make sense of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 23:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone reverse this gif? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 15:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, no. God no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 09:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never talk to her. Know nothing about what she's doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 05:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay I'll agree to that point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 05:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your only point is that the plot wouldn't exist without the vigilantes. That is because there is no story without conflict. That's fundamental to any story. The vigilantes are antagonists because they cause problems for our main protagonist, Kenny. Kenny is the main protagonist because he is the character that the story follows. We don't see the vigilantes or know anything about them. The only interaction we have with them is the orders they give to Kenny. It might even be a stretch to call the vigilantes characters really. Might as well be a  magical vending telling Kenny to do these things. Really makes no difference who is telling Kenny to do this, doesn't change the story.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 05:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you watch CP or molest a child you are causing great harm either directly or indirectly. Not always the case with drugs and alcohol. In most cases, the person is causing harm to themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 23:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the description of the episode:

"After the virus infected his laptop, a teen faces daunting choice: carry out orders delivered by text message or risk having intimate secrets exposed."

Sounds a lot like he's the main character to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 21:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> protagonist

prtanst,prtanst/

noun

the leading character or one of the major characters in a drama, movie, novel, or other fictional text.

the main figure or one of the most prominent figures in a real situation.

"in this colonial struggle, the main protagonists were Great Britain and France"

synonyms:chief/central/principal/main/leading character,chief/central/principal/main/leading participant,chief/central/principal/main/leading figure,chief/central/principal/main/leading player,principal,hero/heroine,leading man/lady,title role,lead

"the protagonist in the plot"


Edit: I don't see how Kenny isn't this character. Look at all the discussion about this episode. It all centers around Kenny. He's clearly the main character.
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 20:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1 round...what kind of casual plays multiplayer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 20:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But we're following Kenny through this whole thing. We don't even know who the vigilantes are. The only thing we know is that Kenny will be screwed if this video gets leaked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 17:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I died the first time I fought pinwheel, but that's because I thought he was grave lord Nito at first. I was afraid to get close to him and attack so I ended up dying. Second time was a cakewalk.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 17:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finished Dark Souls for the first time recently. Started NG+ but I also bought the Witcher 3 and haven't started yet...anyone here play the Witcher 3? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 17:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being a protagonist or antagonist has absolutely nothing to do with whether or not they are the "bad guy" or "good guy." It's just the main character. The vigilantes are still the antagonist. Also, though Kenny and the others deserved punishment, what the vigilantes did would be considered cruel and unusual punishment in today's justice system. Also, by having Kenny run in and Rob a bank and giving them a really short time to drive to locations, they put innocent people's lives in danger. What if they ran someone over? What if Kenny shot someone at the bank/attacked someone?

Also, what about the other guy he was with? Yes he cheated on his wife with a prostitute, but is that really someone else's business to get involved in his marriage? Someone who doesn't even know him or his wife? Not saying his wife didn't deserve to know, but it doesn't seem to me that these people should get to see which punishment is fit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 16:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll definitely agree that the episode humanized people who have sick tendencies, but Kenny still chose to masturbate to child pornography. He didn't seem to care that it was wrong until it was going to be released to the world. No, I guess being a pedophile doesn't automatically make you evil, because you could never act on it, but I'd venture to guess that there's not many pedophiles who don't act on their desires.

Kenny still had a choice even though maybe he couldn't control his attractions. We all have choices even though we may be inclined one way or another. It may be in my genetics that I'm highly prone to alcoholism or drug addiction. I can still choose not to drink or do drugs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 04:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that's what's so great about the episode. You feel what the Kenny is feeling and you want him to get out of this situation. You root for him the whole time and then you find out he was masturbating to CP. Kind of slaps you in the face for rooting for a pedophile. I felt disgusted with myself for being so concerned about Kenny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 23:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was CP though. Yeah I'm sure nobody wants their porn habits shown to the world but CP isn't just "weird porn," it's completely vile and wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 22:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/radiohead 


My favorite band, but the community is pure cancer. It's mostly shitty fanboy/fangirl portraits of Thom Yorke, really bad covers, and the same polls over and over again about favorite albums/songs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 19:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're talking mixed martial arts here. So one dimensional pretty much means not that good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 17:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All it says is they got beat. Everyone gets beat. No need to over think it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 17:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plus hes still got the biggest star in ufc history </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 17:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. People love Ronda so much they can't admit that she's not that great. Nunes is bad as fuck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 19:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish you could just be like, "yeah you're right, fuck it" and then decide to let the world end
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 17:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly, if people would just educate themselves about Islam they'd find a completely new understanding of why the religion is so awful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 17:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm extremely jealous. I wish I could go without breathing in secondhand smoke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 18:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless I missed something, she wasn't going to jump, it was her telling him to jump. I don't remember her saying she's going to jump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 06:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your best bet is to be really mean and unappreciative most of the time so when you get a gift a simple thank you will seem really grateful in comparison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 06:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I try to be a little more outward with my gratitude/excitement when I get gifts from people I'm not as close to. Anyone who is close to me knows I don't get excited easily and I'm not very outward emotionally so a "thanks, I really like it" is fine. I'm sure if the person giving you the gift knows you well enough, they understand.

IMO it's better not to try and fake excitement or be over the top with your reaction to the gift but instead just tell them a simple thank you and that you really like the gift. Nothing worse to me than a fake, over the top reaction.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 06:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Assuming OP is a guy*

Why hello there, shitlord. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 15:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Replace white with any other race, see how people react. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 15:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still don't get why people are going in the holes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just beat the game for my first time! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 06:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
SPOILERS AHEAD

What a phenomenal game. I will definitely be going on the try the next couple games in the series. I remember when I first started the game. I thought it was clunky and outdated and I didn't understand what to do, but I pushed on because I've heard so many good things a d I wanted to give it an honest shot. So glad I did, because this has become one of my favorite games. The only thing I regret is not doing more before defeating Gwyn. I didn't know it would all start over, otherwise I would have. Also, didn't know I had a choice in the ending, I just lit the bonfire out of habit. Oh well, guess I'll have to do that on my second time around! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 02:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Until the moment I got that last hit  I couldn't breathe. Then after that I still couldn't breathe.


At what moment exactly could you breathe? You seem to be a bit delirious from a lack of oxygen! Jokes aside, that's absolutely insane. I would never go into a boss fight with one estus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 00:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoops, yeah that's who I meant. Thought I put I in the description but I guess I didn't!  Merry Christmas! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best Christmas gift! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 20:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been struggling on them for a few days now, but today I beat them on my second try!

Edit: was too excited and forgot to put that I meant Ornstein and Smough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 01:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The purposes are very intense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 19:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the point of doing that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 18:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just posted yesterday about this fight. It's a pain in the ass but it's definitely doable. I've come so close with Solaire. Like everyone else is saying, use the pillars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 18:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does that mean? SL1? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 15:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had nightmares about having to poop in public with tons of people watching. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 03:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I accidentally went with the raw path and saw on boards everywhere that the normal path is better. I don't wanna go back to regular until I have enough titanite to upgrade all the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 03:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks I think I'm at the point where I can beat them. I've come so close. Maybe there's not a ton I can do except fight better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need advice for Ornstein and Smough </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 21:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep dying against them and it's really frustrating. I am summoning Solaire and I can kill one of them but I end up dying against the surviving one because Solaire dies. I've gotten a few hits but there's a few moves I can't seem to dodge (Ornsteins butr jump and Smoughs lunging stab). I was wondering if there's a merchant or anything that I can buy something to give me an edge or am I just going to have to beat them this way? I get really close but I'm running out of humanity to summon Solaire. I want to do everything I can to prepare for this fight. FYI I'm doing a strength build character, I'm using leather armor and zweihander raw +5. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 18:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My thought is that they don't have to earn much in life, rendering their life sort of meaningless, which drives them mad. We all wish all of our problems would be solved, but once they were, then what do we do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 07:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure the mom said "they're kids" to him on the phone. Also the guy he fought asked him "how young?" and judging by Kenny's face it seems like these weren't teenagers. I'm guessing these were children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 21:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be upstairs in my room for a while...nobody come bother me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 19:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lucifer. Such a badass name, but of course you can't name a child after the Devil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 19:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Tracer actually confirmed lesbian? I don't really understand the purpose of giving a player in a purely multiplayer game a sexuality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 19:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DAE play this gem??? *Insert video game icon* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 17:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That everyone can be reasoned with if you talk to them the right way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 04:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone in a long term relationship knows the woman has total control of the sex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
