<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2013</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Metroid Prime Trilogy.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 752 BC Romulus, king of Rome, defeated and killed Acro, king of the Caeninenses, in battle following the Rape of the Sabine Women.  Not sure how "major" that is, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 22:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, I think you mean your guzzoline, bloodbag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 22:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.businessinsider.com/conservatives-purposely-making-cars-spew-black-smoke-2014-7  Workin' out great so far! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 21:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason the Welsh soldiers *love* it there... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 21:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They had it coming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 20:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  and similar work ethic

From the books:

...he [Mycroft] has no ambition and no energy. He will not even go out of his way to verify his own solutions, and would rather be considered wrong than take the trouble to prove himself right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 16:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the best your god can do is Trump to accomplish your goals, I wouldn't worship him even if he were demonstrably real.  I mean, come on, he used to be able to get talent like Cyrus the Great when he needed a good heathen.  What happened? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the biggest mistake your favorite franchise ever made? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 21:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you had sufficient videos of people speaking a language you didn't know, could you raise an infant to translate them for you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 02:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So like, if you just had hundreds of hours of video of everyday life taking place in a totally unknown language, could you just have a newborn child watch them constantly and have him learn the language so that he could tell you what they're saying? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was your most awkward orgasm? [NSFW] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 00:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I quit a job with unused PTO, they usually pay it out to me. If I quit and I've used more PTO that I've earned, can they deduct it from my paycheck? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 22:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Writing Exercises and Prompts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 22:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was the Austro-Hungarian Compromise of 1867 sustainable? Could a nation divided in half like that last? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 22:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always thought the Austro-Hungarian Compromise of 1867 was an interesting solution, and lately I've been thinking about the feasibility of a nation under two governments.  Was this sort of system feasible?  Did any other country have success with it?  Or was it unlikely to ever last long-term? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which person went from almost totally unknown to hated by an entire country in the shortest amount of time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 15:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reverse Dictionary </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 19:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any resources on what daily life is like for people who are blind? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 19:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've tried looking for blogs or diaries online, but I haven't been able to find anything.  I'm just looking for a description of daily life from the point of view of someone's who's blind.  Does anyone know of any resources? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Were there ever any real returns of monarchs after their alleged deaths? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 19:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've noticed that there are a lot of pseudo-monarchs in history, people who claimed to be dead leaders, like Nero and Smerdis and Dmitriy.  But I've never found a story of a monarch being thought dead, vanishing for a few years, and then coming back to claim their rightful throne.  Are there any examples?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 4 Asians </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 16:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hand Bra </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 16:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bathing Beauty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 16:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Medieval Demographics Made Easy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 21:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that in Johnson v Johnson, a judge ruled that although a woman fit the description of a whore, it was still slander to call her one maliciously. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 18:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where's the best place to celebrate your favorite holiday? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 21:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Divinity Dragon Commander Generals Decisions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 21:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Divinity Dragon Commander Princess Decisions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 21:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Big bush under the snow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 06:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't want to get wet! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 06:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mature Bather </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 06:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pierced Nipps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 06:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unsure why they censored only her mouth and nothing else, but I won't complain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 06:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sounds Like Tropico #2: Alfredo Zitarrosa - Doa Soledad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 03:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any diaries or blogs about daily life as a blind individual, ideally blind from birth? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 20:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried searching through the subreddit, but I couldn't find any similar posts, so forgive me if I'm asking a common question, but I'm looking for blogs or diaries written by blind individuals describing daily life.  I tried using Google but I couldn't find much.  Thank you for your help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the significance in Japanese culture of pulling open your jacket? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 02:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/a/aw3f1  Example.  I like the image but don't know the meaning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way to get an email or alert when a particular company has a Groupon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 22:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do I already contain enough bacteria to decompose me, or do they need outside help to skeletonize me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 22:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking, what if I were in a sealed, completely sterile room and died of a heart attack, but the heat and oxygen and everything continued to work.  Would the bacteria already inside me decompose me completely, or would I just mummify eventually?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clodius gets saved at trial because the jurors refused to write legibly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 23:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some say that Caesar made this deposition honestly; but according to others it was made to gratify the people, who were determined to rescue Clodius. At any rate, Clodius was acquitted of the charge, the majority of the jurors giving their verdicts in illegible writing, in order that they might neither risk their lives with the populace by condemning him, nor get a bad name among the nobility by acquitting him.

Souce: Plutarch's Life of Caesar  http://penelope.uchicago.edu/Thayer/E/Roman/Texts/Plutarch/Lives/Caesar*.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something you started doing because of a particular movie, game, or book? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 15:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would your favorite movie/TV show/video game be like if it were made in a world where Nazi Germany won WWII? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 00:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We can do it! [MEC] (aka6) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 20:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Viper King frotting with peasantry [Viper King/Male XCOM] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 20:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dr. Vahlen Stripping [Dr. Vahlen] (Studio-Pirrate) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 02:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> French kiss [Viper/XCOM] (Methados) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 02:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Draw me like one of your French snakes... [Viper] (Gannadene) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 02:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alien Interrogation, the Hard Way [Berserker/Dr Vahlen] (Rakked) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 18:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well, I had to submit a Reddit Request to take over an abandoned subreddit to get it, but I bring you /r/SEXCOM, for all your Rule 34 XCOM needs. Needs some love. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 17:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Female Advent Officer struggling to put her chest armor on because her breasts are too big [Advent Officer] (Methados) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 17:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If all stun lancers looked like this, maybe I wouldn't kill them first [Stun Lancer] (Methados) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 17:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Save 75% on Tropico 5 - Complete Collection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 21:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for people to play and finish multiplayer games with </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 17:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like it's really hard to get a multiplayer game going from beginning to end, and I'd really like to get those multiplayer achievements in Tropico 5.  Anyone want to try to get some games going?  Feel free to add me if you want: http://steamcommunity.com/id/MertvayaRuka/  There's also a Reddit Tropico 5 group that could use more love: http://steamcommunity.com/groups/PlayTropicoYouFucks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do we know about Sostratos or Aegina, from Herodotus 4.152? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 17:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The passage reads:

But after they had been away for longer than the agreed time, and Corobius had no provisions left, a Samian ship sailing for Egypt, whose captain was Colaeus, was driven off her course to Platea, where the Samians heard the whole story from Corobius and left him provisions for a year; they then put out to sea from the island and would have sailed to Egypt, but an easterly wind drove them from their course, and did not abate until they had passed through the Pillars of Heracles and came providentially to Tartessus. Now this was at that time an untapped market; *hence, the Samians, of all the Greeks whom we know with certainty, brought back from it the greatest profit on their wares except Sostratus of Aegina, son of Laodamas; no one could compete with him.* The Samians took six talents, a tenth of their profit, and made a bronze vessel with it, like an Argolic cauldron, with griffins' heads projecting from the rim all around; they set this up in their temple of Hera, supporting it with three colossal kneeling figures of bronze, each twelve feet high. What the Samians had done was the beginning of a close friendship between them and the men of Cyrene and Thera.

From what I've read, Sostratos is never mentioned again by either Herodotus or any other extant source, and I can't find much information about him online.  Is anything else known about him?  

I just find it to be such an intriguing anecdote.  The most profitable Greek trader of all time!  And that's all we know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do other histories have something similar to Plutarch's Lives? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 17:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really enjoy reading Plutarch, and I'd like to learn more about other histories from before the modern area.  Are there writers from other cultures who wrote similar short biographies of many subjects? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When and How Did You First Discover You Had a Kink? [NSFW] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 21:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What will be the title of the chapter in future history textbooks that begins with the year 2016? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 01:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Requesting /r/sexcom, mod has no visible activity for nine months </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 19:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reading </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 19:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kiss with a view </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 19:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking to get The Most Dangerous Game achievement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 21:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm interested in achievements, but not in multiplayer.  Anyone up for a game or two of XCOM2 multiplayer so we (or I, if you already have it) can get The Most Dangerous Game achievement from winning a multiplayer game?  If you need it, I can also give you the Bubonic achievement for XCOM: EW.  

My Steam ID is http://steamcommunity.com/id/MertvayaRuka/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sir, I don't think that's a fair operation name... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 22:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has your party's nominee this primary season made you reconsider your party affiliation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 17:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never Trump Republicans and Never Hillary Democrats, are you reconsidering your party affiliation because of their near certain victories in the primaries?  Do you still feel like you belong in your party? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cute horny big tits asian girl [X-POST from /r/JapanPornstars] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 02:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which two characters from different franchises would make the best couple? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 21:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> By which quantifiable metrics would you consider Obama's presidency to be a success or a failure? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 21:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In terms of things that can be measured, things like unemployment rate, the national debt, the deficit, number of uninsured,  c., which metrics matter most to you, and which would you use to consider Obama's presidency successful or unsuccessful and why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you played Startopia? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 23:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know who she is? Whoever she is, she seems to enjoy being eaten out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 00:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Asian girl enjoying being eaten out. Source or any more? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 21:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/peynlIV.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You can switch any human bodily fluid with a liquid of your choice without causing any medical problems. Which do you choose? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 22:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> She likes an audience </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 19:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Options </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 19:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Join Me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 19:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Big Breasts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 19:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five Friends </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 19:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Calligraphy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 19:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Washing Up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 19:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which seemingly awful leader unexpectedly ended up actually being really good? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 23:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yuu Kawakami in the onsen [Album] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 17:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mai Sakura </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 17:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kaede Matsushima </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 17:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tsukasa Aoi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 17:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thirsty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 17:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Voyeurism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 17:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mixed Bathing at the Bath </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 17:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Waiting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 17:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Co-Ed Bathing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 21:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tiny Tits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 21:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A bit modest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 21:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sounds Like Tropico #1: Wynton Marsalis - 2/3's Adventure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 18:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On His Lap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 16:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> She looks oddly skeptical to me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 15:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cautious </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 15:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astonished </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 15:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Muddy Faces </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 17:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chess by CrystallizedTwilight on DeviantArt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 17:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Younger Agis has a dismissive reply to someone asking who the best Spartan was. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 16:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In answer to a base man who asked repeatedly who was the best Spartan, he said, "The one most unlike you."

**Source:**

[Plutarch's Sayings of the Spartans](http://penelope.uchicago.edu/Thayer/E/Roman/Texts/Plutarch/Moralia/Sayings_of_Spartans*/main.html#ref23)

[Agis III](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Agis_III) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Forest in the background, clear-cut in the foreground. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 23:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hanging Around </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 23:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Agathocles sent his handsome son to a rival commander with a taste for boys in order to distract him before a betrayal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 21:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ophellas of Cyrene was advancing with a numerous army against Agathocles. Hearing that Ophellas was notoriously addicted to the love of boys, Agathocles sent an embassy to him, and his son Heracleides, who was a boy of extraordinary beauty, went as a hostage, with orders to hold out for a few days against his solicitations. Ophellas, charmed with the beauty of the boy, conceived a violent passion for him, and strongly solicited him to comply with his desires. While he was thus engaged, Agathocles suddenly attacked and slew him; and entirely defeated his army. His son also he recovered safely, and without any injury having been offered to him.

**Source:**
[Polyaenus, Stratagems, 5.3.4](http://www.attalus.org/translate/polyaenus5A.html#3.1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thoughtful </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 16:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Four Beauties </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 16:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spying on the Changing Room </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 16:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Group Photo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 16:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coed Outdoors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 15:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skinny </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 15:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Asian Butt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 15:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Haitian Chief of Secret Police had his title on his business card before realizing that it spoiled the secret. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 22:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From among the cagoulards, Barbot began to organize a more formal militia.  The menand occasional womenwho joined it would be known as the Tontons Macoutes.  Tonton Macoute (Uncle Knapsack) was a Vodou bogeyman, said to snatch naughty children and bundle them into a sack.  Dressed in dark blue denim, with pistols on their hips and dark glasses permanently obscuring their eyes, the Macoutes played up to rumors that they were zombies, mute killing machines raised from the dead by Duvaliers magic.
	
Duvalier denied in an American radio interview that the Macoutes existed.  I have never heard them mentioned, except in the American press, he said.  They do not exist in reality.  But exist they did.  Their proud master, Barbot, had business cards printed describing himself as the chief of secret policethough, on realizing that this spoiled the secret, he soon stopped giving them out.


**Source:**

von Tunzelmann, Alex.  Red Heat: Conspiracy, Murder, and the Cold War in the Caribbean.  New York: Henry Holt and Company, 2011.  Page 95.

[Book (Wikipedia)](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Red_Heat:_Conspiracy,_Murder_and_the_Cold_War_in_the_Caribbean) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ptolemy III convinced Athens to lend him their originals of famous plays, putting up an enormous bond as surety. Once he had the plays, he let them keep the money, considering the originals more valuable than the gold. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 20:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ptolemy III (246-221 BCE) is said to have sent messages to all the rulers of the known world, asking for books to copy.  Officials were under order to confiscate from passing ships all the books that they had on board.  Copies of these books were made and returned, but the originals went into the great library (where in the catalogue they were marked from the ships).  Royal agents fanned out through the Mediterranean to buy or borrow more and more books.  Lenders grew increasingly waryborrowed books had a way of not coming backand demanded large deposits.  When, after intense cajoling, Athens agreed to lend Alexandria its precious authoritative texts of Aeschylus, Sophocles, and Euripidestexts that were zealously guarded in the citys records officethe city insisted on the enormous bond of 15 talents of gold.  Ptolemy posted the bond, received the books, sent copies back to Athens, and, forfeiting the bond, deposited the originals in the Museum.

**Source:**

Greenblatt, Stephen.  The Swerve: How the World Became Modern.  New York: W.W. Norton   Company, 2011.  Page 280.

[Book (Wikipedia)](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Swerve:_How_the_World_Became_Modern)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that James Hydrick escaped jail three times. First by kicking through a concrete wall, then by breaking through the gates, and finally by pole vaulting over the wall. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 22:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What tradition, custom, or saying has a fascinating origin story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 18:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bathing with Monkeys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 19:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Visiting with her male friend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 19:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five Friends </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 19:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shy but bad at hiding </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 19:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 19:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flat Onsen Girl (Crosspost from /r/HotSpringsWomen) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 19:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flat Onsen Girl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 19:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another Onsen Blowjob </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 19:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Onsen Blowjob </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 19:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tiny Tits Drying Off </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 18:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snowy Onsen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 18:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conical Hat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 18:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Undressing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 18:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting ready to go in </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 18:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Busty Japanese in Onsen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 23:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OnOff with pictures of Off and On </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 04:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happens to pardoned turkeys? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 21:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone keep track of them to ensure they're not killed and eaten later?  Do they just become turkey studs?  It's not like anyone's watching out for them after that one day.  Is there anything stopping people from just eating them two weeks later? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is this creepy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 19:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I came across this in an old AskReddit thread from 3 years ago about creepy stories, but I don't get what's creepy about it.  Can anyone help?

I got these phone calls on and off for a month. The first three days were in a row. Five in the morning the phone in my dorm would ring, jolting me awake. It was weird to hear it; I have a cell and the phone was only there because it came with the room. But once the initial startle was gone, dread set in. It's hard for me to describe how I felt because it's stupid to feel it over a ringing phone, but my stomach was rolling and I broke into a cold sweat. Every muscle in my body was trembling. I wanted to scream and throw up at the same time. If I had to take a step off the ledge, it felt like death was in the room. I didn't answer the phone. Somehow I fell back asleep. Once the ringing stopped the feeling passed. Until it happened the next morning at the same time. And the next. I had the same feeling and again I refused to pick up. I began to think it was a dream. Convinced myself it was a dream may have been more accurate. It stopped for a few days but would start again. I became afraid to sleep. I started getting anxiety attacks and my friends wanted to know what was wrong. I couldn't tell them, I'd sound crazy. So I did the only thing I could think of. The phone rang again that morning and I answered it. The dread was there, worse than ever. The phone was cold in my touch. But I couldn't live like this any more. So I spoke. "Hello?" "Hello." The voice was normal enough but at the same time it confirmed that everything I feared had been justified. There was something that word, like a song played backwards containing something scary. "Is Jane Smith there?" "I'm sorry. You have the wrong number." Could he hear how scared I was? Could he feel my fear through the line? "Oh, so sorry to bother you this early. Good morning." Despite his dismissal I was the one to hang up. I did not fall back asleep that night. My name is not Jane Smith. But my sister's is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the worst advice you can give that rhymes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 22:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I brought a radio, a television,  c. to Mars, would I be able to pick up anything from Earth? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 18:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always hear about radio waves going into space, but how strong are they?  Could you pick them up with a regular radio, or would you need a specialized radio telescope?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What decoration would you really love to own, but you've never been able to find? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 05:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nanako Kitagawa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-11 17:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yukiko Suo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-11 17:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are fans of the board game go/weiqi so damn vocal about it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 22:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like the best way to find a go player is to wait for them to tell you.  Any time chess is mentioned, someone needs to come in and say how much better go is.  If go is ever excluded from a list of board games, someone has to show up and complain about the absence of go.  

Someone today posted an awesome album of 39 ancient board games at /r/gaming.  Both chess and go were absent.  No one mentioned the absence of chess.  The top, third, and bottom parent comments all ask why go is absent, despite OP saying that he only posted game boards made by a Peruvian artist.

Is this the result of insecurity or what?  I can't think of any other game, and especially no other board game, whose fanbase feel such a great and mighty need to interrupt any conversation to mention go.  Am I just nuts, or what's going on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Easter Island, Tapati 2008, Umzug </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 03:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tapati Festival, Easter Island, by Eric Lafforgue. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 01:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not much to measure... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 16:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not much to measure... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 16:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sunbathing Dusky Beauty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 03:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Volleyball </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 03:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Volleyball </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 03:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Asian On/Off </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 03:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flat Nudist Asian at the Beach </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-26 03:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Surfer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 16:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Surfer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 16:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Subtext Buried In Seven Great Movie Chess Scenes [FiveThirtyEight] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 15:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most oddly specific subreddit you're subscribed to? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 19:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Language Garden (About Chantek the Orangutan) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-07 00:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do headbutts "work?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-06 22:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like, I get being hit in the head hurts, but why doesn't the headbutter get as hurt as the headbuttee?  Do you just hope that your head is harder when you headbutt someone?  It just seems like punching someone in the fist.  Wouldn't you both get relatively equally hurt?  Why is it a viable attack? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Love Your Scars [Mulan] by MeryChess </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-30 06:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch "Chantek, The First Orangutan Person | Lyn Miles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-14 23:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
