<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3535</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My only concern is that Bioware only takes the "its not enough like the OT" complaints to heart and decide to make any future games exactly like ME 1-3 and toss out any of the good things that worked in Andromeda.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying that any comparison between the OT and Andromeda aren't valid, but sometimes, people can make the OT out to be this flawless trilogy of games when comparing it to Andromeda, which isn't fair for Andromeda, especially when it comes to things like writing and characters. For example, when people complain that Andromeda doesn't have any likable characters when compared to the OT, they tend to forget how much they disliked Jack or Vega when they were first revealed, or how divisive and disliked Jacob, Ashley, Miranda, and Kaiden were, and to some extent, still are. 

Basically, While comparing Andromeda and the OT are fine, I just think calling a spade a spade should go both ways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree that not being as good as the OT doesn't equal Andromeda being a bad game and I wish a lot more people had that mentality. But what I also hope people keep in mind is that the OT had its problems and received some criticism when it came to the complaints of cheesy writing, the characters (remember how everyone reacted when they first saw Jack in ME2 or how the human squamates from 1 and 2 were disliked), and glitches(too many to name in one comment).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] When Andromeda releases, try and maintain perspective </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] In light of the recent reviews for Andromeda, try and have a little perspective </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 08:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think those are called sequels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 04:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely. Or it could focus on the efforts to disrupt the Afghan drug trade thats going on right now. (something along the lines of what these guys do. http://www.worldpoliticsreview.com/trend-lines/10623/deas-militarized-commando-teams-honed-in-afghanistan-but-born-in-latin-america) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 03:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But Hardline was made with a general 'crime drama' tone in mind, hence why I emphasized the war on drugs, something  Hardline didn't focus on, as the war on drugs is something that fits more in line with the Call Of Duty tone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And thanks for sharing it. I remember Hardline getting mixed reviews at first that got worse overtime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just out of curiosity, how was Hardline too niche? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Activision can probably fight the lawsuits, so sure why not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [COD] Should there be a crime based COD? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
One of the biggest debates going on in the Call of Duty community right now is what setting should future titles take place in. An avenue that I think has potential is for COD do to a crime based game.

Now, when I say crime based, I don't necessarily mean in the same vain as Battlefield:Hardline, but rather a game that deals with the world of illegal drugs and the efforts to combat them. For those that think that the game based on this couldn't work, here are a few reasons I think it would.

1. It's global: When most people think of the WOD, they immediately think of the Central and South American drug cartels, but illegal narcotics is a worldwide trade, with things such as the golden triangle in SouthEast Asia and the Afghan heroin trade, so a COD focusing on this wouldn't lose the globetrotting the series is known for.

2. It covers decades: A game based on the War on Drugs would have decades of information for the devs to work with, and could cover any and everything from the efforts to combat the growing drug cartels in South America and the Heroin and Crack epidemics in America in the 80's to counter drug operations being done today in places like Afghanistan by Federal Law Enforcement agencies  (http://abcnews.go.com/International/dea-heroin-haul-largest-afghanistan-world/story?id=44216333, http://www.digitaljournal.com/article/334691)

3. Its different: Like I stated above, figuring out where the COD should go next has been a source of debate for a lot of fans. This idea would allow the franchise to explore territory it hasn't been to yet
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should there be a crime based COD? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 23:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 21:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MEA spoilers] This is starting to get pretty annoying </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 21:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, the movie review site Screenrant posted an article about some of the early impressions of Andromeda, and based on some of the negative aspects written about in both the Forbes article (which struck me as a pretty positive one) and the RPS article (which has been debated about already in this subreddit) , it asks the question "should we be worried about Andromeda?" 

This isn't the first time this has happened with Andromeda, where some website will take either the lack of info or some of the flaws with the game or pretty much anything that doesn't match with their expectations and exaggerate them and frame them as signs that the game is a total flop. To be frank, seeing people make a mountain out of a mole hill, with little to no mention of any of the positive aspects, is getting pretty annoying. No game, especially a triple a title like Andromeda, is perfect and is going to have flaws, which I hope everyone keeps in mind the closer we get to release. 

http://screenrant.com/mass-effect-andromeda-negative-impressions/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They would probably be covert branch with a black budget similar to JSOC for the DOD.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 14:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I gave it a shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 14:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair points. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] A rework of Jacob </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 14:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As most us know and agree with, Jacob is probably one of the, if not the least interesting squamates in the ME trilogy. But I think that the character has some potential, so I decided to rework his backstory in an attempt to make it at least a bit more interesting, so here it goes. 

The first thing I would change about Jacob is that instead of being a nondescript Alliance Marine and "Corsair", I would make him a dishonorably discharged N7 officer. What led to his discharge was the mission he and Miranda undertook to stop a Batarian bio-weapon on the Citadel (which he mentions in your dialog with him, in case you forgot). In order to accomplish this mission, however, Jacob had to destroy a transport carrying the weapon, but also had several civilians on board. When questioned about the decision he made by the Alliance, Jacobs gives a response that basically equates to the ends justifying the means. This doesn't fly with the brass and Jacob loses his N7 designation and is drummed out of the Alliance. Jacob's actions, however, caught the attention of the Illusive Man, who offers Jacob a job as an operative. And while Jacob stands by his decision to his destroy the transport, deep down, he feels guilty about the lives he took. This guilt would better explain why decided to defend the defecting Cerberus Scientists in ME3 as a form of redemption rather than the 'I meditated and decided to do this' line we were given. 

Please feel free to add on to this or provide feedback.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 10:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 10:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its strange because I think ubisoft has attempted to connect the games in the past. I remember there was a trailer for H.AW.X 2 where they were providing Close Air Support for a Ghost team.

As for other media, a lot of TC properties are getting made into movies and TV shows like Splinter Cell with Tom Hardy as Sam Fisher, The Division movie, and the new Jack Ryan Amazon series. I'm still holding out hope that they'll try to connect these three and form some kind of cohesive universe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 10:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would make sense, seeing as how we never see any of the 'restore continuity of government' aspect of their mission in the game. That would have been a cool mechanic, where you were able to rebuild the various aspects of NYC in the form of missions, like raiding LMB bases to get weapons and vehicles for the NYPD, investigating the disappearance of the Mayor of NY, ect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 10:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt it since the JTTF is comprised mostly of Federal Law enforcement agencies and intel agencies. The JTF seems like something that was created specifically for the Dollar flu and not something that be around if the virus didn't occur. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wouldn't the Division be a part of Homeland Security? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 05:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had an interesting thought the other day as I was looking for the missing agent intel. Since the Division's goal is to restore continuity of government and they're limited to operating within the US, then realistically, wouldn't they be a part of the Department of Homeland Security? Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 05:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you saying it boring or entertaining? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 05:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's something, I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 04:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any good things about SDV? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 04:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just take the first three transformers movies and edit out the Transformers themselves, and splice the remaining footage together, and there you go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Berg would be a great choice. I would also say Ridley Scott, Paul Greengrass, and Kathryn Bigalow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a movie were to be made out a COD game, I would hope it would be based off of either BO1 or MW1. Both games have distinct characters, set pieces that would make for great actions scenes (imagine crew expendable or the mission in hue city in live action), and a cinematic tone already in them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If its that bad, why would anyone ask to be sent to SDV?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 04:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks man. I forgot about Chris Cassidy for a while. I remember when I was in High School and I wanted to be an Astronaut by way of being a Naval Aviator, learning about him and Eric Greitens made me want to join the teams instead.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 01:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If that's the case, then its no wonder why you don't hear a lot about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 00:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a really good idea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Info on the SDV teams </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 00:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been reading both Seal of Honor (the book on the life of Mike Murphy) and The Heart and the Fist, and one thing I've noticed were that both Murphy and Greitens were in the SDV teams at some point in their careers. After trying to research more info, I haven't found much. Does anyone have any info on the SDV teams, or how a BUD/S student gets selected for them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] Should I play the EA Access early trial? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 00:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've debating for a while wether or not I should get EA Access to play the free trial in a few days. On one hand, I get to play Andromeda early, but on the other hand, I want to go in completely fresh the day I pick it up. Plus, the trial is only 10 hours. Should I play the trial or hold on until the 21st? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> probably.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sailors that aren't part of NSW, but the regular Navy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do big Navy Sailors view SEALs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How often do SEALs travel compared to the rest of the Navy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 07:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the advice. I have to ask, why is an EOD slot so competitive for OCS candidates? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't mind seeing a west coast bast Division. I think the spaciousness of the major California cities like San Fran, L.A., and San Diego would be a good contrast and offer some potential gameplay changes to the cramped NY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some story and location ideas you guys have for The Division 2? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 09:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feel free to include ideas for enemy types, characters, factions, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 08:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would there be a legion of space marines as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And if there were too many RPG elements and a trailer for Andromeda coming out every other day, people would complain about those. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously? I knew some people had a problem with Cora's haircut, but they've tried to connect it to Sarkeesian? I can't decide if that's funny or sad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No spoilers] What are some of the worst/most annoying nitpicks you heard/read about the ME franchise? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 05:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 00:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Believe it or not, there's a sic-fi novel where the SEALs operate in space and the acronym stands for Sea Air Land Space. Its called Starstrike Task Force Mars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 10:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You wouldn't take Guinan from TNG instead? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 07:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The war with the Reapers would be over in one game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 07:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm surprised Nathan Fillion hasn't voiced a squamate in a ME game yet.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 07:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm imagining asking HK-47 what he thinks of the rest of the crew: 
"Statement: I have compiled detailed files of the most efficient methods of terminating your meatbag companions, Shepard. I have also compiled possible scenarios for the termination of the illusive meatbag as well. Would you care to hear them?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The art style reminds me of a Dr. Seuss book (that's a good thing, I promise).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would take The Doctor just to hear his conversations with Chakwas, Legion, and EDI. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
