<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3278</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 08:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, the only issue I ran into was after the Bowser Jr. fight the way forward was a blind jump. I died the first time when I fell straight down on purpose to see what was there. 

Please try mine: BB3F-0000-0074-4C11 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 07:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheesy Meadows

I tried to make a non-gimmicky, regular Mario level for a change. It should feel like World 2 or 3 from SMB3 in terms of difficulty. 

Please give it a shot: BB3F-0000-0074-4C11

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 11:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Level Title: Rebounding

ID: 20CD-0000-0067-1605

Description of Gameplay Elements: After impotently hurling my body at Pit of Panga: P-Break yesterday, I decided to create a tutorial level to teach players how to overcome it's first obstacle. You must jump, then kick a shell while in air into a spring and then bounce off the shell and over some spikes. My level helps you build up to it. Let me know if this is helpful or fun at all. I might make other tutorial levels for the seemingly impossible kaizo type challenges that aren't so impossible if you isolate them.

Video: https://youtu.be/SveqwVIOojY 

Section 1: Demonstrates bouncing over the spikes on a Bullet Bill.

Section 2: When you kick a shell into the spring, you will notice that is bounces back raised off the ground. In order to pass the wall you will have to bounce off it while it is off the ground. It helps me to have a running start.

Section 3: Similar to the Pit of Panga start but with a walkway underneath to prevent insta-death. Jump, kick the shell at the spring, bounce off it and over the spikes as the shell rebounds toward you.

Section 4: Same thing, but without training wheels.

OR

Have a walk down easy street:

Title: Goaltending

ID: CEF4-0000-0069-F7E9

Breakable blocks cover the SMB3 goal and Magikoopas surround that. Chaotic, but short, and not nearly as hard as it looks thanks to the infinite fire flowers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 08:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice one. I had no idea the axe would disappear like that. It was good platforming overall, like a real level almost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 08:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Made me think. I kept trying to put on the helmet. 

Try mine: CEF4-0000-0069-F7E9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 07:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love some feedback on my newest level. I will play yours if you leave a comment.

Title: Goaltending

ID: CEF4-0000-0069-F7E9

Breakable blocks cover the SMB3 goal and Magikoopas surround that. Chaotic, but short, and not nearly as hard as it looks thanks to the infinite fire flowers.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 07:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoops, E073-0000-006A-BD4B </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 07:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for trying it. 

By paths, I meant ways to get to the Yoshi. There are steps, the ice path with a hidden vine, going up via the flying beetle, or bouncing up on the koopas then hitting the other vine. From there bounce on Yoshi across the remaining Koopas to the exit. 

This level was mostly made by my friend who doesn't play much Mario. He made it last week and nobody online beat it at all. So today we sat down together and made it a lot better. Still there are randomly placed fireballs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 07:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Walk in the park. I enjoyed the chaos. Never used Yoshi like that before. 

Please try mine:E073-0000-006A-BD4B </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 07:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beat it! It's great. It reminded me of a Zelda puzzle somewhat. 

Please try mine: 60AA-0000-006A-C7C4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 06:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very classic feel. Less is more. Really enjoyed it. 

Please try mine: E073-0000-006A-BD4B  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 06:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donut Mountain did feel like a traditional Mario level. It was the right amount of difficulty and ease. 

Try mine:E073-0000-006A-BD4B </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 06:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Choose Your Fate

E073-0000-006A-BD4B

My friend and I put together a multi-path level. There are four paths that converge at Bowser. Please give us some feedback. We are about to start playing new levels from this thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 00:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goaltending

CEF4-0000-0069-F7E9

Hectic, yet short and sweet. Get past the Magikoopa defensive line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 22:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what you mean, but the idea was to suggest to the player that you bounce off something over the spikes. Most people aren't familiar with kicking the spring into the shell on purpose so I was trying to lead them into that idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 12:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a lot for trying it out. I made a proper post at https://www.reddit.com/r/MarioMaker/comments/3m57xz/pit_of_panga_intro_tutorial/ that details each section. There is video as well of a completion if you don't mind spoiling it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 11:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beaten! Good use of the propeller. Your tips helped me. I had to get by with my mushroom to the end to beat it. 


Please try any of these:

Tough: 20CD-0000-0067-1605 (look below for details on how to beat it)

Easy: 5B64-0000-004D-37E5, CEC1-0000-004E-F127
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 11:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2nd try! Amazing how all these levels are unique. It felt like a real level from the game. 

Please try any of these:

Tough: 20CD-0000-0067-1605 (look below for details on how to beat it)

Easy: 5B64-0000-004D-37E5, CEC1-0000-004E-F127 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 11:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fine work. Just tricky enough. I kept getting to the end and forgetting about the secret block...

Tough: 20CD-0000-0067-1605 (look below for details on how to beat it)

Easy:  5B64-0000-004D-37E5, CEC1-0000-004E-F127 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 10:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whew. Christ. That took me forever. I had to mute Ashley. It wasn't too cheap overall. I liked each challenge, especially the extended door puzzle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 09:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loved the multiple paths without backtracking being necessary. Big plus to me. After the Bowser fight I almost overthought it because I'd blasted the blocks around the door enough that it opened out into the rest of the level. I chose the door, thankfully. 

Please try any of my levels posted right above you ^^^^^^^^^^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 09:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Level Title: Rebounding

ID: 20CD-0000-0067-1605

Description of Gameplay Elements: After impotently hurling my body at Pit of Panga: P-Break yesterday, I decided to create a tutorial level to teach players how to overcome it's first obstacle. You must jump, then kick a shell while in air into a spring and then bounce off the shell and over some spikes. My level helps you build up to it. Let me know if this is helpful or fun at all. I might make other tutorial levels for the seemingly impossible kaizo type challenges that aren't so impossible if you isolate them.

Video: https://youtu.be/SveqwVIOojY

Section 1: Demonstrates bouncing over the spikes on a Bullet Bill.

Section 2: When you kick a shell into the spring, you will notice that is bounces back raised off the ground. In order to pass the wall you will have to bounce off it while it is off the ground. It helps me to have a running start.

Section 3: Similar to the Pit of Panga start but with a walkway underneath to prevent insta-death. Jump, kick the shell at the spring, bounce off it and over the spikes as the shell rebounds toward you.

Section 4: Same thing, but without training wheels.

The End

Thanks a million to /u/musicalpeaches who beat the level and uploaded it to YouTube.

----------------------------
For a far easier challenge, go with:

Stomp the Yard - 5B64-0000-004D-37E5

Or

Hurdling with Yoshi - CEC1-0000-004E-F127

Please leave a comment with an ID so I'll know to play your level!!!!!! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 09:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will. I got much better at it as well once I spent all this time trying to break down the different elements.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 09:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First try! It was nerve wracking, but I hauled ass

Please try my most popular level: 5B64-0000-004D-37E5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 08:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Easy cheese. I've got another easyish one for you: 5B64-0000-004D-37E5
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 08:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somebody beat it and uploaded this video showing how it's done: https://youtu.be/SveqwVIOojY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 08:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn dude, now that was a masterful recreation. It felt like the real deal. I played that level so much that I had it memorized so I recognized all the spots in your level. If I have one critique it'd be to make the next to last wall jump/piranha plant section more difficult because it was a gimme compared to the areas before and after.

Please try my new level. It's tough: 20CD-0000-0067-1605

You may need to watch this video to see how it's done - https://youtu.be/SveqwVIOojY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 08:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for trying it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 08:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beat it after I figured out I could sprint through the first part in one go if I timed it right. Starred it. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 08:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a video that'll show you - https://youtu.be/SveqwVIOojY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 07:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stomp the Yard (Or Headbutt)

ID: 5B64-0000-004D-37E5

I retooled a previous level of mine that was too frustrating to hopefully be more fun. Now it plays more like a tutorial on using the spike helm and boot in conjunction. The old level that only two people beat is 4B70-0000-0041-54D4 for comparison's sake. For it, I was going for a one man army against all odds type thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 07:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a video of the whole thing: https://youtu.be/SveqwVIOojY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 07:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How far did you get? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 07:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Progressively Harder - That last room was worthy of being its own level. I enjoyed it. I hadn't seen something like that before.

Been liking my newest level: 20CD-0000-0067-1605 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 07:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice puzzling level. I eventually figured out where I had to go and spent some time trying to line up a bullet bill that was high enough for me to bounce on... when I accidentally hit the invisible block. 

Please try my level: 20CD-0000-0067-1605 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 07:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great level. Original. I was happy to die a lot while I figured it out. 

Please try mine: 20CD-0000-0067-1605 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 06:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun. Having that many mushroom power ups should be a lesson to us all. Very beatable but still took skill. 

My new level is tough: 20CD-0000-0067-1605 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 06:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The words were hard for me to read until I was back in the menu and saw the level preview screen. I was running along the top so I never saw the other tubes either until the final one once I was forced to fall down, which happened to be the correct choice. 

Please give my new level a shot - 20CD-0000-0067-1605 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 06:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great level. I first tried it somehow but I had to pull some stunts. 

Try: 20CD-0000-0067-1605 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 06:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Level Title: Rebounding

ID: 20CD-0000-0067-1605

Description of Gameplay Elements: After impotently hurling my body at Pit of Panga: P-Break yesterday, I decided to create a tutorial level to teach players how to overcome it's first obstacle. You must jump, then kick a shell while in air into a spring and then bounce off the shell and over some spikes. My level helps you build up to it.
Let me know if this is helpful or fun at all. I might make other tutorial levels for the seemingly impossible kaizo type challenges that aren't so impossible if you isolate them.

Video: https://youtu.be/SveqwVIOojY

Section 1: Demonstrates bouncing over the spikes on a Bullet Bill.

Section 2: When you kick a shell into the spring, you will notice that is bounces back raised off the ground. In order to pass the wall you will have to bounce off it while it is off the ground. It helps me to have a running start.

Section 3: Similar to the Pit of Panga start but with a walkway underneath to prevent insta-death. Jump, kick the shell at the spring, bounce off it and over the spikes as the shell rebounds toward you.

Section 4: Same thing, but without training wheels.

The End

Thanks a million to /u/musicalpeaches who beat the level and uploaded it to YouTube. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 04:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/MarioMaker/comments/3m57xz/pit_of_panga_intro_tutorial/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 04:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a hard concept for sure. I tried to make it as easy as possible. Blame Panga for his diabolical scenario.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 04:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect! How did you video capture this? I'm going to repost this onto the level presentation thread I started earlier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 03:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice, I'm so glad you beat it! I sucked at this yesterday, but now I can get through it more easily as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 03:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Level Title: Rebounding

ID: 20CD-0000-0067-1605

Description of Gameplay Elements: After impotently hurling my body at Pit of Panga: P-Break yesterday, I decided to create a tutorial level to teach players how to overcome it's first obstacle. You must jump, then kick a shell while in air into a spring and then bounce off the shell and over some spikes. My level lets you build up to it.
Let me know if this is helpful or fun at all. I might make other tutorial levels for the seemingly impossible kaizo type challenges that aren't so impossible if you isolate them.

Images / Video: http://i.imgur.com/9UVskum.jpg [1]

Section 1: Demonstrates bouncing over the spikes on a Bullet Bill.

Section 2: When you kick a shell into the spring, you will notice that is bounces back raised off the ground. In order to pass the wall you will have to bounce off it while it is off the ground. It helps me to have a running start.

Section 3: Similar to the Pit of Panga start but with a walkway underneath to prevent insta-death. Jump, kick the shell at the spring, bounce off it and over the spikes as the shell rebounds toward you.

Section 4: Same thing, but without training wheels.

The End

Leave a comment with a Level ID, and I will try your level. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pit of Panga Intro Tutorial </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 03:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Level Title: Rebounding


ID: 20CD-0000-0067-1605


Description of Gameplay Elements: After impotently hurling my body at Pit of Panga: P-Break yesterday, I decided to create a tutorial level to teach players how to overcome it's first obstacle. You must jump, then kick a shell while in air into a spring and then bounce off the shell and over some spikes. My level lets you build up to it. 


Let me know if this is helpful or fun at all. I might make other tutorial levels for the seemingly impossible kaizo type challenges that aren't so impossible if you isolate them. 


Images / Video: http://i.imgur.com/9UVskum.jpg

Section 1: Demonstrates bouncing over the spikes on a Bullet Bill.

Section 2: When you kick a shell into the spring, you will notice that is bounces back raised off the ground. In order to pass the wall you will have to bounce off it while it is off the ground. It helps me to have a running start.

Section 3: Similar to the Pit of Panga start but with a walkway underneath to prevent insta-death. Jump, kick the shell at the spring, bounce off it and over the spikes as the shell rebounds toward you.

Section 4: Same thing, but without training wheels. 

The End

Edit: /u/musicalpeaches beat the level after 38 minutes and uploaded it to YouTube: 

https://youtu.be/SveqwVIOojY

A million thanks for the assist!!! This video is much more helpful than my descriptions above. 








----------------------------------------------------
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 03:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You kick the shell into the spring. It'll bounce off the ground and that's when you jump on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 03:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, I understand. This level was inspired by the virtually impossible Pit of Panga level. The first challenge in it is the final challenge of my level, and I tried to build the player up to it with three sections that ramp up in difficulty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 03:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll probably end up coming back to yours as I don't have all day for trial and error! Also, the second set of wall kicks has a spike the player is blind to. 

Please try mine: 20CD-0000-0067-1605 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 02:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well done, especially for a first level! It took me a bit of trial and error to get to the finish. I like the usage of the sideways spring. 

Please try mine: 20CD-0000-0067-1605 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 02:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha that was fun. It's challenging and gives the player choices. I found the easy route but it took me a few attempts because I kept running into that impossible room.

Please try mine: 20CD-0000-0067-1605 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 02:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now if you could just make the controls sluggish it'd be a perfect remake! Amazing how recognizable that stage is. You should remake the whole game. 

Please try mine: 20CD-0000-0067-1605 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 02:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wall kicking on destroyable blocks is an interesting puzzle. You should make an entire level out of that. Also the piranha plant section was tricky. 

Please try mine: 20CD-0000-0067-1605 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 02:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The spin jumps were the trickiest part, you're right. Still first tried it. It was the right amount of difficulty. 

Please try mine: 20CD-0000-0067-1605 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 02:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First try without being hit! But it was narrrrrrrow at the beginning. Wouldn't change a thing about this level. 

Please try mine: 20CD-0000-0067-1605 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 02:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kick the shell into the spring and bounce on it. It raises off the ground and you bounce off it to get the extra lift. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 01:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi /r/MarioMaker. I'm pretty proud of my newest level because it serves as a tutorial for a type of jump I didn't even know was possible until yesterday. You will learn how to use shells in a new way, so try:

Rebounding

20CD-0000-0067-1605 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 11:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First try. Got lucky sliding along the wall, and I had a power up still that let me strong arm the hammer triplets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 10:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bounce off the Rebound

ID: 156B-0000-0064-0447

Kick the shell into the spring and bounce over. It's that simple. Every Mario player should learn this fundamental skill need for many kaizo levels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every Mario player interested in kaizo levels should add this skill to their repertoire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 07:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Level Title: Bounce off the Rebound

ID: 156B-0000-0064-0447

Description of Gameplay Elements:

Inspired by the unbeaten level Pit of Panga that made headlines today I isolated it's first challenge: kicking a shell into a spring and bouncing over a stack of spikes. I have noticed that a variation of this occurs in many kaizo levels, and it was a skill I'd never learned until today. 

Images / Video:

http://i.imgur.com/mS3XKsq.jpg









----------------------------------------------------
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 06:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bounce off the Rebound

ID: 156B-0000-0064-0447

Kick the shell into the spring and bounce over. It's that simple. Every Mario player should learn this fundamental skill need for many kaizo levels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
