<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3750</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 16:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I even fucking guessed that we were gonna concede in the 58th... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 16:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relax we are gonna concede two in 5 minutes then Totti will score in the 95th from a penalty.

EDIT: WAIT, NO, FUCK I WAS JOKING </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 16:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that flew over my fucking head so badly. Since I have Roma to win and both teams to score on my acca I think the defence is amazing aswell :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 15:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how the fuck did you understand my comment as a dig, so you decided to counter it, but today they are rock solid, so i'd stop mocking them atleast until the 58th minute when inevitably Juan Jesus will score an own goal trying to tie his laces.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 15:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you kinda jinxed it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 22:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah I really phrased it wrong. What gives me hope is just look at the array of center that came from the Balkans, Divac, Pekovic, Vucevic, we can only hope he is as good as them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 21:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I get you, I just posted this as an info, not as a counter argument, sorry if it came across that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 21:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Btw, Zizic had 37 points and 20 rebounds IIRC, in the last game in the Adriatic League.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 14:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didnt he come back from a break down in the first, and won a set? I think it kinda worked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 08:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ziva istina, tesko je prevest sa divnog jezika na ove jednostavne... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 20:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to brag but he is a part of a very brave nation. I could tell you all about the history of Montenegro, but I think that the battle of Mojkovac will tell you all. On the dawn of our christmass, 6,000 Montenegrin fought 20,000 Austrians and Hungarians, just so the Serbian army could safely retreat. Even though the opponents were better armed and had much more people, we won. 
There is a saying in our country that goes "Nikad Crnogorac kukavica nije, smrt ga gleda on se na nju smije", which basically means: "A Montenegrin is never a coward, while death is staring at him he smiles back". Come to think of it the lack of rhyme really diminishes its sounding, bloody english language.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This right here is what I wanted to say, but Im not sure if I delivered the way I thought to. But anyway, to understand the history of our country you have to learn about so many factors that it is just tiring, goddamn you, our vast, incredible history and stunningly beautiful culture overrun by hatred and idiotism!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was WWII, and even though the Partisans which he was a part of fought against the opressors Italy, Germany and Austria, they also fought against Chetniks since their idea of power was to cruel, and too narrow minded. They hated the communists, and thought no matter how much good they do they were still useless. They had a wrong ideology, wanted to take over every single nation here, pretty much the only good thing they did was the fight against the Nazis, and even that was half-done. 
Ustase are definitely worse than them, but they were bad people, filled with hatred to anyone different.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The last photo of edomir "Ljubo" upi, a Montenegrian law student, activist and member of the Communist resistance movement. Here he is smiling, while facing a firing squad, with shackles on his wrists. He was executed moments later by Chetniks for fighting against fascism and nazism. [250x338] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 16:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 21:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just have to remind everyone that the great Toto Di Natale took care of his disabled sister after his death.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 21:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah dont do this to me, when he broke Tomasevics spine twice, a part of me died. He commited crimes against our nation and I wont have a reminder of it on my sanctuary that is reddit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 21:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Milo mi je sto se konacno Joveti isplacuje to sto se bori kao lav za reprezentaciju, jer nekad zna da precera jer oce previse da uradi.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 21:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is from Pe, which is in Kosovo very close to the border with us but has been a part of Montenegro for a big part of history, so he considers himself a Montenegrian.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 16:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but what made him so mad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 15:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont know if I am an idiot, or should have watched the original but what the fuck was Mad Max? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 01:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sent mine away for the weekend and its heaven here. However he left me a couple of "presents" that I didnt notice when I came home first, so I spent half the day cleaning the house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 13:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ma e druze, koji grad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 08:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude where are you from? Since you know pretty much about our basketball if Buducnost was a cant miss opportunity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 16:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I hope my three month old beagle pup grows out of the "doing my best satan impersonation" phase  and grows up into a loving dog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 23:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God I love Donnie Brasco, one of my favourite movies of all time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 14:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a Celtics fan who adores Rondo, so I might be a little biased, but if I were a Bulls fan I would be thrilled to see the ball being brought up in one of the best and safest hands in the league, besides maybe Wall and Irving cause of his skills. Its a joy to see that he isnt hogging and his vision is still there to provide those fast passes, just needs a bit more syncing with the team, other than that I think he will be very good this year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 17:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun fact: Its called 90 mile beach since back in the day people who traveled across it on horses figured out that the time they used up on crossing it would equal to 90 miles, however they failed to account for the sand which significantly slowed the horses down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 15:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its just the number 1 and 2. If i could make him do it outside or atleast show me he wants outside i would be eternally grateful but noo, this little fucker hates my guts apparently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 15:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in apartment thats the issue number one, so its like a 30 second walk to anywhere outside. Second he keeps sniffining litteraly everything, an eating whatever he can fit. He keeps biting me and other stuff, and imma fucking die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 14:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sit command he learned in like 5 minutes as soon as I gave him food... We avoid putting carpets, but it still isnt stopping him. This morning I was awaken by a tongue in my face from the guiltiest dog ever who shat in my closet and peed all over my room.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 14:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this furball but i have like two issues with him. The pooping and peeing inside the house and the fact that i cant get him of my leather sofa. Other than that ill manage just fine, even if i have to fight him every single day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 07:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like im gonna be shooting myself in about a month, thanks anyway!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 21:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can confirm this is true since I didnt understand anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 11:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry man, I guess I forgot to add that its pretty much accurate when it comes to my opinion aswell, those are just the two changes i'd add, my bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 10:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OHB is definitely Gasquet, and with slice i would go with Dimitrov other than that its pretty much accurate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 23:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inter and like half of the French league, especially those twats from Marseille </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 12:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I love clay cause no one can cheat you out of a point, since there is marks everywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 20:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nike vapor zoom aj3 i think </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 19:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since I only have clay courts around my place, if I ever consider playing on them in these shoes my family has strict orders to shoot me in the face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 19:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah i was so excited for them, and then couldnt find them under 400, even that didnt seem to much since i adore the GOAT, but my bank account didnt agree.
I laughed at the guys dying for limited yeezys, like how can you be stringed up so much on fucking sneakers even if they are limited and now a part of my soul is missing cause of these. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is my holy grail, a wish on my bucket list that I'll never cross out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 13:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
