<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1323</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything that's loud = rocket propelled grenade [source](http://imgur.com/a/vXFDk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 11:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not an expert but I have some knowledge of all this. 

Birth certificates, national IDs and Passports all fall in the same family of documents used to identify individuals but with different purposes. 

The birth cert. is a document that proves you exist; that you were born in a certain time and place and to certain people. These details are used to determine your citizenship, age, and, parents. It serves as the starting point of your identity in official records. All govts ensure new-born babies have birth certificates so that they can track the demographics of their population. This is one of the ways that governments are able to know the birth rates, and population growth rates of their countries. Also, when you die, you get a death certificate, which sort of seals the record that was opened with the issuance of your birth certificate. In most places in the world, you cannot use your birth certificate as personal ID, such as when opening a bank account because they can be misused easily, such as the way you just described. 

IDs and passports are expansions of your public record but with different purposes. Passport is easier to explain because all countries have them. A passport is issued for people who are travelling outside their country. You can apply for one even if you are not travelling and use it as your official ID. However, you don't need a passport and the vast majority of people in the world don't have them and never will. Also, in most countries, you pay a fee to receive a passport. This puts it out of reach of most poor people, meaning that you can't reasonably expect everybody to have one.

National IDs serve as an official personal identifying document for adults. This specific document varies across the world. Some countries issue their citizens actual national ID cards when they are 18 years old. Some countries rely on other documents such as driver's licenses and student IDs. In some countries, only the national ID can be used officially. One thing to note, most countries do not recognize IDs issued by other govts, only the passport because the standards for it are international. 

Tl:Dr; 

A birth certificate records your birth and opens your official record. you use this to get other documents.

Passport is a super ID, recognized in all countries and specifically used to travel abroad. You do not need one, if you're not leaving your country.

national IDs: issued by govts to their citizens to identify adults. They vary across the world, and are mostly useless outside your country of residence.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 09:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why "StewJon"? That's not even creative. He could have come up with something that's more astronomy-y like Stewdaris, Stewdarus. Or even better, "Fuck off, Jon" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 11:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Random thought here. I was thinking recently about the end of the world, or human civilization at least, and the question in my mind is "Will it end with a bang or a whimper?" because the way I see it there are two plausible scenarios but we mostly seem to focus on one. 

Scenario 1: This is what most people see, including the religious nuts and Hollywood "creatives" a sudden and rapid succession of events cause the world to end within a very short period, say less than a year. This could be a nuclear war that causes some sort of devastating winter or an apocalyptic weather event. The initial incident destroys much of the human race and civilization. Only a few hundred thousand or million people are left behind but they die off shortly due to the ensuing disease, conflict and famine. Whole process takes 2 years max and has a very clear and distinct trigger that can be identified as the beginning of the end.

Scenario 2: A series of incidents stretched over a great period (at least a decade) that gradually diminish the stability of human civilization, reduce its population and prevent its growth eventually leading to the mass collapse of the human race and causing its extinction. This could be a series of loosely related wars or conflicts, none of which ever reaches the intensity of what most people envision in a nuclear war. Perhaps most of these conflicts will be slow and boring wars that fail to capture the interest of global viewers for long enough, preventing the attainment of any lasting solution. Then these conflicts increase the social, political and economic pressures on even those countries that arent involved. Refugees keep flooding into Europe; illegal arms keep moving into African states; the economy slows down in Asia; paranoid governments across the globe increase restrictions on civilians; angry civilians respond with mass violence and civil disobedience and paranoid govts. increase their restrictions further. This sequence of events continues until human civilization as we know it is over and the last remaining survivors are finished off by extreme weather, geological events and yet more conflict. And maybe the spark that triggered this devastating sequence of events dates back to December 2012.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 09:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The mimic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
