<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2482</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 19:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My ex constantly calls me fat as an insult whenever we interact.  

I never understood that, and still don't...because she was about 350 lbs when we were married.  She ended up getting gastric bypass surgery, and now weighs about 100 lbs.

Why someone that once weighed that much would make fun of someone else that is heavy just confirms to me why she's my ex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 18:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  but we don't do well on grass.

Speak for yourself! ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 18:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> +1 for C C </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 06:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Malnutrition](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Malnutrition) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Rant] Help with scale! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 16:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I already had one of those fancy-schmancy body measuring scales for at least two years...but once I started keto, I realized how inaccurate it was.  (Yes, I did all my weighing on a hardwood floor, stable surface)

It would give vastly different weights from one measurement to the next, even taken right next to each other 10 seconds apart.  I'm talking 10lbs differences.

I ended up getting rid of it, because I couldn't trust it, and bought a halfway decent electronic glass scale without all the bells and whistles...but I don't trust it now either!  Over the past week, it's been giving be wildly different results, down 10 lbs one minute, up 10 lbs literally one minute later.

TL:DR - Can anyone suggest a reliable, dependable scale for me to purchase...that you have experience with already and that hasn't failed you?  I'd really appreciate it!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 20:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohhh, ohhhh!  Or, a years' subscription to a meat of the month club...in honor of Keto.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 19:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about a premium spa package?  Can include a note saying you hope to make her feel even a small percentage of the happiness she allowed you to feel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 19:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Married for two years....
She was taken to hospital three years ago "When she was young"...

Hmmm, something fishy here. =) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 17:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am surprised that Trump didn't offer a cabinet position to Snowden. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 17:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG.  I've been lurking here and reading for a LONG time...and I always wondered what the heck the Discovery Channel Shark Week had to do with anything, and why people always talk about the end of it.   

*lighbulb!!!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 17:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No doubt!  Buy that man/woman a thoughtful gift! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 15:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Why is it America's job to defend Eastern Europe?

It's not.  It's America's job to uphold our agreement to support NATO, like all members in it are supposed to do.

When Trump gives a tiny middle finger to NATO when they ask for help with aggressive Russian Expansion, we will become pariahs in the international community and no one will trust us any longer.  

It will go downhill from there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 22:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Much of it is mental.

After I started, I thought I was hungry, but then when I distracted myself and thought about it a little later, I realized I wasn't hungry any more.  

In my opinion, I was so used to eating all the time, and so much, I think that my brain was telling me that I SHOULD be hungry.

Now, when I (think I) feel hungry, I just do a quick self reflection and realize that I'm hungry because I'm BORED...and when I get back to not being bored, I quickly forget I was hungry.  Living decades with eating when I'm bored is a hard habit to break. =) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 22:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, don't chickens lay an egg a day?  So you're getting three eggs a day?  That seems eatable! =D  

I might be wrong about the eggs/hen/day though...I'm just guessing. =) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 21:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a recently retired Navy guy, my advice to you is...

Find a better partner to hold your ankles, if you catch my drift. =)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 21:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YEssssssss.  I have wanted a stick blender for so long!  Now I have a reason to go get one! =D  Thanks, that sounds fantastic! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 21:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take a low-carb tortilla or two, heat it up dry in a skillet until it's stiffer...spread a layer of guac over it, give it a sprinkle of shredded cabbage for a little texture and crunch in the bites....some shakes of hot sauce on it.  Mmmmmm, and you'll fit in with everyone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 20:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha, yes, thanks for sharing!  Also just ordered.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 19:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  it smells like someone's brewing coffee in the next room all the time

I could live with that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 19:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck!  Make us all proud!  

*haha, feels like I'm rooting for the home team* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 19:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they ask, I sure will. =)

A couple people in my life have asked about my recent weight loss, though, and when I describe it, and tell them what I eat, they immediately write it off as being faddish and unhealthy.  

The food industry has a chokehold on societal norms for what works and what doesn't, for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 19:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great story, thank you for sharing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 19:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your story!  That was a great read and very uplifting.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 17:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't feel right about it.  It almost feels like the professor is giving a test, and I have the answer key.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 17:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't feel very ethical doing that. =( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Office is having a weight-loss competition! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 16:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just got an email this morning, one of the ladies in the office is putting together a $10 buy-in weight loss competition to run for 12 weeks, with the winner receiving a gift card in the amount of money that is collected.  (Determined by % of total weight lost)

Holy cow, they don't stand a chance against this keto guy! ;)

I actually feel it's unfair, personally, so I emailed back and asked if I could just join the competition in a non buy-in fashion...and not be eligible for the prize if I won, but more as a "public" way to hold myself accountable.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 21:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome NSV. =D   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 19:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa. That is drool-worthy!  

What kind of nutritionals are in that one burrito?  Cals/Carbs/Protein/Fat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 19:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the contrary..."most of the people" are NOT gluten sensitive or allergic.  We're talking less than 5% of the population.

Granted, for those few people, avoiding Gluten does help.  However, for the extremely vast majority of people, Gluten has no effect on them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 18:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I...uh...don't even heat them. *blush*  I just eat them like they're jerky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...I'm sorry...SAD?  Huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 17:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I claim no political party.  I was just pointing it out.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 17:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're supposed to leave those at home in a jar on the table, and only take them out for special occasions! =) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With the election result, now might be a good time to invest in Twitter, since it will be relevant for at least four more years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 17:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 16:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I will also add that I was very happy to vote for someone who has not been in politics for his entire life. 

President Obama was new to politics.  In fact, one of the largest Republican criticisms towards President Obama in 2008 was that he had no political experience.  
Cut to 2016...and now Republicans are touting having no political experience as a virtue.  

Consistent much? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 16:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did you drop? =) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 15:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so glad that I can't find any Halo Top around me.  I would find it hard to maintain my calorie deficit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 15:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I (personally) wouldn't eat those...I don't trust the Sugar Alcohol.  My opinion of course. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 15:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are at the Walmart near me as well, in the produce section, of all places.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 14:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But lan told me to do it!  Blame lan. =( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: Mr. Trump is the oldest U.S. President ever elected into a first term. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 14:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 18:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I know the feeling!  I just (had to) chipped in $22 for an office-wide catered lunch we're having in a week in a half.  It's from an Italian place, and there isn't one single keto-friendly item on the menu.  I plan on just mingling with a small plate and push the food around, and then leave it without actually eating anything.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Rant] Keto PSA for Scale Pics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 21:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 21:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait...how did you find out about the magazine we found!?  =) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 21:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can lose weight by not restricting calories, yes, but it requires an expenditure of energy...i.e. exercise.  

So, essentially, if you eat at maintenance calorie level, but you exercise to burn calories, you will lose weight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 21:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hard to believe...but once you are fully in ketosis, you will be surprised at how easy it is to not indulge in those things you currently crave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 21:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not about the keto, it's that she doesn't feel like her opinions matter to him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 19:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Firstly, you are doing great, and the difference between your pictures is very dramatic.

Secondly, 
 but just remember that your body is like a showcase to show people how committed you are to your health and well-being.

I couldn't agree less.  That is a thought process that leads to eating disorders and an unhealthy body image.  

If *your* reason to lose weight is to showcase yourself for others, that's perfectly fine...but just know that not everyone shares that mindset. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 18:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't leave that mess lying around!  What kind of tournaments!?  =) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NSV] Outback restaurant and getting your hands dirty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 18:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took both of my kids to Outback this past weekend, because a) They've never been, and b) Steak!

I completely forgot about the bread they bring you before the meal!!!
I used to LOVE that bread.  

I was able to cut slices of the bread, spread butter on them, and hand them to my kids and see their expression of happiness at how yummy it was, and I still didn't have the urge to eat any myself.
Thank you ketosis!

Since you're wondering, I had the Filet Mignon with a side of grilled asparagus, and a Blue Cheese Wedge Side Salad. =) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 18:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must...resist...saying...that...210 minus 180 is 30...not 20.

Damn, I didn't resist hard enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 19:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you find out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 19:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The IRS apparently ruled her name as a "commercial asset" to her estate, so that's how they get away with it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 19:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My kids would love to make that a weekly trip to a local parking lot where hundreds of birds like to hang out, and let them have a feast. =)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: V.C. Andrews died 30 years ago, after having published only 7 books. Because her name sold books so well, her ghostwriter has published over 80 books in her name since her death. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 19:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 16:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the way to trick of treat with the kiddos, I just grabbed a Keto McDouble from McDonalds (and they got their normal food).  Held me over through the night of walking, and all the way until breakfast this morning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 16:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I might tend to agree with you ashelia, taken out of context in their relationship.

The fact is, however, that there are many things we do or don't do in a relationship with a significant other in order to make things run more smoothly.  Compromise, if you will.

Context means alot.  Consider a wife that doesn't drive after sundown, "because my husband doesn't like it."  Taken out of context, that might sounds abusive to her.  
What if the truth is that he had a traumatic accident himself due to night-related incidences, and instead of triggering his PTSD by driving at night, she chooses of her own accord to help him feel better by not driving at night?  Not so abusive anymore...now it's a loving compromise.  

Context! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 17:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  and butcher chicken yourself

I don't think that means what you think it means. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 15:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!  I've never been before, and now I know what to look for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 21:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you get at Boston market? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 20:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish people would stop using cavemen, etc as examples of great eating.

A caveman was also lucky to live to be 20 years old.  

I'd prefer to not compare my eating to a caveman, thank you very much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
