<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1863</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The history of student loans goes back to the Middle Ages - and there used to be a literal chest for collateral </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 14:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 14:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really, really, really long, but Robert Caro's biography of Lyndon Johnson is amazing.  If you don't have the months to work through all of them, the most recent volume (detailing how he succeeded Kennedy and his brilliant maneuvering to pass the Civil Rights Act) stands alone.

I'd also second Donald's Lincoln.  I'm not a big fan of  McCullough's Truman. It seemed to me to spend too much time on early life and not enough on his presidency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TDIH March 17, 1946: Jackie Robinson played in his first integrated game, a spring training tryout in segregated Florida (he went 0-3) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 14:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 14:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The author is a professor at Indiana University-Purdue University Indianapolis and the author of a book on this subject. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jackie Robinson played his first integrated game 70 years ago today, during Spring training tryouts in segregated Florida (he went 0-3) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 14:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 14:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do people feel the need to write political obituaries for him already? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 14:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oops, forgot the source:
We also found that some self-treaters are the using a helminth called the rat tapeworm (Hymenolepis diminuta), which sounds truly disgusting. However, people are using this helminth because it is inexpensive and easy to produce, and may provide a very effective treatment for a range of inflammation-related diseases, including migraine headaches and depression. People eat them and report that about 30 worms per month does the job, although the number varies depending on the individual.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that some people swallow rat tapeworms, up to 30 a month, to treat a range of inflammation-related diseases, including migraines, with some success </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 13:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 13:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From a researcher who studies relationships between inmates and correctional employees:
 Some inmates have told me that they prefer to establish inappropriate relationships with staff members who they perceive as unattractive, overweight or sexually frustrated.
One inmate, Oscar, explained to me that these types of employees are easy to control and manipulate.

We like single, older women who are basically tossed out and nasty, he said, before claiming that women who are neglected in the free world will be worshiped by inmates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL male prisoner often target their advances at female prison employees they view as unattractive, overweight or sexually frustrated, in order to have inappropriate relationships </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 13:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 16:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe not Pamela Anderson, but [others](http://www.stcatharinesstandard.ca/2015/11/15/deer-hunt-draws-demonstrators-on-both-sides) [do](http://www.bostonherald.com/news/local_coverage/2015/11/animal_activists_try_to_stop_blue_hills_deer_hunt) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 16:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because a person with a hispanic name can't conduct research? Pew is one of the most reputable survey organizations out there - if you read the report, you can look at their entire methodology and the detailed responses.  If you see bias in the methodology, then go ahead and assert it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 13:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We can trace it back to another success story. With the passage of the Marine Mammal Protection Act in 1972, seal and sea lion populations began to rebuild along the West Coast. White sharks eat seals and sea lions, and having more of their favorite food available enabled them to make a comeback, too.

TI-also-L that the shark increase is slower than we think:
If it seems that theyre turning up in ever greater numbers, its because incidents are more visible now: there are more of us and were all ready with our smartphones, capturing and sharing footage whenever someone yells Shark! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the increase in Great White Sharks is due to the success in protecting seals and sea lions, which the sharks eat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 13:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 22:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you read the article? Apparently not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 15:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pope Pius XII, who some critics say remained silent during the Holocaust, played a pivotal role in coordinating covert spy operations and efforts to take down Adolf Hitler, a US author says.

Author Mark Riebling's new book, Church of Spies: The Popes Secret War Against Hitler,  
unveils a series of plots and acts of espionage involving Pope Pius that sought to bring down the tyrannical Nazi regime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pius XIIs covert war against the Nazis and Hitler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 15:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's time for economists to measure 21st century aging with 21st century tools </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 15:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 13:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  At the University of Florida in Gainesville in 1924, Ku Klux Klan members (including the citys mayor and police chief) kidnapped and castrated a Catholic priest serving the small group of Catholic students there. They believed that the priest was converting Protestant students to Catholicism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
