<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2159</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 16:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because Kagero became the awkward stepchild of the IJN DD line doesn't mean the whole game has gone to shit, my friend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 15:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were simply trying to make Kagero into the same playstyle they're trying to make Shimakaze with high risk high reward. It does it worse than shima, of course, but it's not a T11 ship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 15:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've stated this many times to others, but Gearing and Fletcher are not the contributing torpedo soup because of their quantity, damage, and speed of torpedoes. They still need to get closer to the enemy which puts them into counterable range where teamwork can take them out. 

If and by hotkey counters you mean radar, it's funny because in our scrims a few teams have tried to use radar ships but generally it's incredibly difficult to use it effectively if the enemy team plays well as it is hard to get cruisers into range and have enough firepower to take out DDs in time. From my perspective, most changes they've made to game make teamwork better, which I can't complain about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 15:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kagero is still the stealthiest ship on the sea, which counts for a lot. The inability to counter hovering planes is also a problem for the other two DD lines as well unless you're an AA spec US DD. I still don't see the problem. Use teamwork and get your CV to help out and/or get closer to friendly ships. 

Edit - it seems you changed your whole post since I saw it and started my reply </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 15:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Destroyers kinda need to be hard to play or they'd be ridiculous. In competitive play, countering the enemy destroyers is generally the hardest thing to do as they play close to the fleet and it's hard to get cruisers into good range of them so you have to use a combination of your DDs + air cover to neutralize them. I don't really see the problem with this, tbh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 15:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand what is wrong with what DM said that you find game quitting worthy. Explain? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 22:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As silly as it is to buy headphones without doing appropriate research, people finding it helpful that this guy points out a lack of noise cancellation is them doing appropriate research. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 22:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And extremely poor maneuverability. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 16:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kiev doesn't use smoke much anyway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 00:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> damn that LP is bass from start to finish  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 22:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is some MLG shit guys, come check it out it's fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 20:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be nice for like a small credit boost because you know we're plundering shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 20:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks good, nice job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 20:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta be a mod to do that. Iku couldn't hammer a fly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 19:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For sure. Atago is still used though. It's good at doing things solo like pushing side caps and flanking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 18:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Video? Replay? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 18:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> warships.today is also my suggestion. They have a WTR score that measures overall performance per ship really well and good leaderboards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 16:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the AA is insane.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 16:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right, mostly. It's pretty strong though. I play in competitive clan vs clan stuff and Kutuzov is the most used cruiser, even more than Atago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 15:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's likely the 3 second penalty is an intentional nerf to smoke, SA being bugged is another story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 15:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well there's a good chance that the 3 second penalty is an intentional nerf to smoke, so I'd learn how to play with it. Whether SA being bugged for it is intended is another story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 15:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kutuzov is so strong I doubt they'll sell it again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 14:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fucking sneaky like m8 I run by you and you be doing double takes on the wind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 13:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh hell yeah Tirptiz is back up for sale too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 13:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea why but you're absolutely right that an i5 is enough for 99.9% of games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 13:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You won't just be detected out of nowhere. It's mainly to do with going offense smoke.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 13:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ITT - anecdotes 

Pics? Video evidence? These are what we need to figure out what is going on, not story time by the campfire.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 13:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was probably just not in smoke all the way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 21:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listen up, girl, I was banging pigs in the shed out behind my father's coffee shop before your mother even thought about which lucky guy she was going to hold hands with in preschool. Now I could stick around here and tell you about the time we first had tryouts to determine whether you were worthy of reproduction but between all the video games and tax write offs I'm getting as a result of the government wanting me to keep my mouth shut on this shit, I don't have time for dealing with the kinda folks that wouldn't have made it past the first round. You would have been left to hanging upside from that bobogola tree in our south Africa camp just like those other 8 year olds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 21:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think Blizzard is trying to distract people from anything. They are offering exactly what you see and if you like the maps and movespeed and match length of TF2 better than Overwatch than boy do I have a great game suggestion for you..... try TF2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 20:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TF2 also has much bigger maps iirc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 20:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I bet it's clear looking through those red shift issue glasses you got with your recurring subscription to "I Have Shit Taste Monthly." This country really took a turn for the worse when we started allowing mothers with a history of being mentally disabled to raise kids like you. I miss the days we used to slip those dull green pills into the coffee of those we didn't like, making the reproduction of this country one that focuses on quality and not quantity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 20:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Other fps don't have teleports and hero size difference and special abilities and supports that buff movespeed and dash moves and jetpacks and wallrunning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 20:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of the fast characters are already very hard to shoot and the there is Lucio who can buff movespeed. If heroes were faster this would be absolutely crazy. I think the movespeed is very balanced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 18:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to play 100 hours to be good enough at the game to not be part of the clusterfuck, same as everyone else. If a game's skill ceiling is so low that it doesn't take time to get good that's a huge negative imo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 16:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I tested, firing guns or not did not change the 3 second smoke penalty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 16:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's as much of a PSA with twice the amount of misinformation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 16:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I see in that thread was a bunch of anecdotal evidence of that one time someone was spotted for 4 minutes and pinpoint accuracy and such and such. I wanted to make a thread of what I tested as real world application of how these changes are affecting playstyle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 16:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah I see. Very good to know but this still won't change the length of this penalty to being in smoke lasting longer than 3 seconds from what I can tell. Hopefully war gaming are working on this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 15:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see nothing in that thread that backs up such a statement as server discrepancy causing 3-20 seconds of difference for this penalty. Am I missing something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA - There is a 3 second penalty to going undetected in smoke </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 15:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen a lot of talk about the Situational Awareness bug and the changes to spotting. There have been a few changes to the way that debuffs are applied but I have not done much testing on these. What we did test however is the most relevant change which is a 3 second penalty to going undetected in smoke which is NOT REPORTED BY SITUATIONAL AWARENESS. We tested this last night and confirmed it that for 3 seconds after SA reports you being invisible in smoke, the enemy can still see you. 

Sometimes it feels like it is longer than 3 seconds but you have to keep in mind that if you pop in and out of smoke a couple times (from slowing down or such) the penalty is applied every time. So you have to be careful at what speed you are going when smoking. 

As an aside, it was tested in a Benson that you could not go 1/4 speed while remaining fully undetected setting up the smoke. I don't remember it being like this before but I am not 100% sure this is a change and not anecdotal. 

Edit - It is worth pointing out that among all the confusion about SA being bugged the only time we have found SA to be reporting inaccurately is for this smoke penalty. In every other case it seems SA is working fine, but if someone finds something else wrong please let me know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 15:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not longer than 3 seconds. It's been tested by more than anecdotal observation. If you pop in and out of smoke though, the 3 second penalty gets applied every time which would make it seem longer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 13:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's more of a nerf to using smoke screens that simply a spotting mechanic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 13:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All these reports of it being an extra 10 or 20 seconds are exaggerated. It's a 3 second penalty to entering smoke. Been tested a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 13:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did some testing with this last night. It seems there is a 3 second penalty to entering smoke and a 2-3km penalty for being on fire. SA simply doesn't report those extra 3 seconds in smoke. Is there more to this bug than that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 00:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What an amazing picture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 21:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah man fuck everyone for liking something you don't like. It's only popular because of bourgeois propaganda anyway not because it's good or anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 19:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kripp? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 17:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, because the consistency of full pens and citadel hits will make up for the fewer amount of shells. MK has the biggest cruiser citadel for the tier as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 15:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good write up. Though , as someone with over 100 games played in the MK, I would not want to fight a heavy cruiser 1v1. Especially a hipper. Unless they are just giving you broadside at 8km, MK AP shells don't citadel other cruisers very well. If I have to engage a heavy cruiser at 12km+, I'll probably lose.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 15:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blizzard is notorious for over nerfing things in every game they make. And rarely if ever do they go back and buff them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 23:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That said I cut everyone a lot of slack at low levels because everyone is bad and new.

-subject2159  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 23:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such a high quality shitpost getting this few amount of upvotes speaks to the disconnect I have with this sub. However, I do not take this as a loss. I see the prospect of a world filled with shitposts and it fills me with determination. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 23:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's not unfair to say that some games can have a reasonable expectation of other player's participation of the game's meta.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 20:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just playing the game involves picking a good comp. I mean pubs are a little more care free, sure, but the entire point of the game is a good comp and team coordination. If you don't want to participate in that then you're going to be ruining other people's attempt at playing correctly. That said I cut everyone a lot of slack at low levels because everyone is bad and new. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 19:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its dat boi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comprehensive guide to effective T10 strategy. Steps by steps for all classes! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 18:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all know that T10 gameplay offers diverse and interactive teamplay. But it can be a bit daunting and counter-intuitive for new players to succeed in waters saturated with T11 ships. And now that T10 is much more affordable to play and more players than ever are getting there, this comprehensive guide should help many players. 

~~Step 0 - sell your T10 ships and play something more fun~~

Step 1 - Get your mind right. This is serious boating action you better fuckin be serious about it.

Step 2 - Play a T11 ship. Balanced ships are bad ships. Go OP or go home and teach those Montana's what it means to actually be the top tier. 

Step 3 - Group up with a division and do coordinated shit. 

~~Step 4 - When you start getting shot at blame your teammates.~~

Lemme start over. I'm getting side tracked. 

Step 1 - When the match starts, don't do anything for 10 minutes. He who pushes first dies. The enemy will get impatient and start trickling in. You can snowball from here.

~~Step 2 - If you bring an Erie, MM will compensate your team with more T10 ships.~~

Ugh sometimes I really don't even.

~~Step 1 - If the enemy has the DD advantage you've probably already lost unless there are huge amount of potato.~~

FUCK

Step 1 - If your team starts pushing before that 10 minute mark, cuss them out but I guess you may as well join them because fuck it you're about to lose anyway. 

Step 2 - It turns out that planes are really good in this game for spotting and helping control caps. You should think about picking up CVs  ~~and actually being useful for once for your team.~~

Step 4 - Be nice to your teammates. Chances are they are people too in most cases and people are pretty cool. I mean we're probably all going to die in a couple decades to massive weather changes caused by global warming #bushdid9/11 so just have fun fam

Eh, good enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 17:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's all good man you made a good point too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 16:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll give it an upvote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 16:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's more that Potatoes made the statement "shima only has 33% more torpedoes " which is a fault statement that I was correcting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 16:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Myokos should have that 10 out of 10 times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 15:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The forced humor is a deal breaker for me personally. It might be hard to imagine that good gameplay can be overshadowed by this but holy shit guys this is just childish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 14:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I was mod I would have so many flags in here people would be like "holy shit this selection of flags is impressive and I am struggling to pick which is my favorite because of the overwhelming quantity of flag choices given by this subreddit moderator team" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 14:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fuck is a vibe? We got mother fuckers vibrating in this thread? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 13:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excuse me, captain shitnuts, I am always respectful when I talk to others.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 06:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No no my friend. 10 to 15 is 50% more. Check the mathsss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 01:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 00:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its tru fam </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 00:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gearing's ability to nuke ships is far less (especially from far away) than the Shima because of the reasons I stated. If you do not understand this then you should probably just give up on Warships and play something new, to be completely 100% honest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 00:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the Gearing takes out all the enemy DDs in the first couple minutes than fucking kudos to him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 00:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you are going a little crazy tbh. Who said anything about the Gearing having better torps than Shima? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 23:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shima has 50% more torpedoes that do more damage. So yeah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 23:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are stating unfounded opinions on T10 balance without any experience yourself at what the implications these ships have on how matches play out then yes. You are a fool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 23:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> T8 gameplay is drastically different from T10 gameplay. Maybe you would know this if you actually had a few T10 ships.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 23:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not only do the ships play very different, the meta from T8-T10 changes drastically which alters the influence that different ship classes have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 23:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I don't feel like spending too much time addressing this but a combination of torpedo speed, damage per torpedo, and quantity of torpedoes makes your argument of

All of your points are also not exclusive to Shimakaze.

false. 

And you've had the reasons why these arguments are false explained to you before, hence the downvoting and moving on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 23:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ship's ability to influence the match goes beyond their statistical damage numbers and average damage. Especially for a ship like a super stealth DD.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 23:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't you say you would contact me before making any posts regarding game balance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 21:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Besides poor ROF, everything else about the guns is quite strong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 21:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's more that you're rarely the top tier. And it's even more that T10 gameplay itself is yawn inducing skilless frustration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 21:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't drink and reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 20:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember now why I avoided commenting on politics on reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 20:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ffs this is too much meta tbh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 19:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has nothing to do with pandering as Sander's stance has been the same regardless of demographic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 18:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clinton is for whatever the current demographic she is speaking to is for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 18:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 18:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 15:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still a welcome event.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 15:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because T10 meta is so boring and now everyone and their mother can spam T10 games. Makes T8 ships suck to play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 14:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh the only bundle that was like that that I can remember was the Tirptiz. Everything else was reasonable. I remember the Lo Yang bundle cost the same as base T8 Prem price $50 but came with a couple extra things and people were still bitching about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 14:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice events. Commander skill reset event? Wonder how that'll work.

And booo at T10 still being discounted. Guess another month of me not playing T8. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 14:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But but mah bundles are cancer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 13:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So fucking stupid  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 13:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Different regions, different markets, different economies, different player base sizes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 13:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty rare since NA can't see other servers ships. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 13:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh the first salvo missed and could have very well been random fire. The second salvo you were detected right before he fired. This kind of stuff has happened loads of time before this patch. Not conclusive evidence imo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 13:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buying games from actual good developers is the best thing to do for the game's Industry. Don't know what you're talking about. Just because Ubisoft goes to the shits and people stop buying their games isn't bad for the industry. Good thing really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 01:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try out some BBs. It's good to play different classes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 00:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing news worthy here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 15:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Torn Banner's problem is when they release controversial balance changes dumbing the game down then go AWOL for 9 months come back to a dead game then try to salvage it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 15:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure you know how children work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 02:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right, I was being unreasonable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 00:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If what was the plan? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 23:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it could vary player to player. Even in games that require quick reaction times, this can be offset by having better game sense and preparing yourself for what you expect to happen. That said, reaction times don't slow that much until you get much older than 30 on average. Just doing some quick research I see a lot saying it goes up at like 40+. But of course this will vary person to person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 23:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I don't even know what's not to like about it. I didn't even give any odd opinions or anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 22:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I said at the start.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 22:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their player base is already dying quickly. Probably why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 21:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be very surprised if it was any different than you say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 20:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now you're using your head. Best tag me as "is probably right". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 20:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The slow USN torps hit less often and less hard per torp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 20:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DPS numbers from stat sheets don't tell the whole story and do not represent how they end up playing. In competitive, we use all 3 DDs interchangeably depending on how we want to play the map and Fubuki definitely satisfies the torp role far better than Benson because of the speed and spread and distance of the tops. We even use Tashkents depending on the map as a DD killer fleet escort for 10km fleet brawls. Everything has its place right now, this thread is full of misinformation and a lack of understanding of the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 20:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to stop commenting on balance to be completely honest. You've been wrong every time I've ever seen you give any opinion on balance changes. I know this is rude but you're just being foolish every comment in this thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 20:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And giving it attention only encourages it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 19:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah realistic overweight Americans in our fantasy polish RPGs. GG SJW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 18:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it is. Unless you're sitting still full broadside at 4km from a cruiser. Even then I don't there's enough alpha not including damage saturation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 17:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I know they're really different but it just doesn't seem smart timing for the release date. I want to play Battleborn too but I'm worried it's just going to suffer tremendously from Overwatch. And healthy populations are the key for these games and ranked match making.

Edit - don't know why I'm being downvoted for this, I'm simply stating a concern. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
