<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2469</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 17:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think names would be OK though I'm not sure...but avoid revealing personal info such as birthdays, address or anything that could give away your location.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> See with you soul, Anastajsa a., Digital painting, 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 21:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 21:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an art channel so it's easier for me to make videos because I just record my drawing process. My final drawings are what matter the most to me so once I upload the video to youtube, I delete all my recordings so that I always have more space on my computer. I wait a bit before deleting though, for example 1 week or 2  because sometimes I'd want to re-use them in new video edits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 08:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it is important to get those, it diversifies your traffic and it can only help for more views. However the downside is that you have to be very active on those as well to get people, if you have too many platform to handle, it's a matter of how much time do you have to handle them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drawing challenge day 5: Painting in Sakimichan's style </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 20:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Under the shade (part 1) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 10:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OC] Under The Shade (part 1) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 09:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Under the shade, Digital Painting, 200MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 18:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 10:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> have fun ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 10:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'r welcome, have a nice day/night too :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 09:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really understand youtube ranking system, but I'm pretty sure I heard from Derral Eves that likes and dislikes are healthy for your channel, he is pretty famous for youtube video consulting...in fact when someone like or even dislike, it shows that your video is engaging, because the people took the time to rate it. Therefore, it will help your video ranking. It's just the personal experience of the viewers who rate that is affected. I don't think you should remove rating, even if you get tones of dislikes, but you can always experiment :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 07:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think like and dislike are meant for personal user experience...if someone likes your video, then youtube is likely to suggest them some more of your video in their personal recommendations. If someone dislikes your video, youtube will take the information into account and they will not receive anymore of your video on their personal recommendation, perhaps they will not even receive similar video to your and it will be like that until they initiate the search themselves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 03:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we are on the same boat my friend but be grateful for the active subscribers. I guess the 4% is not fixed people because at some point youtube is supposed to remove the really inactive subs, so I think that people watch some videos but not ALL the uploads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Challenge day 3: Drawing in Sakimichan's style </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 19:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 12:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd suggest to first try to get less broke XD ... depending on what you are aiming for, there are tones of advices that you can google and on youtube. Don't only aim for what's cheap, because you may end up buying more cheap stuff in quantity and end up spending more than when you buy something more expensive with higher quality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Art Journey 2 (2014), Traditional, 50MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 09:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Challenging myself to draw in Sakimichan't style [day 1] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 08:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 08:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome, there are some subjects that are in my opinion avoided, I don't know exactly why, maybe people don't see the need to give relevant advices on them or people are afraid of giving the wrong advice. For example about google adSense, I've made some research about it and it seems to me that google takes users responsible for invalid adclicks and therefore they advice people to learn how to use google analytics to section the traffic, but it was so complicated for me to understand...so some tips about that would be for example helpful in my opinion. But that's only an example, and you should probably do more research. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 05:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well it could work since you have 1m+ subscribers...I'd say I could be interested and then follow up for a few months, I'll follow the ideas and then see it it works. But I'd be disappointed if it's not working and I'll just stop the subscription...the one factors for you to take into account is to give something that would be best for anybody. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 05:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used google AdWords, but I'm no longer sure if sharing my experience is a good idea, mainly because I have spent a lot and didn't go boom as I was expecting. I reached 1K subs but subscriber viewership is really poor, bellow the average 7%. Now I'm reflecting upon my actions. You will not get the results in few days, some ads are gonna do well and some not, for me it took a year with a constant, non-stop daily budget. All I can say is that it's really risky, but I don't regret anything considering that I've seen some people took almost 10 years to reach 1K subs, and I did it in one year using adwords. I could elaborate more on my methods, but if you want to take it at your own risk, pm me to ask for the details. The best is still to grow organically, get people who are really interested in your channel to subscribe so that your sub viewership don't go this poor :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 00:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much for sharing your experience...I think that's a better idea, I did a test today and I was quite struggling with the internet...it was awkward...I couldn't properly focus on what I was doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 13:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you w  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finally hit 1K so I made a special thank you video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 08:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 20:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be trying out several topics and I'm not expecting anything huge...though if anything turns out well, I'll be sure to make some tips   tricks about it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 20:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just responding to you saying "no one is really THAT interesting" ... not really talking about myself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 18:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure that if popular artists like sakimichan or yuumei go and do something like this, there will be people staying even for one week life streaming ;)...or I am too out of date and other artists are more popular now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 18:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahaha, the goal is not to have people stay there for 15 hours...but I though I might have several people passing by and checking my stuff out, and since everyone don't log in at the same time, maybe I'll get more people that way...Thanks for the advice though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 16:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahaha....thanks for the tips </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] Does anyone know if life streaming on youtube for a long period time is beneficial for a channel? has anyone tried this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 11:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello all,
I'm planning on doing some crazy life streaming that last more than 15 hours with regular breaks if my internet and computer don't give up on me in the meantime. Basically, I'll do some really long and detailed digital paintings. I'll do it no matter what the outcomes but I'm just curious to know if anyone think it's gonna be beneficial. I'm also a bit exited about it, it will feel like painting in the middle of the street while people comes by and go as they please. What is your experience if you had already tried this? otherwise what do you think is the most efficient way of life streaming? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Princess 1K, Digital Painting, 200MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 20:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 18:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a round and round vicious cycle, just like "egg before chicken or chicken before egg" ... though I know some people gain weight naturally because of the way their body function so they are fat no matter what they eat :-/ ... and some other people are skinny no matter what they eat :-/ ... Well, I think the essential is to stay as healthy as possible :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bussiness Man, Digital Painting, 200MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 09:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 06:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's really awesome, good job :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 19:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lovely cat w, awesome drawing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 18:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow, amazing indeed, you must have kept perseverance...good luck with your new idea then  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 18:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That I don't know, given the fact that you work very well on both, I guess they'd have the same chance, and all depends on the type of content you have </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 17:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can always have as many channel as you want but you have to check it your time allows you to have two, taking care of one is already a huge work. BTW: Congratulations for hitting 2000 subs in two years, must have been an awesome journey ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 10:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how exciting, I hope you enjoy your photography training :) ... not all photography is art for me, for example I cannot consider a passport photo as a piece of art XD, but I've seen some photography that holds so much emotion so I guess that's the idea of artistic photography. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 08:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> beautiful, I don't understand the language but thanks for showing...you use it's acrylic colour, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 08:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> right isn't it, I'm feel like I'm already working really hard but can never reach his level w </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Storm, webang111, Digital Painting, 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 18:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Businessman [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 18:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Green hair [watercolor #1] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 14:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Green hair, watercolor, 500M </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 06:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yoko Littner (Gurren Lagann) Fanart practice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 12:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 10:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never had a one hit, I still can't figure out how to get organic views using keywords and SEO ... everyone is talking about that but I've been trying out everything I could... I think your friend should exploit that video getting 25K views, make some variants of it and make more video on the same topic, maybe he will break his record again :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stuck at school on a summer day [final], Digital painting, 200MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 07:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 18:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> obviously the idea of a gaming channel is to release game related videos...there is no recipe of how to stick out in a saturated field, in fact all there is is competition and you just got to do it or not to do it...it's all at your own risk...you could have one or two off topic video here and there of course, but it's all at your own risk, you should have faith in your audience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 12:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the most important thing in your case now is to get your surgery and recover ... lol ... You could just send out a notice video to your fans saying you'll be inactive for a while...I wish you good luck for your surgery and get better soon after it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stuck at school on a summer day, Digital painting, 200MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 10:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 22:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well, there are surely tones of people like that on youtube, best thing is they never get far, and in the case they do, they will be noticed and then banned ... I'd suggest to leave him be, so that he learn his lesson by himself, or else if you are really concerned send the link of the stolen video to the video owner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good luck to you, Digital medium, 50MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 19:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 06:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's the same as growing any other channel...but given the fact that you post daily videos, you have the advantage of consistency. Just try to be as creative as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 109 Alleyway [Digital Painting] by webang111 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 21:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 109 Alleyway, webang111, Digital painting, 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 20:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy curl part 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 08:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 21:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the feedback, I actually don't talk that often but I'll surely see what I can do in the future...yes, I also noticed it was too loud, I actually forgot that my computer volume was too low when I was editing the video, so it ended up this way o.O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inspired by Barbara Palvin, Gus Romano, WATERCOLOR, 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 20:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 14:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw your leave notice, have a nice break...it's always good to chill out from time to time...well I do art, but I don't think I could provide anything video game related...hope you'll find someone though :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yellow Combo Pearl and Diamond, Wooa Kim, Traditional media, 2014 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 07:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 07:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never done that, and I think if you want to do that anyways, there should be a valid reason otherwise it's a misleading description...however, if you mention the channel in your video, for example if you make a review or something that would require mentioning the channel, then it totally make sense and then you can go ahead and tag them ... if your content is similar to theirs, then you could just mention something along that line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 21:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> work hard! expect little! use those two expressions for starting out ... perhaps you should just dive in and see for yourself if it is possible or not :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Curly Hair and blue eye, Digital painting, 200MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 22:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 20:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll go ahead and post mine here then
https://youtu.be/tly4Gh0S91E </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 20:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you could just post it in the review section you know, everyone can then give you their opinion...I'm really sticking to my point here ... lol ... sorry but if you are teaching something, you gotta put some voice over...I rarely talk in my channel but when I teach or give some info I make 1000% efforts to talk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 18:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it is something that is supposed to be informative, I'd rather have some commentary on them...I came across so many videos of that sort with tones of written text or just the mouse moving on the screen, I found those extremely annoying every time, especially when it was supposed to teach me something important.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 15:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Other than playing video games, you could review games: discuss about the pros and cons, the prices (if it is worth it), exct ... you could as well have one or two videos talking about yourself from time to time (personalised videos)...like what are your hobbies and interests beside video games for example </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 07:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, agree with the others, I just started Facebook recently and it wasn't before long that I noticed that Facebook completely devaluates youtube videos (it must be about market competition). I have around 900 likes and my youtube video posts don't even reach 30 people, however, when I upload a video directly on Facebook it can reach up to 200 people...So make a small video trailer of your video (the shorter the better, even 30s is really good), try to make it catching enough and link your video as click for more/watch more at the end of the video.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My channel trailer, what I do! what I offer! what you can expect! :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 09:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Black neko final part, Digital Painting, 300MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 19:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 18:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's a difficult question...naturally the answer would be: If you are not in the mood then it might end up really bad quality ... on the other hand if you want to make it as a youtuber you have to be dedicated and never miss a scheduled upload deadline... I would say it's OK to miss one or two upload dates, but the risk is that if you start missing one, then you're probably going to keep doing it...so I think the best  is to make a small re-evaluation of your motivations, go back to the first reason why you make videos and gain a bit of self esteem by remembering all the good things that happened since you posted video (forget about the negative) ... also it doesn't always have to be a really good video you know, on those days I'd just post some random stuff I have in stock, and I usually plan these in advance, even before I know that I'm not in the mood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 14:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really much to say, you sound alright with the camera with respect to sounds and video quality is good...it's too long though, try keeping the video under 10 min. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Video] 3 easy and simple steps to master a graphic tablet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 12:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy curl Part 1 [Digital Painting] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 11:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sketching Happy curl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 07:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 06:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really, we can't ... but I usually look other things and try to guess, I might be wrong but I'd just trust my guess, I heard somewhere that the best view rate is often around 10% of the number of subscribers, so when it goes 10K views while 1K subscribers, I usually assume these might be paid views...I then check their social media such as Facebook and see the number of likes or followers then start to guess from that as well... But still 30K while 1K sub may not be organic...also look at some other videos, maybe you'll notice some have 100K and some 1K views, that's already a sign ... I classify viral videos to those that gets millions of views. Sometimes I look at their earliest videos and if these have too many views I assume these might be paid too...it's not only Adwords that sells views, there are other platform, but I trust Adwords more because it's a google product that promotes another google product. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Black Neko, Digital Painting, 300MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 06:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 06:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe you could learn from their channel then, are you sure they didn't use Adwords, that means they might have something exceptional going on...see how long it took them the succeed and compare the quality of your video to theirs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 05:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well, we are around the same age :D so I don't wanna say we are old...lol ... but if you are working, you should probably dedicate some budget aside and look carefully into paid promotion such as google adword, there are a lot of informations online about how to use it, so don't jump in it straight away, make some research... however, make sure your stuff is goof enough, i.e. make sure you did everything you could to get things such as: Youtube banner, channel trailer, videos are pleasing to watch and are captivating...perhaps you could ask your reviews from your friends or better, from some people who are used to criticise you...anyways, it's still a huge risk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 11:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give it some time, keep uploading and always re-evaluate your performance on every single video and compare them with the previous ones. It takes a long long time, and it's a question of endurance, especially if you don't have any budget for paid promotion.  If you are still young, you have the advantage of time. But even if not, there is no rush and enjoy yourself most of all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 09:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is your channel about? Maybe you could set up a Patreon support account, with 3K+  subscribers, I think you could get support from them, if some decide to be your patron you could reward them with some special content (ex: Private live streaming or Special events, special contents, even a custom thank you postcard) ... It's a bit difficult here because we are all starters youtubers who would all like to have some supports :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 06:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm other here https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCTXfr3wxAMV5TezyqYP7INg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
