<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2577</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 12:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well this has made my day.

Would have loved to have seen Turk and Carla though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 04:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know we have sarcastrophe's ^ in English to denote sarcasm.

E.g. ^especially for working one day a week.^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 02:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, my grandparents generation grew up during the civil war and later dictatorship.

 I would say most of their females friends were in horrible relationships but they stayed with the man because it was essentially either that or become homeless - with a high chance of dying through starvation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 18:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 80s remix  original. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 18:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10 years ago I had that ringtone that was really high pitched and old people (which I considered 25+ then) couldn't hear.

Now I just have it on vibrate; I accidentally had it on loud (not vibrate) the other day and when someone asked if my phone was ringing I said no; turns out it was and I just didn't recognise the ring tone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 18:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After the men's valiant effort against Brazil in the world cup it is excellent to see that the women's team are also a force to be reckoned with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 18:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you re-up a new link or post a mirror link, please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 18:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over the years, quite a few American redditors have told me that I wasn't Latino because I'm white.


I had a few people call me a liar in a political discussion, when I mentioned a UN statistic, despite me linking to the UN's website as proof. Apparently the UN website doesn't count as proof of a UN statistic.


A few people called me a liar when I mentioned it was my birthday once.


Sadly it always seem to be that the minute a subreddit get's a decent amount of followers the trolls come out.

What I'm never sure of though is whether the trolls are actually arseholes or just thick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: If you get a pop up website that won't close just press ctrl + w. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 15:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 14:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The people of Siberia disagree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 12:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah my friend got married recently and the priest gave us a big warning not to jokingly say yes :D :D :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 12:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know it's an actual crime to say yes if you don't actually have a genuine reason; imagine being arrested for that.

Still, at least the daughter will be able to provide tips on how to survive prison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 12:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As O- mosquitoes constantly attack me, I always have to travel with deet. I ran out whilst travelling across Thailand and in one night I was bitten at least 20 times on my ankle, so much so that my ankle swelled and I couldn't walk for 3 days.

When I'm not being savaged by mosquitoes I do donate blood as often as I can but if not completely on with my donating I get a good 3/4 calls a week for the blood people asking me to donate.

My dad and sis are O+ and my mum can't donate (cancer) so I'm the official emergency contact in case anyone needs blood :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 03:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that he's ok with slavery as long as they're not from the mainland. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 03:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have an inner voice but when I'm calculating advance maths I see shapes forming.

I'll simplify here but imagine when you add 6 and 4. Well I'll see a small rectangle and square and they will fuse into a cube (10). It's hard to explain to people who can't do this but honestly it's a godsend.

For really long equations I'll see a mountain range and on the rare occasion (really advance unknown maths) I'll go into space as for some reason stars help me with new calculations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 02:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had this discussion with my family the other day. Turns out my mum has a full on voice in her head, so if she wants some water she'll talk to herself something like 'I'm thirsty, I think I'll go get some water'. Whereas my dad and I don't have this voice at all.

The way I would describe it to people who have a voice but can't understand not having a voice; imagine when you're eating and you just cut up your food and eat it. At no point are you talking to yourself saying, cut, chew etc. Now imagine if that is how is was for everything else that you do. 

I find the whole idea of having an inner voice a bit annoying as to me it just seems like a waste of time and makes all tasks longer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 00:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My uncle (Spanish) was forced to fight for the axis (or his family would have been killed), when he was captured by the soviets they send him to a concentration camp for 30 years, long after the war finished and he never got to go home again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 00:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You understand inflation right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 00:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Essential items, like tampons?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 00:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was (might still be) the world record holder for two video games, so I fancy my chances at either one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 16:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who is bilingual in Spanish and English I have a different laugh depending on which language I am speaking/hearing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 00:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say the opposite here people bite your head off at the drop of a hat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 23:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably that being gay is not only ok but also that gays can marry too.

A close second would be whites and blacks can also marry too and society is happy with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 21:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been working fine all day for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 20:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My partners old school were having a fundraising day so we volunteered to help out. There'd been an accident on the nearby motorway so loads of people were being delayed.

The hired clown was running a few minutes late so a teacher asked could someone fill in for 2/3 minutes. I stepped up and did a few minutes of juggling tricks.

When I finished she looked very confused and said that I never told her that I could do that, so I replied you never asked.

Then a bit later one of the bands was also running late so I volunteer to play the guitar and sing a few Disney songs (and getting the kids to join in).

She was genuinely furious when I got of the stage and she asked why I didn't tell her I could play the guitar. She did not find it amusing when I replied, again, that she never asked.

I get home two hours earlier than her every day so I use most that time to practicing a hobby in our attic (unofficial man cave which she never goes in to), so there's a few things I'm alright at that she has no idea about :D

It might seem odd not to tell her but she's a bit sensitive about the fact that I have 2 extra free hours than she does, and I know she'd be annoyed if she knew I was having fun whilst she was travelling (crazy I know but that's her), so she's under the impression that I spend most of that time cooking and cleaning :D :D :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 20:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you've messed up the link OP; it takes me to a page about Bill Murray. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 13:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anyone in the US legitimately been gaoled for stealing mail? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 13:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's a wired phone :S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 13:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't until I saw a big thing on it here that I learnt that Americans have only just started with the chip and pin.

I was absolutely stunned that they still use cheques as I've never even seen a cheque in my lifetime, let alone write one. Would the bank even give you a cheque book if you requested one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 13:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An odd one for me is that its illegal to cross the road (called jaywalking) in America except at designated places.

In Europe it's fine to cross when you like, you just have to use common sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 13:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That a lot of American's say 'I could care less' when in fact they mean 'I couldn't care less'. Seen this loads on your tv shows and it annoys the hell out of me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 13:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would you know if your mail got stolen from your mailbox though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 04:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well on the plus side, I'll probably get a gold medal for ground pokmon in the coming week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 04:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah Christmas makes more sense for jynx. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 03:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just had 4 cubones appear on my street and normally there's nothing here. They've all been worth 6 candy each, didn't know catching candy was doubled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 02:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's because it sounds very much like Chechnya. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paul Beatty becomes first US winner of the Man Booker Prize </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 01:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 00:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HEY YOU GUYS!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 23:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't noticed any improvement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 23:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 23:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm put grimer as my buddy, only seen 1 and even though he's crap better a weak muk than none.

I did see Muk on day 2 of launch but the game crashed when I tried to catch him :(

After Muk I might do omanyte.

Whatever doesn't get done I'm assuming we'll have a similar event at christmas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 22:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For us Europeans UCT is the same as GMT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 22:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Britain is just waiting for Trump/Clinton to mess up the USA, then they will strike. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 22:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess you needed to talk about Kevin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 22:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Health warning on cigarettes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 15:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The big question is did he place a bet on it back in 93 though.

When I was a teen I bet 50 on a new player in the Spanish youth squad to become our all time top goal scorer. He went on the play exactly one match and has since changed his nationality :D :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 03:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who says 'not' anymore :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 03:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Green park isn't a no cycling park :S

I think it's a sad state of affairs when someone is complaining about people riding a bike in a park. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 03:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As imgur is down atm, what number is in the op? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 22:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Native American? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 21:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Press

enter

twice

for

proper

spacing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 21:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lose Virginity.

Be cheated on.

Cheat on someone.

10,000th wank.

Wank over partner's sibling (parent option too).

10,000th condom.

Sex with an older lady/man (+10 years).

Sex with a younger lady/man (-10 years).

Have sex with a minor: 99.9% of people would get this from 
having sex when they themselves were a minor but you know not everyone will believe you :D

Sex in public.

Sex in every continent.

Mile high club.

Mile low club.

Good threesome.

Bad threesome.

Dick/pussy swelled from over wanking.

Wank at work.

Sex at work (also school).

Have a one night stand (ruining millions of girls' good girl image)

Complete the kama sutra.

Injure yourself attempting the kama sutra.

1,000th wank over the same women/man. (everyone will want to know who this is, especially if you're single)

365 days without sex.

Fancy mate's spouse.

Climax whilst thinking of a different person.

Pay for sex.

Swallow.

Try viagra.

Brown wings.

One minute wonder (climax 1 min)

Catch std.

It is a big deal! (Can't get it up)

I'm on a boat!!!

Cum one, cum all (orgy) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 20:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally anyone can get a star though as you can just buy one/a spot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 15:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I had that space to store mine, I had to thrown my boxes/cases all away :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 12:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to a strict Catholic school so we never had any sexual education classes. 

I had to learn everything the hard way.
A couple of girls in my school got pregnant in their teens, which I believe could 100% have been avoided if we received any sort of sexual education.

You can blame the parents sure but you have to remember the sort of parents that send their kids to a strict Catholic school are not going to be open minded enough to talk to their kids about sex.

The government should make it a legal requirement to teach kids about sex in school and get an outsider to do it, with no option to opt out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 04:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Electabuzz is great for taking down gyms, I use thunder shock and thunder combo and he's practically unstoppable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 03:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So 11pm gmt or midnight for most of Europe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 03:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably because he was forced to get the tattoo's because he was someone's bitch in prison. Bulking up = harder to become a bitch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Barcelona footballers are allergic to water bottles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 00:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 21:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People saw it more like an Xbox S than a new console. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 18:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well he was 100% Asian tbf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 15:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sacrifice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 15:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a man I'd never worn makeup in my life, then I was interviewed a couple of times for the news (in studios). The amount of makeup they put on me quite frankly was shocking. I'm only in my 20s and have good skin so honestly I didn't think I had anything to cover up.

I asked what each thing was for and the makeup artist told me 'this is nothing' the presenters get double what you're getting :O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 15:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can buy it almost everywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 15:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My whole area only gave out mewtwo promo cards during the first movie. One kid in my class had seen the movie out of town and got an electabuzz card and everyone was super jealous of him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 04:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Portugal with one of the worst economies in Europe simply want to know when their football team are playing next. It's an odd mix of admirable that they want to move on but also sad that they seem to be just sweeping it all under the rug. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 03:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From one glass only? :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 00:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Three years later and he's still waiting for his mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 00:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean it used to belong :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 00:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what did you think happened to Harry in the scene where he accidentally says diagonally when using the floo network? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 00:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's how my family have always done it. Amazed others haven't started to do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 00:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love going for a jog in the rain for this reason. In London the canal is near me and I can run a good 20 miles without seeing a soul, absolute bliss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 19:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait but I'm ambidextrous, do I live? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 19:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, so mormons don't drink :O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 19:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> D would struggle to feed a family of four more than B. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 19:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine how annoying hearing two kids laughing all the time would be though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 04:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a better cartoon duet than Mariah and Whitney? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 03:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a coincidence when it's planned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 03:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Op seems to be ignoring the thousands of years that men have been raping women. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baby Jesus statue in Canada turns heads with artist's shocking restoration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 02:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 00:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm genuinely furious that I forgot what I changed my old password to on my old account (10 years old) so I had to create this new one :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 22:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So no VR? Come on Nintendo you're suppose to be the revolutionary one of the big 3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 22:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should have had a nintendogs game interacting with the real dog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 11:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know technically British athletes don't get 'paid' but they have they living, travel and training expenses all covered.

This 'expenses' budget is up to 57,000 ($70k), so they are hardly poor. I think most of us would give up our salary if we got that expenses budget. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 01:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The British don't use bidet, that's more us western continental Europeans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 01:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know a fair chunk the British, French and German one's (and obviously my own (Spanish))

If you paid me 1m I couldn't sing one line from the American one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 00:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else freak out by how weirdly the dogs tongue is coming out of the side of his mouth :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 00:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to see jokes that go all in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 23:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else feel dirty for liking something on fox news :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 00:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And not forgetting vice president Mr. Peanutbutter  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 00:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come on brother, chorizo completely changes the taste of our paellas.

I'll allow different mariscos but chorizo is too dominant.

Also con cebolla para mi :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 23:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an iphone case grandad ;P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 23:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't honestly believe you guys popularised the pizza do you :D :D :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 23:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Spaniard our food is definitely about flavour.

If you want to butcher a dish fine but don't call it tortilla or paella; just give it a new name so as not to insult our traditional food. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 22:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do it and show us pics of what they have available! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 22:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I grew up in a town in which it was normal for kids to wander around. Everyday I would hang out with my best friend and his dog.

We were on our way to our forest hideout, that we'd be working on for the last two years, and were just arriving to the forest when we saw a really dirty looking Asian guy walking along with a big stick. He then squatted down, pulled down his pants and started to take a crap on the floor.

He didn't know we were there until he heard us gasp. He looked back and said what the fuck you looking at and then began to chase us. I ran into the forest, towards our hideout, whereas my friend and his dog ran in the other direction.

I didn't stop running until I got to the hideout but when I stopped shaking it became apparent that the guy must have chased my friend instead. I slowly left the hideout and walked towards where I knew my friend would have hidden. 

Except when I got near I saw my friend with very bloody hands. I ran over panicking and shouted if he was ok. Turns out he was but the guy had flipped out, started shouting at him and when his dog started barking loudly the guy beat his dog to death with his stick.

I couldn't believe it so I walked over to where my friend said his dog was and honestly this guy had definitely carried on hitting the dog well after he was dead as it looked like a bomb had gone off.

I can only imagine how traumatic that would have been to witness. Took my friend years before he could actually tell other people what had happened/what he'd seen.

We got back to his house and I had to tell his mum what happened; she called the police and I had to tell the story on his behalf as he just froze up.

Unfortunately the police never found the guy; they assume he was just a crazy bum wandering through town. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 21:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an old sports injury and from time to time I get a moderate nosebleed out of the blue.

I was at a bar with my girlfriend and her girlfriends when it happened. No biggy I told them not to worry and that it's an old sporting injury and happens from time to time and excused myself whilst I went to the loo to stop the bleeding and clean myself up. My girlfriend followed me, as she usually does, just to make sure I'm ok and don't make a mess as not everywhere has a mirror.

When we went back to our table her girlfriends were gone but I could see them outside, so we go outside and the idiots had called an ambulance for me. The make matters worse whilst I was apologise on the idiots behalf for wasting the paramedics time her friends were shouting at the paramedics to ignore me and take me to hospital. One even shouted 'he's lost a lot of blood, he could die without medical attention'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 21:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an accountant for HMRC I have argued with soo many people over this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 20:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else not surprised that German don't have Schindler's list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 20:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently left open: 7 in Alaska and 2 in both Oregon and Texas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Blockbusters still have 11 stores. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 19:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 18:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see my noisy cricket get wicked on ya, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 18:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never lent money to my friends and not got it back. Jugding by all the down-votes I guess a lot of people must just have arsehole friends who can't be trusted to pay it back.

I would say the lesson here is to get better friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 18:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL most people actually visualise a bar :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's because 99% of the time there was no need to bring it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a native English accent but I'm actually Spanish. I once said a paella and this English girl said it's actually pronounce (insert bad spanish accent). I had to say I think I know how to speak my own language :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
