<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3313</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-23 22:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm jealous. and looking up one way plane tickets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-18 22:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> love the himym reference.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-18 21:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I foster kittens for our local humane society, so far up to 36, and I'm pretty sure there isn't much I haven't seen now. You think two's bad? Try having six at once. haha. I don't know if this will help, but this is my advice.

1. It's kind of normal for kittens to not know how they clean themselves. I would suggest using some wet wipes on her butt, or, wash it with soap and water. Usually when I do this to a kitten, they freak out because they're wet and proceed to groom themselves for like half an hour. You said she claws at everything... Wouldn't you if someone was holding you up trying to put things near your girly parts??  Try holding her by the scruff - I promise this doesn't hurt them, the mom-cats do it with their teeth; it's an area with limited nerves and it releases endorphins, it will instantly calm her.  Also, try a different flavor wet food. Maybe don't give them wet food for a day, eventually they'll eat the dry food, then you can proceed to give them wet food more sporadically, or once a day.

2. The scratching is completely normal, in fact, I'd probably say expected for a kitten. You can try to trim her claws, or when you take her to the vet, have them do it since you haven't owned cats before. Really, the hardest part is getting them to stay still and as long as you trim a few millimeters from the tip, you should be fine... but, if you're not comfortable doing this, by all means, don't. A scratching post, as I saw someone posted, would also be a good idea. The biting is normal too, especially if they're teething, they want to chew on everything.

3. The rough playing happens with all kittens - it's how they learn their normal cat behaviors - the stalking, chasing, all that. Boys are usually rougher than girls. There's no reason for him to seriously hurt her, honestly, i know it looks bad but it's just what they do. Also, the grooming is normal too :] and of course, cute.

4. I literally just had two fosters, a stray kitten that was paired with another unrelated kitten. So... while they're young, they may have still not wanted to interact with people as stray cats. But also because they're young, you can kind of teach them some things. This will take time. What I'll do sometimes is when a kitten is sleeping, take it and put it in your lap - generally they'll go right back to sleep, cuddle, purr, all that good stuff. You can go looking for their little happy spots - some cats like being scratched under the neck, some of them like their scruff massaged - something that makes them purr. Also, they won't be too lovey if they're in a playful mood, usually it's when they get tired. It'll just take some time, some getting used to for them. They'll figure it out. 

Just love them with all you've got. :] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-18 01:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> does it bother anyone else that he wears his pants like urkel without even a shirt tucked into it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-17 22:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> especially when it's a middle school student! my god. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
