<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject398</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 04:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When ever you are ready. I'll be looking around till then. Good luck in all you do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 04:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very nice post. I respect it when someone isn't afraid to lay out the knowledge for others with out expecting a payment in return. My question is (and it is self serving) are you ready to do it again with custom home brew kits for the home craft-brewing crowd? What I can bring to the table is 2 master brewers to formulate custom kits, kit building, order fulfillment, shipping and a few thousand start-up capital. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-28 16:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> O Brother, Where Art Thou? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 14:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 140 degrees F is the goal temperature to kill them and their eggs. If a dryer isn't available just loosely put everything (luggage and all), that can survive that temperature, into some black plastic trash bags and place them in the sun for a few hours until the heat can permeate everything. Anything that you can't treat with heat just clean the best you can with what you can. Remember, bed bugs like to hide in the folds of clothes, beds, and such so as a preventive think about treating your backpack or other luggage with Diatomaceous earth leaving a tiny amount in the folds, hems and corners to help kill any further infestations. As for the itch and rash, it is an allergic/histamine reaction to the insects saliva, so take an anti-histamine or an allergy med and enjoy your travels as much as you can. Tell the Hostel about the problem so they can get ahead of the bugs and not complicate other peoples days.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 04:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Latin America bound this winter, the "return ticket"? How do you get visas and entry into countries without a ticket to travel on? I plan on slow traveling, 2-3 months in one place with no set plans on where to go next. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-05 03:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have family and friends in the business and have dabbled in it myself, 6 figures in not uncommon if the spots are right and you work it year round.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 13:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People do not believe the money that is made with a hot dog stand and a good spot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-02 23:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously though, why is suicide illegal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 03:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wear clothes naked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 14:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if you woke up from a comma and while out had become blind and deaf? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 19:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is called the speed LIMIT not how fast you have to go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 18:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> one dollar over what I need a day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 14:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taco Tonto's for burritos, don't expect just the standard stuffins.
Main Street Grill for REAL Greek food.
Hot Soss Don food truck, sorta hard to find but if you ever see his truck pulled over, STOP! Best damn comfort food in the area.
Find out where Roger Hoover is playing, you will be entertained.
The Bike and Hike trail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 15:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't you dumb asses know that knitting is traditionally man's work and still practiced as such in some cultures? Go learn some shit.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-13 00:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are your interests and hobbies?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have a dream, a link, some $$ and a Fiverr account, lets do a step by step. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-13 00:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am doing this so Noobies will have some sort of game plan.
I have you folks, a dream, a link, some $$ and a Fiverr account, lets do a step by step and see if I can make any money by having Fiverr do all the work they can, from article writing to landing page to back links and such. I belong to a private affiliate network in a nice niche. I am going to work with a well known niche brand's new product line that the store I'm working with carries. The line I will be promoting only has 3 products (flavors) which were just released this week.

I figure that my first purchase will be a nice size article or 2 to have when I purchase the landing page.
I hope to do all that is needed for around $200 but we will see.

Edit 1: I've decided to hire a keyword search done first. 15 SEO keywords $20
What else do you think I should be doing?

You folk's feed back on this will be the backbone of this experiment.
I will post all results win or lose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Long term travelers, what luggage do you travel with? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 20:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am sure this has been covered before but I don't have luck with Reddit search so sorry. Long term Latin America travel where stays in more than one place may be weeks or longer, Backpack, suit case, what? Size? Not sure how I will be getting from one place to another. Looking forward to you folks actual experiences with this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 14:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are correct sir. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 01:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AND, my oldest boy once ran a music store and hired and fired one of his best friends, it also blew over because the friend was in the wrong and knew it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 01:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My son fire my other son, his older bro by 6 years, and it eventually blew over. People know when they are in the wrong and if you make solid moves for the right reasons they will get over it and if they don't they aren't very intelligent to start out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 04:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not just ask Reddit how to fix your oven? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 04:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you the band leader? If so fire his ass and hire another guitarist.
If you have to sit down and discuss it with the other band members quit the band and become a band leader. The band is not going to make it as a "band democracy". I gave my son this advice when there was a riff in the band he was in, (his brother and a long time friend was in the band at the time) hire your musicians, be the owner of the band, control it. He took my advice and after the dust settled he hired some band members and started touring, to this day he's making damn good money, 6 figures some years. 16 years later, he's 36 now and married, and still tours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-05 22:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 62 and starting this year. Wish I would have started at 27. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 13:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been told I'm an old cool guy more than once (even though I don't feel cool anymore) so maybe I have that going for me. I have friends of all ages from their 90s to early 20s. I get along with all of them. I'm very non-judgmental which seems to allow people just to "be" and they like that. I've had old ladies in their 80s and 90s tell me about their sexcapades when they were young and I've had 20 somethings cry on my shoulder about their failures in life (if they only knew what was ahead) and all sorts of tales from all ages in between. If I'm not, I believe I can fake the "old cool guy". Thanks for responding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
