<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1195</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Either Trump is lying about his campaigns Russia ties or US spies are </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the first three Pirates of the Caribbean movies that Gore Verbinski directed did gross like $2.6 billion worldwide (plus his first horror film The Ring was a huge hit). I imagine that buys a lot of clout in Hollywood.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump asked a black reporter if the Congressional Black Caucus are "friends of yours" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump asked a black reporter if the Congressional Black Caucus are "friends of yours" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [International] Moonlight Shines At International Box Office As A24 Grows Biz Model </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 20:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 5 stages of watching A Cure for Wellness, from curiosity to raving insanity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 19:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 18:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, that's a terrible premiere number for Doubt. It's yet another flop for Katherine Heigl.

Lethal Weapon continues to perform impressively. 

Glad to see The 100 stay steady - I recently started watching it on Netflix, and I'm really enjoying it. 

And Colbert beat Fallon yet AGAIN! So glad to see his ratings winning streak continuing. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TV Ratings Wednesday: Doubt has soft premiere, Lethal Weapon ticks up, The 100 steady </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 18:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy fucking shit. Trump is INSANE. They're going to fucking crucify him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Battlestar Galactica is a great show to binge-watch in these trying times as well. I've always described it as "The West Wing in space." 

Parks and Recreation is another endlessly rewatchable show in a similar vein. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Battlestar Galactica is a great show to binge-watch as well. I've always described it as "The West Wing in space." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 13:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ba Dum Tish! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 00:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very well-deserved. His political humor has been top-notch since Trump was elected.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking spineless cowards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 19:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a series-low and finale low for The Celebrity Apprentice. It will be interesting to see if NBC cancels it or not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been approved now. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 12:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always thought Jonathan was hilarious on 30 Rock, so it's pretty awesome to see Maulik Pancholy involved with this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 05:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The winning continues!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A B+ Cinemascore for Fifty Shades Darker is actually quite good for the type of film it is (trashy erotic romance), so I wouldn't call it "abysmal" word-of-mouth personally. It seems to be far better well-received than its predecessor. This is very similar to how Magic Mike received a B Cinemsscore and a lot of audiences left disappointed, but its sequel Magic Mike XXL received an A- Cinemascore. 

Fifty Shades Darker may be trash, but it looks like Universal figured out how to make a film that delivered on what the target audience wanted to see this time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 18:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hidden Figures is continuing to display insane legs in its 8th weekend. It only dropped 22%, and it's STILL in the top 5. It could very likely gross $170 million+ at this point. 

I really need to check it out before the Oscars.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 18:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope you enjoy it! I thought it was fucking awesome, and I can't wait for the next sequel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 22:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obey the constitution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 22:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Superb number for John Wick: Chapter 2 - I saw it today, and it was a blast. I'm really looking forward to the next sequel now. 

The Lego Batman Movie recovered nicely on Saturday and Sunday - I hope it has really good legs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 22:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Baldwin, who again played Trump, brought in a bigger rating than the real thing. When Trump hosted the show as a presidential candidate in November 2015, the episode brought in a 6.6 overnight rating.

http://money.cnn.com/2017/02/12/media/saturday-night-live-ratings-alec-baldwin-donald-trump/index.html

Oh, boy - a certain someone is not going to be happy about that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, that was a little over 11 years ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mod here - yes, we do change the upper banner every so offen. I'll look into changing the banner for 2017, and we'll hopefully have a new one up in the near future. Thanks for the input! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, the dude's a loonie alright.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 17:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great number for John Wick: Chapter 2. It's awesome to see Keanu Reeves be in a hit franchise once again - the dude deserves it. I'm really excited to see it tomorrow afternoon! :)

Good number for The Lego Batman Movie, even though it performed below many expectations (including my own). However, I expect it to have a huge increase on Saturday and end up at #1 with around $58 million or so. It's likely to have great legs as well, since people are loving it.

Excellent number for Fifty Shades Darker as well (although it's obviously a huge drop from the first film). It's going to drop precipitously on Saturday and Sunday, of course, but it will still be an enormously profitable film for Universal (even if the quality of the movie is not great). 

Hidden Figures is continuing to display insane legs - wow. Glad to see Split hold up well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Lego Batman Movie is still likely to have a big increase on Saturday, so it could get close to $60 million (probably around $58 million).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 03:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome news! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 03:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WE...ARE GROOT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 03:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, man! You rock.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 03:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to go to there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 23:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are superb numbers for The Lego Batman Movie and John Wick: Chapter 2. I wouldn't be surprised at all if the projected weekend number for The Lego Batman Movie gets even higher, since it's likely to have a massive Saturday.

50 Shades Darker is also doing very well, especially considering its low budget and the poor reception the first film received among fans of the book series. It's not surprising that the sequel is going to have a huge drop-off from the first film, but it will still be very profitable in the end.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Alec Baldwin is hosting this Saturday! It will be really interesting to see how many sketches he's in as Trump. I imagine that we'll get some very angry tweets regarding SNL from our President on Sunday.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad to see Kevin Weisman involved - he was wonderful as Marshall on Alias.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're tremendous failures! The BEST! We're going to screw up America BIGLY! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 00:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump's probably furious right now. Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 00:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome news. The Trump Meltdown will be glorious to behold.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 23:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, man, Trump is going to go fucking ballistic. I expect a tweet from him in the near future shitting on Gorsuch. What a clown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 00:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this past episode was the best of the season: the Sean Spicer sketch, the immigration commercial, and the Totino's commercial with Kristen Stewart were all hilarious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 00:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So say we all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 00:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, that sucks. He was excellent as Zarek, and the mutiny plot line that he was involved in was the show at its very best.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Claire is definitely the best part of these Marvel Netflix shows, IMO. I'm happy to see that it looks like she's going to have a substantial role in this one as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Solid number for 24: Legacy, but it's still a far cry from the ratings 24 used to get at the height of its popularity. Good for APB as well, but I expect it to fade fast.

Ouch for Timeless - it will almost surely be cancelled now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 01:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Voter fraud isn't petty. There just isn't any credible evidence whatsoever that 3 to 5 million people illegally voted in the election like Trump claims. Even Trump's own attorneys (as well as a number of top Republicans) say there's no evidence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 21:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GET THE OUTSIDER! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 21:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So we're getting two very well-reviewed, highly anticipated movies this weekend, huh (this film and The Lego Batman Movie)? EXCELLENT! *Does air guitar* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, indeed - the film is a world-of-mouth sensation. It's definitely going to gross $150 million+ domestically now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this film is currently at 91% on Rotten Tomatoes. I'm glad to hear that this and The Lego Batman Movie are apparently both really fucking good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The massive monster at the end was fucking sweet. I can't wait. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 18:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet another great weekend for Split - I'm happy to see it take the top spot for third weekend in a row. Very well-deserved. 

Meh opening for Rings - it's going to absolutely collapse next weekend and end up with around $25 million domestically. It'll eventually eke out a profit thanks to overseas business, but it's definitely a failed stab at reviving a long-dormant horror franchise (similar to Blair Witch).

I'm not surprised to see The Space Between Us bombing - it looked terrible. 

Hidden Figures had yet another terrific hold - damn, the legs on this one are insane. I still need to see it before the Oscars.

Rogue One is finally out of the top ten after 8 weeks - it had a fantastic run.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 14:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our judicial system fucking ROCKS, man! You've been checked and balanced, Mr. President! *Does air guitar* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 14:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm loving our judicial system right now. You've been checked and balanced, son! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 00:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, indeed. Minions grossed $1.2 billion worldwide to be exact. Wonders never cease, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 23:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, The Dark Knight grossed $535.8 million in the U.S. alone. I seriously doubt The Lego Batman Movie will reach those heights, but hey, if fucking Minions could gross $1 billion+ worldwide, it's definitely possible. It has a great chance of reaching $250-300 million domestically, though, especially considering the great reviews and what will likely be stellar word-of-mouth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 22:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad to hear good things about this film. I was a little worried since Phil Lord and Chris Miller weren't writers on this one (even if they were producers).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 20:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Death of a Salesman is a critical plot element of the film (members of the cast are performing the play). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 18:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Incredible, beautifully filmed movie. It also has one of my favorite musical scores.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 17:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Trump meltdown when the 9th Circuit rules against the immigration executive order is going to be BEAUTIFUL to behold.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 17:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since Rings is apparently terrible, I'm hoping that it drops on Saturday a good bit, and Split's inevitable big increase on Saturday will give it the #1 spot for the third weekend in a row.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 17:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much. Cheap horror film = $$$$$$. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 05:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking awesome news. I will go to bed happy tonight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 05:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More bad news for the Trump administration in what must be an incredibly shitty day for then (what with this and the halt of the Muslim travel ban). That's music to my ears.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 04:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Federal Judge James Robart, you're the real MVP. *Wipes tear from face*

It's nice to have some actual good news (even if only temporary) in this shitstorm that is the Trump administration.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 02:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's hoping that Old Lace (the dinosaur) is involved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 13:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Old Lace better be in it - it would be incredibly disappointing if he isn't. I believe that Brian K. Vaughan is involved with the show as well, so hopefully he would push for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 00:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I rather enjoyed Voyager, too - there were some great episodes over its run. The Doctor and Seven of Nine were especially wonderful characters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 23:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to go with a 1.4.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 18:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an excellent number for The Flash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 16:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This will surely go over well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 16:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GOP: Fuck ALL the rules! We'll make new ones! 

Our country is so fucked. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 02:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope that the Democrats hold up Gorsuch's confirmation for a looooooooong time. 

Payback's a bitch, huh, Republicans? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 02:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would begin violently throwing up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 02:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/YLCfyvP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 02:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 02:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, boo fucking hoo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 22:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go fuck yourself, Trump. You're the worst. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 21:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank God - this show is hilarious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 21:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's definitely on track to gross $100 million+ - I'm seeing a final gross of at least $130-140 million (maybe even $150 million).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 05:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/ewtUQ2a </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 22:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, I'm sure that the irony is lost on him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Superb drop for Split. A horror/thriller film having a drop under 40% in its second weekend and a $8,212 per theater average? Word-mouth is obviously stellar, and it's the zeitgeisty film of the moment, so everyone wants to see what all the fuss is about.

Hidden Figures is a word-of-mouth sensation. It's almost definitely headed to $150 million+ now. 

Solid number for A Dog's Purpose, especially considering all of the controversy. The video definitely hurt it in major cities like New York and Washington, apparently (according to The Hollywood Reporter).

Decent number for Resident Evil: The Final Chapter. It's cleaning up overseas and wasn't expensive, so it's going to be yet another profitable entry in the series. They're definitely guilty pleasures of mine.

Excellent increase for La La Land as well. I'm glad that Lionsgate finally expanded it to 3,000+ theaters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 18:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be fucking incredible if it happened. Here's hoping.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 19:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully its huge financial success leads to a lot of high-profile films hiring on Anya Taylor-Joy, who's terrific in the film (as well a greenlighting a certain film that Shyamalan really wants to make. Wink wink.)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 17:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent drop for Split - I'm glad to see people are really digging it. I'm hoping to see it a second time tomorrow. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 09:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Star Wars  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grey's Anatomy is still a beast after all these years. Wowzers - I expect it will continue for a very long time.

Not a great debut for Riverdale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 18:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Oh, boy."

"Yep, Ziggy says there's a 100% chance of this country being utterly fucked." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SHIA SURPRISE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 00:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Rock is an action masterpiece, IMO, so Bay always gets some respect from me for that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 23:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bet: It will be a clean sweep for La La Land, and it will win all 14 of the Oscars it's nominated for (similar to the clean sweep that The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King did in 2004).

Nice to see Arrival get nominated for so many awards (even though Amy Adams was snubbed. Boooo). It's my favorite movie of last year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 18:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fantastic numbers for This Is Us and Chicago Fire. There have been no signs of audience erosion whatsoever for This Is Us, so I'm sure that NBC is ecstatic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 04:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Split is worth seeing simply for the wonderful performances of James McAvoy and Anya Taylor-Joy. Plus, the cinematography is aces.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 03:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm happy to hear that this is apparently quite good. The trailer freaked me the fuck out - always a good sign.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 18:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing opening for Split. After its terrific trailers, I had a feeling it would do well, and its performance has surpassed my wildest expectations. Congrats, Universal, Shyamalan, and the rest of your cast and crew! You made a pretty awesome film (with a wonderful ending that left me grinning leaving the theater). 

Patriots Day is definitely a financial disappointment for Lionsgate now with its substantial drop this week. It was definitely too soon for a movie about the events of the Boston Marathon bombing (same with the events depicted in Deepwater Horizon, which also flopped big time). I hope that Peter Berg and Mark Wahlberg learned their lesson.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 16:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just wonder what percentage of people actually understood the ending twist - it all depends on whether a certain something is a cultural blind spot or not. Did anyone here who saw Split see confused audience members walking out?

I, for one, loved the twist, though. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 00:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This movie was a blast - James McAvoy and Anya Taylor-Joy were both superb. The ending left me with a huge smile on my face.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 23:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, it's going to be insanely profitable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 21:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here! The ending was amazing (I just got back from the movie). It was a very good, intense movie - both James McAvoy and Anya Taylor-Joy were incredible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 17:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spicer flat out lied through his teeth - he should be called out for doing so. That's responsible journalism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 02:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source: https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2017/jan/21/womens-march-washington-chicago-los-angeles-trump?CMP=oth_b-aplnews_d-1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 01:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The man cannot accept any criticism whatsoever. How can this man be our fucking president? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 17:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Terrific number for Split - I was hoping it would break out in a huge way, and it definitely has. This might have pretty decent legs as well, since people are raving about it and its twist. I hope to see it tomorrow myself.

Pretty disappointing number for XXX3, although that's not surprising at all. It's been wayyyy too long since the first film, so most people don't care about another sequel (even with Vin Diesel back).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 18:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an excellent number for Split. It's going to do extremely well this weekend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 18:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yayyyy for The Good Place! That finale was terrific.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 16:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope the protests today are YUUUUUUUUGE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 16:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so ashamed of America today. *Shakes head sadly* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 05:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to love all of the deliberate Lost references on the show as well (from Eleanor's eye opening in the first shot of the pilot to the flashback sounds). It's pretty awesome to see a sitcom that is hugely inspired by it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 03:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loved the fire monster appearance!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 02:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 02:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHAT A TWIST! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 02:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "He's from Florida? He belongs in the Bad Place." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 23:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, I'm sold.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 23:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Malkovich, Malkovich, Malkovich!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 23:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Split is going to do very well at the box office this weekend. People have been waiting for a great horror/thriller film, and this film looks to have it in spades. The marketing has been incredibly effective, and the reviews are very good. I see it doing anywhere from $25-30 million this weekend and probably around $75-80 million total.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 21:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Split is going to do very well at the box office this weekend. People have been waiting for a great horror/thriller film, and this film looks to have it in spades. The marketing has been incredibly effective, and the reviews are very good. I see it doing anywhere from $25-30 million this weekend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 21:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really, really, really want this to be good. I'm hoping this delay means they know what they're doing, and hopefully the show's creators are trying to make the best possible version of Star Trek they can (instead of rushing a half-assed, poorly scripted retread).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 18:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yikes at Agents of SHIELD's series low. I would love another season, but at this point its chances of renewal might be dire.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 01:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> La La Land will likely gross $150 million+ now. 

My bold prediction: La La Land will be the #1 movie on the weekend of either January 27th or February 3rd (as a result of the many Oscar nominations this will surely receive). It's more likely to be #1 on the weekend of February 3rd, since I don't see any of the new releases that weekend doing particularly well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 18:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ouch for Timeless. It may not get renewed at this point now. That's kind of a bummer - I enjoy the show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 16:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's a pretty nice theater. I really like the reserved seating, and the reclining seats are very nice and comfortable. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 14:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was terrific! Ryan Gosling - who's now one of my favorite actors - and Emma Stone have incredible chemistry together. I really liked the songs, too. I'm definitely going to have to get he soundtrack now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 01:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was sold out this afternoon today at a theater I sometimes frequent as well (in Carlisle, Pennsylvania), along with Hidden Figures and Sing. The showing of La La Land (which was excellent) I saw today there was at least three quarters full. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 17:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hidden Figures is a freaking beast. With a possible Best Picture nomination coming on the 24th for it, this movie is going to have some terrific legs.

La La Land had yet another incredible weekend (I'm finally seeing it this afternoon!). This will likely gross $150 million+ now. My bold prediction: this will be the #1 movie on the weekend of either January 27th or February 3rd (as a result of the many Oscar nominations this will surely receive). It's more likely to be #1 on the weekend of February 3rd, since I don't see any of the new releases that weekend doing particularly well. 

I'm not surprised by Silence bombing at all. It looked very non-mainstream and inaccessible. But this is Martin Scorsese we're talking about: he'll definitely recover from its financial failure. The Irishman and The Devil in the White City will almost surely be hits.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 21:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, this thing will probably have insane legs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 23:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great numbers for Hidden Figures and La La Land. I wouldn't be surprised at seeing La La Land at #1 in the near future.

Decent number for Patriots Day, especially considering its small budget. It won't be the box office disaster that the expensive Deepwater Horizon was. I still think a lot of audiences think this movie is insensitive and "too soon" in depicting its subject's events, though. 

Surprisingly good number for The Bye Bye Man. I did not see that coming at all. Low-budget horror wins yet again (even if this one is apparently terrible based off the reviews and audience reaction). Hopefully this year will be a goldmine for horror at the box office once again, like 2016 was.

Awful numbers for Monster Trucks and Live By Night. The former is the first big-budget bomb of the year, and the latter is a critical and financial misfire for Ben Affleck, which doesn't happen too often with him these days (The Accountant was a big hit).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 18:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice to see The Good Place rise. I think a season 2 renewal is very likely. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 02:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Swanson Safe Company! Nice Parks and Rec reference.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 02:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Dad, we need to talk." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 01:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tonight's episode is the next to last week of this season of The Good Place (next week are the final two episodes of the season). I'm hoping that there's plenty of Janet in the last three episodes.

GET HYPED. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 00:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let Down - Radiohead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 18:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Terrific numbers for This Is Us and Obama's farewell address. I'm really going to miss that guy (and Biden!).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 18:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trumps's favorite word of the day today: "tremendous." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 03:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joe's the fucking man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 03:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOCK HIM UP!

Oh, man, it would be beautiful if the FBI arrests Trump before he gets inaugurated. Poetic justice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 00:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a superb number for La La Land - it's going to do very well this weekend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 00:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you like working with Matt Smith, Karen Gillan, and Arthur Darvill on Doctor Who? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 23:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I'm glad to hear that. This season has been excellent so far (the Ghost Rider story line has been very well-done).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 03:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this point, I wouldn't be surprised if it's the #1 movie of the weekend in the near future (it's even going to be on about 100 IMAX screens this weekend, which will boost its gross even further). Lionsgate has done a brilliant job marketing this film and all of the awards buzz and acclaim has come together perfectly, so interest is through the roof.

According to Deadline today, it's now the #1 top-selling movie on Fandango and has been the top-seller for every hour since 5 a.m. So, yeah, this movie is going to do gangbusters business in the weeks ahead.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 05:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steve Carrell and Kristen Wiig's comedic bit was easily the highlight of the show. "Fantasia Day." Oh, man, that had me laughing hard.

Jimmy Fallon's bits during the ceremony were pretty cringe-worthy. They should hire someone like Carrell next year, who actually has excellent comedic timing and improv skills.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 05:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was easily the highlight of the night and the only moment that actually made laugh very hard. 

They should really hire Steve Carrell as host next year - the dude has amazing comic timing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 05:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Jimmy Fallon's bits during the ceremony were cringe-worthy (he's getting bad reviews for his hosting job from Hollywood publications like Deadline already). They really should have Steve Carroll or someone with actual good comic timing and improv skills host next year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 05:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> America's long national nightmare of watching Jimmy Fallon host The Golden Globes is finally over.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 05:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm hoping that it gets a Best Picture nomination at the Oscars. *Crosses fingers* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 04:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, man - I can't wait to watch Lemony Snicket's A Series of Unfortunate Events. NPH is the man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 03:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, wow - I did not see The Crown winning Best Drama Series coming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 03:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm loving Anna Kendrick's dress tonight. Wow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 03:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yayyy, Zootopia! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 03:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steve Carell wins the night! Get him to host next year, please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 03:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kristen Bell, you are amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 03:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, I really hope that Powerless doesn't suck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 02:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, Emma Stone looks absolutely stunning tonight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 02:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go, Rachel Bloom!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 02:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, at least Questlove is there being a badass on stage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 01:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm rooting for Rachel Bloom to win! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 01:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a brilliant idea, dude. Hopefully someone from The CW is reading this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 23:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rachel Bloom would be awesome as well in the role.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 22:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Terrific number for Hidden Figures - it's going to be really interesting to see whether it or Rogue One gets #1 in the end when final numbers come out tomorrow.

Another great weekend for La La Land - after some Golden Globes wins tonight, it's going to perform extremely well next weekend. 

Why Him has had a quietly impressive run even with pretty meh reviews.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 20:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's definitely one of my favorites as well - it sucks that it is no longer on Netflix, though. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 20:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just started watching it on Netflix within the past week (I'm on the fourth episode now, I think), and I wholeheartedly agree with you. The comic panels in the opening are wonderfully done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 17:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank God it was renewed. The CW is fucking awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 17:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a huge relief to see it renewed - it's such a fucking good show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 02:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty awesome to see a show that has an-all female writing, directing, and producing team, especially since most Hollywood shows unfortunately still have a predominantly male staff. But with this, Jessica Jones hiring all female directors for its next season, as well as Crazy Ex-Girlfriend having a mostly female writing staff, hopefully this trend continues.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 01:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TV Tropes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 01:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All-day Netflix binge and lots of blowjobs and pizza  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 00:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She did write the screenplay for the movie Jane Eyre, which is what the article was referring to (since it's a Hollywood publication).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 23:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yvonne Strahovoski (of Chuck and 24 fame) is also apparently starring in it. It really does have an incredible female cast.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 22:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure I read something in the past that Last Man Standing explores a lot of conservative, Middle American values. So my guess is that a sitcom that is proudly in support of those values appeals to a lot of people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 20:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks pretty great. I'm really digging the cast - Elisabeth Moss, Alexis Bledel, and Samara Riley (Poussey from Orange Is The New Black). 

I guess I'll have to read the book before the show starts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 19:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great number for Hidden Figures - this will probably have superb legs.

Weak for Underworld: Blood Wars. I'm hoping that the final installment of Resident Evil does better later this month (I find those movies to be huge guilty pleasures).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 18:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, that's huge for Last Man Standing. 

Pathetic number for Sleepy Hollow - this will definitely be its final season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 18:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm hoping that The Good Place ticks up in the ratings for its last few episodes. I want a second season REALLY bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 14:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, Stannis.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 03:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Eleanor from The Good Place! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 03:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm unabashedly looking forward to the final Resident Evil movie coming out this month. They're huge guilty pleasures of mine. Don't get me wrong - they're dumb as fuck, but they're a helluva lot of fun (and they look great). Plus, Milla.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 18:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's likely to do gangbusters business in wide release. I can't wait to finally see it myself. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 18:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty meh for The Celebrity Apprentice - this may be its last season.

Solid number as usual for The Bachelor - it always does consistently well for ABC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 18:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, that was a quick reversal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 04:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The First Gentleman  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 21:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> La La Land continues to do amazing business - I really need to get around to seeing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 22:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rogue One continues to do great - I'm really happy to see that it will do $500 million+ and be the #1 movie of the year.

Sing is quite a beast - I never expected it to be the massive hit it is.

Passengers has really recovered nicely after its poor opening day - ahhh, the wonders of the Christmas season.

Moana is doing very well in the face of huge competition - it looks like at will end up with at least $230-240 million domestically.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 18:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it does have some good talent involved (including some writers who wrote some great Trek episodes in the past), so mayyyyybe it will be good?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 05:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lost  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 03:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> _ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 05:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was an incredibly talented woman. I'm going to re-watch Singin' in the Rain this weekend in memory of her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 03:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My deepest condolences go out to her family. No family should have to bear two of their own dying within a day of each other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 03:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2016, you are history's greatest monster.

My deepest condolences go out to her family. What a fucking terrible week this has been.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 03:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus, 2016...why you can't just fucking END already!!?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 19:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her wonderful guest appearance on 30 Rock brought us one of the best Jack Donaghey quotes: "Never follow a hippie to a second location."

What an awesome woman she was.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 19:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really going to miss her. She was such a talented and beautiful woman. RIP, princess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 19:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIP, princess. You will be sorely missed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 18:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here, man! My mother thought it would be a good movie to show my siblings and I since it had cute bunnies (we were like 9 or 10 maybe). We definitely weren't expecting bunnies being brutally murdered. Needless to say, a lot of tears were shed that day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 16:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so happy that La La Land is performing well. I hope it does big business when it's in wide release.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 19:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very good expansion for La La Land. I believe it's supposed to have another expansion next weekend? Hopefully it has a low drop.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 19:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oof, that's terrible for both Passengers and Assassin's Creed. 

Rogue One and Sing are both performing fantastically well, though. They should have very nice Sunday numbers. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 18:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw it three times in the theater - it's a brilliant, hilarious, and heartfelt film. It's still my favorite Pixar film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 11:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, Janet, that was a rather disturbing fun fact. *Sighs mournfully* Guess I need to reprogram her again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 06:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks pretty damn good! They're really delivering on the gore this time, I see.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
