<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3318</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 06:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shot in the dark, but a easy check.......Is there a MM/MC switch on the amp.  (moving magnet/moving coil cartridge)  switch it over if there is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 06:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am "that guy" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 00:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, you can have a pity party or get back on your horse and start riding again.  Pick up your head, dust yourself off and lets get going.   We have a life to live.  No sense sitting around thinking about what you cant change, but you can steer your future in the right direction.  

Lets go, time is being wasted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 23:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get it, this is interesting. Geez, what about the mercury vapor?  I guess its in the name of science. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How does the magic potion called "soap" work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 23:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cutting every day things in half with a water jet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 15:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 00:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you  for sharing.  Getting older and becoming more aware of stuff.   Every time I have heartburn I wonder if this is what my old man felt and if it is time.  I wish you all my best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Redditors who have/had cancer. What happened or what was it that led you to go to the doctor in the first place? Did you suspect cancer at all before you went to the doctor? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 16:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wildlife population and hunting during the great depression. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 04:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My great grandmother spoke of lard sandwiches and soup lines during the great depression. When I think about what I would have done during the great depression to feed my family, I immediately think I would go hunting.  Is there any evidence that the population of wildlife decreased or the sale of hunting guns increased due to families hunting to survive.  

Edit - In the United States </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5:What makes a music conductor renowned, good or bad? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 18:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I can tell they wave their hands around, keeping tempo and telling people when to start and stop playing.   The way I see it is they are telling the musicians to do what is written on the paper and they get all the cheers.
So what makes a conductor good or the best?  How would I know if a conductor made an error?   Have conductors ever been blamed for music not sounding good.   
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 23:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are stronger!  You love your body!  Others actions don't determine what you do.  You are posting because you are sick of the way you have been and you want to change before you hit rock bottom.  You can not change him so don not try, you can change you
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 02:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Zippo lighter in the front and a bandanna in the back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 02:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Amish friend explained it to me like this....To paraphrase - We all agree that there are some evil/bad things on TV that may pull you away from Gods teachings and lead you to sin.  Some might say, well turn off the TV.  However we believe (Amish) that we should rid our lives of anything that may lead us to sin.  
On another note, here in PA a law was passed that milk must be refrigerated once it leaves the cow...(What to do??)  install generators!  Since we have generators, we have vacuum off the engine.  They now have sewing machines that work off the vacuum of the engines.  Hand sewn quilt anyone?
Finally, all decisions are made by the bishop of the parish.  Some are more lenient, Read as....interpret the bible differently.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 17:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like I just read all about myself a year ago.  You are a mirror image of what I was.  Here is the secret........Quit drinking.  It is not what you want to hear and that's ok - nobody wants to hear the truth.  
Now if you think by my saying "Quit drinking" you will stop - you are wrong - it doesn't work that way.  (I would be rich)  You are going to have to really hit rock bottom or get a big kick in the butt or hopefully you can just make up your mind to stop before you really screw up your life.   The facts remain, we can't do it for you and you are hurting yourself.   When you care enough about yourself and the people around you, you will quit drinking on your own.  Your not special, there is nothing different in you that you can keep going and living like you are - we have all tried and said "no not me"  and "I can just cut back"  Bullshit.  You wont cut back and you cant make deals with your drinking.
So there is the answer to your problems. Quit drinking.   Stop bargaining with yourself or bargaining with the booze "oh just one more day"  because you are lying to yourself and the booze will always laugh at you.

Balls in your court Dr.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 03:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a knob for a drawer and the screw.  There are no threads so the knob can turn on the screw.  If it is a glass knob I place it around 1930's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 03:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right!  
Whenever anything hits your car you must say it flew off a truck etc...and hit your car never touching the the road.  (had to pull over and could not catch up to the truck)
If it falls of a truck bounces off the road right in front of you it is a road hazard because it touched the road. 

Many years ago I insured logging trucks in the Carolina's.   We would record the call and if the caller said a piece of wood came off the truck, hit the road and bounced damaging there car we would tell them to take a walk.  When we explained and they changed  their account of the story..... we had the recording.

Word of advice....Stay clear of logging trucks, they are paid by the load.  The faster they go the faster they make money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is one thing a Muslim would like to ask a Christian? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 01:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 01:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As you may well know they were sold by Radio Shack.  My experience tells me that Radio Shack had some really great products, the problem was when I was young I could not afford them. 
If the drivers are fine around the edges (not deteriorated)  I think they would work just fine for everyday use.  Get them off the floor and mess around with the crossovers.  Not going to give you "Audiophile Quality"  but they will definitely handle what you give them as long as the signal is clean.
Good Luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
