<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8657</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How can I continue running while in recovery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 02:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cannot begin to describe how much or even what running means to me. i started at 14 and haven't looked back since. 

Nonetheless i have recently FINALLY stopped counting calories, and although it feels so liberating i have gained a bit of weight and i am very apprehensive about it. I don't know how to cope with it. i do have more energy but i am very tempted to go back to tracking calories and macros even though i know how triggering that is for me. 

How can I safely run and stay on track in my recovery? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: how does BED affect a relationship? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 12:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been dating someone for 5 months now and things are going great, besides the fact that I've just developed bulimia. Another problem is that we're in a long distance relationship. I'm hoping someone here with experience in how ED affect a relationship could share their story and maybe even give me some advice. 

Thing is I worry if I can handle a LDR while struggling with bulimia, and I also worry about how he might take it. But hopefully by reading what you guys have to say I'll be able to decide what to do - or at least be more aware of how my BED may affect him (I believe he has the right to know what it means to be in a relationship with someone who has bulimia).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Hair Thickness and Recovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 02:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have questions for people who have recovery under their belts. Did you ever get back the thickness of your hair? My hair has thinned significantly since I relapsed and I am wondering once I have some solid physical recovery under my belt if my hair will get some of its body back. Much appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Do I have an eating disorder? Can anxiety be the problem? What can I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 14:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever I'm under a lot of stress, or really anxious i starve myself. I don't want to though, I don't want to lose weight but I can't stop myself from not eating.

Does this mean I have an eating disorder? And does anyone know anything that might help me over come this? Please help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Found out my girlfriend has an ED, need to know how I can support her </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 01:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend and I are in our 20s and have been dating for several years and one of the things I fell in love with her for was her love of food. She would eat just about anything and I loved it, she was never significantly overweight, but throughout the time we've been dating, she's gotten lighter and lighter. I come to find out about two years ago that she has an eating disorder where she hyper analyzes her body particularly around stressful times for her, typically around times where she's stressed out because she doesn't have control of the outcome. For her, her intake is something that she can control, so she uses that to feel like she has some control over her life.

I'm struggling to provide a strong support network for her where I don't want to guide her or tell her what to eat, but she often goes through these yo-yoing phases where she'll eat all of the food she likes, and then she'll feel like she's losing control of her image and her life and will either not eat or eat small portions of "healthy" food.

Can someone who has been on the other side of the table give me some advice on how best to help? She's been seeking treatment but I also want to give her a strong system socially and emotionally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Involuntary vomiting with EDNOS and purging, what can I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 01:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have had a problem with EDNOS on and off for several years. This year it was more intense and I had issues with purging. Sometimes I find myself randomly having little throw up just randomly. i am involuntarily throwing up. 

What can I do about this?
If it is related to my EDNOS, and how can I start to get help to prevent more problems? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Want to try Vyvanse to treat my BED, but worried about being judged for my marijuana use. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 01:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking for some help regarding the treatment of BED with Vyvanse from someone who is/was a regular user of marijuana.

For nine months, I have successfully stuck to a specific diet and lost some weight, reducing my weight from an "obese" to an "overweight" BMI. But my binging habits (which I recognize I've had for years) haven't stopped and have severely hampered sustained weight loss. In this time period I tried counseling, which unfortunately didn't help. I'm also a daily, but not heavy, marijuana user. I don't feel that my marijuana consumption exacerbated my binging significantly, although it definitely hasn't helped.

For unrelated (job) reasons, I am no longer using marijuana for the next four to six weeks. However, I have a doctor's appointment in a few days and want to suggest trying Vyvanse (I've done the research on it and considering all other factors, I think it's a viable option for me personally). I am concerned that revealing my history of marijuana use will raise a red flag because Vyvanse has a high potential for abuse, but it's my understanding that urinalysis is pretty standard for amphetamines to check for dosage efficacy anyway.

What's the best way to bring up this subject with my doctor? I fear that asking for Vyvanse, with a history of marijuana use, screams "drug seeking behavior," when I really just want to get my BED under control.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Anxious about treatment for BED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 20:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have recently contacted a therapist about starting treatment for binge eating disorder, but have not yet had any real conversation with them and I have no idea what to expect. I have had anxiety issues for a long time now and have been to therapists unsuccessfully in the past, but I have been coping with stress by overeating nearly every night even as I tell myself to stop, and it has prompted me to really stick with getting help so I don't compromise my health. 

I am really terrified to begin, though, and really want some input on what treatment for binge eating disorder really looks like. I have known for years that I have an "unhealthy relationship with food", but now that it has turned into a real issue, I know I need help. But I desperately want to know what to expect from therapy, etc. I don't like going into things not knowing what to expect, and am terrified that I will stop going like I always have with therapy in the past. 

Does anyone have any suggestions, words of encouragement or advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Crampy, upset stomach and no appetite. How can I deal with this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 19:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obligatory note: I've never been diagnosed with an eating disorder but I'm almost certain I've been on the edge of anorexia for about a year. I went through a rough bout of depression last spring that led to me undereating every day. Food began to not look edible, even my favorite dishes. Anti-depressants helped get me back on track but i still eat much less than I should, and its not a healthy diet at all.

Recently (about 1-2 weeks), when i would normally have a grumbling stomach, instead its just been crampy and generally/vaguely upset and not feeling hungry. Enough so that I don't feel like eating and the thought of eating or strong smells can make me nauseous.

I'm unsure if this is my body progressing into a deeper stage of hunger/eating problems or if it could possibly be related to a new medication I've been taking. I'm taking minocycline for acne (once a day even tho it should be twice a day). The pharmacist says that it shouldn't make me nauseous at all but I can't help but wonder if its causing this problem.

What could be causing this feeling?
How can I eat enough when I do not feel hungry? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Stuck, how do I deal constructively with difficult emotions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 21:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over the past 3-4 years I have been struggling with an eating disorder. I have recently done a lot better this past year and have gained weight. 

I have been looking at old pictures of myself and have become very upset that I am not as skinny as I was a year ago. I have been crying about it a lot and I just don't know what to do anymore and I feel like I don't have anyone to talk to. 

I guess I just need some advice for this situation.

Why am I upset comparing myself to before? 

Who can I talk to about this?

How do I deal constructively with difficult emotions?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> REquest: My girlfriend has an ED, bulimia. I want to be as supportive and sensitive as possible. What is it like being a partner to someone with an ED? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 15:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is clearly a sensitive situation and I need to be methodical about how I engage in this but can use any advice possible. 

She does not know I know about it but I read something she wrote on a paper about binge and purging. I didn't mean to find out something so personal this way and she is keeping her eating disorder a secret. She definitely has an eating disorder no doubt about that. I do not know how to support her in this and do not even know if this is a good place to ask.

How can I support my girlfriend with binge purge ED?

What am I getting myself into? We have been together almost a year now and are talking about long term life goals together. I love her so much and want to be a support system for her.

 Should I confront her about it or let her tell me when she is ready? I notice she always goes to the bathroom after we eat a big meal out in a restaurant and I don't think she is just peeing.


One other thing to note is I know she has a counselor that she talks to regularly but about what I don't know exactly and that's her business but I assume it revolves around this. 

I also want to know what leads someone to have a binge and purge ED?

 I want to know what it is like being a partner in this scenario and set expectations for myself. Do I need to see a counselor to help me be supportive? Do I need to be supportive or hands off?  

Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How do I get over the shame of having an eating disorder? How to deal with people making casual jokes about EDs when they don't know I've done the work to recover from one? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 15:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was diagnosed with anorexia over a year ago and saw an ED specialist and went to therapy for awhile. I have gained my weight back and am a healthy weight.

Sometimes people make jokes about eating disorders around me, and I'm not sure how to react. I've only told a handful of people about it, so the people making the jokes are never people that know. 

I've got a really good thing going where I seem like a very happy and non-fragile person, so people don't really censor themselves and probably don't think they'd ever have to watch themselves joking about EDs. 

I was underweight last year and stayed at that weight for months. It was noticeable that there was a problem, but nobody ever asked and I never told anyone I wasn't close with. Because of the bubbly exterior, I'm sure people assume nothing was wrong.

How can I tell people that it's not cool to joke about eating disorders, especially around me, because that would involve me telling them about mine?

I need help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My girlfriend has EDNOS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 11:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So recently my girlfriend has been going through a lot with regards to her EDOS and ive spent time googling what I can do to help her. But I thought I would ask here for a more personal approach. She will often binge and purge, shes been very open to me about this. But I feel like I could be doing more to help her. We also go to the gym, she will run for a while but my PT said that people use exercise as a form of escapism. Pretty much im just looking for ways I can support her and try to avoid putting her into situations she feels like she needs to purge or binge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I struggle with body image and self-esteem, but I'm not sure if it's an eating disorder. What should I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 04:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went through a phase of eating a very small amount and diet pill usage around 5 years ago (when I had low self esteem), I got more confident but my acne triggered my low self esteem and therefore made me hate my body almost as bad as I used to. I exercise moderately and try to eat healthy, I don't think I have a healthy mind set when it comes to weight loss/body image. I obsess over my body, my boyfriend has noticed that I just stand staring at myself for ages "sucking my stomach into unnatural poses". I'm considering diet pills again just to shed a little more weight. I'm a healthy weight at the moment according to my BMI, I know this but I still think I'm too big.

I don't want to try to get help if it's just low self esteem and will go away because I don't want to rack up any more mental problems.

Do I have an eating disorder, and should I seek help for it?

How can I stop these thoughts and behaviors before it becomes worse? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Missouri Senate Endorses Eating Disorder Bill Requiring Insurance Companies to Cover the Diagnosis and Treatment of Eating Disorders. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 04:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My roommate might be relapsing into his ED... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 21:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
To give you a brief history, my roommate and I are both in recovery for drugs and alcohol (3 years for me, almost 1 year for him). He also had an eating disorder back when he was using. 

He is pretty overweight and I am somewhat, but I am working on it through diet and exercise. Since I have been working on my body, I have been wanting to buy a scale. I mentioned this to him and he told me how insane he got over scales when he was using (restricting and he has ended up in the hospital for this before) and that he would probably do that again. This worries me; that he doesn't think he would have enough self control to have a scale in the apartment at all. 

Last night, he asked me if I had gotten a scale yet and I told him I wouldn't tell him if I did because I don't want him to start starving himself. His response to that was "How do you know I haven't been doing that for about a week now?"

He loves to fuck with me, but I really don't think he was joking. I am worried about his health both mentally and physically. I am also worried that if he starts starving himself to lose weight again to get to what he refers to as his "heroin body" he might actually start shooting heroin again.

As far as I am concerned, I could break the lease and move if that happens. The issue is that I really do not want to see that happen to him. 

I don't know how to talk to him, since I don't know much at all about eating disorders and he is incredibly hard-headed in general.

How can I talk to him about his eating disorder when he seems so reluctant to share? 

Should I try to help him or just move out?

I am sorry for how long this is. If I could get this posted and get some help with this, that would be wonderful.
Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 16:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful posts:

[Selective Eating Disorder](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1fgmhy/post_request_im_suffering_from_selective_eating/)

[SED](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2t4dfo/request_19_yo_male_and_new_to_all_this/)

[Subreddit for Avoidant/Restrictive Food Intake Disorder](http://www.reddit.com/r/ARFID/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Bulimia behavioral questions about my girlfriend. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 16:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know my girlfriend is bulimic. Is just mentioning that I know, making clear there is no pressure to do anything, still potentially bad? How could I say something?

Can people purge silently?

Is there any surefire way to know if my girlfriend is purging when she is in the toilet? 

Is it plausible for a bulimic to wait four hours before purging? 

Is it plausible to purge last thing before and first thing after sleep? 

---

Mod edit: In replies, please do not share methods on "how to purge silently" (if there are any) or give information on how to hide being bulimic. OP wants to know how to help girlfriend, and if he some behaviors are plausible.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Feeling a need to relapse without official treatment-- I feel I won't get treatment until I "look" sick enough, how can I cope and deal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 15:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
I've been struggling with restricting and body image for several years. In the past year, I haven't been restricting very much (mostly due to guilt, since my parents are paying for a fairly expensive meal plan and I feel obligated to use it), but I often have urges to do so and my body image hasn't changed much.

In the past, I've seen a therapist mainly for depression (she didn't seem too concerned about my body image/eating, since I've never gotten to the point of being very underweight), but I haven't had much else. 

I realize that inpatient isn't an option for me at my current weight and I've been having urges to restrict more, partially because I miss it and I hate my body, but also for the purpose of getting to a point where I'm "sick enough" for inpatient treatment.

I realize how incredibly messed up that sounds, but it feels like I can't truly recover without that experience though. Like somehow if I make myself sick enough to need to be in inpatient treatment, my struggles will be legitimate and I won't be a normal weight teenager who just cries a lot about food and her body and used to "diet". 

Somehow, if I got to that point, I wouldn't feel like a fake asking for help to sort out my mind.

I'm sorry if this is kind of scattered and doesn't really make sense. Any advice or thoughts on getting past those feelings and that desire would be greatly appreciated.

What should I do about feeling I need to look sick enough to get inpatient treatment?

I want people to know I'm having a hard time, how can I learn to deal with these inner difficulties?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Selective Eating Disorder/ Food Avoidance Disorder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 15:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

I have a loved one with a food avoidance disorder. I know it is a more rare eating disorder, especially in adults. 

How difficult is it to find a therapist for Food Avoidance Disorder in adults? 

I have also read that CBT and exposure therapy are most effective in treating this disorder. 

Can anyone who has struggled with this disorder tell me what has been helpful for them?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Detecting ED Behaviors in Partner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 02:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My partner has suffered from Bulimia (Binging and Purging) for many years. He claims that he is recovered, however based on the timeline I've created (anecdotes, friends, etc.) it seems like he last engaged in ED behavior most intensely about 6-8 months ago. While I do believe he is making progress towards recovery, he still exhibits some behavior that leads me to believe that he isn't as recovered as he claims. 

For example, he considers snacks meals that consist of two main ingredients, ruling out food groups and over-exercise.

My questions are as follows:

1.What are some signs or indications of things I should look out for that would suggest a relapse? He says he's recovered but I don't believe it.

2.What is the likelihood of being "fully" recovered after only 8 months, and what is the likelihood of relapsing?

3.What are some ways I can be supportive? In this case, he claims his ED wasn't/isn't about body image but rather about control.

4.He is going into a very stressful time in his life, and lately he hasn't had much time to hang out, I don't know if this is him trying to isolate and engage in this behavior or if he is really just that busy. I spoke with a mutual friend (who has experience with ED's, and she's not so convinced he's recovered) and she feels that he's also pushing her away.

Any thoughts, ideas, resources and advice would be excellent. Feel free to ask any follow up questions. I've been seeing him for 6-7 months and I don't have much experience with ED's. A part of me thinks this all might be okay and normal behavior, but I would like some input from someone who knows more about what is and isn't and what I should/could do. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 17:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Health consequences from Bulimia from NEDA:


The recurrent binge-and-purge cycles of bulimia can affect the entire digestive system and can lead to electrolyte and chemical imbalances in the body that affect the heart and other major organ functions.  Some of the health consequences of bulimia nervosa include:

Electrolyte imbalances that can lead to **irregular heartbeats and possibly heart failure** and death.  Electrolyte imbalance is caused by dehydration and loss of potassium, sodium and chloride from the body as a result of purging behaviors.

Potential for **gastric rupture** during periods of bingeing.

Inflammation and possible **rupture of the esophagus** from frequent vomiting.

**Tooth decay** and staining from stomach acids released during frequent vomiting.

Chronic (as in lifelong) **irregular bowel movements and constipation** as a result of laxative abuse.

**Peptic ulcers and pancreatitis.**


Health issues due to laxative abuse, also from NEDA:

Disturbance of electrolyte and mineral balances.  Sodium, potassium, magnesium, and phosphorus are electrolytes and minerals that are present in very specific amounts necessary for proper functioning of the nerves and muscles, including those of the colon and heart.  Upsetting this delicate balance can cause improper functioning of these vital organs.

Severe dehydration may cause **tremors, weakness, blurry vision, fainting, kidney damage,** and, in extreme cases, death. Dehydration often requires medical treatment.

Laxative dependency occurs when the colon stops reacting to usual doses of laxatives so that larger and larger amounts of laxatives may be needed to produce bowel movements.

Internal organ damage may result, including **stretched or lazy colon, colon infection, Irritable Bowel Syndrome**, and, rarely, liver damage. Chronic laxative abuse may contribute to risk of colon cancer.

---

**Hopefully helpful posts:**

[Laxatives and problems](https://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2ecubf/request_have_been_using_laxatives_to_diet_i_cant/).

[How do I decide to recover](https://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2s5uti/request_help_how_do_i_decide_to_recover_bulimia/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My friend is abusing laxatives. What are the risks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 16:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was bulimic for a long time and now instead of vomiting she takes laxatives. 

What are the risks of vomiting? 

What are the risks of laxatives? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: 23 and I'm freaking out. Panicked, undereating, that leads to eating in my sleep. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 03:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 23 years old and I have an ED. I spend most of my days not eating enough and I don't know how to change this. I'm gaining weight because of my medication and its freaking me out and I don't know how to handle it and its becoming more and more obsessive. 

How can I get through a day without panicking? 

How can I eat more?

Also recently I have found out that I have been eating in my sleep. Is it a stress thing? Is it a my body trying to get food even if I'm not awake to get it? what is it?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How do I get help? 16 and cycles of binging, restricting, shame, etc. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 16:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 16 years old and I have always had issues with self-esteem. I'm constantly critiquing every little thing and blowing it out of proportion. 

I never tell anyone, because no one would understand. My parents do not believe in any mental illnesses, and my friends are all rather shallow and judgmental. 

I see myself as weighing much more than I do, I am at a healthy weight but I don't exactly know what I look like. I see a distorted version of whatever I truly look like. I get complimented fairly often, occasionally on my body and how it is an ideal shape, but I feel as though everyone is just lying to me. 

All of these thoughts have led me to go through a cycle of binging, restricting, fasting, feeling ashamed, and then the cycle repeats itself. 

I'm writing this because I have no one else to tell this to. I wish I could just live my life as a teenager, but it's becoming more and more difficult. I just need some help.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How can I get better in a stressful environment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 06:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello all, It is the first time I seek help for my eating disorder. 

I always managed to keep an healthy weight but in my teenage years I was undereating because of stress, which later on turned into over eating and bulimia during high periods of stress. Now I gained weight in a few months as I over eat. I feel breathless and without energy all the time. I don't say anything to anybody even my boyfriend, who does not understand any hint that I give him (willingly or not). 

I have to say I am currently not leaving in my home country and I don't like my life here and I don't like my work, I hold it responsible for my high levels of stress, hence causing me to over eat. I can't fit in any of my clothes anymore and I am wearing only a black dress all the time. I can't go shopping as it is too depressing for me. I would like this to stop but I don't know what to do, I can't pay for therapy and I have in mind that going to therapy will make me even more sick once I am fully aware of the illness. 

Do you think going back to my home country would help ? I have a boyfriend here and I don't want to leave him but I hold my stay here responsible for the quick degradation of my psychology. I wonder if I go back if it would help or if I will just be as sick anywhere, but it seems my highs and lows are closely related to my confidence in my environment. 

How can I deal with this situation? What can I do to feel better?

Thank you. Also, sorry for my poor English, it is not my native language. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Girlfriend with esophageal rupture - how can I help her? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 03:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend binged/purged this weekend after I left and it resulted in an esophageal rupture. It caused her to awaken late that evening with the need to vomit (not self induced). She lives alone and was very scared to see blood - and the realization that her BN has caught up with her hit her hard.

I convinced her to see her general physician and she was open to that. She was honest with the Dr. about what happened, and the Dr. told her how important it was to avoid purging for the next week so as to not exacerbate the problem. But I was surprised to find out that she couldn't even go 24 ours without purging.

I've been dating my girlfriend (31F) for a year and a half. 8 months into our relationship she was honest and told me she had been suffering from BN since she was 15, is on antidepressants, and has only told 1 other person about her BN in her life.

I've read as much as I can online, and have always tried to gently broach this sensitive subject and express my concern, but she'll often refuse to talk about it. This episode with her esophageal rupture , vomitting blood, and inability to follow Dr's orders for 24 horus has escalated my concern to a whole new level. She admitted that she was upset with herself after reading about ED tips online (she sounded jealous). While normally a rational girl, she doesn't think she needs help, and I'm starting to understand how completely distorted her perspective is.

Anyways, I'm not sure why I'm posting here. It has taken a toll on me as well. If she gains any weight then she closes off to the world. Unfortunately we live in a very remote area, but from what I've read think group therapy, or at least someone else to talk to would be super beneficial. Multiple times she has expressed the desire to talk to someone else, but there is no group setting here, only a psychiatrist who she refuses to see.. Additionally, I've reached out to a friend of mine that also has BN that I've recognized via Russel's Sign. I'm hoping to at least ask my other friend for advice, and see if she may be interested in talk to my girlfriend.

Just spitballing here.... Would it be bad to privately reach out to her mom (who she's close with) and make her aware? I live in a small town, and happen to workout with her general physician at the gym - would it be inappropriate to touch base with the physician (also female) to discuss my girlfiend's condition? I'm looking for any words of wisdom.

I think today I'm going to call reach out to the local psychiatrist and see what she has to say.

It has been helpful to write all this down. It's been racing through my head all night. Sorry for the wall of text. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Survey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 03:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The survey contains triggers. 

---

Im researching people who currently or previously deal(t) with eating disorders for my Thesis, and I am looking for willing participants to fill out a related test. Please find the details of the research in the following link, and fill out the test if you think the topic concerns you.

 https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1q_4j9q2OexcGwn7qKvs1U0X4eKUzvDbQoQwLY30dDXo/viewform?usp=send_form

Completing the test would help me with my research, but also, its a chance for you to show how you feel, and have it published in a truthful and honest manner. If you can give the link to anyone who you think could and would like to fill out the test, or if you have a website/blog/other community where it would be appropriate to post it as well, please do so. I would be eternally grateful. 

Thank you, and have nice day, 

Botond

Kroli Gspr University,  Hungary

---

From what we have seen, this survey is appropriate for this subreddit. If it is not, please notify the mods.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 05:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Possibly helpful posts:

[Hunger hormones](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2f0p7y/anorexia_to_binging_its_not_about_will_power_its/)


[Diabetic sight loss](http://www.edinburghnews.scotsman.com/news/singer-lost-sight-due-to-diabetic-eating-disorder-1-3444205)

[BED](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1t355s/request_have_i_developed_binge_eating_disorder/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Type 1 Diabetic, help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 04:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Someone please help. I just need someone to talk to. I won't make this a binge-confessional, but I need to stop and I can't. 

I'm a type 1 diabetic and am making myself very ill. I'm alone and don't know who to turn to. I feel like I can't help myself right now.

What can I do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Worried about my friend-how can I help her get help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 01:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a 19 year old woman who attends university. I have a friend here who I am nervous for. She is extremely thin she is always extremely stressed about her weight. She constantly talks about losing losing more weight and if she indulges in certain foods, she gets extremely upset at herself. I

n addition to that, she is a dancer and we go to a university with a high prevalence of eating disorders because of the competitive atmosphere here. I do not wish to offend her in any way and do not want to hurt my friend, but also do not want to let her suffer from a possible eating disorder. 

What could I do to help her? What are some resources that have helped the people here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How can I help my girlfriend? I'm nervous she's developing an eating disorder. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 01:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My gf of 3 years has been showing some signs recently and I just don't know how to handle it. She's always been healthy and happy but recently I decided to start exercising everyday and got her into it, I figured it would be a fun and proactive bonding activity. Within the last 2(ish) months she's started limiting caloric intake, not super drastically but enough to where it progresses more it will be a real problem, and complaining none stop about being full after small meals, saying she has the mind of someone with an ED. 

She's still a healthy weight and has always and still claims to love food. She even acknowledges that she just really doesn't like her body type to which I reply she looks great and she just needs to learn to love what she has. Nothing is really helping, she doesn't seem to know what would help, and I have to admit I am not very good at handling this. 

I know its not a problem with logic but I just don't know what to do. How do I best handle this? Is it possible to tell if she has an actual disorder? We've always really bonded over our meals together so its really trying for me to not let this drive me totally crazy. I want to help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 17:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Other posts that might be helpful:

[Assault](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1hb23b/post_request_it_started_with_a_toothache_then_i/)

[assault](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/wr7jd/request_im_at_my_wits_end_my_girlfriend_is/)

[Health conscious](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1g9rtm/post_request_unsure_if_eating_is_disordered_or/)



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overcoming an Eating Disorder With Instagram: Showing the hard work of getting better. - The Atlantic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 17:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 16:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out the Hunger Hormones link in the sidebar. That will help a lot.

Also:

[Chewing and spitting](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/15kn0g/postrequest_chewing_and_spitting_occasionally/)

[Not recovering from an ED](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/pra4x/heres_what_happens_after_having_an_ed_for_over_30/)

[Fear of weight gain](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2b1tl1/request_questions_fear_of_being_mentally_healthy/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 15:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From user hoursaid:

Many of us develop ED as a result of a family member suffering from it- it's reasonable that your mind would eventually considering trying it out without your conscious consent. Panic attacks are absolutely unbearable and you deserve to learn more about the process that's occurring behind that anxiety response. The best advice I could offer you is to start some therapy ASAP- you've got to get this off your chest. Internalizing it so much will probably only fuel its crippling grasp. Always keep in mind that you will get through this and that how your mind is thinking right now (that threatened voice scared of gaining weight) will eventually be quieted if you're truly sick of its bullshit. There's many facets of your mind you have yet to fully utilize in order to rescue you from that nasty loop- therapy can genuinely help you learn to get your life back. With my experience with ED- I'd say you're much deeper into it that you realize. I consider myself to be still a bit ridden with ED and all i deal with is an hour or two of restricting per week. I don't suffer panic attacks around it anymore and I can put myself in check fairly quick. The description you've given of your mental state is too much for someone to be forced to manage with every bite of food you take. Working with it weekly or biweekly should really be a priority now. You know you're dealing with a mental ailment and you're healthy for realizing that. Panic your way into the therapists office if you need to- it'll be worth it once your mind starts to accept that it can live just fine without that mess you've described.

Best of luck! I genuinely hope you feel more yourself soon.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Has anyone developed an ED from Rape? How do control issues relate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 15:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me just say that I can't believe I'm on here typing this. I'm fairly new to reddit however reading other's life experiences has helped me to realize how "normal" most of my cognitive processes are. 

I've been a chef pretty much since I graduated high school. I've had an awesome early adulthood--traveled the world, cooked in top restaurants in multiple countries, run my own restaurant by age 22, started my own (successful) health-food focused catering business by 23, and currently cooking for yoga retreats internationally at 24 (currently in Peru) with a specialization in certain foods. My obsession began around 6 months ago. I've always considered myself a very stable and level-headed person. 

My older sister was always the trainwreck--diagnosed with OCD at age 6, heavily medicated by age 7, and suffered a 10 year battle with anorexia nervosa/bulimia beginning around 9 years old. I was always her only friend and confidant and I was the only true witness to her inner struggle through her illness. She is much better now regarding her eating disorder but now struggles with substance abuse. Because I was so intimately involved with my sister's eating disorder I never considered that I may one day develop one. 

When I began cooking professionally I prided myself on my passion for enjoying food, regardless of it's effect on my health. When I began to focus on health food I became obsessed with education of what was "good" and "bad". I have truly made a career cooking what I consider good food for people so I'm very attached to a certain diet that is almost my trademark at this point. I am very good at what I do and to admit that I may have gone too far in my categorizing of "healthy" and "unhealthy" has been a huge step for me. But I really have gone overboard. I don't blame it on one factor--so much in my life has led up to this moment. 

I believe the catalyst event that began my body struggles was over two years ago--I was raped by an Indonesian fisherman with a spear to my neck--it's amazing how adrenaline will give you strength you never knew you had-- I was able to fight him off with my bare hands and escape, but the terror of the experience has not left my subtle body until recently. I was in denial for a long time about the long-term effects of such a life-altering experience. It destroyed an otherwise positive romantic relationship I was having because I was uncomfortable with intimacy--nearly 1.5 years later. Soon after I ended the most positive relationship I've had yet over my intimacy and body-image issues I began to be obsessive about my weight. 

I lost a lot of weight in the year in a half since my attack, but most of my weight loss was from positive lifestyle change  so I thought nothing of it. It wasn't until I was "left to my own devices" that things seemed to spiral out of control. After leaving my boyfriend I had a few fleeting rebounds with men who were quite close to me, but left me with a bad taste in my mouth. It was then that I began to go inward--obsessing over the "bad" food I ate when my self-control was not intact. After eating something as simple as that, I could fall into a guilt trap for days, depriving myself of essential nutrients.

In the past six months it's just continued to spiral. To some degree, My career pushes me in the direction of cooking purer and purer food for a customer base that demands it-.  On the other hand, my obsession with control has gotten completely unhealthy. I limit myself like never before. I can't seem to step out of my boundaries without experiencing extreme panic and anxiety. 

Even though I am very thin and in shape, it doesn't feel like I am thin enough. There is a logical voice inside my head saying "You exercise regularly- you can afford to eat anything you want", but it's matched with another voice from a darker place saying "you're not thin enough, you need to gain more control!" 

As I stated before, moving past the denial stage has happened as recently as the last day or two. I realize I am in the early stages of an eating disorder and I need help but right now, the idea of eating another way, or even worse, putting on a little weight, is the most terrifying thing you could propose to me. 

I guess I'd just love a little feedback.

Has anyone had an ED due to rape?

How do control issues around diet and food and exercise relate to EDs?

How can I get help?

As I said, my whole career is based on cooking healthy food for others and I feel like such a fraud for having these issues when I've spoken out against negative relationships with food after all of this time. I know that I need some kind of help, because the idea of letting go of my preoccupation of control is too much for me to bear. 

Thanks for reading. Any advice would be welcome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Scared that I might be developing an eating disorder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 04:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a 19 year-old female in college. I have struggled with body image since I was about 15 years old. I believe this may be due to my mother's eating problems, as well.

I first struggled with binge eating. After constantly being teased by my family, I had gone on a strict diet and kept reducing my calories. I didn't want to gain weight, so I kept dieting.

My psychologist intervened, saying I shouldn't be so concerned about my body and it would be fine if I increased my calorie intake. She asked to see my food diary, which I obsessed over constantly. I was really scared to increase my calorie intake and I told my mom about it. She told me I could lie on my food journal so that I wouldn't have to actually eat more. I did that for a while but I eventually listened to my psychologist and recovered.

My younger sister has since developed a severe case of anorexia. She has had to be hospitalized for several days because of it. I have tried to stay out of the situation because I know I am not confident about my own body image. However, I can feel myself slipping away.

I do limit my calorie intake and I really don't want to increase it. I find myself chewing food and spitting it out and I'm scared that I'll make that a habit. I don't want to gain weight but I don't want to ruin my health. I don't know what to do. I can't talk to my family about it because they just get mad. They say they can't deal with my problems, too. I can't go to that psychologist anymore because she only sees adolescents. I don't know where to turn at this point, because all of my mental health problems just seem to be getting worse and worse but I'm afraid of people thinking I'm crazy. 

I need advice. What can I do?

Sorry for the poorly-organized post.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How can I help my cousin? I am worried she is developing an eating disorder. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 00:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I was hoping I could ask for some advice on how to help my cousin. She's 15, and has a history of self harm, so I'm worried about her. Last week, she told me she, purged for the first time and has done it about two more times. She also limits her caloric intake, as well.

She has self image issues, and sees everyone as beautiful the way they are, but sees herself as having too many flaws to count. She says that she's doing it because dieting and working out don't work for her, and because others have done it to lose weight, she's convinced it's the only way she can become skinny and pretty. 

I've tried to assure her that she's beautiful the way she is and that going on this path won't make her pretty, as that has to come from the inside, but as she lives in another state I'm not sure what else I can do to help. 

How can I help my cousin from get help?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Abstinence in OA versus no forbidden foods... I'm so confused! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 01:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to my first OA meeting last night and I basically panicked the second I heard the word "abstinence." Over the last couple months I've really hit bottom in my issues with food. I'm desperate, and I had no shame in asking OA for help. But, am I willing to go to any lengths?! I don't think I can abstain. 

I recently started a reading a book about Intuitive Eating and basically the FIRST thing they tell you is ABOLISH FORBIDDEN FOODS! And eat them uninhibitedly until the obsession has been lifted- and the authors and testimonies are seriously convincing that this works. But so are OA members, who abstain.

I don't know what to do. I'm in another 12-step program for a different reason, and I love the 12 steps. I thought OA could help me, but I balked at abstinence.

I need direction... Is the feeling in my gut that abstinence will fail me worth listening to? Or am I ACTUALLY afraid of trying..?

If you have any advice, I am open to any and all suggestions. I just want to find recovery that works for me, that makes me passionate about owning my problems with food and coming out on the other side with experience, strength and hope.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Girlfriend enters residential treatment then tells me she cheated on me and expects me to think that's okay. Why did she do this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 05:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in a pretty rough situation with my girlfriend, and I'd like to get some perspective from other people fighting EDs since she won't talk to me much about it.

Basically what happened was that she cheated on me, then after she told me about it she left for residential treatment. What she wants to do is completely sweep her cheating under the rug until she gets out of residential because she doesn't want to fight two battles at once.

Her actions make me feel awful. I don't feel like it is fair of her to completely ignore the fact that she cheated on me for the next month or more. At the same time, I have always been fully supportive and caring of her fight with Ed. I'm just having trouble understanding why she prioritized things the way she did, and think that maybe some people here could offer some insight that I won't otherwise get to see.

Why did she do this?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How can I support and talk to my good friend with anorexia? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 17:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My very good friend suffers from anorexia and her parents have placed her in a clinic of some sort. I don't know too much about the clinic nor her disorder because she's very quiet and doesn't talk about herself much.

She has access to social media and I am going to visit her tomorrow.  How do I bring this (her anorexia) up and make it a more 'comfortable' topic to talk about?

Thank you in advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to help girlfriend who refuses treatment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 05:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, My girlfriend has been struggling with bulimia a long time. This has become an issue of contention in our relationship and I need support in how I can help her. I've run out of ideas and she refuses therapy of any kind. Thank you
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to deal with triggers in inpatient treatment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 04:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi,

I've suffered from bulimia nervosa for about 8 years, and before that I had diagnosis for anorexia for a few years. So I've lived with this disorder for about ten years, I'm 29 now.

I've been in inpatient treatment center for about a year now. I have been there the longest of the patients. My weight is in normal range and eating doesn't cause that much anxiety anymore.

My problem is that other patients trigger me. New patients, especially, because they are...well, really sick, physically too. I know I'm the biggest patient here right now, and it makes me feel awful.

I do realise that this being a treatment center for eating disorders, being biggest isn't that...awful.But it feels that way.

Is there something I could do to not compare my size to others and be triggered by their behaviour?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists manage to give mice eating disorders by knocking out one gene - Washington Post </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 17:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Recovering bulimic - how to deal with weight gain from needed medication? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 20:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a recovering bulimic who was recently put on medication that has made me gain weight.

I'm terrified that It's going to exacerbate my binging/purging, but need the medicine for my bipolar/depression. I feel trapped in a vicious cycle where my depression won't go away if l gain weight, but it also won't go away if I don't take my medication. 

What is your best advice for dealing with inevitable weight gain?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Worried I might be developing an eating disorder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 18:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello. I am a girl in my early teens, and I'm worried I might be developing a bad relationship with food and body image.

Around December I started trying to live a healthier life, striving for the "perfect body". I started working out regularly and cut out every unhealthy food. Now this is all very good, but I tend to get a little over obsessive with things. I'm not really sure how to explain this. I think a lot about food. Constantly. I pretty much want to eat all the time, even if I'm not hungry. I deny myself because its not 'healthy' to eat and I think I'll gain weight.

I deny myself all unhealthy food all the time, at home or out in public. Always. Even though I really want to, and it makes me feel horrible. I can't eat anything 'unhealthy' without feeling horrible either. If I think I ate too much early on the day I'll starve myself until dinner and not eat anything else but that. I check every food label and do an 'estimate' how many calories I've eaten.

My mom is also worried about me. The other day I completely broke down because of some food related stuff and she asked me if I needed professional help. I said no, but I'm starting to get worried as this is having a really negative impact on my life.

I also worry an extreme amount about my appearance and find things I don't like about myself or aren't 'good enough'. Those things also make me really upset. I researched the internet quite a bit about some eating disorders and body dysmorphia and took some 'tests'. The results of the tests all showed that I needed help and stuff.

I don't know what to do. Is this something serious? Is it just puberty? Part of being a teenager? I don't even know if I explained it well enough. I don't know who to talk to about this. Please help.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Am I Bulimic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 08:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of my friends have become concerned about me and I was wondering if I had Bulimia?

I'm a college freshman and things have been very stressful but I believe this goes back to my ex about a year ago. When we started dating I was at a low weight and was still self conscious and my ex told me he loved me either way, however, that changed. Eventually he told me to restrict the foods I ate and cut calories and eventually had me hooked on his Vyvanse because he wanted me to be as skinny as his exs.

This is what led to my first binge I can remember where I had no solid meal for a few days and ended up consuming a lot when everyone went to bed that night. After that I felt like crap and starved myself but after that I only binged after his Vyvanse. Eventually I moved to college and broke off the toxic relationship and the unlimited dining plan took over my life. I would binge and then starve myself. It became harder so I used laxatives diets. It was and still is a cycle and I gained weight in 6 months and I've come to hate myself so much I can't even change my clothes unless the light is off. My parents aren't supportive because they don't believe in these type of disorders or let alone depression which I don't know if I have or not. I don't have money for therapy and Ive become really obsessed with monitoring calories. I wake up I think about calories and my weight. It's come to the point where I have all the calories memorized of all the foods at the dining hall. I don't make myself throw up but I do still use laxatives and starvation methods after my binges. My roommate doesn't understand because I usually have my binges on weekends when I'm alone and she leaves for the weekend and I've become so obsessed with how I look I haven't been able to wear anything else other than a hoodie for months and I feel so ashamed and I don't really know what to do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Worried about hair loss </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 08:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was bulimic from the end of HS into college.  One day, about 2 years later, I was having some stomach pains so I decided to stop.  It's been (going on) 2 years since I quit and I have some questions.

My teeth have turned quite yellow, but I'm accepting of that.  My real issue is with hair.  I've had a bald spot above my forehead for the past 18ish months and balding eyebrows.  One hasn't suffered much, but the other has progressively gotten worse since I quit.  Anyone in the know have any tips for me?  Ways to help heal it?  I was patient about it for a while, but it's shown no signs of healing so I'm getting annoyed.  Any help is appreciated, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Do eating disorders need to be about body image? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 19:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the last few weeks, I've almost completely lost my appetite. I frequently feel extremely, uncomfortably hungry, especially after having not eaten for as much as a full day, but I still cannot seem to eat anything. When I try to force myself, my throat is uncomfortable and I have trouble swallowing, my stomach usually doesn't like it (even for very mild foods) and eating is just generally an all-around unpleasant experience that I feel I just have no desire to take part in.

I don't have body image issues. I'm a healthy weight, and I exercise regularly, and I've always been generally comfortable with my appearance. I have no conscious desire to avoid eating in order to lose weight or for any other reason, but I've also been under a great deal of emotional stress in my personal and professional life in the last few weeks, and I can't help but wonder whether my symptoms are psychosomatic. (I moved to a new city about a year ago and haven't really made a single friend since I've been here.) 

Lately my frustration with this has started to affect my work, and among other things. I'm making plans to make a career change and go somewhere else within the next few months, in the hopes that I can get past this with a fresh start in a new community.)

I've also tried using marijuana to improve my appetite, with no effect.

Anyways, my main question is this: is it possible that I've developed anorexia? There's a great deal of literature on the internet about "stress-induced anorexia," but it all seems assume that the problem starts with underlying body image issues which are exacerbated by external stress.

I have a psychologist who I saw for some time and who I would ask about this, but due to an insurance marketplace issue I can't get an appointment until next month, so I was hoping to get some advice before then.

Does it sound like I have anorexia?

Does anorexia have to do with stress or is it all about body image?

What can happen if I don't overcome this issue?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Do I have Binge Eating Disorder? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 17:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
So I've always had an addictive personality, and I used to be really addicted to video games. (I would still be addicted to them now, but I don't exactly want that, so I got rid of all of my video game systems, so that I didn't have the temptation around me.) I've also lived my entire life with parents who are total foodies and who have encouraged me to eat unhealthy amounts of food. (My mom is a huge stress eater, and she's encouraged me to be a stress eater as well.) This has all contributed to what I'm pretty sure is Binge Eating Disorder.

Every week, I go grocery shopping with my mom, and it's up to me to buy my own groceries, since I'm an adult and that's what adults do (I'm a 28-year-old female, just FYI). I tend to buy tons of snack foods, since there's no one telling me not to. My version of "snack foods" is a bit different than most people's, though, since I have acid reflux and hypochondria, so I tend to want to buy healthy-ish snack foods, they have no nutritional value except calories, but they aren't sweets. However, I do buy more of those things than I should, which leads me to my next problem: overeating.

I don't have a full-time job right now (I do have a part-time work-from-home job, but it only gives me about 4 to 6 hours of work per week), so I have a lot of free time. I spend some of that time volunteering (I volunteer two days a week at my local library and two days a week at an organization for people who have autism like I do), but I still end up with more free time than I know how to handle. 

And I tend to spend that time alone in my room, mindlessly snacking. I like to snack for as long as I possibly can, until I feel over-full and my reflux kicks in. I also like to eat huge lunches, and, again, I tend to eat until my reflux kicks in. I feel like that stems partly from my aforementioned addictive personality (I love the actual sensation of eating, and these days, it's one of the few things I really enjoy, so I tend to do it to excess), and partly from the fact that I struggle with depression, and my depression makes me want to hurt myself and make myself fat.

I know that I probably do have Binge Eating Disorder, but the fact that I don't tend to eat quite as much or quite as unhealthily as most people with BED (which, again, is due to my acid reflux and hypochondria) makes me wonder. So, any words of wisdom would be really appreciated.

Does it sound like I have Binge Eating Disorder?

Do people with Binge Eating Disorder binge on "healthy" snacks?

If I have it, what can I do to recover?

Thanks for reading, and sorry this was so long!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I don't know how to stop my bulimic episodes, I feel like I've lost power over my behaviors. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 13:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the title says, I'm basically reaching out for help.

I have no idea how to stop.

I'm not totally out of control yet, but this binging and purging has been getting worse over the years. It started out when I was 12 and I wanted to "experiment with bulimia". Not such a good idea, in hindsight I wish I had never knew about it. Nothing really happened for a few years, I had an "experimental anorexic period" for a few months at 16, but that stopped before anyone really did anything about it; my parents weren't really around much to notice stuff going on. I was a stupid teenager. Anyway, fast forward, and at 18 my "bulimic tendencies" came back out and got worse, I was having random patterns of eating healthy and then going on binges. I would say I'd B/P probably every 6 weeks or so for a year. Then it got worse, Maybe B/P for a week straight once a month. And now, at 20, I'm B/P every week at least once or twice. It's getting out of hand. I'm educated in the health field, I know what I'm doing to my body and I know I need to stop, but I just don't know how. I'm too impulsive and can't stop doing it.

What do I do? Is this something I need therapy for? I should mention, I've never been diagnosed with anything, hence all of the quotation marks around everything. How can I help myself?

Thanks in advance.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Not sure what my disorder would be qualified as and I feel like that's where I need to start. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 13:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that I have an unhealthy relationship to food. I have googled eating disorder and I have looked through /r/EatingDisorders but I feel like I pull symptoms from different places so I thought I'd ask all of you if you've got any insight. 

*I am OBSESSED. Unless I am completely engrossed in something (playing a show, making out with somebody, watching a movie in the theater, etc.) I am fixated on when the next time I can eat. I wake up and it's the first thing I think about. After a meal I'm waiting for the next appropriate time. 

*Food is ritualistic for me. I have a certain process for everything I eat. I disassemble and reassemble my sandwiches; I eat certain parts of cookies in a certain order; every bite has to be perfect, containing every element of the food. There is a particular procedure for almost everything. 

*I only eat what I consider "bad" foods alone. I initially did this out of shame but now (even though I do love making and sharing meals with others) if I get it in my head that I'm going to eat alone and someone else is going to be around I get angry. It almost seems like I get the gratification/guilt of eating something "bad" if I eat it in solitude, even if it's a salad. 

*I get furious if my food is not exactly the way I want it to be. I try not to show it but I want to rage when my food is not absolutely perfect. At restaurants I have about a hundred requests for servers because I'm so particular about my food. It's like every meal is sacred, like every meal is my last. 

*I get into patterns: I'm addicted to one food and need it several times a week for months at a time and then it's on to something else. 

*I don't eat until I'm full; I just eat until I'm not hungry anymore and I don't mind leaving food on my plate. (This confuses me because it seem atypical of binge eating disorder.) 

*I am overweight but not dramatically but I obsess over my size and wish desperately that I could look "normal." How I see myself fluctuates. My weight can stay the same but some days I feel massive and disgusting and some days I feel pretty. 

*My weight will often fluctuate drastically throughout each year. I will exercise and diet (basically starve myself) for periods of time until I am the weight I want to be, hold that for a few months, then go back to being overweight. 

*When I used to do a "cleanse" (don't worry, I quit that) I found a certain inner peace because knowing that food was not an option gave me some respite from my obsession. 

*Some days (I'm talking one or two days a year) I will just wake up and feel indifferent to food. I will not have to have my food perfect, I do not obsess between mealtimes, etc. I just feel so at peace on those days. 

*Eating actually does make me happier. If I'm upset about something and I get ice cream it's like my problems disappear for a while. I used to cut myself and the instant relief is very similar. But sometimes I eat because I'm upset about my weight. 

Other things you might want to know: I have bipolar disorder but I am medicated, I cook very healthy meals when I'm not intentionally eating "bad" foods, and I'm very social and have never had any kind of problems eating around people (aside from listed above). 

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to stop feeling guilty every time I eat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 23:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't help but feel guilty every time I eat. I always think about the amount calories I'm consuming and I especially feel guilty if I feel full after my meal. I know this is harmful thinking, but I really can't help it, so what are some ways I can stop feeling guilty?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Advice for couple in recovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 23:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are both in recovery...me from anorexia and her from bulimia. We said from the start that we would not be with each other if one of us relapses. She had sometime of abstinence from purging (I think at most a few weeks). For the past few months, however, she has been acting on purging/bingeing-purging behaviors at least a couple times a week; this does not account for restriction behaviors. I, too, have acted on behaviors from time to time with exercise about two times a week on average.

 
I've always been supportive and non-judgmental whenever behaviors have come in. More recently, I have found myself getting scared and frustrated. My ED gets frustrated because I am trying to not use behaviors and she continues to do so, which makes some parts of me fearful that I am going to get chubby and she will lose interest in me. She says she doesn't want to continue using behaviors and still does so parts of me are also confused. I've talked with her about everything and it's hard. What makes it hard is that I am afraid that she will think that she is not good enough and that she'll never be good enough and then stop being open with me and use behaviors because of me telling her about how I feel about things.


The questions I would like input on are: What defines a relapse? Is it individualized to the person? Although, behavior abstinence is the goal how many times a week of b/p-ing is considered a relapse? Through work does its frequency per week get less and less? Is anyone else in a relationship with someone also recovering from an ED? If so, what comes up for you when the ED comes in and causes a disconnection between you both? What would you feel if your boyfriend/girlfriend, who was also in recovery from an ED, confronted you about your ED behaviors? What would be helpful to hear from your significant other? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anorexia nervosa: New research underlines importance of getting help before chronicity sets in -- ScienceDaily </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 15:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Overcame an eating disorder 6 years ago; still having side affects. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 00:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6 years ago, I stopped eating because I was overweight. I would eat nothing for long periods and then binge and repeat. I overcame my disorder 5 years ago. After five years, I still suffer from muscle weakness, even with healthy eating habits, based on a diet of a nutritionist and muscle building in the gym, with a great coach, I have no results. Are there after effects related to an eating disorder that I should have a look at?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Bulimia bloat or weight gain? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 00:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been in recovery from BP for just under a month. My stomach is really, incredibly bloated right now. How do you know if it's just water retention? Are there any steps I can take to help reduce the symptoms aside from drinking the tons and tons of water I currently down?

My GERD symptoms have gone away, which I started getting right before recovery. I was bulimic for about 2-3 years off and on, with the later part getting very bad. I purged about 4-5 times a day near the end. I'm in therapy and have a nutritionist but how do I help this bloat?

Also, I've skipped a period this month. I'm not pregnant. Is it normal to skip in recovery? I need resources!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Realizing I have binge eating disorder - where to start looking for help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 22:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
I'm coming to terms with the the realization that I have Binge Eating Disorder and/or some kind of food addiction. I always thought I was weak, had no will power, I just needed to try harder etc. But I started doing some research and reading books from the library about BED and food addiction and I understood what's really going on. I have disordered eating.

 Part of me feels relieved to know I am not alone and that there is a name to put to the hell I've been going through for years. The other part of me is terrified to begin a journey of recovery because I have no idea where to start.

I still live at home with my family and do not feel comfortable at all discussing this with them. Which leads me to the next question...how do I go about getting counseling or therapy for this? Do I just call any therapist? Or is it best to go to an ED therapist? Do most people go through insurance or is it out of pocket expenses?

And to anyone who has been through this same journey please feel free to share your stories because I am really comforted by finding forums such as this after suffering alone for so long. Thank you!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Dealing with guilt over BED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 03:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all. I am in the process of recovering from BED. I was binge eating in response to stress for 3-4 years and it ended up having very damaging health consequences for me. I am now recovering from this, changing my lifestyle, and working hard to eat less/better. I am seeing improvements in my health, too. It will still take a lot of work. And I still do struggle with desires to binge and relapse occasionally. But I think with some more time I will make it bake to a healthy place.

However, the hardest thing for me to overcome is still the psychological burden of what happened. I feel incredible guilt and regret. I feel like I lost these years of my life and will never recover them. Feeling like I have to work so hard to regain my health is very psychologically frustrating. It's also hard for me to deal with the health problems that are still with me now. I feel pain from them and just feel intense anger and regret. 

How do people deal with these psychological/emotional challenges during recovery?

I feel like even if I regain my health and recover from this, I will still have regret over this long period of time lost in my life.

Does anyone else have any insight regarding these challenges?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I need help with my binge eating disorder. Thoughts of self harm. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 03:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am an 18 year old male. I have had weight fluctuations since I was 11 years old. When I was 11, I lost a lot of weight at the urging of my mother. Soon I became obsessive. Shortly after that I started high school and my obsessive control over my diet slackened and I began to rapidly gain weight which I held on to for many years. I developed pediatric problems and symptoms of binge eating disorder. I won't bother explaining the symptoms, they were and are textbook.

About a year and a half ago I somehow managed to regain control of what I ate. At first it started slow, and was healthy. But there was a tipping point and I started intentionally undereating whilst overexercising. I also started using laxatives, at first because I thought I was constipated but now I understand that it was symptomatic of my obsession. I went from the "Overweight" BMI category to the lower end of "Normal".

Today, a year on from there, I'm in the middle of the normal range for my height. The road to this has been plagued with inner dispair and self hate. I relinquished my iron-clad control over my diet at the urging of my parents, just like when I was 11. I tried to use my fitness pal to facilitate healthy weight gain but I soon spiralled into old eating habits. My weight gain was slow at first. I countered my binges with restriction of food and drink. When that inevitably lead to more binging, I purged on occasion. In the final months of school I saw a psychologist who diognised me with the disorder. She didn't really help me, I saw her several times. Nothing changed except that being 18, I was allowed to drink. So I drank.

I would binge drink when out with friends because it eased my worried mind. My concerns about food faded and I felt like myself. I could actually enjoy eating without guilt.

However, I would wake up feeling angry at myself. I forced myself onto many diets. They all failed. Several times. So I drank. On occasions, I purged. It hurt. I drank. Eventually, I started habitually drinking when alone. Alcohol dependence was on the ticket, so I quit drinking. Since then I have been filling the void by chewing nicotine gum and drinking diet soda. However, as soon as I stop to attempt sleep, I have to eat. I can't resist. This usually occurs at night after a day of moderation (or obsessive restriction).

All this erratic behaviour has driven me to self despair. I want to bang my head against the wall and wring my own neck. I have emotional ups and downs. I lack motivation in all fields, from sex to exercise to reading. I fantasize about disordered behaviors. I have to fight these urges, amongst all my other urges constantly.

I've tried everything. Diets, calorie counting, mindful eating. You name it, I've tried it. I am at the end of my rope. Please, tell me what to do. Please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> REquest: Looking for advice for family member </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 17:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A family member who is now 26 was anorexic and in and out of treatment centers from 12 to 22. Since then she has suffered from binge eating, where she will stay up all night and just eat whatever is in the fridge. She also won't leave the house after she is at a certain weight because she doesn't want anyone to see her. 

She has been to several treatment centers to try to help with the binge eating, but nothing seems to be effective. She might have a good week, but she always goes back to binging. She has held a few jobs, but says that all she thinks about all day is eating. 

We are trying to figure out other options for her... One option is she could apply for disability and then have a live-in caregiver to keep her from overeating at night. Right now she is at her parents house, and they basically can't keep any food in the house. 

If anyone has any thoughts on how to handle this, it would be greatly appreciated!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Trying to understand how she thinks as far as her eating disorder! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 12:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a good friend of mine who struggles with a pretty serious Eating Disorder, and i am just trying to understand how she thinks with her weight so i can help her out when she comes to me with concerns about said weight.

You see she the other day, she was telling me how much weight she has lost since Christmas, which was something scary, and she said it as if she was worried she had lost so much, as she was already very thin before Christmas.

However last night she came to me and said she had put some weight over the past 2 weeks and said she was angry at her body for putting the weight on?

I understand that it is a constant back and forth fight and although she constantly wants to eat and indulge herself in everything that will help her gain weight, she feels guilty for doing so.

I guess what i am struggling to understand is, what is her thought pattern there?

Why is she angry at herself for putting on weight but also upset with loosing so much weight at the same time? and how do i react to this thought process so i can help her here?

    Concerned Friend

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How To Not Worry About Calories </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 12:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a vegan teenage female with a healthy weight and I eat a healthy amount.

However, I do have quite an unhealthy relationship with food. Even I eat very healthily (almost completely veggies, grains, and fruits), but I still worry if I eat too many calories.

I go through phases of counting calories in things like myfitnesspal or Cron-o-meter and restrict. After a while, I'll tell myself that I shouldn't view food like this, and I'll stop counting calories for a while.

The problem is that since I've been counting calories for such a long time, I pretty much know the calories in most foods, and still worry about it. Eventually, if I gain a pound or two, I'll start logging calories again, and the cycle continues. I want to be able to eat without constantly worrying about it.

tl'dr I want to know how you guys stopped counting calories. And even if you still count them, how not to worry about it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Concerned Friend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 12:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a friend, I'll call Emily, whom I care greatly about that I found out believes she has bulimia. She has admitted to purging on occasion and sometimes just does not eat. I'm very concerned with this especially due to the fact that she has Type 2 Diabetes. To me, these two illnesses together seem like they could be a ticking time bomb if she is not treated for bulimia.

The problem is, Emily does not want to tell anyone. She lives with her mother, and her mother is not very supportive about mental disorders. Emily's brother self injured himself in the past, and when Emily's mother found out, she ridiculed him and told people what he did instead of taking a healthy step to help her son.

I do not want to betray Emily's confidence in me, but it is my firm belief she is in desperate need to see a doctor about her eating disorder. She is only 17 years old, so is still fully connected with her mother's insurance. I'm really looking for some tips where I can help Emily see a doctor and get professional help without her mother finding out about Emily's problem.

Thank you so much for any advice you can provide Reddit
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> France Moves to Ban Underweight Fashion Models to protect the working models. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 14:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Girlfriend struggles with anorexia and I would like to help her </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 12:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend has a long history of struggling with body image and she understands that her habit is unhealthy.

Before we had met, she had seen therapists in the past but she still is living underweight. I've tried talking with her about it and she has said she thinks it's an issue of control.

I love her and I fear for her well-being, but I don't want to make things worse. I'm trying to use words like being healthy and reinforce the fact that I love and support her. What all can I do? She says she is doing alright, but I haven't seen any sign of progress. How can I help and encourage her towards recovery? Thanks!!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Is Male Anorexia real? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 12:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lost a great deal of weight in 7 months and need help.

At my heaviest, when I came forward people laughed at me. Just a chubby white kid.

I then lost a lot of weight, by not eating. I'm concerned

Is Male Anorexia real? What do I do?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Advice on losing weight after recovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 19:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had an ED since I was 13 (now 24), and have mostly stopped all behaviors. I have recently gained weight through over eating because of trying to avoid thinking about food at all.

I am now overweight and it's causing me some difficulty emotionally and physically, I don't feel healthy.

I want to lose weight, but do it without re-triggering behaviors. How do I go about this? I've asked for help from my doctor, but I don't qualify for any help because of not being underweight.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Permanently burst blood vessels / bloodshot eyes from purging? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 14:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 24, struggled with BN for nearly 4 years, but I've been purge-free for almost nine months now. When I was purging regularly, I used to get a lot of burst blood vessels in and around my eyes, very red and bloodshot.

Since stopping purging, though, I've noticed I still have a few lingering bright red veins in the whites of my eyes. 

It's not painful or affecting my vision, so I doubt it's anything serious, but I'm just extremely curious if this is a known or common phenomenon?

I am wondering if anyone has had any similar experience with this happening? 

Is it permanent? Or is it likely unrelated?

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Any advice for binge eating disorder (BED) recovery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 04:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been dealing with this for a while now. Have one or two week phases when I will not binge and it feels great, but at some point have reverted back to my old ways and find myself stuck in the same old patterns.

Just wondered if anybody has been successful in dealing with BED? Share your stories and actions you've taken to help you recover, whether it was therapy or self-help books etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Do those little ED habits ever go away? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 11:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been in recovery for about a year and a half. I sometimes still struggle with random days where I have low confidence and I restrict or at least consider it, but 99 percent of the time, I eat a healthy amount.

However, I've noticed that I still have some odd habits that formed while I had my ED that I just can't shake. I don't like to eat in front of others if I'm the only one eating, I don't like to be first or last to finish my food, I have to cut my meat a certain way, etc.

Do these things ever go away? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Request: Will my immune system ever return to normal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 11:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been recovering for 2 years now; I eat fairly normally albeit less than average people. My immune system is a major issue though... I am literally sick every other week with something new. Pneumonia, upper resp infection, strep, flu.... it's always something. My workplace has been less and less forgiving. I had to stop going to the doctor recently because I ran out of money, so I have to ride out whatever it may be (except for when I had a 104+ fever). I CAN'T TAKE MUCH MORE. When did your immune system return? Will it ever?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I'm starting treatment for bulimia - what are some good resources for my husband? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 00:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
After a fairly long and terrible period of denial, I'm seeking treatment for my eating disorder. I downplayed it for a long time, but I was assessed last week and diagnosed with bulimia, which means I no longer have the option of pretending that this isn't real.

I've put my husband through hell with this - he's a therapist himself and hates that he doesn't know how to help me. 

Can anyone recommend some good books for spouses/partners of ED patients? 

My treatment center offers family therapy and he plans to do it, but I'd like to get some supplemental materials for him. This is a really shitty time, so I appreciate the help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Eating After an ED? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 00:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a really restrictive diet and possibly an ED.

I'm well within the underweight range. I've lost my period, my hair comes out in chunks and now I temporarily lose vision every single time I stand.

I want to develop a healthier and more positive relationship with food and I'm not sure where to start. 


Problem is I haven't snapped out of my narcissistic self image based mindset as of yet: I don't want to look any different as of yet. I just want to not feel like I'm dying.

Does anyone have any suggestions? 

Any ideas on how to healthily and slowly eat more to a moderate amount?

How can I overcome my body image issues? How can I find self-worth not dependent on body image. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: do I have anorexia athletica/exercise bulimia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 14:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all, I'm posting on this subreddit because I've been going through a tough time recently and I'm wondering if I could possibly have an ED.

I've been slim/skinny my entire life but never had a good body image, went to college and gained some weight - enough to push me into the 'normal' category of bodies instead of 'slim/lean'. It's been a 6-month struggle of self-loathing ever since, with calorie restricting and religious exercising 6 days a week. I've seen some results (but not enough) and I don't feel much better about my body. The thing is, I practically depend on exercising now to 'justify' calories that I eat - I feel terribly, horrendously guilty if I don't exercise and/or eat more than my 'allotted' amount of calories. I have a heart rate monitor as well, and push myself to burn 'more' calories each time.

I've recently sprained my ankle, and the fear/guilt at not being able to exercise at all for several weeks is overwhelming. Couple this with some rather insensitive comments that relatives made about my gaining weight in college that triggered my self-loathing big time again, and it's pretty much led to me holing up in my room. I even avoid outings with my friends so that I won't be tempted to consume more calories in the form of food/alcohol, especially now when I can't exercise.

I can't quite find the words to express how angry I am at myself for not being able to exercise and how I can't control myself around food. It's as if the past half-year of restrictive eating has driven my body into a feeding frenzy. At the same time, there's so little information about anorexia athletica out there, and I don't seem to have the classic symptoms of AN or bulimia. 

Can anyone offer some advice?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Request: How to Handle a Weekend Beach Trip </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 09:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Traveling to the beach in a few weeks for a weekend trip with some good friends. Although one of them is my SO (who knows about my issues with extreme calorie cutting and exercising as well as a past history of purging), the rest I don't feel comfortable with knowing about my struggles.

Maintaining normalcy during meals and regular events will be difficult enough, but actually making a beach trip is a different thing entirely. 

I'm on the low end of average weight and build for my height, and I'm at the point where intuitively I understand that I'm healthy and a bathing suit shouldn't be an issue. I'm just too repulsed by myself in a swimsuit to want to wear one in public, but i also can't exactly wear a shirt and pants to swim in. 

Has anyone else been in a similar situation / have any suggestions of how I can control my eating during the trip? I suppose it sounds silly, but when I'm fighting so hard to get this ED under control, the beach just sounds like one more giant hurdle. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Binge Eating as form of Self Harming? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 09:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always had issues with my weight and definitely binge eat.  I will be good for awhile and then binge until I feel physically sick.  I've always assumed that I just had an issue with food.  

During my last relationship I had a some very rough moments where I found myself self harming (cutting) as a way to deal.  I couldn't figure out why this was suddenly an outlet for me in my 30's as I'd never self harmed before.  When I thought about it further, it struck me that maybe the binge eating had been my way of self harming before this.  If I'm dieting I almost enjoy getting super hungry and making myself endure it, and when I'm binging it's in an almost hateful way, like it's physically and emotionally painful but I force myself to endure it.  

Is this a thing?  Can an eating disorder be a form of self harming and if so is it better to seek treatment for the binging or treatment for self harming? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How long did it take you to stop feeling the urge to act on your eating disorder? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 01:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently recovering from bulimia. I have not binged/purged in 3.5 months. Although it happens significantly less often, I still have moments where I want to binge and purge. I don't expect these urges to be gone after only a few months, but it made me curious how long it took others, if at all, to not experience wanting to act on their eating disorder. Sometimes, I feel disheartened that I still have these urges when I know recovery is best for me. I guess I just want some confirmation that there is light at the end of the tunnel.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Advice on achieving a healthier weight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 12:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a teenage male who would like some AN advice.

I have been diagnosed with AN, and I feel like I need a boost to achieve a healthier weight. I enjoy exercise and the foods I prefer tend to be low calorie, such as vegetables and fruits, smoothies and protein shakes. I barely enjoy other foods. Since I have such a small drive to eat, I feel I need to force myself to. I fear I would become bulimic if I do that, which I do not want all.  I just keep dropping weight. I have no idea what to do, as I have become very depressed and self-conscious. Even though I feel healthy, I get weak, dizzy, and have spells causing me to lose all sense of balance and collapse. I need advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vyvanse Approved for Binge-Eating Disorder in Adults </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 11:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Figuring out why I constantly overeat and obsess about food </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 17:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been in a cycle of yo-yo dieting my entire life. I will have some motivating factor (tropical vacation, wedding, etc.) that will give me motivation to diet/exercise, but then once that passes, I try to rely on hunger cues which puts me right back at constantly overeating and obsessing about food.

I almost always eat until I'm very full, and while I'm not eating I'm counting down the minutes until it would be somewhat normal to eat again. I don't want to think about food forever. I just want to lose all of this fat and then maintain a normal weight without obsessing about food. I want to actually be able to have a normal life.

I recently did a bodyfat test at a gym and I'm not happy with the result, and in the past, my cholesterol has been high when I've had extra weight on. This is the heaviest I've ever been. My doctor has done tons of tests on me to figure out why I'm always "hungry" and he says I have no physical issues which would cause this, which makes me think it's a mental issue. My insurance doesn't cover mental health, however, and $100+/session is not something I can afford.

Can anyone help me?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I'm afraid I suffer from BED, but cannot reach for counselor help. What to do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 17:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been overweight during most of my life. I'm 22 at the moment, and little by little I've been fixing that. Eating healthier and working out at the gym is how I'm achieving my goals, and I can see results. However, these results are barely noticeable over time because I have at least 1 binge episode a week. I'm not hungry, I don't even particularly enjoy the food that I'm about to eat, but I can't stop. Sometimes I buy something from the vendors on my way home, or on the convenience store between classes. Working part time at a restaurant doesn't help either, because I am free to eat anytime whatever I want.

I am aware that I have a problem. I am sabotaging my own effort by not being able to control my eating. I carefully crafted a meal plan that provides me enough nutrients to work out, but I still feel that i NEED to eat -note, I'm not hungry-. I am currently living in South Korea, and if any of you doesn't know too much about the perspective korean society has of mental and psychological issues, they are considered somewhat a tabu. Finding counselours or therapists is almost impossible, and most of them are linked to a religion. Also, the language barrier makes it harder to effectively communicate one's troubles.

I've been trying to see my school counselor, and while I appreciate her help, I don't think these sessions are being really useful. Most of the time she just listens and nods. Listens and nods, and tells me she understands. 5 sessions so far in the last 3 weeks. After reading some articles people shared on other subreddits I suggested that we try and discover the root of my problems, why do I do it? She nods and agrees, but goes to repeat the same cycle. I am not sure of her qualifications, and I'm sure that she empathizes with my situation, but that's not the reason why I'm looking for a counselor. I need help. Any advice?

Thanks
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to deal with stretch marks both mentally and physically? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 22:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am recovering from an eating disorder, and during the process I have created noticeable stretch marks. They are mostly on my legs.

I break down into tears every time I look at them and think about what this summer is going to be like. I won't be able to wear shorts, or go to the beach... not without wanting to cry every time someone looks at me. I don't have the confidence to walk around like this. This whole ordeal is making me slip back into my disorder and I'm terrified.

To get to the point: what can I do? How am I supposed to handle this mentally? It's like I worked so fucking hard to learn to accept myself at a healthy weight, and then this happens and I have never been so disgusted by myself. I now see myself as fat because that I have stretch marks, and even if I lost weight again, they will still be there to remind me.

Has anyone had any experience at all in regards to stretch marks during recovery? I honestly don't know how I am going to handle this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Has anyone been diagnosed or tested for LQTS? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 09:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My doctor referred me to a cardiologist for possible LQTS. Of course, nothing else has been ruled out yet but I mentioned shortness of breath and dizzy spells and that's where I'm assuming LQTS comes into play. From what I understand it's largely genetic but most of my family is healthy.

What did the first appointment with a cardiologist go like, and how does it affect your life now? I've read into it but am trying not to get too scared. Honesty is still appreciated, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to overcome a missaying? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 09:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So basically my boyfriend tried to give me a compliment for my body but it ended up with him telling me that he has seen persons with better some features than me. Later on he told me I misunderstood him.

It's not like im trying to forbid him to find other people more attractive, but I do not want to hear about it at this point in my life. For me this was absolutely soul crushing. I got really sad, and now I cant get over it. I cant do nothing but feeling a great urge to hide my body, and start with this unhealthy pattern again. All I think about is this and I don't know what to do. I had come quite a long way in recovery, but now I'm at square one again.

How can I get over this missaying and deal with this in the future? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Girlfriend struggling with ED wants to try new diet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 07:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like many of the posts on here, I am dating a perfect girl despite her struggle with a binge/purge ED.  She has been working at this for a few years with professional help and has her ups and downs and lately she has had more ups than downs, but just tonight she told me about a new diet that she is dead set to try (I don't know if I can say it on here or not, let me know if I can). She was eating healthy and working out at a reasonable rate and was losing weight, but not fast enough, according to her. She was most upset because I hadn't noticed enough to say anything. In hindsight, I suppose I am an idiot for knowing that she was working hard and I didn't affirm it, although I did praise her work ethic and how drive to do things in a healthy manner. 

She has a deeply rooted issue with overdoing it at the gym and taking laxatives, and has basically stopped that, but she will occasionally slip back into those habits. She claims that I am a huge help with body confidence and so on and that she would rather talk to me than her counselor, but I feel like I'm watching my best friend drown and I don't know how to swim. I do not feel as if I am fully equipped to be her go-to, but I am honored that she feels she can feels she can confide in me. 

I don't want to make this about me, but it hurts me a terrible amount to see her go through this and know that I can't put an end to it with the snap of a finger. I guess what I am looking for is: A) more/better ways to help her, B) whether her new diet will be healthy, and C) a virtual ear to hear me, because she doesn't exactly want my friends to know, so I don't really have anyone to turn to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Looking for help accepting weight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 11:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
25yo guy here. About this time last year, I was in a hugely stressful job and started drinking heavily every weekend to cope. That had side effects in terrible hookups. I decided to sort my life out.

After I'd quit my job and had been unemployed for a couple of months, I took up Thai boxing. It was great for stress relief and helped me sleep better. I avoided a lot of the depression that would have come with unemployment and the dieting and stress relief stopped me drinking.

I was bullied for being a fat kid when I was younger. The other thing was that I grew up in a conservative Christian home. I lost my faith a few years back, but I always had trouble caring about my body. The only thing that really mattered was my relationship with God and so external health was a bit of a side pursuit.

I'm a keen cook, and so it's easy for me to know how much is in everything I make. I lost weight and am aware what goes into my mouth and read the calorie information from everything else.

When I started I was way above my correct weight category. In the last month I've been about right. I could be less. I'm basically trim, but not ripped. I'm very much a beginner though, so minor weight losses are nowhere near as important as getting technique right. Frankly I could be a higher weight and I'd be fine.

What's started happening is that I diet over half the week, and then I'll eat way over. Then, I work hard the to undo the damage. But the main thing is I just obsess about food.


I just want to be my weight and not think about it. I put on one pound and I'm a failure. I'm scared of going on holiday, going out midweek. Whenever I eat with friends I tend to overeat.

I've been in my job for about 6 months now. It's in a different city and I haven't met nearly as many people as I'd hoped. I'm tremendously lonely and last month I had a huge argument with my father for unrelated reasons and I've just started to feel incredibly isolated.

I want to spend more time on other things, but if I eat too much in a day, I have to go to the gym. If I meet up with friends, I'll get upset if we drive anywhere. I'll purposefully walk long pointless routes everywhere I go to burn calories.

I thought this was the best place to ask about how to be sensible.

How do I accept my weight and regular fluctuations in it?

How do I not obsess on food?

How can I not be upset going out to eat with friends?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My Girlfriend is in recovery for her ED; asks tough questions about whether she looks like she's gained weight or not? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 12:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've had a long, bumpy right, but let me first say it's been positive and marvelous. She's recently been hospitalized, and I wish to be as helpful as her family has been to her, but there's certain "boyfriend" questions that always get me. In particular, now that she's in inpatient, she's asking if I can tell if she's gained.

Of course, she has, and I can tell simply by how much healthier she looks in her face and hands, but any direction I take is a pitfall, because I can't dodge her wanting a simple 'yes' or 'no' response. 

What is the best response? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Am I on my way to an eating disorder? Guilt around eating. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 12:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a 20 year old male who have had a turbulent last few years. I don't want to go into detail, because that's a whole other story, but for a short summary so you know what it's about.

Three years ago I had surgery to correct a nerve condition in my arms. This had hindered me to work out for almost a year by the time I had the surgery, and has prevented me from working out full ever since. Before I the problems started, I was going into elite training for sprinting. I worked out at least 6 times a week and held a good diet. I was very healthy, apart from that nerve condition.

However, ever since I wasn't able to work out "properly" I've been having pretty big body image issues. Since I can't work out to get the body I really want to have, I've been struggling to accept the body I have now and "settle" so to speak. The ways I see myself in the mirror vary a lot, sometimes I see a skinny-fat nerd, sometimes an athletic runner. This messes with my selfworth and also with my approach to food.

I tell myself I eat healthy. I don't eat candy, cakes, muffins or anything like that, I don't drink soda and I stay away from fast food. I always eat a big breakfast, but I think that's mostly out of habit nowadays, since that's something I've always done. The kicker is my unwillingness to eat lunch and dinner.

I hate feeling hungry, but not more than I hate feeling really full. I also get really guilt-tripped by myself if I eat big meals when I haven't "earned" them, like having worked out before. This has become a big problem now, because in my current place of living, I can't work out as often as I really need to. I do get out, but not as often as I need to feel I deserve to eat.

So far, this hasn't stopped me for eating my proper share of food per day (I think), but the guilt has been towering, and culminated the other day when I almost threw out a whole meal when I got the notice that my soccer practice that evening got cancelled.

I haven't talked to anyone about these feelings of guilt with anyone, and I am sure that to an outsider (and to my roommates) it would seem that I eat and feel just fine. But the truth is, I don't, and I'm worried this might escalate if I don't do something about it. But I don't know what to do. 

Does anyone have any advice or any similiar experiences? Anyways, thanks for reading, and I hope you all have a wonderful day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Post: Doctors that don't trigger you? Obese, ADD, and fibromyalgia with an eating disorder. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 12:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I had anorexia because I was unhappy and didn't know how to express my emotions any other way. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 10:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Help! trying to end with bulimia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 10:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It all began about 1 year ago, when I started paying attention to what i was eating, like counting calories, stopped eating cheese, pasta, bread, eggs, etc. I lost weight very fast. After a while it became more and more difficult to keep track so i started cheating but doing more exercise the day after instead of making myself vomit. Then it all went down when i tried to throw out. It looked so easy to me! I could eat whatever I wanted and all i would have to do was to purge. That way, i wouldn't feel bad and all my efforts wouldn't be ruined. Lately I've decided that it was enough, that I could not spend my life having this weird/disgusting/love-hate relation with food. 

I tried to get out since by eating normally, reintroducing forbidden food in my diet and most of all, stop purging. But it became worse!! I've gain so much weight cause i don't feel satiety anymore. And i just binge all the time, like literally eating non stop, i can't control myself.

Can anyone give advice on how to stop this? I need help!!!

(sorry for the mistakes i am not a anglophone)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My GF told me she is bulimic, how can I be a supportive boyfriend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 10:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I posted this in the relationship subreddit too, wanted to post here and get opinions from those who have first hand experience.

So I've been seeing this girl for a few weeks now, things have been going pretty well, she is amazing! She told me she has bulimia, she feels fat and horrible when she eats and she purges it afterwards. She tells me she's getting help for it which is great! I wanna know how, as her boyfriend I can help her through everything. I love the girl so much and I'll do anything to make her happy. I have been telling her how much I care about her and how beautiful I think she is (and mean it!) and I'm doing what I can think of to be really supportive but sometimes I seem to screw up. Today she found herself having to eat in front of a bunch of people and she was really uncomfortable with it. She texted me that she wanted to purge and how she felt fat and I told her not to feel pressured and just to eat as much as she could without wanting to purge it afterwards and she did, afterwards I asked her if she ended up purging and she said "no" and I told her I was so proud of her but I accidentally pissed her off by asking. I didn't realize that was something I wasn't supposed to ask, I was trying to be supportive. Now she's mad at me, I don't want to keep accidentally making her upset. What are things to be aware of and that I should/ shouldn't do to be a good boyfriend and help her without accidentally offending her? 

tl;dr My GF is bulimic, I don't know how to be supportive besides usual Boyfriend stuff, I accidentally offended her. What should I do in the future to be better for her?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Are non-aerobic exercises still considered purging? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 12:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I'm not sure if I specifically have AN, but I've been underweight for a little under a year and have been carefully watching everything I put in my body.

Anyways, the good news is that I'm finally starting to reintroduce a wider variety of foods into my daily life, including ones that I thought of as "junk" foods. The bad news, however, is that some of these foods still cause me anxiety. Just this night, for instance, I purposefully ate something that caused me anxiety, and I immediately proceeded to start strength training exercises afterwards (muscle, not endurance/aerobic). I'm already strength training twice a week for about 20-30 minutes each, but I always seem to add an extra exercise on the days I eat these foods.

Should I be OK with my current twice a week program and just remind myself that it's OK to eat these foods, should I focus on the quality of my food more, should I train more frequently, or should I plan to eat these foods only on the days where I'm lifting?

I can't seem to shake my anxieties over these foods. I've dropped most heavy cardio, so I don't think this qualifies as purging. But I want to make sure I'm following a healthy path. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: General Doctors Not Getting It </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 08:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to a GP after literally years of not seeing one. I saw one about 4 years ago when I was getting ready to go to treatment and since then everything has been done with my psych. 

I have been absent from all doctors (including my psych) for almost a year due to a lack of health insurance. I was recently eligible for insurance again, so I went to a GP because I need referrals (all those dealing with this kind of insurance in the States get me). When I was diagnosed, I was an ED-NOS special snowflake, which under the new DSM would just be bulimic. One of the many ways I purged was using laxatives, but not to the point where I am dependent on them (I know some of my treatment buddies have to use them on a regular basis).

My GP hears about my, to put this nicely, occasional irregularity, and tries to prescribe me a laxative. I told her no, and explained why. She didn't understand why I wouldn't want to have laxatives in my apartment. I mean, it's one thing to get it once, but to have a prescription bottle full of the stuff is just too much for me. 

I would rather just deal with it with natural ways (like fruit or something) than having that around. Like, I thought of it as like me being an alcoholic and my doctor saying, "eh, just keep a bottle of vodka around the house... you know, just in case."

Does anyone else have trouble explaining to a GP their ED issues? This isn't the first time that I have experienced something like this in the general medical field, and I was just wondering if others have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I'm binging at my parents' house </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 07:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...and pretty much *only* at my parents' house. When I come home from college for weekends or holidays, I find myself binging on cereal and hating myself for it. It's always cereal. It's always at my parents' house. They're supporting three kids (besides myself), so I can't ask them to just stop buying cereal, and I can't *not* visit them over holidays. 

I struggled with (and continue to struggle with) anorexia, and after several months of treatment (which my mother arranged for me) I was released back into normal society. Now, however, she doesn't seem to notice that all of the cereal in the house vanishes when I come over. She just says it's "healthy" that I'm eating again. 

But it's not healthy. I eat until I'm sick and disgusted with myself. I don't even know why. I look at these bags of cereal and think, "This stuff isn't even that great," and I eat it anyway. It's always at home. It's always when I'm bored as hell and alone while everyone is at school (everyone is either a student or a member of the local school staff). 

Please help me. My mother is blind, my stepdad is ignorant, and my siblings don't understand. How can I get passed this?

Thank you,
-J </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to deal with stretch marks both mentally and physically? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 07:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am recovering from an eating disorder, and during the process I have created noticeable stretch marks. They are mostly on my legs.

I break down into tears every time I look at them and think about what this summer is going to be like. I won't be able to wear shorts, or go to the beach... not without wanting to cry every time someone looks at me. I don't have the confidence to walk around like this. This whole ordeal is making me slip back into my disorder and I'm terrified.

To get to the point: what can I do? How am I supposed to handle this mentally? It's like I worked so fucking hard to learn to accept myself at a healthy weight, and then this happens and I have never been so disgusted by myself. I now see myself as fat because that I have stretch marks, and even if I lost weight again, they will still be there to remind me.

Has anyone had any experience at all in regards to stretch marks during recovery? I honestly don't know how I am going to handle this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Think I'm bulimic, gonna see doctor on Fri </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 03:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey! So I'm pretty sure I'm bulimic. It started with a diet that worked, but I gained all the weight back. Now I fast at least 2 days a week and I binge at least 2 days a week. It really sucks and also I'm slightly gaining weight which I totally hate.

Anyways I'm going to see a gynecologist on friday, which I guess they can also work as a primary doctor? Anyways I have parents who I really don't want to know about this (TBH they're a huge part of the reason I'm like this anyways because they're abusive) so how would I find a therapist? Cuz my parents can't know? And even though I'm in high school our school counselor sucks (I'm not going into it but I'd rather have bulimia 5ever than see her again). So yea that's the main problem here.

Cheers! I'm /u/winetes, please message me if you reply :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I'm thinking of seeing a nutritionist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 03:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, I should start by saying that I've never been diagnosed with an ED, but I have an unhealthy relationship with food, that started in my childhood. I purge, binge, and do other unhealthy things, I also try to mantain a healthy diet.

But lately, I've been acknowledging the fact that something's not right with my eating habits, and I should seek help.

I've been to a nutritionist before, but this is the first time I visit one, and I'm going because I'm suspecting something's wrong with my eating habits.

What should I expect from my first visit? Since I'm visiting as a patient who needs help with her unhealthy habits, instead of a patient who wants to lose weight and is overweight- supposing there's a difference-.

Thanks!

I also would like to say, to all of you who are in recovery, that you're stronger than you think you are, you're so much more than a number or someone's negative opinion. Don't let setbacks make you feel like a failure, you're amazing!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I feel like I have a part-time eating disorder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 16:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am 31, a mother and a wife. I am over weight but not by a large scale, just heavier than I should be in order to be in the healthy BMI range..

About 6 years ago I lost a significant amount of weight in just over a year. I became obsessed with food and dieting.

Over the years, I have put some of that back on. I know how to eat healthily, I know about exercise but I get into these self destructive cycles where I will diet and exercise and start to see progress (feel and look better) but if I fall off the wagon by over eating one day, I will occasionally purge. I feel broken by relationship with food and calorie counting.

I have always associated bulimia with making yourself sick after every meal. I do not do this. When I am not dieting, I don't eat with much moderation but when I am in a frame of mine where I am not dieting, I don't purge.

When I keep food diaries I am borderline obsessed with everything that goes into my mouth and hate myself if I go over my deficit calories. If I do, I purge.

Because I go through these two week cycles of "not caring" and then dieting to undo the damage which sometimes involves purging, I stay the same weight. I can't break the cycle. I just want to be an a "normal" BMI and eat in moderation.

I really want to lose this extra weight but I don't know what to do. I am mortified by my behaviour. No other human being in my life knows this. There is no way I can tell my husband or talk to a doctor. I have tried to will power myself out of this cycle but I keep failing and it is exhausting. I don't even know if I have an ED or what to make of all this. How do I get a handle on this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How do you deal with the reality of a diagnosis when it is something you've already known yourself? Thoughts in overdrive. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 00:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always known I've had eating issues, and a disorder. In fact, I have accurately self diagnosed it seems. I've been struggling since I was 13. 

I was recently diagnosed with Atypical Anorexia Nervosa. I self diagnosed that previously (hence why I said I was correct).

 So...why is it hitting me so difficultly? Why are all my restrictive habits/thoughts in OVERDRIVE since diagnosis?

How do you deal with the reality of a diagnosis when it is something you've already known yourself? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: It infuriates me when he asks me what I'm cooking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 10:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have not been diagnosed with an eating disorder, but I do have a tendency to binge. I'm also in the middle of a bad bout with depression.

It doesn't happen every time, but when I'm making something for me to eat and my boyfriend asks me what I'm making, it strikes a nerve. I just want to scream at him "Food! I'm making food! You aren't going to eat it anyway, so why does it even matter what I'm making!?" He asks me what I'm making so much that it makes me feel guilty that I'm eating at all. I know he doesn't mean to make me feel this way, but I do. I don't exactly know why. 

Is this a symptom of a disorder, depression, or just something that I need to learn to deal with?

I have talked to him about it, but it usually ends up with me being angry, and things don't change anyway. He just continues to ask me what I'm making. I don't really know what to do about this. I don't even know if this feeling is common. Honestly, I don't even know if I'm looking for advice, or sympathy, or someone to relate to. I guess mostly, I'm just looking for calm.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to handle meal times when my friends coming to visit me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 10:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello there! I am currently living away from home to attend school in the PNW. Recently, several of my friends from back home have been talking about coming to visit me. Two sets of sisters will be flying up to stay with in April. The first pair will be coming the first week or so and the second should be arriving shortly after the first two go back to California. Obviously, I am really excited to see my loved ones and show them around the new place I have fallen in love with. However, I am really nervous on what meal times are going to look like and would really love some advice. 

All the friends who are coming to visit me know I have a history with ED so it's not like I have anything to hide but still. The first set of sisters are kind of triggering for me as it is seeing as they have a body type my ED finds very appealing and have very sporadic eating habits due to their extremely busy schedule of working nearly full time and putting themselves through community college. I don't know- I just feel like the pressure to eat out daily will be really anxiety producing for me and I am just really nervous on how to handle it. 

Does anybody have any advice? I hope I gave enough context to shed light on what's troubling me.

Thank you and I wish you all the best! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: A question about recovering from bulimia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 02:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will be almost a month since i stopped binging and purging and I have noticed that I gained weight. It hasn't been significant, but enough to put me into a panic. I have been watching what I eat ever since I stopped B/Ping and logging the food I eat to keep track of my calories. I am trying not to obsess over my weight and have stopped weighing myself every morning to prevent myself from being dejected the whole day in case I have gained weight. I know this will be better for me in the long run and have decided to only weigh myself every 2 weeks to once a month so that I can get a better picture of my real progress. The question is; how can I keep myself from obsessing over my weight and continue with my new lifestyle? Also, is it normal to gain weight after being bulimic for so many years? Thank you in advance for any comments/suggestions you can offer.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Recently diagnosed with BED-What are my options? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 01:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've just been diagnosed with BED and I was wondering if anyone could give me some information about the types of treatment available, tips for recovery, etc. 

My therapist said we would not be focusing on food at least for now (so no food journals and such), and I also don't want medication. 

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Made a mistake last night. Please help. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 19:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After over 10 years without a purge, I slipped up last night and I worry about this becoming a habit. My husband is aware that I have bouts of anorexia, but was not aware that I also occasionally purged before meeting him.

I've been trying to maintain a healthy weight and I am right in the middle of the BMI scale for healthy weight. I have a tendency to binge, but I normally just eat slightly less the next day. I remind myself that even a one night binge won't cause much weight gain. I've been on track. I have a math brain and so I work out the exact weight of the calories I consumed to show myself it's not a huge mistake.

But last night, I was about to go the sleep, but my husband complained I was going to sleep 'too early' and woke me up. Being woken up, is a trigger for me to binge. And I did.

So I asked him to please not wake me up again, because it causes me to eat food I really don't need. And he replied 'Well why don't you just throw it up then.' In a half joking, half annoyed that I complained manner.

So I did. And I was so ashamed my myself. My daughter's bedroom and my stepson's room are right outside the bathroom. I'm sure they must've heard me vomiting. All for the sake of a few hundred calories.

I went back into our bedroom and my husband said 'Did you just have a bath?' I shook my head no and he knew then. He said 'Why would you do that? I was only joking.' And I know he didn't know and didn't mean anything by it. But at that time, he suggested it and it seemed like a quick fix.

I don't want to fall back into this bad habit. I don't want my daughters to notice, or to think this is a normal behaviour. I don't want to end up with bad teeth or a heart condition. I am setting ground rules for bedtime tonight and insist that I not be woken up unnecessarily. Do any of you have any insight into this? How do I stop binging? How do I make sure I don't get into this awful habit again?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How can I adjust to a healthy body weight without feeling triggered to use behaviors? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 01:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the around high school until my junior year of college, I had gradually worsened my eating habits into an EDNOS. I finally got help my junior year via therapy, but I was only in for a few months. 

I started on the right track to get better and my closest friends who knew and my SO have been supporting me immensely.

I've just moved countries, and I'm trying to better myself. I eat three meals a day now (which I had a had time doing before), and I'll snack during the day too. I used to be at a lower weight for my body and still felt it was "too big". Now, I feel as though I'm gaining weight (I don't have a scale) which is healthy, and I'm exercising quite a bit, but I'm having a hard time coming to terms with how my body is looking now. 

Sitting down is the worst - I feel horrible about my body when I look at my stomach.

How can I stop this? I want to feel better about myself, I want to get better, but it's hard when sitting down feels like it's triggering me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Afraid I'm developing an eating disorder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 01:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've noticed recently that I've been counting calories more than I should be, and trying to exercise to balance my day out. I'm obsessed with my intake and output, and I know that I am on a very slippery slope. I'm wondering if anyone has any tips to get out of this mindset? I am worried I am developing an eating disorder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
