<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5711</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 04:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my sister is doing all these things but i believe so different from her 
i think its crazy not to vaccinate i mean even if it causes autism (i don't think it does) its that or death really 

Co-sleeping i proven to increase SIDS 5X more 

so much more it pisses me off  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 04:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have hearing aids and have been asked about an implant i said no I'm 20 years old. But deaf people have there own schools ,there own language everything. Sadly like saying black people could just not be black they have there own culture why should we change it. So what i am saying is that children should not get the implant until they are old enough to make these choices for themselves.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 04:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if i ever have children it will be ONE  ( older child and adopted)no more then that because its the ability to be a mom but also be not overwhelmed with whining children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 04:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you are preaching to the choir i know exactly how you feel but really theres nothing that can be done. I would really suggest getting some counselling. Offer her to come to if she says no then you don't need that negativity in your life. It will only hinder your recovery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 04:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have 2 other siblings and i am the oldest i would 100% choose to be an only child not that i don't love my siblings. I feel i was meant to be an only child i am very selfish and quite a loner. I don't like(actually i really hate her) my sister who is close in age. I expect to have all the attention( yes i am bitchy i know) so for me i am a strong believer in only children </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 00:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fat people are fucking disgusting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 00:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> beat me to it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 00:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ER or doctors now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 00:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i think thats a miscarriage memorial ornament but still scary as fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 00:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats not safe for life  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 00:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you could give it to a school they love stuff like that  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 00:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so glad i am allergic to bananas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 00:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did you taste it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 00:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i must look this up i have the same issues as you so many ear problems but i lived with 2 chain smokers for my whole life always right next to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 00:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mind if i ask how you go could go deaf from smoking  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 00:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no i cant stand her yes yes 3 months pregnant and has a 4 month old didn't finish 10th grade and is 18 so you know. But she does take good care of him thats really the only good thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 23:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> exams YES i think its just my sister then she dosent drive. Refuses to cook for clean and hands the baby off to my parents. She doesn't pay bills or have animals and her son sleeps more then any baby i know 8+hours a night.+3 naps a day 1.5 hours  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dreaming about cancer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 22:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 22:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i am 20 i am not solid on not having a child but i know 100% if i do i will adopt an older child and just have 1. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> moms who don't work </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 22:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i know this is a little off topic but i just wanted to know what you thought about it. 


My sister has a 4 month old if you remember my last post. she is always saying that she's so tired and being a stay at home mom is so hard and my jobs no that hard. Always saying i don't know what its like to be tired she is living with my mom well she's pregnant and looks after her 4 month old i have seen what she does all day. 

She sits playing on the laptop ,smokes in the kitchen, watches bad talk shows and ghost shows. Then she has a nap or two. Takes a bath then makes a few bottles.


no your not working harder then me i go to school and i work as a nutritionist in an office with lots of clients and co-workers.

I'm sorry being a stay at home mom is NOT a hard job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 22:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just forget it what good could come of  bringing everything up and then theres cops and court and trials  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 21:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> gag me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 21:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is offensive to everyone with anorexia LIKE ME </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 21:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> her face looks like a car hit it. She actually looks like a pig </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-19 23:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cars those oppressive assholes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-19 23:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh so thats why i got cheated on right right good to know i will hit the gym ( i have a bmi of 17.2)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-19 23:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> holy shit 1 mile thats like 5 minutes more if you cant do anything for an extra 5 minutes your not in that great of "shape" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Imaginary friends </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-19 04:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have been with my wife for 2 years and she's always talking about these friends she has. When we were just dating she would always say that she was hanging with friends. She tells me stories about her adventures with them. Heres the thing i have never seen or talked to a single one of them. she's never texted any of them. i know she's lying but what do i say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-19 04:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i had the same thing i didn't brush my teeth or floss for years and went to the dentist i have GREAT teeth no cavities nothing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-19 04:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my sister is 18 years old ( turned so in july) and has a 4 month old and is 3 months pregnant with just a grade 10 education it makes me want to scream as well  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Family is trying to kill me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 22:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i am deathly allergic to bananas even touching something with banana on it will cause me to stop breathing.
i am currently staying with my family for the last few months 
but my family doesn't seem to care i have allergies they give my 6 year old brother bananas, juice with bananas and he just runs around and touches everything. My mother keeps them in the fridge with everything saying they help her when she has a headache she yelled at me that she hates headache i yelled at her i hate to be dead. Now my sister is feeding her 4 month old bananas i kiss that baby. they don't let me know that it happening because they dont want to upset me. 
OH the best part we live 2 hours from a hospital so if something happened i will die and epipens only last for so long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 22:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> have you checked the website? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 21:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They get what they want and they still arnt happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 06:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i think its so that they feel special. i am not embarrassed at all its low compared to 20 year olds in 2013. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 06:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as someone with anorexia this pisses me the fuck off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 06:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes i am a female why is this sad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 03:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> go to craigslist its the best for quick sex  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 03:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to be completely truthful i really don't know 
i think it makes then feel a little better and make then feel superior. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Virgin think again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 03:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have told every single person i have been with man or woman that i was a virgin when we go together and they were my first.
i haven't been a virgin since i was 14.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 02:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> same with stop urinating  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 02:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how is surgery to remove your tonsils going to stop you from peeing your self  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 02:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i think you just mind fucked me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 02:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this needs a NSFL tag </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 02:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> im actually proud that this is happening and i think that more people should take advantage of this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 02:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why is the 40 year old with no kids fat and ugly 

Im going to look better then ever  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
