<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6681</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 14:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hi! Anorexic Vegan chiming in here!! Honestly, it all comes down to personal preference. If you think you can handle going vegetarian/vegan I would say give it a shot, because it has alot beneficial aspects outside of losing weight/ED related things (eg. Environmental, Animal welfare, etc.) . However with that being said, we must keep our diagnosis in mind as well. Not all veggies have eating disorders, but it's common for people with eating disorders to be veggies. I only want to mention this because it could potentially be a slippery slope that leads to restriction. All in all, it's completely your call and no ones elses. You eat what you want to eat!(:   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Away at University </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 21:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys,

So a couple of you guys may have remembered my posts from a while back, where I talked about skipping over therapy and moving away from everyone in order to go to university. Many people including my friends/ family at home were very worried about me moving so far because 2-3 months prior I was hospitalized for my eating disorder. (If I am being honest with myself, I probably should have taken a year off in order to really give recovery a shot).. but I told everyone that I would be okay and they didn't have to worry. 

And now that I am here at university, things are just so -- surreal. Like, I don't know anyone here? No one gets concerned when I say that I don't want to go have breakfast. In a way its slightly liberating that no one is hovering over my back.. but at the same time, it's really stressful because i have to eat in the residence cafeteria where there are thousands of people eating. And I /cannot/ eat around that many people. I have a very select few that I can eat in front of... and they are all back at home over 8 hours away. 

I still really haven't figured out how I am going to eat at all here. I haven't made any solid friends and I feel pretty uncomfortable eating around anyone here.  Ontop of all that, classes begin tomorrow and I feel like that will just add to the stress levels. 


Sorry if this post sounded very ranty, I just had a lot on my chest and I thought I would update you guys in the process of it all. 

I'm pretty lonely so far from home, so feel free to message me anytime.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 17:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a feeling I've been able to relate to for a long time now.... I just wanted to say that if you need to talk to anyone, I am here for you and you can PM me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 19:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast:Skipped

Lunch: Skipped

Dinner: ????

Snacks: ????

Total: 0 Calories (so far)

Note: Now that I'm done therapy, my goal is to stay around 130-133 lbs until I move out (which is in a couple days). I ended up restricting though... by 2pm today, I will have completed a 24 hour fast. Not sure if I should end it, or see how long I can continue. I don't want to raise to much suspicion before I leave. I will update later.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone else hear voices? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 18:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello friends,

Sorry if this post seems a little "out of the norm". But a thought recently came to my attention. Before I had an eating disorder, I didn't really understand the illness that well. I was ignorant, and thought it was all about being underweight. Now I realize that there is a strong mental component aswell. In the beginning, it was described to me as "disordered thoughts". But as I ventured farther and farther into therapy I realized multiple therapists/doctors refer to the "ED voice" aka those disordered thoughts. 

I've seen it time and time again on posts across the internet but I don't know if it's been really addressed. When you guys hear "the voice of ana/ed" in your mind, do you hear it as if it was an actual auditory hallucination? I heard some people do and some people don't. 

For me, it can vary. Sometimes it just feels like very strong thoughts that aren't my own (whether I recognize it or not). Other times the voice feels so clear, I can give it a gender. For me, "ED" doesn't feel like a suitable name because it feels a lot more feminine in nature. Hence why I prefer "ana". 

I guess a natural extension of this question, is do you considered yourself delusional? Delusions (aka strong, fixed, false beliefs) is generally a marker of a psychiatric illness, such as "I believe aliens implanted a microchip into my brain". I've heard it argued before that people with anorexia suffer from the delusion that they are "severely overweight, despite being extremely underweight" .... However, personally, I have a hard time believing this one. For the most part, I actually do feel as if I have a lot more weight to lose. 

Anyways, back on topic. When your "ED voice" is going off in your mind, do you guys actually (sometimes) hear auditory hallucinations? Or would you consider it just strong, obstructive thoughts? 

I'm curious about this topic!(:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 19:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hoping to eat nothing. Although I did say that yesterday as well... I think I am noticing a pattern lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 19:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello! And welcome to our community. 3(:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 08:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, when I was first diagnosed I refused to believe it. So I guess you could say that my diagnosis forced me to take a good look at myself.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 18:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Skipped

Lunch: Tofu (315 calories)

Dinner: Skipped

Total: 315 Calories

I made sure today was a restrictive, low carb day. Hopefully it will help shed some of that water/sodium weight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's finally over. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 22:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today is the day I have reached a goal.


It's not a weight loss goal. It's not a calorie restriction goal. It's not a fasting goal. 

 nbsp;

I have finally escaped therapy.

 nbsp;

A couple months back, when I was near my lowest weight, I thought I could tell my therapist about the voice in my head telling me that "I wasn't worth the food". She spent many weeks working with me through psychotherapy, but to no avail. My weight was still dropping dramatically. When I reached my lowest weight, she gave me an ultimatum. I could either go to hospital to get myself checked out, or they would call an ambulance. She said if I tried to run, she would call the police and they would force me into hospital. After two painful weeks on a psych ward, I was discharged and put into outpatient therapy. Ever since therapists, doctors and my parents have been monitoring my weight/ food intake.


I long for the days where no one knew about my illness. I long for the days where I could fast for days and no one gave a damn. The voice of ana in my head truly regrets ever letting anyone know about it's existence.


That's when I decided I am going to get those times of secrecy back. On September 3rd, I am moving far far away for university. Far away from anyone I have ever known, or loved. 


I have been working for this, for a very long time. It took a lot of carefully planned lies and deceit. The entire month of August I have been skipping meals and purging. I have been rigging the scales at the doctors office with weights. I am a horrible human being. 


Today was my last "weigh in". From here on out, no one will be monitoring me. I move away in less than two weeks. I will not be continuing therapy when I am there, despite what my current therapist wants. 

 nbsp;

This time, No one can stop me on my long descent into starvation.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
