<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3094</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could you lovely ladies take a look at my routine? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 23:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys! I've done a TON of research and I've put together a lifting/meal plan for myself, and I would love any input or advice y'all might have. I'm 23 years old and currently 155 lbs at 5'5. I would love to lose about 20 pounds, which is what I've packed on in the last six months or so. Yuck. I've struggled in the past with anorexia and one day I just snapped and decided I couldn't do that anymore, or I'd end up dead. Obviously it wasn't quite that easy, but I've come a long way in the last six months. I'm over wanting to be stick thin; I want to be strong!  
  
I read Mike Matthew's [Thinner, Leaner, Stronger](http://www.amazon.com/Thinner-Leaner-Stronger-Building-Ultimate-ebook/dp/B0098PYV7Q/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8 qid=1407187793 sr=8-1 keywords=thinner+leaner+stronger) and I really loved his views and how much research he's done. He has a pretty strong hatred for the way the media and fitness world thinks women should be working out (low weight/high reps), and stresses heavy lifting.  
  
My workout schedule goes as follows:  
All exercises are performed 3x8-10 unless stated otherwise  
  
**Monday: Legs**  
-Squats  
-Leg press  
-Barbell lunges  
-Romanian deadlift  
  
**Tuesday: Arms   Cardio**  
-Alternating dumbbell curl  
-Triceps pushdown  
-Barbell curl  
-Seated triceps press  
-Cardio: HIIT on treadmill for 15-20 minutes  
  
**Wednesday: Chest   Abs/Cardio**  
-Bench press  
-Incline bench press  
-Incline dumbbell press  
-Assisted dips (3 sets to failure  
-Abs: Cable crunch (3x15), captain's chair to burnout, air bicycles to burnout - I do these back to back and rest for 1 minute as 1 circuit, and I complete three circuits.  
-HIIT cardio 15-25 minutes
  
**Thursday: Back/Cardio**  
-Barbell deadlift  
-Bent over barbell row  
-One arm dumbbell row  
-Close grip lat pulldown  
-HIIT cardio for 15-25 minutes  
  
**Friday: OFF DAY!**  
  
**Saturday: Shoulders**  
-Seated barbell military press  
-Upright barbell row  
-Side lateral raise  
-Bent over rear delt raise  
  
**Sunday: Cardio Only**  
-HIIT cardio for 15-25 minutes  
  
**Nutrition**  
As far as meal planning, I'm eating around 1550 calories a day, and my goals are 32g fat, 140g carbs, and 180g protein.  
  
**Supplements**  
I'm doing fasted training and I train first thing in the morning, about 6:00 am. Before my workout I take about 7g yohimbe, 10g BCAAs, and 2 VPX Meltdown fat burners. After training I have 2 scoops whey protein, green tea extract, fish oil pills, and a multivitamin. At lunch I'll have more green tea extract, multivitamin, and fish oil pills. I have another scoop of whey protein after work and I take the last of the fish oil at night.  
  
I've done so much research that my brain hurts, and I think at this point I'm over-thinking it. Any feedback y'all have would be so greatly appreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-12 20:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The past? It's not like she's talking about something that happened ten years ago. It was three days ago, Jesus. She clearly hasn't even fully grasped the event. She's obviously struggling with what her emotions are. All I'm trying to say is insensitivity in this situation doesn't help anyone, and that's what the original comment was: insensitive. "you should have" creates guilt, and that a dangerous feeling to press upon someone so soon after such a horrible experience.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-12 20:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminding someone and telling someone what they should have done and all the people that will now suffer because of their decision are two different things. There's a reason that rape goes so highly unreported, and while going to the police would be the ideal decision, you have no idea how hard that decision is until you have been in that situation yourself. All I'm saying is that comment had absolutely no point other than to bring guilt to OP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-12 19:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, because guilt tripping someone who just went through a god FUCKING awful situation is obviously the right thing to do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-12 00:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fairly flexible; I haven't had any flexibility issues with anything else I've been doing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-11 22:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It always seems like my hips are going to give out. They even pop sometimes, and not in a "oh, just getting warmed up for a rep" way. More in a "holy fuck, what the hell was that" way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
