<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6210</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 06:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It goes straight to my ass and thighs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 06:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oatmeal, egg whites, veggies, broth. That's usually what I eat, all low cal, but filling. I don't have any recipes though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 00:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the idea of changing every month.

I like the colours yellow and turquoise. But I don't know if it'll fit with the theme </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 00:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same thing here. I wish I could keep going to school, but I know I need to take a break and recover.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 18:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are talking about healthy life choices, like eating well and exercising, then they will probably learn that and not unhealthy habits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 01:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would never tell my mom that she most likely triggered my ed, because other than that she is absolutely amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 01:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cinnamon (147)

Lunch: Simply egg whites (30), celery (6), red bell pepper (11) and cucumber (8)

Dinner: Vegetable bouillon with celery and carrots (27)

Snacks: Diet coke (0), mio sport (0) and peppermint white chocolate tea (5)

Total: 234 cals
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 00:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom isn't like yours, but she is very triggering. She always made comments about how gross fat people are when I was growing up, she still does it, but not as much. This created my huge  fear of becoming fat. She would also make comments about what I ate when I was going through puberty. She would tell me that if I kept eating muffins I would get fat (even though I was extremely underweight). Those comments definitely triggered my eating disorder.

My mom is also extremely skinny. She has a bmi of 19, and she's 60 and had 3 kids. Her chest bones are very prominent. I love chest bones and mine are barely peaking out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 22:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to wear a 32A, but I haven't worn a bra in months so I don't know what size I would be now since I've lost weight. But my boobs definitely got smaller </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 21:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Overweight. I'm terrified of becoming overweight, especially since everyone in my family is super skinny, so becoming the fat one really scares me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 21:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate VS because they seem to only cater to women with large breasts. I'm a 32A and I have only ever found 1 bra in my size at VS and it had crazy padding. But they had plenty of 32DD bras...

I stopped wearing bras completely a few months ago, and I love it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 21:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to sit out in the cold too, but I usually wear a coat because it's really cold where I live. I also like to sleep with my window open when it's really cold out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 20:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in the same boat. Most of it is probably food/water weight. I lost most of it in a few days of restricting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 18:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make sure you are getting enough salt and potassium. You need both to keep your heart beating </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 17:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to eat my food in a certain order. It can't touch while it's on my plate. I trust one of my measuring spoons, but not the other. I eat the exact same thing everyday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 16:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that sometimes. I don't know what it is though. If it gets really painful, you should go see someone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 06:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. They know they can't force me to eat, so there isn't a point in fighting with me, it would just upset everyone.

Plus I am going into treatment soon, and they know that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 05:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You have a lower BMI than 99% of females aged 15-29 in your country"

"You have a lower BMI than 97% of females aged 15-29 in the world" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 05:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it is nice that I didn't binge. I just really hate the isolation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hate family dinners </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 01:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate family dinners so much, they make me feel so depressed. 

Everyone in my family knows about my ED, which is nice because it allows me to stick to my very strict meal plan. But it really sucks when I have a family dinner because everyone is eating delicious food and I'm just eating my stupid little broth with vegetables.

Normally it's just me and my mom for dinner, and that doesn't bother me because she often eats foods that I don't really like. It also feels less lonely because we each have our different meals.

But when my siblings are over for dinner, it just feels so much more lonely. Everyone is enjoying the same food, it was chili tonight (one of my favourite meals) and I just ate my shitty little meal. I feel so much more isolated and depressed.

Urg, I don't know, at least my sister is leaving tomorrow, so there will be less family meals now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 01:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cinnamon (147)

Lunch: Simply egg whites (30), celery (6), red bell pepper (11) and cucumber (8)

Dinner: Vegetable bouillon with celery and carrots (27)

Snacks: Diet coke (0), mio sport (0)

Total: 229 cals
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 00:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love that feeling of empowerment. The Christmas cookies that I was binging on all of last week are sitting on the kitchen counter and I don't even think about eating them. I feel so powerful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 21:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Skeletal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 04:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cinnamon (147)

Lunch: Simply egg whites (30), celery (6), red bell pepper (11) and cucumber (8)

Dinner: Vegetable bouillon with celery and carrots (27)

Snacks: Diet coke (0), mio sport (0) and 1 mandarin orange (35)

Total: 264 cals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 03:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I think it has to do with the fact that I have the emotional maturity of a 13 year old. So I want to look the way I feel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 03:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the time, it's super triggring. I know I can't have the body of  child, yet I want it so badly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 02:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I'm a big fan of making a meal plan and eating it everyday. So I'll be eating that for a few weeks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 01:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a huge list of things to not do when I have kids, and it's mostly things that my mom did as I was growing up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 23:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I had long legs, I'm tall, but my legs are really short </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 23:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might be anemic, you can buy iron supplements at any drugstore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 20:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not as bad as what happened to you, but once my mom told me to stop eating muffins everyday because I would get fat. I was 85lbs at 5'7 at that point. It was probably one of the many things my mom did that triggered my ED.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 18:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you add me to the group you made, my kik is labellemort </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 05:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ISTP. I feel like some things are very accurate, while others are completely wrong! So I don't know what to think about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 01:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cinnamon (147)

Lunch: Simply egg whites (30), celery (6), red bell pepper (11) and cucumber (8)

Dinner: Vegetable bouillon with celery and carrots (27)

Snacks: Diet coke (0), mio sport (0) and 2 mandarin oranges (70)

Total: 299 cals

It feels great to be restricting again. I can walk past all the Christmas cookies and chocolate and not even think about eating them. Hopefully I will lose all the Christmas weight quickly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 06:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit! I was just thinking the exact same thing! I'm going through the same thing right now. I really hope someone answers this because I'm really worried too.

Hopefully it's just water and food weight, and we'll be right back to our pre-Christmas figure in a few days. I really hope so </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 01:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not that great, I ate way too much and I got fat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 22:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lucky, I've been binging all week. It's disgusting.

Don't beat yourself up if you gained weight, especially if you ate more than usual </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Post Christmas plan? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 22:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So since it was Christmas, most of us probably over ate and possibly gained some weight. I know I did. I'm pretty embarrassed of the amount of food I ate and weight I probably gained. 

So I was wondering what is everyone's plan to get back on track with their weight loss.

I'm going to start restricting to below 300 cals a day, starting tomorrow (Dec 26). I made a meal plan that is about 240 cals a day. I'm also going to have a few mandarin oranges the first few days because they help me poop (sorry tmi). I'm also debating starting to do EC stacks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 20:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely want to cut outr my stomach and intestines and empty them out.

I can't wait to start restricting again tomorrow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 20:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, you look great! That is such a big difference </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 06:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't exercise at all! I hate exercising. I even avoid stairs like the plague. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ephedrine in Canada? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 05:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 04:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I'm probably going to go into inpatient or intensive outpatient, so I would be spending my days at the hospital. So I wouldn't be able to go to school.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 03:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really, it's not like I can start eating normally before going into treatment. 

I have a lot of time on my hands since my doctors are making me drop out of school.

Plus I want to reach my ugw.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 01:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm most likely going into treatment at the end of January or the start of February. Until then I'm trying to lose as much weight as possible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 23:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been binging for Christmas, it sucks. But tonight my family is having a Christmas dinner and we're opening our gifts. It will be nice, I'm having my favourite dessert! Tomorrow we are going to some family friends for another Christmas dinner.

Urg, I've gained so much weight, hope I can lose it all quickly

I'm also hoping the lax I took last night (that didn't work) doesn't kick in during Christmas dinner  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 18:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been binging all week. I feel horrible physically and mentally. I look pregnant because I'm so bloated, and my intestines feel like they have been taken over by Satan. It really fucking sucks

Plus I got weighed today and I am at my highest that I have been in a long time. I keep telling myself that it's all food weight, but I couldn't have gained 7 lbs of food weight, so I'm terrified that it's all being turned into fat on my body. I really hope I can lose all this quickly, I need to get to my UGW before I go into treatment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 02:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been eating the same thing everyday for almost 2 months. I loved it! It's great not having to decide what to eat and to have the same calorie count everyday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 02:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm always freezing. I wear leggings and sweat pants with a big sweater most of the time. When I'm at home I wear a bathrobe on top of my clothes. I love you heating pad, I'm usually cuddled up to it.

Lately I haven't been cold because I'm pretty sure I've gone hypermetabolic because of the Christmas binge. I'm always hot and sweaty these past few days. I'm sleeping with my window open (its like -20C) and I'm sleeping without blankets and I'm still sweating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 02:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was raised in a really fat phobic environment, and I developed a very strong dislike for overweight and obese people. Some of them are very nice people, but I can't get past the fat. But I'm working on it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 06:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved secret eaters! It was super interesting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 06:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I counted 12 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 03:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do that too! After a binge I can see myself getting fatter, but I know it's not real </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 03:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, my assessment for admission is the 5th of January. Hope I get to my goal! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
