<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3132</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 20:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have previously bought some from the Co-op at Etihad Mall. They should have it, though on occasion it seems to have disappeared. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where to purchase camel meat...? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 19:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello all. I am on the hunt for some camel meat for an upcoming BBQ. I can't seem to find it at any of the stores I have visited recently (Carrefour MCC, HyperPanda, LuLu Arabian Centre, Aswaaq). Anybody got an idea of where I can find some? Cheers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 22:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is Ramadan at the moment so you are in luck to have a night of varied experiences depending on what you choose to do and where. 

Food wise, an extensive array of buffets for Suhoor are available at most hotels and Iftar tents around the UAE. Many street vendors selling (THE BEST) shawarma are also open late. 

You could take the metro to the Walk at JBR for a late night walk though it is quite humid at night these days. Cinemas are open late too I think. 

I fly out on Thursday! Safe travels :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 15:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any update? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 09:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just saw your timings that you'll be here. You could still head down to the waterfront near the Burj Khalifa for a nice walk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 09:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could head down to Dubai Mall and view the world's largest indoor aquarium, the largest fountain in the world and the tallest building in the world! 
It gets quite packed in the mall on the weekends though. Have fun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 12:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will make sure to organise a more official one later on, though I am heading out tonight to watch a movie and chill afterwards. If you're interested in chilling out, PM me and we'll see what we can organise. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 05:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, so I guess I will try organise one. It all depends on how many would be able/willing to come. What do you want to do?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teenagers in Dubai meetup? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 19:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any chance we could hold one of these? Being a teenager, I do enjoy the idea of attending a McGettigan's brunch though I don't think it is the best thing teenagers can do in this wonderful city!

Cinema, bowling, etc..! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Thanks] Thank you /u/Killerpet for the Puffin postcard! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 13:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks very much! Arrived about 5 days ago :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For Nepal! Donate and you'll get a postcard from Dubai or Nepal! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 10:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Offer] Postcard Project w/ Nepal and Dubai [WORLDWIDE] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 19:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 10:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem :) Sure thing! PM me your address and I will send one off to you as soon as I can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Thank you] Thanks to Marisska, Mokomann and PenguinsOnTV! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 09:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the exchange! The cards are lovely! 

Arrival Dates:
Marisska- 13th or 14th of Jan
Mokomann- 23rd Jan
Penguins- 23rd Jan

:)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 04:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've lived in Dubai for years and didn't know this place existed... I guess I will have to visit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 17:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Horse Soda would go great with a Bear Taco. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 14:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure! PM me your address :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 10:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, PM me your details :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 07:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, that's great! Any way we could send any to you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Exchange] Beautiful Dubai postcards! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 07:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have lived in Dubai for years and never really explored the 'touristy' side of the city till the other day. I came across some lovely postcards of the skyline and a birds-eye view of the Dubai fountain. I also have one that resembles some camels taking selfies. 

I would love to exchange these cards to people who can send a nice card of their own over. 

PM me to swap addresses


To exchange:

- ~~Dubai night skyline (black and white)~~

- ~~Daytime Dubai fountain~~

- ~~Camels~~


:)

**EDIT: All current cards are taken. I will send them off ASAP. Getting more in the next few days though, so if you are still interested, there will be one for you soon**
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 07:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only recently started a card collection, this would be great! Is living in Dubai a problem? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WANT] Stephen King books! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-01 20:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello! I am an avid Stephen King reader and would like to try out this sub. I own many of his books and am looking forward to reading more. Have any? I am willing to pay in Paypal $$ or might have a book that you want. Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-01 19:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also read The Stand by Stephen King. It took me a fair while to finish it. Out of curiosity, how long (if you can remember) did it take you to read it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 15:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! Looks like a great read :) I got The Green Mile! Can't wait:D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> M-O-O-N, that spells "Merry Christmas"! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 05:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got up early this morning to relax and finish the last 30 pages in The Stand. Hope you all are having a lovely Christmas! Maybe you will find a SK book under the tree for you..Merry Christmas! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
