<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1637</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 22:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought at first when the security guard took it he was like "alright that's very funny but enough of this, I'm going to have to dispose of this child." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 13:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does the effect stack? Is it +45%? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 00:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Romania former without Wallachia *or* Moldavia?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 22:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's weak is trying to link foreign policy to abortion. Foreign policy is an entirely different beast from domestic. The difference is that *Americans* do and should have control over what happens in *America.* We can be perfectionists about our own country, we can work for fairness and just governance within our borders. 

Outside the US, we take what we can get. We're pragmatic, concerned first and foremost about the safety of the American people. Israel isn't the perfect ally. Nor is Saudi Arabia. Nor is Japan or the UK or France or Canada. But alliances with these countries, which sometimes means giving money to those that will use it for objectionable things, keeps *America* safe. 

I care about Israeli babies just as much as American babies, but our government needs to be working for our safety above the safety of other nations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 21:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we give money to Planned Parenthood and say "you can't use this for abortion," then sure, they won't use *those specific dollar bills* for abortion. But they *will* use that money for other projects, and take the money they would have spent on those and, you guessed it, *spend it on abortion.* One dollar bill is exactly equal in value to any other dollar bill. That's what a fungible quantity means. That's why it makes no sense to specify which funds can and cannot be used for abortion: the fact is that for every dollar you give to PP, PP will spend a few cents on abortions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 21:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Money is a fungible quantity, saying "you can't spend these funds on this specific program" doesn't make any sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I run for a club officer position? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 19:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm running for Vice President of conference planning at my uni. Though I am a freshman, the club itself is brand new and I've got a lot of experience on the staff side of high school conferences (crisis director, chair, usg, etc). A lot of other members have some mun experience from high school, but none have done it in college. Would it be a good idea to run? I wouldn't want to overstep my bounds and be that obnoxious freshman, but I also feel like I could put a lot of effort into making the club grow  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 21:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair means everyone gets what they deserve. As a Christian, I believe everyone deserves a happy and satisfied life. As a person with common sense, I know that life isn't fair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 08:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my sweet old sixth... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a community where I can live a "night-owl" lifestyle? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 23:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like the same as a normal life, except I sleep during the day and am active during the night. Not just as a night watchman. Are there ways for me to do that as, say, a computer scientist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 23:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're trying to frame my statements as bigoted instead of actually listening to what I'm saying. I'm not saying homosexuals are evil, I'm saying that the White House is trying to pick a fight with the Church. Again, I'm sure the Holy Father won't take the bait, but trying to provoke the Church is kind of an asshole thing to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 19:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'm upset. The White House is displayed a complete lack of decorum and respect for the Church. Would you celebrate a visit from the King of Saudi Arabia by serving pork? No, because that would just be an asshole thing to do. I'm sure Pope Francis will be nothing but pleasant, kind and loving to these guests. But still... dick move, Obama. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 04:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The life of Aaron Burr, portraying him as a Machiavellian Underwood-esque mastermind. On the one hand, not entirely accurate. On the other hand, he pretty much built Tammany Hall and tried to take over the United States through a legislative technicality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 04:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The winter of our discontent is coming... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 23:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her response to his comment about her face was a blow that Trump couldn't deflect. Her business record is bad, but during the debate she defended it successfully. Granted, a cursory fact check would show that the criticisms of her record were very accurate, but just from the debate it would seem that she did well.

As for "hate and lies," those are rather strong words. Care to point out something specific? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 17:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does the Catholic church promote behavior, conditions, or attitudes that foster stereotypes of social roles based on sex?

Well, yeah. Men and women were created different, we have different physiology and very different psychological needs. I think a better definition for sexism would be "discrimination based upon sex," which still applies but is more justifiable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 01:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fiorina has proven her ability to play the attack dog. It will be immensely helpful to have a candidate who is strong, but professional and reasonable, while the running mate makes painful and powerful criticisms of the opponent. Not to mention it makes the whole "war on women" bullshit look much more ridiculous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 00:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The article did state that money was the main cause. Quote, "Walker didn't want to limp into Iowa." In any event his exiting message was clear and completely welcome: he wants to take the lead of the losers and encourage other low-polling candidates to drop out as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 00:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rubio/Fiorina, or *maybe* Fiorina/Rubio. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 00:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not talking 51% here. I meant that if a vast, *vast* majority of people agree on something, they should have their way. If 90% of the country was totally for a proposed law, then it should (and will) succeed, even if it requires a constitutional amendment.

It isn't wrong to say "since 90% of the country believes x should pass, x should pass," so logically it isn't wrong to say "if 90% of the country believed that x should pass, then x should pass." Replace x with any religious law you disagree with and you'll see that supporting it isn't unreasonable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 00:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never got the impression that she was saying there was a video of it... I rewatched it and she did imply that there was but I never thought that she meant it as anything more than an "imagine this scene...", a rhetorical appeal to emotion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 00:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would pose two questions to you:

1. Should people have the right to change their laws to make the population happier?

2. Should the majority have the say in what laws the nation makes?

Imagine if the vast majority of Americans were devoutly Christian. They implemented laws that coincided with their religious beliefs, and they implemented policies that made them feel more satisfied. Sure, the small portion of non-Christians would be uncomfortable, but nobody's stopping them from moving. In fact, it might be encouraged for them to move to a nation that made laws according to their faith.

Narrowing it down, is any individual in the society wrong for believing that Christian laws should be implemented? After all, the vast majority of the country supports them. Shouldn't the majority rule?

When people state that America is a Christian nation, they aren't necessarily saying "I want America to force my opinion on others," they are often saying "I want the people of America to be people who agree with me." Above all, we should value democracy, the right of the majority to rule and the right of the minority to be heard. Under the assumption that just governance is our goal, people should not feel unfair in saying "America is a Christian nation," because what they really mean is "I think America is a Christian nation, but if the majority of people disagree with me their word should be law, not mine." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My college professor mentioned in a video lecture that he makes $4,500 per year. How is that possible? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 18:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing that his housing and food costs are covered, but how can this intelligent, tenured professor with a doctorate be making so little? To be clear, he mentioned it in the context of how much money students made in the past year, and guessed that the average student made $10,000. That's more than twice what he claimed to make. How is this possible? Is he getting paid in other ways than money? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 23:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of the Republican base was unhappy with G.W. Bush after his second term, but they're inclined to remember him more favorably after 8 years of a Democrat that they perceive to be dangerously weak on foreign policy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 16:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a textbook strawman argument. No one is arguing that a woman is communicating that she "wants to be raped" by drinking. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 05:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're referring to the edited videos, which are indeed heavily edited for shock value. I've watched the full footage, and the evidence is there. I don't expect you to just take my word for it, so go and watch the footage (or just read the transcript) and decide for yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 05:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would encourage you to watch the videos, edited or unedited, and then read the specific criticisms and decide for yourself. You will find that all the claims that were "debunked" were tangential to the main point in the first place. You can nitpick and fact-check every specific claim you want, but at the end of the day there is incontrovertible evidence that members of Planned Parenthood have been profiting from the sale of body parts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 02:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What fun! May I join? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 19:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Impressions:

**Rand Paul:** Had a very good performance last night, but the message he was delivering won't sit well with most Republicans. He's unelectable, but nonetheless did well.

**Huckabee:** Didn't really stand out. His delivery was good, he didn't make any big mistakes. His supporters weren't disappointed, but he didn't make a big impression on the rest of us.

**Cruz:** Same as Huckabee, didn't stand out. Not to say he didn't do well, simply that others did much better.

**Rubio:** Knocked it out of the park. He came across as both energetic and professional, with detailed answers to every question he was asked. Particularly on foreign policy, Rubio had an A+ night. He played the "immigrant" card a little too much, but the message was clear to strategists and donors: I can win the Hispanic vote. He would make an excellent general election candidate.

**Carson:** His tactics were good in theory, but flopped in execution. The moderators handed him a question where he could say with credibility that Trump's views on vaccines were dangerous and irresponsible. He declined, stated the facts and said that "Mr. Trump is a smart man, if he would care to read up on the subject, I'm sure he'll come to the right answer." But his delivery was weak and the "graceful, calm, and soft-spoke" persona didn't really come through.

**The Donald:** He took a lot of attacks last night, and for the most part he attacked right back. But through the brash persona we saw some of his weaknesses. Fiorina and Bush both managed to take the wind out of his sails more than once. Trump may have survived, but he's not unstoppable.

**Jeb Bush:** Better than the first debate, but still came across as weak. He let Trump interrupt him several times and handled it poorly. His shining moment was when he proclaimed that his brother "kept us safe." However you feel about the statement, it was satisfying to see the tortoise come out of his shell and make a strong statement with conviction. He'll survive for now, but he really needs to step up his game in the next debate if he wants to stay in the running.

**Walker:** Total flop. His delivery was poor, he didn't speak much, and what he said was dull and uninspiring. Tied with Carson for the worst performance last night.

**Fiorina:** Phenomenal job. I would say she's the winner of the debate, with Rubio in second. She was strong, professional and passionate. Most of all, she went head-to-head with The Donald, and not only survived but *won*. On foreign policy, she came prepared with specific details of her positions and made very convincing arguments. On her record, she defended it gracefully. Overall, her conviction and crisp delivery won her the debate. 

**Kasich:** Did not stand out much at all. His comment near the beginning, that criticized the format, was very good, but he otherwise said nothing noteworthy. Not a good night for Kasich.

**Christie:** He came out swinging this time, and a lot of his jabs connected. Played the 9/11 card too much, and his little spat with Rand Paul was unattractive. However, his derision of Carly and Donald for arguing over their careers was apropos and popular. Overall, good night for Christie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 19:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rubio came off as experienced, polished and professional. Fiorina was a bigger winner, IMO, because at a couple of points she showed that she could stop Trump in his tracks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 18:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's kind of an untested constitutional question. If Biden resigned, then it's pretty clear that they would lose the case. If Biden set himself apart from Obama, he might get away with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What catch phrases do you give your villagers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 15:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made Limberg call me "boss," I like to imagine him as my right-hand man/mob enforcer.

Pekoe says "peekaboo" because it fit just too well with her name.

Edit: I also plan on giving Sterling either "Phrasing" or "danger zone." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 14:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Battle Hymn of the Republic, previously Servant of Evil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 22:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the Kingdom of Hawaii was overthrown by like 1 Pinkerton, 2 Germans and a dozen mercenaries. I'll check.

EDIT: 5 Americans, 1 German, 1 Brit and 6 Hawaiians. So 13 total. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 14:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This reflects a misunderstanding of tax exempt status. These individual churches, whether they help the needy or not, do not make profits. Any money they earn is either used to cover costs or given to employees as bonuses. The church (lowercase c) is not a corporation that exists to make profit for its shareholders. It is a *non-profit*.

Go ahead and take away tax exemption from churches, there won't be any profits to tax. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 17:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theologically, the priest is acting in persona cristi, as an instrument of Christ. Christ is forgiving the sins, he's just doing it through a priest.

Practically, confession functions as free spiritual therapy. Like office hours for a professor. The priest can counsel the confessor and help him/her overcome the temptation to sin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 02:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That could actually be an interesting mechanic. What if the ability to invest was somehow tied to economic tech? Like, researching Stock Exchange allows bureaucrats to invest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Theatre at Virginia Tech? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 18:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a freshman majoring in physics, but my passion is acting. How can I get involved with theatre at Tech as a non-theatre major? Are there clubs, or extracurricular programs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 17:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thing is, people aren't using "literally" in place of "figuratively" because they think they mean the same. People use "literally" as hyperbole, not actually meaning the literal definition but exaggerating top emphasize significance. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-07 20:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I, too, am taking Intro to Astronomy 1055. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-07 08:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure about the wave of separatism you predict if Kurdistan secedes. The Kurds are the fourth largest stateless nation in the world. No other group in the region comes close. In fact, I would say that the Kurds are the only stateless minority in the Middle East that stand any chance of creating a successful country.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-07 08:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or maybe you're the hot cousin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-06 21:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'm better than everyone else, but I still rely on other people for everything so I fret constantly over other people's opinions of me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 16:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that really grammatically proper? I thought hypotheticals could use "was" or "were." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 01:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh shit you're right, woops. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is "Jap" considered a slur? How bad is it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 20:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my WWII class whenever the Axis did something stupid/insane I would laugh and say "those crazy krauts" or "those crazy japs." I remember people laughed much more when I said "those crazy krauts," and someone told me recently that "jap" is a racist slur. 

I always thought it was like military slang, not so much a slur as a casual way of talking about a group of people. Like "kraut," "tommy," "doughboy," "rooskie," "red" or "yank." Is "jap" really considered offensive? Is it like on the level of calling Englishmen "limeys" or Frenchmen "frogs," which are never really used seriously and at which I can't imagine people taking offense, or is it like "paki" for Pakistanis or "nigger" for Africans?

EDIT: Wow, ok, clearly it's an offensive term. Question answered, thanks guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 20:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well as one episode of Archer has taught me, semi-annual means "twice a year," whereas bi-annual means "once every two years." Following this, I would conclude that bi-weekly means "once a fortnight," and semi-weekly means "once every two weeks."

However, as has been pointed out below, Merriam-Webster accepts both definitions for bi-weekly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 20:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if this has ever been put to trial, but if I was his/her lawyer I would argue that public defecation amounts to indecent exposure, but is obviously not criminal when done in a public restroom. Hence, the stall of a public restroom must temporarily be considered a 'private' area, so it would be no more criminal than if you did it in the privacy of your home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 18:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun fact: Bhutan measures their Gross National Happiness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 17:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Sunless sea*

*Bastion*

*Transistor*

*Gunpoint*

*Assassin's Creed: Black Flag*

EDIT: Also *To The Moon* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 18:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't try to distort this into a question of social justice. It's a matter of pragmatism; one room for stalls and one room for urinals is simply the most efficient setup. Any differences in the experiences of men and women are purely coincidental. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 17:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever since I read the first book, I wanted to see a film adaptation. Partly because I wanted to be cast as Artemis, but now I'm just super excited to be able to watch it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 17:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The trials did serve a purpose, namely to determine what punishment the leaders of the Third Reich deserved. However, the crimes for which they were being tried were defined ex post facto, so the Nuremburg Trials were not a regular criminal court. The justices acted mostly without precedent or tradition, relying on their own judgement rather than any well-defined rules. I'm on mobile now, I'll try to dig up some sources when I get home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 14:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's one hell of a Great War. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 01:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Don't refer to men as males"

"Call these people 'white males'"

The fuck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 17:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "To measure what is measurable, and make measurable what is not." -Galileo Galilei </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 02:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah 1804 was a typo, sorry about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if Aaron Burr had been elected president in 1804? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 00:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The election was tied between Jefferson and Burr, so the House voted by delegation to choose the president. Federalists voted for Burr as the lesser of two evils, while Republicans voted for Jefferson. For a long time it was deadlocked at 8 votes Jefferson, 6 votes Burr, and 2 abstentions. 

What if one Republican state switched success, and the two abstaining states voted for Burr? What would a Burr presidency look like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if Aaron Burr was elected president in 1804? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 00:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 17:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything in the scriptures indicate that Christ was God and the Son of God. There is little room for a purely human interpretation of him.

Also, while I have great respect for pious followers of Islam, we must acknowledge the inherent bias in the Quran. Mohammed was a political leader as well as a religious one. His interpretation of God brought him respect, glory, and all manner of worldly treasures, whereas Christ offered himself to be crucified for mankind. *If* (and this is a big "if" here) some of Mohammed's writings were for his own benefit, it is only natural that he should respectfully denounce the Christian faith. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 03:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did Genghis Khan conquer Asia? One steppe at a time.
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-22 12:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nvm sorry I'm stupid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-22 11:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is as stupid as insisting that Obama was born in Kenya. Don't let yourself be dragged down to that level.

Edit: I'm bad at humor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 23:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kek </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-20 02:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Data" is a plural noun (the plural of datum). I was just being pedantic for the sake of humor. May I repost it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Data WERE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-20 02:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-20 02:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to have snowball fights with my villagers in the winter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 22:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's good for the fandom to have a "filler episode" every once in a while. It serves as a way to imply that a lot of meaningless adventures happened off-screen, so the fandom has a clear point at which to set fanfics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need to open a bank account for college. How do I avoid getting screwed over? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 20:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Long story short, I have to close my old bank account and open a new one in a new bank. My parents won't be there to help me this time. I'm 18, so there shouldn't be any legal problems, but I want to be sure I'm not suckered in by a bank scam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 19:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Were you at Cornwall?" "Yeah. And I lost a part of myself in that hellhole." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 12:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 12:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They claim to be a super accepting community (and they usually are) but banned for posting to TiA? Some people might be offended but we're not a *hate* sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Banned from /r/OffMyChest for posting in /t/tumblrinaction? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 12:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 12:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, sorry. Thanks for the heads-up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Banned from /r/OffMyChest for posting here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 12:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 11:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There can't be hard and fast rules for what is ok and what isn't. If the perceiver always gets to determine whether or not something is offensive, then sjw's can take advantage of it and cause serious damage in the name of furthering their cause (see the Redskins). If the speaker always gets to determine what is and isn't offensive, you'll get people purposefully offending others out of spite and then claiming that they didn't mean it so the victims can't take offense.

What is ok to be offended by is a matter of personal judgement, and should be determined on a case-by-case basis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 10:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it's as thought-out as that, it's more like I don't know what else to say. I'm really in this destructive spiral of self-centeredness, where I see that self-centeredness is a big problem for me and I try to fix it by focusing on it, which just means focusing more on *me* and *my* problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is it always about me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 09:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why am I so selfish? I only ever think about me. The only way I contribute to conversations is either expressing *my* feelings, or saying "me too." I'm never interested in what others have to say, I try to get engaged or interested in their lives but it's always so that *I* will be a better conversationalist. It's all me. Why am I like that? Am I so self centered that I can't see anything without relating it to myself? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I invited friends over. They don't drink, I had a rum and coke, and I feel like a fucking moron. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 08:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me outline the situation: 10 people came over my house while my parents were away. They were all from my theatre troupe. There was me, the girl I have a crush on (call her J), our director (call her M), and 8 others. Of the 11 of us, everyone but myself, J and one other girl was over 21. Thing is, most of them don't drink. We're dorky people, it's not really our thing. But since my parents were gone, I thought I'd live a little and have a drink. I made myself a rum and coke, without any regard to my present company. Besides one boy, nobody else drank. 

I didn't get drunk. I probably wasn't even over the legal limit, though I sure as he'll wasn't going to drive. But after the little party was wrapping up, I made myself a mojito. I poured a little too much rum in, so it was stronger than normal. I intended to sip on it while reading the draft of a book that J was writing.

My friends, however, didn't know that. An hour after they left M sent me a message asking if I was ok, because she left me with a strong drink and wanted to be sure I wasn't drinking myself to death. I played it off, said the mojito was for my cousin who put up with us and assured her that I am a responsible drinker. She believed me, but now I'm realizing that my friends probably think I'm an alcoholic or a party maniac. 

I really am responsible with alcohol, I take pride in it, but I lost respect tonight. J was very clearly not impressed. I just feel so embarrassed. I should have known my company and just drank soda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-14 00:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Where is your family from?" usually works for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I restart? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 23:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had ACNL for about a week now, and while it's generally good there are some things I don't like.

1. I only really like maybe 3 or 4 of my villagers.

2. I *really* dislike the layout. I thought it was fine at first, but more and more it is getting on my nerves.

3. My native fruit is peaches, and I would much rather it be apples/pears/oranges.

4. I don't like my avatar's face. I assume I can get a haircut, but the eyes are shaped weird and I find myself wearing sunglasses ALL THE TIME.

5. I chose a poor place for my house, and it's really bugging me.

How much of this is fixable? Should I stick with my town and try to remedy these problems, or should I turn over a new leaf (ha, ha)?

EDIT: Seeing the consensus, I decided to restart. I got a new map layout which I love (MASSIVE private beach right below my house), and my character features are not hard on the eyes. I still have peaches as my native fruit, but I figure that I'll eventually have all types of fruit tree in equal proportion. All in all, very satisfied with my new town. Thanks for the advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 23:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm very new to the series as a whole, but I have Rowan and Fang in my village and I really like them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 08:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He just moved into my town yesterday! Maybe I shouldn't restart after all...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who are your favorite villagers in ACNL? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 07:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EDIT: Guys there's 4 upvotes and 34 comments, if you like this topic then do the thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 04:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My theory is that Mr. House hired them to make sure that the Brotherhood of Steel was tied up on the East Coast.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 01:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there any workaround? I bought a brand new Lenovo recently and I really want to get rid of their shitty software. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 00:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about those Balkans, huh? Big Romania and Yugoslavia? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 23:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is sweeping the polls because he has the highest name recognition. He was, for several months, the only candidate that people knew. Now that the first debate has happened, and the campaign season is really starting up, other candidates will start to be recognizable and Trump will fall out of favor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 23:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we don't treat him like a legitimate candidate, we'll never beat him for the nomination. The GOP has to face him as an equal so that his supporters realize that, while he makes a great public figure, he's a shitty politician. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 00:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tropius, I have one on my fossil team and she's a total boss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 00:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ludicolo. a) because I caught a shiny one and b) Mirror b. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-09 19:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you know of any diy game cases that are easy to make? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-09 08:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DIY game cases? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-09 07:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever heard of Irish Orthodox? Yeah, I think we know what the answer is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-09 02:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want her to respond to "Jeeves." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-08 12:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rune Factory 4: the farming soil quality mechanic. It's great in theory, but in practice it's confusing and difficult to get every plot on the same level. When a hurricane strikes, I end up with a patchwork of bad spots in an otherwise good field. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 09:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has actually been happening a lot in my games, especially starting from Charlemagne. Most of my eu4 converted games include a disgustingly Balkanized Iberia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 03:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best part is that only one person needs the game, the other can play multiplayer with ds download play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 18:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Data-finding rigour?" Are you kidding? You've never taken a statistics class, have you? Now I don't reject her results, I'm willing to accept that there is a bias in the industry, but come on. We don't see any records. There's no scientific method. She ran an informal, improvised experiment, and her results are not scientifically nor statistically credible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 17:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, perhaps there's a selection bias here? People that accept the obvious gender bias might read the article, upvote and move on. People who disagree feel the need to make their case in the comments. Thus, there's going to be a disproportionately high number of comments that disagree with the article as opposed to comments that support it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 17:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Story of Seasons, formerly known as Harvest Moon, is a good place to start if you are looking for pure life sim. Rune Factory 4 has a lot of additional RPG elements, and doesn't sacrifice much at all in terms of quality of the non-combat parts. I prefer RF4, but if you are *really* looking for a non-violent experience, get SoS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 17:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pop Island! It's wild fun, a charming little capture-the-flag game with firecrackers and snowboarding penguins. If you're unsure, get Paperfield first, to see if you like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 17:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are those problems that require special training to deal with, or can they be managed by a general practitioner?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: how is "women's healthcare" any different from general healthcare? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 14:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Besides abortion and contraception, what is so special about "women's healthcare?" Is it a specialized field of medicine, or could a normal doctor practice it acceptably? Why is it such a big deal, but I've never heard of "men's healthcare?"

EDIT: Downvotes aren't making me any less ignorant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 10:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like girls that are complete smart-asses. I myself am a smart-ass, and if a girl can keep up a witty back-and-forth with me I am instantly interested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there any way to make custom commands for Cortana? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 06:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 06:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No DIY fixes available? Shame, I hate buying new styluses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 04:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Star Fox 64, Kid Icarus. Rune Factory 4 maybe? Look into original DS games too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 04:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My stylus, which came with my 3ds, no longer fits in the stylus-hole. It slides out as soon as I tilt the system. Is this a common problem? Any reccommendations on how to fix it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 11:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did you like about those two games? The aesthetic, the gameplay, the story...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 14:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Layton games are really good, lots of variety in the puzzles and a quirky, charming story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 14:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For deleting games, go to system settings and memory management.

For games, you've got a fantastic lineup already and I would add Rune Factory 4 and Animal Crossing: New Leaf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 14:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same, I don't have a N3DS but I still want my Little Mac amiibo for Smash 4. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-30 10:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never heard of Zero Escape or Legend of Legacy, what do they have that you're excited about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-30 10:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can I transfer my Pokemon from Emerald (gba) to Alpha Sapphire (3ds)? What else, other than the 3ds and the two games I have already, do I need to complete the transfer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-28 21:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joebama OTP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-28 04:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha already got it, just wondering if AC is worth my time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-28 03:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try Rune Factory 4.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-28 03:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does Animal Crossing: New Leaf have ANY combat, romance, or farming? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deodorant? Aftershave? Both? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-25 00:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Getting ready to go out, should I wear only deodorant, only aftershave, or deodorant and aftershave? Also, I know that it is possible for one to put on too much cologne, should I also be afraid of putting on too much deodorant/aftershave? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-24 21:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Classic eggshell skull scenario. Wouldn't it be manslaughter and not murder though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-24 08:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Attack on Titan. Think of all the modern inventions I could take credit for if I brought them to that pseudo-renaissance world. I'd live like a king. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-24 08:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent! That's 50% of people out of the way, well done. Now you just need to learn how to love the other half. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-24 04:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think there's there's been a living fuck in you. *Ever.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uhh... Third Reich? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 21:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool! I was planning to wait for the official release before getting my laptop. How do you like it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
