<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8986</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 22:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. It's definitely much easier to find 28, so ill be sticking to that. If anything, I'm trying to gain weight anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 22:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great! Even though it is tight, it's definitely more comfortable with what I used to get (32C). And yes, I'm scooped! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 22:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the recommendation! 

So if its a shape and not size issue, should I still keep the same sizing or go up to an E? Is that what could impact the middle not being flat against my chest? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-26 07:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if this is the case with her, but there's a lot of controversy over the diagnosis of anorexia nervosa and weight. For instance, if you weighed 200 lb and lost 50 lb in a month or two, that would be extremely drastic and unhealthy. But, this person would still be 150lb and wouldn't be able to get a diagnosis of anorexia nervosa, or even be considered underweight.. This person would still be very malnourished and perhaps close to death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-23 10:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My boyfriend does this by walking the dog in the middle of the night. He's out right now actually, 1am. He loves it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-17 01:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another thing similarly that I do is to do dishes while I wait for things like when i cook. If I need to microwave something for 5 minutes, instead of sitting down and waiting impatiently, I've decided I would be productive and get a few things clean. It's surprising how helpful this was for me! Even if its just a few dishes at a time. I feel like no time is wasted because it kind of double tasking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-15 10:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think higher fat content lasts longer. For instance, whole milk lasts longer than skim. So cream should definitely last longer, and butter as well. I think I've heard this fact in relation to room temp but it should be true for refrigerated too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 04:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, after that, shampoo with a purple shampoo. I use Sally's generic version of Shimmer Lights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 18:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's actually keeping two! I don't think she's going to do it long-term. Her 21 year old cat passed a few months back, so she's been wanting one or a pair (siblings).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 08:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or, how I learned how to say it: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=A1MAXJgzHzs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 20:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've brought this up in conversation before and a good conclusion seems to be that when someone is looking at you very closely (in distance) then they are somewhat cross eyed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-07 19:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to call it Pre Traumatic Stress Disorder.

For me, avoidance is just an unhealthy coping mechanism. Once I actually do it, though, it's not as bad as I thought it would be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-31 21:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't read this yet but it's would make sense if she's talking to people around her age, or people that don't go to bars and whatnot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-29 05:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, thank you for reminding me! I've been stressed out about DOING stuff lately, I totally forgot. Just submitted it. I also just received my W2 last week so maybe it makes sense. 

I just read that it's first come first serve... it's been open since the 10th, why hasn't it closed yet? I mean, I'm happy it hasn't...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-27 22:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I work at a Japanese grocery store actually. Maybe sriracha and kewpie mayo? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-27 08:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's to represent increased blood flow to the erect weiner </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-27 08:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I'm definitely interested in making it and just never thought about doing it, since I get spicy tuna hand rolls for $1.60 at work. Some habit I have, like how people pay a couple bucks for coffee in the morning or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-27 05:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another thing I love in them is (raw) spicy tuna in a hand roll. I don't know how to make it from raw tuna unfortunately, but it's so good. Add a tiny bit of soy sauce... yum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-26 23:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The shape makes it get stuck on my tongue, that's why I hate it. Ick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-26 23:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, cvs brand. I live next to one and work next to one so I don't think it's worth trying to find a rite aid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-26 23:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The shield ones are the ones I like! Er... Can deal with. I think it was the non generic. It feels like the ones I take perfectly fit all edges of my throat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-26 23:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you take XR or regular adderall? The blue 10mg regular... Maybe generic adderall is yummy :p unfortunately I can't take it anymore because of my fast heart rate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-26 18:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I take it whole it tends to always get stuck. I guess it's a way to get me to drink more water though :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-26 18:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, since they tend to stick on my tongue, they basically crumble either way. It's strange because I can take four omega3s at once, just not lamictal! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does lamotrigine have to be so unpleasant to take? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-26 11:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on 250mg of lamotrigine right now. So, I have to take one 200mg and half of a 100mg. That's fine but the 200s are just so big and icky that I have to break it into fourths to stop the feeling that its stuck in my throat, so I end up taking 5/4ths of a pill.  Why can't it be tasty and sugary like adderall? 

I do think brand name Lamictal has a better shape. I just hate these white circle ones that seem to be the exact shape of my throat or something. I know it's a minor issue but eck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 09:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a study that asked college students to pick up some heavy object for x number of yards for $100 after being pepper sprayed and they all said yes and completed the task. The actual variables are more impressive to get a better idea but I don't remember. Point being is that both pepper spray and a crotch shot will probably only anger the dude even further. Definitely run at any chance, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-24 05:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one time I saw it was at Tiffany's in New York a couple years ago, so I suppose there are some around still. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-24 05:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seemed like he says he developed it because of the deaths, but schizophrenia generally is something a person is born with and just comes out with stressful events.  Not trying to get unemotional and analytical, just interesting how he portrayed it as if the deaths almost gave him schizophrenia. I wasn't surprised though, from the first moment it looked like something was off about him, not just having a bad day. Reminds me of my schizophrenic uncle, who speaks a lot less, and definitely not about what would stress him out. I wonder if in this situation he would though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-20 22:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not true, at least not with all anosmics, people think taste and smell are more closely related than they are. Also, the experience between being born without a sense of smell and losing it is much different. I was born without a sense of smell and I can still very much taste things like chocolate, it isn't just sweet with some hints of bitter. But I can't really taste things like some spices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-11 21:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have so many responses, but if you do end up getting to this one...

I'm on the side of your SO. My boyfriend, who I knew has been addicted to stuff in the past, is addicted to GHB. He hid it from me for the first 2 years we've been together. I was upset for him hiding it, mostly, and I had no idea he had been doing it. He's even been passed out (really bad and strangely), but said it was from mixing alcohol and ambien (he has a prescription).  If your SO is like me, you're more important than her knowing you're intoxicated. I was very upset for a week, maybe, and I have seen him differently, but I think that's to be expected.  If you can handle knowing that, please tell her as soon as you feel it's okay. 

You can even start with seeing a therapist first, as I wish my boyfriend did.  He doesn't want to tell his psychiatrist and doesn't want to see a therapist because he's afraid of letting them down. I know he's trying really hard, but I'd be so much more proud of him for getting professional help. It'd mean a lot if you could do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-11 13:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in the same boat. Love falling asleep thinking of her. Saw her today actually... Yay! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-10 20:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really sorry to hear that. Similar time frame as my boyfriend. His dad died and a month later, his dog of 10 years died. Dad died of unknown circumstances so bf had a lot going on, and he only lived with his dog. The dog had a tumor in his brain and kept seizing and whimpering for a few days. Bfs snake died a couple months later. Bad year for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 08:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually let time pass longer than recommended, especially with teas that don't get bitter like mint tea.  On the other hand, I'm very sensitive to bitterness in teas, and am really shocked when there's sweetness (I don't like it). I haven't tried different temperatures, though. I usually just use kettle-boiled water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does taste or smell draw you to tea more? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 07:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no sense of smell (congenital anosmia). But, I love tea. I don't really like sweetened teas and strong tea flavors.  I've heard that lacking a sense of smell can make my taste stronger, so maybe it's that, or perhaps it's the idea and culture behind tea that I love.

I honestly don't know if I'm just bullshitting myself into liking tea when sometimes tea tastes only slightly different than hot water. 

Do you find that a lot of your enjoyment of tea is through smell? Just curious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-26 21:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another thing that can be done is spray the back of the canvas with a water bottle with water. When it dries up it should dry flat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-25 09:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. I love large bills actually. It makes my box neater and not crammed with 20's. it's also easier to count ten 100's than fifty 20's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-24 06:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a cashier, some of the only joy I have is complaining about customers to my coworkers. 

Jokes that customers think are "witty" like the ones that have been said in this thread is like listening to your druncle tell some stupid joke, but instead of a relative it's a stranger so it's even weirder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-22 19:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At Sprouts supermarket (they're only in a few states though), they have spices in bulk and little baggies that you can fill with as much spice as you want. The cashier weighs it and whatever spice I get I usually spend about 50 cents for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-21 10:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since hair often falls out about 3 months after the stressful period, and when it grows back it starts from the root, perhaps it just is that length for a very long time.  

It does make me wonder because there are people whose hair really doesn't grow past chin length or whatever, so at least the follicles have some idea on hair length. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-14 21:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe bring it up in a way that'll empower him. It's not fair to him if you actually are unsatisfied! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-13 22:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell him! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-07 07:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/BPD might be what OP is looking for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-07 07:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm busy buying stupid shit :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-06 06:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like Pet Society, game on facebook, and someone just decided to customize their character to look like AT.

edit: Looks like it's one of those weekly themes for the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-03 05:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who works minimum wage... are you joking? Like, are people saying "holy fuck, I only live on $100 a day!"

I thought this video was just making fun of how expensive it is there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-26 02:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where can bones be available? When I looked at grocery stores, bones were pretty expensive.  Is there a cheaper cut of bone to look for? Should I go to a butcher? 

Also to add to OP: adding lentils or beans is a good, cheap way to bulk it and add protein. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-19 00:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the toy camera scene happened before instagram. They've been selling them at Urban Outfitters for years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-18 22:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> or even amazon for generics.

i took mine to the apple store and they gave me a new one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-14 22:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I decided to take breaks from my school work to study french. It definitely is fun... I can't believe I procrastinated learning with learning. I do wish there was an offline version though (unless there is...) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-14 01:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He reminded me of LSP, even though he had a Peebles look to him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-08 20:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No... the shorter the better. Unless you fear fried ends and don't want your hair shorter. I only grew my hair out because it had been bleached and dyed black already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-08 15:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it naturally black or dyed black? How long is it?

If its virgin short hair its a lot easier. I've had my hair all colors, but before I went white I grew out my hair for a while so it was virgin hair which makes it 100000x easier. 

Try doing 2-3 bleachings with 20 developer. Wait a week in between. What I did was went light pink after my first bleaching so I didnt have icky orange hair. Dye bleached out rather quickly when it's pastel. Then about a month later, another bleach and it turned out pretty white. I used 30 developer. When you do bleach your hair, make sure it never dries out or else it stops working and just damages your hair.

For color, get the darkest purple you can find and mix it with conditioner. Check snakebitesparkles (I think that's her name.. google Melon lady) and she has a good tutorial and is very fun. Just youtube lavender hair, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-19 01:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as someone who works there, i thought the same :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-18 07:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A pretty extensive recipe, but I made pho recently and bean sprouts were an amazing/necessary topping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-17 09:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can try winter semester or spring (starts feb). fall semester ends late december. it's still worth considering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-17 07:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okcupid is much cooler, in my opinion! good suggestion, though.

op: have you considered taking a class at a community college? it can seem very lonely in the beginning, but right now i'm actually making friends in my art classes. i'm going to class to transfer, but a lot off people are just taking it as is. slowly i've been making friends with similar interests as me. i'm going to santa monica college (in LA) and one class is less than $100. i definitely recommend an art class, even if you aren't an artist, because in my opinion people are much more willing to be social to everybody. might not be your thing, but it helped me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-17 07:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for listening :)

I stopped going to therapy a few months ago because I was doing well, and my therapist agreed. Before I left, my boyfriend did come in with me because I was having trouble with the fact that he hid his addiction from me for 2 years. 

I think the fact that he hasn't seen real consequences from it is hurting him. In addition to the drugs, his mom still helps him financially. I'm not sure on the specifics. I have never shared finances with him, though. I can't afford a place to stay without him, and being with my parents would be much more stressful. I do wish I could have a place to myself sometimes.  This is especially so because of my lingering control issues (which was expressed as anorexia in the past) and I wish I could just have a clean house without anyone messing it up.

One of the things that he did see was the fact that I didn't want to have sex much anymore.  We used to do some light bdsm, with him dominating, but I can't see that anymore when I can't respect him as much.  I wasn't trying to withhold sex or anything, just loss of libido.  I told him that I need him to work on everyday stuff, and he said he would try to, and did for very short time.  So it seems like sex can motivate him (what guy wouldn't be?)

I'm afraid of becoming a nagging girlfriend. I remind him things, like getting his car fixed, but he just doesn't do it. 

Your response helps just to make me feel like I do have the right to feel stressed (I don't act out on it). Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-12 11:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought of the same thing. I'm a cashier at a grocery store and I don't do that until I'm really bored or if people seem friendly to talk to. I'm actually not much for small talk, but standing in a 2ftx2ft space for 8 hours doing the same shit hundreds of times gets boring.

I have a few friends at TJs. Maybe I'll ask them if the rule is the same.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-11 06:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a feeling you knew you liked girls before starting to watch The L Word :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-08 09:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like the single words are the categories. So, it would be how the reproduction system is affected. "Incontinence, Endometriosis, Fibroids, Ovarian cysts, Low Sex Drive, and Numbness in the Genital area" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-07 04:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Us, too. There was a recommendation of taking photos of cleanliness just in case. Restoration crew might have also taken notes, so you might be able to contact them.

Pretty curious.

Also, there was some info I got about a camp dumping their stuff, including their entire bar in someone's truck. This is around 4 c. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-05 19:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, my mom's side of the family lives in Japan. I remember visiting and being surprised someone called my aunt "obasan" when I was younger and thinking, she's not a grandma! And then connecting the two dots. But I've never really hardcore studied japanese even though I'm fluent so I thought maybe it wasn't the formal way of saying it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-05 06:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grandpa would be more like ojiisan and ojisan is just an older man? Same with obaasan (I don't know how they would be spelt) and obasan. That's what I thought, anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-01 21:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard it only works if you have a deficiency, anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-30 08:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just curious, why did you specifically study dogs? I don't often see the homeless with other types of animals (cats, lizards, whatever) and I'm wondering if it's just because the other ones are more well hidden or because there's something more to dogs? For isntance, do homeless cats usually become strays, and dogs stay? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-29 18:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been trying cold brewing to make iced green tea and it ends up becoming less bitter than hot.

edit: cold brewing as in letting the tea bag sit in cold water for a few hours. not in some fancy machine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-20 21:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's such a good idea. My boyfriend made me a stuffed shark but I lost it about a year ago. The spray is a great idea, but I can't smell :/ Wish there was something similar I could do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-19 21:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've made her recipe and it was actually pretty good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-18 13:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I switched pdocs because of the first was retarded, the second because of a switch in insurance. I'm also on the same meds (Lamictal and Zoloft specifically) and am doing well now, so I try not to worry about it too much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-18 13:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, I'm in the same boat! Decided to stop psychology and do art. Less morally stressful, I think.  I'm also diagnosed with "Mood Disorder NOS" since I've just started seeing my 3rd psychiatrist. He basically told me that how I was feeling is more important than any diagnosis. 

My first psychiatrist diagnosed me with depression, borderline personality, anorexia nervosa, adhd, generalized anxiety and panic disorder. my 2nd psychiatrist was probably just depression and anxiety, and my therapist said anorexia, ocd and depression. now it's just a "whatever". i also like to ask my boyfriend if he thinks i've been acting different and that helps a lot, to get an outside perspective. so if you live with someone you trust, that might be a good idea too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-18 12:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like knowing about how to diagnose and whatnot makes me feel like I'm "faking" a diagnosis for myself. It almost seems too easy to just lie and say I have x,y,z symptoms.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-14 04:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it was right after my 18th birthday but it was a few years of the same behavior. 

Also I absolutely hated her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-14 00:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My pdoc now does not think I have borderline but my 1st pdoc I had, who i hated, diagnosed me with it. So that's why I was put on lamictal right away, which was a good thing and helped with some aspects that might be borderline behavior. I'm only 20 so I can imagine some things I did when I was 16 could have been self destructing but because I was a teenager and I would've gotten over it. 

I think medicine-wise I'm getting the treatment I need. I just recently changed pdocs (because insurance) but so far so good. It's just funny/confusing that I've gotten so many diagnoses that it ends up just being Mood Disorder NOS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-14 00:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope you're doing better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-14 00:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I feel like I've never been given actual diagnoseses(?) that I'm okay with, like on a piece of paper. It'll be more like "Your social anxiety makes you blahblah" or something. I've seen 3 pdocs and 3 therapists and it's usually like that. 

I know I definitely have depression, possibly double depression (lots of dysthymia) but I just don't know if I get hypomanic or it can just be irritability or mood changes due to other things.

It just almost makes me feel like I shouldn't need help if I don't have a specific diagnosis, but I know that's wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-13 12:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i totally understand that feeling. i just end up doing that thing where you can not get the updates from the person. they can even be people close to me but i cannot stand updates about someone complaining about something. it just irritates me to no end because i try so hard to not post anything personal to my facebook. so i just end up becoming friends with them but just try my hardest to not look or communicate. i ignore lots of people though, not so good. but your brain will remember how you felt when this person was in your life, so it might not be the person specifically but where you were in life. like, imagine a time you were infatuated with a person and listening to a song. its the feeling that was important, not the person you were infatuated with.

so, with triggers, i just do my best to avoid the situations. i do also tell myself that rationally nothing will change in my life because i feel strong enough. it's a combination of both, i'm not sure if it's the healthiest but it has worked so far.

another thing right now that is happening is that people are staying at my house and my privacy is so limited and it makes me not want to leave my bedroom, thus i can't feed myself (anorexic) so i just have to push through it. i learned that in therapy. just push through your comfort zone. but it's been incredibly hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-13 12:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm a bit tired to understand (sorry if that's disrespectful) but i am on lamictal (antiseizure, for mood stabilizint) and zoloft which works great. also klonopin which i am thinking is also anticonvulsant qualities. pot is great since i also am anorexic, but it makes me dissociate more (definitely not as bad as pre-lamictal). i currently only smoke what i can get my hands on and i don't have much money to get a card (im in california) but i'm wondering if it's worth it. is there a certain strand i should look for? '

it isnt for seizures but more mood stabilizing for myself. are you saying pot is better for yourself? i ask because i am on anticonvulsants and i've read pot can also do the opposite. i'm not a frequent smoker but i am willing to try more if it can help. my only problem is the dissociation but that might just be because i deny my munchies (on accident). i also may be bipolar ii (well, mood disorder nos). i also have anxiety and ocd-ish. it's all a blur.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 16:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not me. I'm not even on Wellbutrin. It's for my boyfriend with a G addiction and is also on Wellbutrin.  Apparently, when he increased in Wellbutrin dosages, it made the withdrawals from G worse (he's quitting now), so I think he stopped taking Wellbutrin. He's on Lamictal and Adderall now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-15 10:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in the same position in the last few weeks. My boyfriend's niece is couchsurfing with her daughter (age is irrelevant in his family, we're young people who aren't used to lots of people around), and they were here for about 2 weeks. They are housesitting for us at the end of this month so I felt I needed to be extra polite. I didn't want to leave the room which made me not get food which made me more upset. I had some space because I'm also housesitting right now so I got to leave the house about half the time (I have a dog to take care of still) so that helped.  I tried to look at the positive side of it which was that I don't think I acted as depressed while they were around, especially with her 11 year old daughter around.  Although it's more comfortable to be by myself, I know that social anxiety is something I need to work on. Hope you're doing better. It's been a few days for me and I can definitely say I'm feeling better (I just switched meds too though, which is still good, probably some of both). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-14 19:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't go to the last two burns (although I bought tickets) and this is my first year going. I'm going to ("just") community college, so it isn't a huge deal if I'm dropped, but I'm much more likely to get dropped.  I've gotten responses from all the teachers except one. 

I asked for advice from a head professor and he basically just said ask to not be dropped, and the best excuse is a family thing/wedding if they ask. Teachers didn't ask, but my work did. I don't think it's necessary to say more than that, unless you want to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-13 09:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kaya gets down with a lady in True Love! Although it kind of bored me so I didn't watch much of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-06 22:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't smell. Is there a visual way to tell if an egg is rotten (cooked or not)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-05 10:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, listing of facebook and craigslist wouldn't hurt. A lot of money can go into shelters with bills and things, so if you can do it on your own in any way it could be helpful, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-05 10:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That seems kind of illegal :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-02 08:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of [Murakami's eyes](http://www.esquire.com/cm/esquire/images/jellyfish-eyes-murakami-0908-lg-9163923.jpg). Awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-30 01:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am still primarily looking for iPhone deals, which I don't think those companies have. I'll look into it, though. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-29 23:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not rude at all! I just haven't found what I needed, so that's really helpful. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-29 21:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like the [coverage](http://www.showmycoverage.com/mycoverage.jsp?id=P6198TEL) isn't too good, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prepaid phones?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-29 20:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was wondering if anyone has any information about prepaid phones. 

My 2 year contract for my old phone ran out last month, so I'm pretty free to get anything.  I was looking at iPhones, and came across articles about prepaid phones and how over time it saves you money.  For those that don't know about it, this is what I know: You have to pay the full price of the phone (which might be as much as $600 or whatever, as opposed to the $99 with contract deals), but the monthly bill is $30-40, depending on the service.  It's generally with unlimited data / text too. That's more important to me than minutes. 

I went to a Sprint store and asked about it, and they explained that their prepaid service, Virgin Mobile, doesn't have as many towers so you get worse reception or something.  I live in Los Angeles and wonder if that's very important, since I live in a big city and assume there are enough towers around.

Is it worth it? I only see articles about it being cheaper, but no first hand experiences.

Also, I'm in the market to buy a smartphone in general.  I was specifically looking at the iPhone since I have a Macbook Pro. I know none of these options are the most frugal.

Edit: I am also looking at family plans to get a plan with my mom, but it doesn't look like smart phones have much savings for individual vs family plans, compared to the $10 per added line that we had previously. Any specific suggestions for that would be helpful, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-29 20:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have two cards and I'm 20. I just applied for an Amazon credit card and had no problem. I got my first one a few years ago.  I've had a debit card before that, and basically use the credit card in the same manner. I don't buy things that I know I don't have the money for, for instance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-29 18:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a college student, try looking for a torrent of the books. I've found a lot of my books this way.  If it's a book for an english class, you can also try finding audiobooks along with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-24 02:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i disagree! i've had it work 4/4 times. i even met my boyfriend of 3 years there! but only okcupid. much easier to explain what you want out of the relationship i think, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-20 09:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm.. makes sense. I want a professional to say something about this, too.

I've been making kimchi and read someone describing it as "controlled rotting" or something, on the topic of fermentation. So refrigeration is controlling any rotting of any food. Rotting food is bacteria and living things and stuff. It doesn't stop it, but slows it down. 

Actually, I have a book I never read called Wild Fermentation. I should look at that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-19 04:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you know anything about mixing GHB and wellbutrin, by any chance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-18 06:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, oh yeah. A photoshopped poster somewhere. Either way, good joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-17 03:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happens during a linguistic seizure? I did a quick google search and couldn't find out more.  Is it a symptom of something else, like Bipolar? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
