<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3259</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 00:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god that made me laugh so hard! But i agree 100% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 00:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dogs are so precious  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What small thing makes you go from feeling blah to sexy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 00:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whether it be makeup wise or clothing wise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 22:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! Congrats on that!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 22:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the little things like that make us with depression and anxiety one step closer to a better self! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 22:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Three weeks?! That's insane.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 22:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 22:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This made me laugh! Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a dewy looking bb cream, what do you recommend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 00:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have pink hued skin with acne scars and uneven texture, so I also need coverage. 

I currently use reckon colorstay mixed with the Marc Jacobs foundation but they make me look cakey and I'm sick of wearing foundation every day. 

I'm looking for a lightweight, medium to full coverage bb cream or light weight foundation that will make me look dewy but not shiny. 

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just got my period after almost a year of not getting it. What weird things are you celebrating recently? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 23:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been dealing with an eating disorder since early this year and haven't got my period since then. I woke up today and there it was...so I guess I'm celebrating finally getting it and returning to good health. 

What weird or unusual things are you celebrating as of late? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 22:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of all the holiday desserts if have to say Yule logs are my favourite. These look so yummy and you can tell you spent a lot of time and effort into making these. Nice job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nutella-filled cinnamon rolls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 21:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gingersnap-crusted cheesecake for my mom's birthday! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 20:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 20:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly my experience with yeast is that it's best to experiment with 
 recipes before you make them expecting a perfect result. Yeast is very finicky and if the liquid you add to the recipe is too hot you run the risk of deactivating the yeast. 

Rising time is also key. You want to let your yeast doughs proof for exactly how long the recipe states. Let them rest in a well greased bowl (make sure to cover the dough in oil too to prevent it from getting a dry coating) and place in a warm place(I usually preheat my oven and turn it off 5 mins before adding the bowl of dough). 

For cinnamon rolls there's the initial rise and then you roll the dough, fill and cut it and then let it ride again and bake! They gain height in the oven as well. 

If you want a good recipe just send me a message and I will tell you it. It's been a foolproof recipe for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ladies, what stops you from making the first move? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 19:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally feel like I'm not confident enough and am worried about rejection.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you guys have a "problematic" brow? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 07:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My right brow is a mess while my left is smooth af... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most drastic change you've made in your life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 04:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whether it'd be from switching your hair colour or changing your career, what is the most drastic change you've made in your life? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you guys survive family dinners? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 05:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since Christmas is so close, I was thinking I can't be the only one who dreads family dinners. They give me anxiety and I don't like my relatives enough to put up with the stuff they say. Currently how I deal is by either not going or drinking until I can deal... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] A book about a young girl who gets tricked by her teacher </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 04:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This book is about a young girl who lives in a small town where the statue of Jesus and Mary is stolen from a church. There's stuff about a cult and I remember it ends with her finding out her substitute teacher is evil and he tries to kill her. He also leaves cryptic notes around for her to find. I think she also takes care of an old woman but I can't be sure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nutella rolls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 21:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was chopping onions when the "Christmas shoes" song came on. What unfortunate coincidences have happened to you recently? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 16:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The dreaded "Christmas Shoes" song  came on while I was chopping onions...my eyes were already misty and by the time the song finished, tears were streaming down my face. I had to explain to my family that the tears were from chopping onions and not the dang song!

What unfortunate coincidences have happened to you recently? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 13:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem! Hope you enjoy them  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 05:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel you...it seems like every year i simultaneously get excited and dread Christmas at the same time. I feel like everyone just becomes so materialistic and greedy and that makes me angry. 

Christmas is about giving and family...not sales and shopping. I feel like Christmas is more towards kids than adults. There's no longer that magic of waking up on Christmas morning. Instead, I wake up and dread seeing my family as they all sit around stuffing their faces and pretending to stand each other's presence. 

Am I bitter about Christmas? No. But I am bitter about how Christmas is viewed. 

So how I deal with it is simply by living it like any other day. It's only one day of the year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 01:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, sorry... my wording sucked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 21:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are super cute! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 21:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They may be ugly but these guys are super delicious!

I used Betty Crocker's recipe for cinnamon rolls and used eggnog in place of the milk. I made the icing with powdered sugar, butter, vanilla and eggnog. 

The filling is a melted butter, eggnog, nutmeg, cinnamon and sugar blend. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eggnog cinnamon rolls! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 21:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If it were socially acceptable for men to wear makeup, would you start wearing it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 17:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know some guys wear foundation etc but usually it's viewed as weird or just not right. 

Soooo if wearing it was the norm for men, would you guys partake? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 17:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 17:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Homemade cherry cheesecake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 21:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 06:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definition of a fuckboy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 00:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was diagnosed at a relatively young age (about 14), but sufferer years before I told anyone or asked for help. 

It's not easy to ask for help as somehow we've created a stigma surrounding mental illness and it's still a taboo topic. What you have to do though is make sure you tell someone you're comfortable around. Whether it be a parent, family member or friend, make sure they're able to get you help to diagnose you. 

I told my schools guidance counsellor and asked that he call my mom and tell her for me. When she learned, she was upset I didn't tell her but understood and booked me an appointment where I was diagnosed with depression. 

There are resources you can go to if you're not comfortable telling family or friends. You can tell your doctor and ask for help. Remember that you don't have to tell everyone but make sure someone knows.  Please get help before things become worse. 

Wishing you well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your "I can't believe I was in that relationship" stories? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 23:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I had a fling with this guy for two months. At first he was nice, sweet and respectable but then he just got really disgusting. I worked with him and when we were alone together he popped random boners and wanted me to "show him a good time". And when I refused to send him nudes he became rude and whiny. He was also racist, sexist  and lazy. He expected me to be thin but was significantly overweight....I honestly look back on my relationship with him and cringe the fuck out. Sometimes I questions my decisions haha...

So, women of Reddit, what is your cringe worthy relationship story? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 17:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Solved! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 17:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THANK YOU!!! As soon as I saw the cover I instantly recognized it! Thanks!!







 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you guys do when you get down about your looks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 05:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 22:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it doesn't ring a bell :( thanks though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 22:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I checked that series out as it was the top result of my searches but that's not it. I know it's by a female author if I remember correct. Thanks though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] A YA sci-fi novel about different teens when everyone suddenly disappears </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 21:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a sci-fi young adult novel with a blue cover and a bird on the cover I think. It had mini stories of each person and they were in different parts of the world. There was a story with a nerdy guy and an actress when everyone disappears and they travel around looking for other people. 

Sorry if it's not too much info but that's all I can remember as I read the book about 5-10 years ago. 

Edit: They're not really stories it just switches to different narrators throughout 

EDIT: Solved, thanks to u/vermontcheddar ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 05:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I felt like baking but didn't have any of the essentials so I swung by bulk barn and picked up some cake mix, cookie mix and mini cookies. This is the lazy man's "brookie". Cookie dough layered with mini cookies and chocolate cake batter, cooked for 30 mins. 

I enjoyed eating the raw doughs but the final product I found too dry and sweet. It was fun to make but I'll just stick to normal cookies and brownies for now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My take on a "Brookie" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 05:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the one thing your mom did that you said you'd never do, that you do now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 12:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have become a nag monster.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 12:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are so pretty! Kudos to you for taking the time to do such details:)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 12:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As good as these all look, I find myself being drawn to those rice Krispy squares...hot damn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 09:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My skin is really uneven in texture due to previous acne and I  have hyper pigmentation. It's also really red and puffy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you guys ever feel guilty when you wear makeup? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 09:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know...maybe it's because I have awful skin and NEED to wear makeup when I go out, but I kind of feel guilt or shame wearing makeup. I feel like makeup does change how we look and it can make people see us as someone completely different. 

Does anyone else feel this way or similar? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the dumbest thing you were told you couldn't do "because you're a woman?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 05:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 02:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cookie dough base with condensed milk middle. Chopped cookies, caramels and chocolate in the middle too. Then topped off with cookie dough and more sweets. 

Last night I made chocolate chip cookies which didn't turn out too great so I decided to make something with them. 

I tweaked a recipe from Sally's Baking Addiction. I chopped up the cookies and added them between the layers along with caramels and kit kat bars. 

As expected it's very sweet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Ultimate cookie bar. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 02:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 01:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an Italian pastry that's usually filled with ricotta and candied fruit peels. The layers are basic flour and water and then brushed with a lard and butter mixture. It creates a very crunchy shell which mixes with the creamy inside. 

If you live near an Italian bakery I'd recommend trying one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some creative/artistic career paths that actually pay well? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 00:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 23:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wishing you luck and love! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 23:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha same here! I get convinced that one more drink wouldn't hurt. Learned my lesson after I woke up passed out on the couch covered in vomit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 23:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Believe me...I think I swore as much as I did all year making these! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 22:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They may not look pretty, but they taste pretty damn good!

I used the sfogliatelle recipe from here: 
https://crumbsoflove.wordpress.com/2013/11/27/sfogliatelle-an-italian-tail-three-ways/

I know you're supposed to use ricotta filling but I decided to do an eggnog cream filling. All it was was 1/2 cup sugar, 1/4 cup corn starch, 2 cups eggnog, pinch cinnamon and nutmeg and one egg. I added salt to taste and chopped up some chocolate(which melted). 

This took me half a day and I broke my kitchen aid pasta machine attachment before I could finish my last sheet, so I had to roll it out by hand. 

Overall I would make these again just with the ricotta filling and a fixed attachment! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tried my hand at sfogliatelle... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 22:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ladies of AW, what kind of drunk do you get? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 15:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As it is the holiday season, I'm sure some-if not most-of you are planning to get lit as a Christmas tree. (Whether it's to deal with having to be with family or just going out with friends, drinks are heavily a part of this year.)

Now typically women are portrayed as the squealing-OMG-wobbly drunks. I know this isn't true so I'm curious...what kind of drunk are you when you drink?



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 15:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow that's pretty interesting! I've always wanted a nose job because I absolutely hate my nose and it doesn't suit me at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
