<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject375</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 10:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to see the methodology used behind the "People check their phones 2600 times a day on average" because that's A LOT! Like, probably not a correct statistic because it's so much. Just do the math, an 18 hour waking cycle would mean people check their phones 144 times an hour, or twice per-minute. I'd wager my daily average is on the higher end, and I don't come anywhere close to 144 times an hour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 07:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was definitely something generational for a decade or two where, culturally, gamers were considered losers, freaks   geeks, including the girl gamers at the time. 

When I was a teenager, it was considered laughable by my female peers to be playing video games. I succinctly remember several occasions of being insulted or derided (the way kids do) for playing video games, almost exclusively by girls. I also remember a few occasions where I tried to get a girl to play a video game only to be met with an expression of revulsion. To this day, my girlfriend maintains a similar attitude where if I'm playing a game and I want to show her something cool she will roll her eyes and act like whatever I just showed her was sooo lame. I love her regardless somehow. 

The generation of kids younger than me did not seem to have this same issue. I found that girls born in the 90's are not repulsed by video games as much, and younger girls don't have any aversion to video games at all. This is all anecdotal of course, as I'm not a kid and cannot actually embed myself in that culture.

Modern society's viewpoints on gaming/technology and geeks/nerds has shifted quite a bit, to the point where being a geek became so cool that people wear fake "nerd glasses" as a fashion statement. This newfound acceptance has been accompanied by mobile gaming, which appeals to a much wider demographic of people who wouldn't have touched a video game controller about 10 years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 06:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting, any sources on this? From anecdotal experience, some of the most irreligious people I know were ones who went to church like 4 times a week as children and learned it was oppressive nonsense. Many of the religious people I come across rarely go to church and just believe because it's, like, nice to think about or whatever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Sub-optimal" presumes an optimum, and in a post-modernist society there is no such thing as true optimization. How could you be so hateful? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, this! Take your time with the series because once you've seen it all, you've seen it all. 

I recently came to the realization that I had never finished watching TOS Season 3 and I was so giddy with joy to realize I had I unwatched original content still to enjoy. I'm doing one episode a week and I've skipped a few that I will revisit years from now if I can hold off on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 10:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They can be, can't they? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
