<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2482</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stalker much?

Believe it or not, you don't have a right to know the whereabouts or status of someone's phone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is filmed in front of an audience, yes.
Also, there are signs that light up that say when to laugh.

Source: Attended a taping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Off to steal (hotwire) OP's car to prove him/her wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps the Big Crunch model is correct, and we'll all end up back to the spot where you were born!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, why are mug shots of people as well as charges and names freely available to the public before the person is even convicted and found guilty, yet this lady has been found guilty, served time, and freed...yet her image is somehow DRM'ed. Hmmmm.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  paying their waitresses

Am I the only one that noticed the innate sexism?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this, you are wrong.  If (from my example), they chose to not submit their resignation letter, they would be put on the books as being Resigned from the position, and told not to come into work the next day.  
You can call it fired if you want to, but the HR systems and the paycheck folks see "Resigned" in the system. 
aka..Forced Resignation.

Source: I work in govt HR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you 12, /u/ThePerfectScone?  

That's how the world works.  People are forced to resign ALL THE TIME.  
A real-life example...when a new U.S. President is elected, all the old Presidential appointees are either re-appointed by the new President, or they are *forced to resign*.  They have no choice, it's the law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LPT: If an employee is giving you free stuff, they are trying to smash </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I read that most of their testicles were destroyed beyond repair

Wait.  Was repairing their testicles supposed to be an option? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 06:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On Taco Tuesday (tacos for the kids), I make a bed of cauli rice...put the leftover taco meat over it, and put shredded cheese on top of that.  It makes a really tasty taco-ey mixture if you get the ratios right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 08:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama invited the rapper Common to the White House, and conservatives flipped out because of his controversial lyrics.  

Trump invites a self-described murderous dictator to the White House.
"Naw, we're cool with it." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 05:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pedant in me had to stop and say, it's Little Sister, not Big Sister. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, about that $1.50.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the same reason that you could take a huge breath at the surface, and dive as far as you wanted to, or were able to.....then come back up to the surface as fast as you wanted, and you'd be perfectly safe.

If you take air at atmospheric pressure, and go underwater with it...it will compress as you go down.  And as you come back up, it will never expand past that one atmospheric pressure you originally got it from.

It's when you take air down with you that's already pressurized where you have to be careful on your ascent rate, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you told me you loved me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, this is that girlfriend. You still owe me $1.50 from that time I paid for your bus ride, you cheapskate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah...with how I feel waking up in the morning now, vs. how I felt 20 years ago? I'm pretty sure mortality runs in my family. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 04:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...that's no moon... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Command: air and naval operations

Such an under-rated amazing game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Candy bars for some reason have a very selfish bent to their ad campaigns.

Butterfinger, nobody better lay a finger on my Butterfinger.

Twix, two for me none for you.

KitKat, break me off a piece of that KitKat bar.

Snickers, grab yourself a Snickers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/cheeseisthenewbread recently had a post where she made a Ham and Cheese melt on cheese bread.  I made it over the weekend, and it was really...freaking...good.  I felt like I was cheating on Keto.

(I modified her cheese bread recipe to not include parmesan, I don't like the bitterness it gives to the "bun")

[Her post is right here.](https://www.reddit.com/r/keto/comments/66de8o/fp_low_carb_ham_cheese_sandwich_on_cheesy_buns/)

**Edit** Also, her instagram is a WEALTH of amazing Keto recipes.  She needs to write a recipe book.  Seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL: OP is a sexist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 07:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why I never get an omelette or scrambled eggs from a diner type restaurant...you can't trust they aren't doing the batter thing.  I always order my eggs over medium, so I can be sure I'm only getting the eggs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We will forever live parallel lives, never to meet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you trying to get a Rise out of me? Run. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be careful what you wish for </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess you feel about him, the same way that I am immediately feel about you when you use the word cuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LPT: See a doctor, because your digestive system isn't processing your food properly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heck yah. No homo bro. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa whoa whoa...thanking OP's for their user names is a slippery slope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "How to find the true identity of any poster on Reddit in 1 easy step! What no one wants you to know!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 15:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ALWAYS gotta be a pedant in the room! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 06:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That really bugs me.  FDA states ingredient lists are to include the simplest forms of the food item in the list, and should there be a blend of some sort, they are to be listed in parenthesis after the blend. It should say Chocolate Liquor (Cocoa Butter, Cocoa Oil).

What the hell is Cocoa Butter and Cocoa Oils, anyways?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 06:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea who Kevin is. I assume you're her husband.

It has been awhile since I've watched them...but one thing that jumped out at me was when she talked about having a "carb up" day, where you purposefully (in her words) eat "all the carbs", in order to "shock" your body out of its routine.

I get the impression that her videos are aimed at newbies to Keto. In my opinion, it's really not the best thing to tell newbies to keto to do a carb up at all.  

All in all, sure, she's good for the keto community if she gets people on onboard to try it, I suppose. She's just not my style of eggs is all. (Keto pun ftw) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched a few of her youtube videos. They were ok....but she said quite a few things about keto that made me raise my eyebrows....very pseudo-science mumbo jumbo-ey, so that put me off of her.

I kind of realized after how popular she got, going on book tours etc....she's in it for the money now, of course. (Not that there's anything wrong with that)....But some of the things she says just strike me as populist type "increase the cult following" things.

All my opinion of course. If anyone loves her channel or how she motivates you to KCKO, more power to ya. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just did a quick google, they are at www.ketobars.com. Looks to be $21.99 for a 10 pack...so $2.20 each.  

I'd try them out, but they look way too yummy, and I'd probably eat 5 in one sitting, so I'm not going to order any. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chocolate Liqueur is the #1 ingredient?? That's interesting. Lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. I always have a package of Genoa Salami slices in the fridge. Wrap a thin cut slice of provolone around one, and eat 2 or 3 of those, and I'm satiated for awhile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was on my way into work the other day, and a little bit across the parking lot was a cheetah!  I looked at the cheetah, and the cheetah looks right back at me. We both sort of nodded at each other and then immediately took off racing towards the front door of work. It was neck-and-neck, the cheetah was winning, I was winning, we were going back and forth trading places for the leads.  Then, at the very last second, I pulled ahead and made it to the door before he did.  

Moral of the story:  Cheetahs never win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This!!!

So many people "say" they are atheist, but really aren't. I hate how it's the accepted standard that if you aren't religious, you're automatically categorized as an atheist.  Ummmmm, no!  To be an atheist requires just as much "faith" as being religious! 

TL:DR - 95% of people calling themselves atheists, are actually Agnostic. (If you say "All evidence points to that there probably isn't a God"....you're Agnostic, not Atheist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 05:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't pick a hobby. A hobby picks you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [FP] Like Lemon-based desserts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ['I Breathe I'm Hungry'](http://www.ibreatheimhungry.com/2017/04/58-best-keto-lemon-dessert-recipes-low-carb.html) has you covered! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, congrats!!

Also, clean thy room! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant video link

[This video](https://aeon.co/videos/the-plodding-photon-or-how-the-speed-of-light-looks-sluggish-on-a-galactic-scale) gives a fantastic sense of scale for either a) How huge the distance is between the tiny specks of planets in our solar system or b) How slow light really is in the great scheme of the Universe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So...the third will include marshmallows on a roasting stick? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great post </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Article] Daily consumption of sodas, fruit juices and artificially sweetened sodas affect brain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2017-04/bumc-dco041817.php](https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2017-04/bumc-dco041817.php)

Disclaimer:  This is a re-post from /r/Science, but I thought it was definitely Keto related </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 00:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure I will get down voted for this, but how about using the resource that you have, which gives you the entire depth and breadth of human knowledge instantly.

 A simple search for World War II Stalingrad movie would have given you the answer of Enemy at the Gates, instead of typing all that about not actually knowing what the name of the movie is.

Your post has a very "I want answers but I'm lazy and don't want to even look up the most basic thing to try to find out the answer." vibe to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eft this story, man, eft this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, but in the capacity of something completely ironic.  Say...Secretary of Women's Rights or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can do the squeezing yourself, but it's more fun to let the local massage parlor do the squeezing for you for $100. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait....so, a Stone is equal to 14 lbs?  

So, they (British) use a weight measurement based on our Imperial measurements, but go with metric for normal every day use.  Interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cook for two kids as well as myself...and I'll try the carbs that I make for them, to make sure that it's ok sometimes.  Just a 1/4 spoonful of mashed potatoes isn't going to throw me out of anything...and I can tell if it's too/not salty enough, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats!  (Hey, you're my stats twin!)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r/todayilearned should be called r/ThingYouDidNotKnow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have only one, flawed, imperfect point-of-view.  Your own.  But, that's getting into philosophical issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well....technically...you could start celebrating your death day...and then just make it happen the next year.  

That's a long way to go to prove a showerthought wrong though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, now we know where Godzilla will be coming from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not going to go find it for you, but if you look at the transcripts from the White House's site for Trump's speeches (especially his early ones...he hasn't said bigly in awhile), they read "bigly".   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scariest part of this showerthought is "but I've found that..."

The things OP must have experienced! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
