<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1863</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 13:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no politics here.  Mods have read the politics into it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Resistance In Color: Yarn's Craftivist Moment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 12:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 12:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  For example, even among people who can identify the skirt that Scottish men wear as a kilt, the statement A sari is the skirt that Scottish men wear is rated as more true when it is read twice versus only once. On a six-point scale, the participants truth ratings increased by half a point when the known falsehoods were repeated. The statements were still rated as false, but participants were much less certain, rating the statements as possibly false rather than closer to probably false.

 This means that having relevant prior knowledge does not protect people from the illusory truth effect. Repeated information feels more true, even if it goes against what you already know.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that reading a lie multiple times makes people more likely to feel it is true, even if they know factual information contradicting the statement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 12:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 15:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, if you hit something in your bike, most likely you hurt yourself.  Hit someone in your car, and you could kill a bunch of other people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Older Russian Americans Applaud The Putin-Trump Thing; Millennials Just Say 'Nyet' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 13:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 13:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regular users tend to become accustomed to the drug, particularly in terms of cognitive disruption or psycho-motor skills. Because they are accustomed to the drugs effects, this means they may function better relative to nave users. Smoked marijuana produces a rapid spike in THC concentrations in the blood, followed by a decline as the drug redistributes to tissues, including the brain. The psychological impact depends upon a host of variables. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL marijuana levels in the bloodstream do not match levels of cognitive impairment, making it difficult to test reliably for driving while stoned </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 13:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 15:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, but there was also a sentence I took out ahead of the Secondly, so I was avoiding _.... Secondly,..._ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 14:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Secondly was the fact that it was very expensive.  But the author wasn't being very concise so I used an ellipsis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police Commissioner Evans Hopes To Extend Boston's Body Camera Pilot Program </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 13:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 13:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make America Glow Again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 13:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RadiThor. This energy drink was simply radium dissolved in water. It was sold in the 1920s in one-ounce bottles costing about US$1 each ($15 in 2016 dollars). Its manufacturer claimed the drink not only provided energy but also cured a host of ailments, including impotence.

...consumption of these energy drinks never developed into a major public health crisis. This is primarily for two reasons. Firstly, unlike Radithor, most of the other energy drinks on the market were total frauds and had no radium (or any other type of radioactivity) in them at all.... So only the wealthy, like Byers, were able to drink [Radithor] on a daily basis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL of Radithor, a health drink in the 1920s that contained radium and slowly killed its customers. But it didn't cause a public health crisis because it could only be afforded by rich people (unlike cheaper, safer knockoffs) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 13:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 13:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know what's impressive? ONE DOLLAR.  I've got a Sacajawea dollar coin that I'll sell you for 100 cents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New System Could Connect Cell Phones to Real Cells and Treat Disease </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 13:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 13:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except for the guns and bootlegging. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Holyoke Mayor Wants City To Be A Center For Marijuana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 13:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 13:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From a fascinating article on the history of scholarly publishing:
 If a gift succeeded, the gift-giver might, like Galileo in this case, be fortunate enough to receive a gift in return. Gift-givers could not, however, predict what form it would take, and they might find themselves burdened with offers they couldn't refuse. Tycho Brahe (1546-1601), the great Danish Renaissance astronomer, received everything from cash to chemical secrets, exotic animals and islands in return for his discoveries.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
