<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3504</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 07:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They swoop anyone remotely near the best just as a precaution? Jesus! But otherwise homies? Damn, I want to go Australia so bad to be with my spirit people! But the fucking animals are insane!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 07:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting! Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 07:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I grew up in the same type of culinary environment. If they are hostile then let them be. Who cares. Learn to not care. I hid it painfully. (Throwing away meat given to me in secret lol)
1. Don't buy in to fake meat. They should only be used as a weaning method and nothing more. Super processed. (A soybean into turkey, huh?)
2. Research. Research. Research. Diving right in can be fatal to your moral.
3. Go on YouTube and look up vegan/vegetarian bodybuilding. They will show you how to implement this diet into losing weigh and gaining muscle.
4.It's ok if you are lost! STICK WITH IT! The first few months are hard. (Insert fake meats for weaning.)
5. Learn to cook in general not just random recipes. You'll feel stuck when the recipes get old. A veteran veggie head can cook anything you throw at them. Check out my post to r/vegan. I just threw together what I had on hand. This helps with meal planning!
6. PEOPLE WILL BE DICKS. I SWEAR TO GOD DUDE. "Bro, how do you get protein?" "Are you malnourished?" "YOU CANT BE VEGAN/VEGETARIAN AND GAIN MUSCLE?" "You're gay?" (Aimed at men idk why meat is associated with masculinity) refer to #3!! You'll be okay! Stay focused! I've been a veggie head since 2011. It's totally normal.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not Australian! Are magpies a legit threat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Song lowkey ripped </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm crying right now this is so funny. The music split my fucking sides. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 05:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or take longer breaks between hits. 2-3 mins. Some people puff till the bowl is gone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 05:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does your PT represent Portugal or Brazil? A speech impediment? Hmm never saw it that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant paths for other languages as well:
Swedish-Norwegian or vice versa? Languages that are related in a sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this because Portuguese is more nasal? Sometimes I can't hear a certain accent. Like the word for bread (po) isn't as easy as just saying pow (incorrect). Spanish is "clearer"? Maybe that explains the one way understanding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best language paths? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking Spanish-Italian-Portuguese. I think understanding the previous will help the next? What paths did you take? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand what you mean by prioritizing languages but mandarin is HARD. The real question is why the hell did they include Klingon?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 10:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe in karma so I only roasted him in my head. You said it not me.

Capheus: Huh?
Me: YOU SAID IT NOT ME! Damn..can't he hear? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My-Tho noodles with carrots, broccoli, corn, and onions. So yummy. (Noodle are naturally gluten-free) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! The usefulness of French in Canada is like Spanish down here in the states. German is useful in Ohio and Pennsylvania.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Disneyland, they have name tags that say "I speak..." in that language so people know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just a quick question! :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I am currently trying to learn a different language on Duolingo to better my communication skills. How has learning another language or being fluent in one, seriously helped you when working? Curious! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They look nice though! Free-form? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have locs too! I just love the loc community! Did you see Whitney Mixter's hair? When she had it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have locs!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in target and smelled someone dank. I almost broke my damn neck whipping it around so fast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao I wonder how many people on this sub post because their partners are away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 10:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was wondering how sun was just renting motel rooms and walking the streets like okay????? No one sees her? Or is only the detective looking lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 10:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He didn't take her seriously at all. I was so pissed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 10:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same on younger jonas. Didn't have to add it to Capheus' mother though lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 10:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's be real. Besides the amazing screenplay and casting, we came for the orgies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 10:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her name is Min-Jung. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can do it girl! I thought I was alone in feeling so fucking weird. Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I, also, am the only I know that can't drive! I felt so alone in this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always liked not contributing to our depletion of quality of life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you have any fear of driving? I feel like I am OK I just want to kind of get it over with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you ever feel weird when it comes up in conversation? I feel so freaking awkward.
Yes! The dependency is terrible. My girlfriend is a perfectly capable driver, but I almost never asked her for rides when she had a car because I just felt so bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got a new job! Getting a beater sound doable. My gf can drive so it wouldn't be a waste. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually grew up in Los Angeles county. Where you can cover the entire county by buses alone. Also, there are large metropolitan areas that you can pretty much cover by trains. I lived in Pasadena. Traveling to downtown only took 20 mins!(They just added in a new extension that goes to the beach which is pretty awesome.) Point is, If you really needed to get around w/o a car it was doable.

Now, I moved to a place where you NEED a car. And now I'm screwed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look up vegan recipes and how to eat/cook better. Tempeh, tofu, and fake meats are all essentially weaning foods. You can't live off of them. You can find high protein snacks. LOOK AND TRY. If the diet is the only reason why you wont be vegan, just go vegetarian so you can understand more. It seems like you lack knowledge in the vegan area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smartphones are ruining the alarm clock business. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, don't make me cry.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do you live? Facebook vegan groups! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would change only AFTER taking a comsci 101 course. You are a chem major failing chem. What if you fail at comsci too? You'll be able to drop if it's too hard. If you totally understand it and enjoy it then go for it! I'm a comsci major and I think it's totally fun!

"If you love what you do, you never have to work a day in your life."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 09:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am excited mostly for a show that's ACTUALLY scary! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 09:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 9:11 :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I might just be my palate. :( I can't stand it no matter which way it's prepared. Could be worse. I could think cilantro taste like soap.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kitty Kush </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How was it? I want to go to a Football country so bad!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of Candle Cove. Bizarre coincidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE think that black pepper taste like ash? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol you nasty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like this is 75% of the reason why people want to become polyglots. Just to have fun and talk to people. Breaking the language barrier really opens people up. I think some Americans assume that foreigners are rude when really maybe they don't understand. No one walked away from him. They all stayed to have a chat. What an epic video. I'm re-downloading Duolingo!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 03:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Head bunts=kitty hug </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 02:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think of it like Thanksgiving and waiting hours to eat it lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 02:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I met some Aussies who felt almost embarrassed that they almost walked away without tipping. They were informed that that is what we do here. I told them that it was no big deal, no need to tip. I was pretty embarrassed as well. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only Americans, I think, that kinda live in a demanding tip universe. I only tip if the service was great or my order was correct and the person wasn't a douche (common). I never tip a douche. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That made ME feel guilty lol damn! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Made a few days ago! Couldn't see in other post! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was going to throw away this box. I decided to make a slightly interactive bed instead. Cats sure do love cardboard! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably In America. As an American, I can say we do not like being so close. Not in a negative way, just who we are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah!...awww </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 00:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's hope for at LEAST a 2-14 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Warm water, nice food. Small place? Sure. But don't worry what people think! It was my favorite vacation! Try Aulani! It's the Disney Resort there! They have their own private beach and you can get drunk on the beach. Character meet and greets. Private snorkeling reef, the character buffet has a woman singing while you eat! It's amazing to be honest. If you rent a car you can go to waikiki in no time! Check it out! Entertainment everyday! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hawaii? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmfao is this meme really called "black guy confused"? But pick it up and chuck back at 'em! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grubhub? Postmates? Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbh, like four. I thought he was trying to get me lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fraud maybe. The cost cost of a child is too fucking high! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 13:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I'm the only one who read this in Dave Grohl's voice I'll be sad! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 10:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My school tried to do this but for a test. We didn't take it and we all had a protest. We skipped class and sat together on the school lawn! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 10:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did men wear those pants? Nowadays, guys would be like "owww..my junk!" Were they stretchy? Or did everyone's balls get smaller? Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 09:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big Red One made me into a COD fan! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP is referring to Yogi the bear if my memory is correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got her from a coworker! Thanks! I was mostly wondering just in case her specific breed needs certain care. Her hind leg was limp from birth. I know some breeds have health issues, so I thought maybe it was from a certain breed. But she might just be a beautiful mutt with a gimp leg haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is my favorite place </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made a list compiled from the internet:

(Parenthesis means not likely, but just in case.)

Asian Semi-Long Hair
Birman-(ColorPoint)
British Long Hair
Chantilly-Tiffany-(Golden Eyes)
Cymric
Himalayan-(Colorpoint) 
Nebelung-(Green eyed, Black)
Norwegian Forest Cat
Traditional Persian
Ragamuffin/ Ragdoll
Siberian
Turkish Angorra </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My new baby, Mia. What breed is she? She is medium sized, slightly fat, with longish hair, and born with a non-useable foot. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 09:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weird, today was approximately 70 Degrees. Perfect weather! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 06:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are born after 1984 you are technically a millennial!


I think lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know why but I am super surprised to see Baltimore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, the Outback is looking nice right now.



(Spider probably African)

It's black.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100% agree. Kind if cringe when I see that. It's basic, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HOLY SHIT BALLS.


Exactly as I thought. 

BUT STILL


ANY DOCTOR WHO FANS? SENSE 8 ON NETFLIX HAS FREEMAS TITTTTIIIEEESSS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 10:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try ONE hit and see how it feels after like 15 mins. You may get pretty high because you have never smoked before. If you're good then chug on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
