<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1120</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ugh! I hate this thumbs up/down thing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 02:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> i have an issue with numbers, especially large ones and I can't get my brain to even do this. I just need to know what percentage 4.5 million is our of 7.5 billion is? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 00:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Me IRL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 21:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 20:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol yes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 08:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here you go, this video came out today and covers the case, including the magic angle, well. Weird it came out today.

https://youtu.be/vS6QJoagFKA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 08:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It did, still has some uses. And some biases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 08:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's one I'm really hazy on, I am really into unsolved disappearances, but I seem to remember one case where someone claimed an Africa American boy,who was autistic maybe, was kept in a basement and then reported missing. There was speculation on the charley project that the child did not exist. 

I really need to start writing this all down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 06:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's going to make a helluva book. If we can still print books that is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 05:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, that's a Twilight Zone episode right there.  Poor man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 05:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/UnresolvedMysteries/comments/39y11g/last_thing_heard_by_his_parents_was_oh_shit/

There you go! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 03:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> School stopped. Once school stopped everyone vanished, not in a bad way, it was just natural. I realized how stupid I'd been. Then it just stopped. I had my moments after that, of course, but all those people who talk about being friends forever in H.S. and all that shit, it's not true. Once you leave school and start your life or college, focus on that, you'll see how easy it is, get away from the toxic people, focus on your life and poof, you're a new person if you do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 02:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not well. I drank or smoked pot when I could, never did my school work, I was suicidal for most of my school years. I hung on to people who used me for sex or whatever, people who made fun of me behind my back. Basically, just trying to keep myself alive day to day. If i knew then what I knew now, I wold have shaken all those toxic fake ass friends off and threw myself into my studies. I regret it all wholly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
