<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1713</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 05:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was a kid, me and my sister were left alone at our house while my mom was away on errands. We are sitting in the living room watching TV, when we here a knock. Thinking my mom was home I looked out the window expecting her, but I see no-one. I go back to watching TV, thinking it must have just been the house creaking or something. My sister and I continue watching TV, when I hear the knock again. This time I realized it came from the wall in the hallway. Me and my sister freaked out thinking it might be a ghost or something. Eventually we got brave enough and I went to the hall way and looked around. There was no sign of a ghost. For some reason I decided to knock on the wall, and then a second later I heard I knock in return. I freaked out still thinking it might be a ghost, I knocked twice and my knocking was returned with two more knocks. At this point me and my sister were freaking out so we ran to the garage and locked ourselves in. We continued to hear knocking so I called my mom and she came home. To this day I don't know what it was.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 05:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad, cuz I had to pay for all of the therapy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 21:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The final fight in uncharted four was legendary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 14:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright I'll probably go with both of those examples. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 14:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone know who created this site was it Laird Wilcox or just someone who knew of him? My professor says it doesn't seem like a legitimate source. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
