<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2797</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> are there some papers that you feel everyone interested in a career in maths should read? if so do you have any links or sources for them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking mostly in terms of "classic" works like papers written by Lagrange, Monge, Poncelet, Poincare etc...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol I've come to the honest conclusion that I'm not doing what I want to do in life. I keep having to jump through all these stupid hoops like gen eds and multiple unpaid internships while working a job I absolutely hate and do not care about. I also have no social life, and no it's not because I'm "too busy" it's because nobody seems to really have an interest in me. I'm just so tired of not doing what I want to do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> same. I just cant' kill myself because my parents don't deserve that. but sometimes I wish something else would just kill me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 21:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're a math major? so you're good with numbers huh  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> every heard of a problem in topology that involves reflective rays inside a closed curve ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 20:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a professor the other day mentioned how a circle has infinitely many points such that a ray would reflect off the other side back and forth infinitely, also an ellipse would have 2 pairs, and asked if there are other examples of shapes that do this. thats my best way of describing what he said.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 05:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice thanks. do you try to use blobs to think about most theorems in topology?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> how can I intuitively think of the closure of a top. space? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 04:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Studying analysis and basic topology from a book. I understand the definition to an extent, but I'm not completely sure how to picture it or think of it. advice is much appreciated  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no my b I was having a shit day and overreacted  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 06:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the first time I saw this I had tears dripping down my face and my abs were sore for at least a week  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 09:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but what's wrong with that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> is there a such thing as general addiction to drugs/alcohol </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 09:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tend to do whatever I can get my hands on, usually sticking to 2 or 3 key drugs, drinking alcohol every day. But I don't feel addicted to a specific drug, just to being NOT sober in any way possible. If I have to go a full day completely sober from everything I have a really hard time keeping my cool and I get really depressed and agitated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 08:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is it a vague question? Why does everyone on /r/math keep saying this in response to my posts? It's a simple question that I was just curious about there's no need to be rude. If I ask a specific question I get redirected to another damn thread  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What mathematics has been inspired by the go game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 06:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have heard/read that maths research has been inspired by the go board. What branches of math have theorems inspired by this game? Does anyone have any papers on this I could read or links etc.? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 23:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> applied mathematicians use results from pure mathematics though so... think of it as having a trickling down affect so to speak  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 23:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> alright here's a really embarrassing question. If you wanted to get a job in cryptography do you need to know an absolute ton of programming ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 20:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just trying to explore future career options. I love math but I couldn't possibly hate programming more. it's so ugly looking and it's a pain in the ass idk how anyone likes it at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 01:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well, I'm tired of not having my damn degree yet. I'm 22 and I still have 1.5 to 2 years left before I get my bachelors. I'm always broke working a dumb ass low paying job. and again, no social life. it seems like everyone else is happy and perfect and having fun but me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 04:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe I'm just mad at myself  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 21:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the ability to relate to at least one person who I am friends with. to have a job that is actually in my field, to be highly skilled at something. and to have friends who actually invite me out once in a while. I'm a college student with a completely abnormal college social life... as in I don't have one. and I have absolutely no idea how I'm supposed to start one. it seems like an impossible and highly complicated task, which everyone seems to understand but me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah I just don't understand how to go about it. deep breathing doesn't seem to work very well, my heart remains pounding and my adrenaline is still pumping if not even more so with that extra oxygen  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tried therapy. but it just seems to be the same thing over and over again that I'm told in terms of how to deal with it. but it never really changes. "think about what you're doing before you do it". it all happens incredibly fast there is no time to stop and think I just get possessed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [University Physics 1] motion in a straight line </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 16:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is a test question I did not think was very fair. a girl tosses a ball vertically upward and times it to measure the height of a pole. once she tosses the ball, it passes the top of the pole the first time in .5 seconds, then on its way back down passes the top of the pole again after 4 seconds total. how high is the pole? (ignore air resistance) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 16:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> especially driving and having to be around other people all day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 16:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats pretty cool actually  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sounds like you were at least out at a party. those things I never get invited to. try being a blackout drunk who always drinks alone in his room. well at least I don't have to worry about getting home  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> same. that's literally all I can say is same.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> is anyone else constantly angry? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm either angry or on the verge of snapping over something completely ridiculous 24/7. sometimes I'm even thinking pretty violent thoughts. I just hate the fucking world. even my dreams have been fucked up  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> alright thanks. well I kinda like PDE's so maybe I will eventually find something that uses them. I'm just a little upset because I really love topology but I'm about positive the only thing I could do with that is to be a professor lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 02:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was gonna say 4 colors theorem lol it's so disappointing in my opinion. but of course I have been shit on by reddit for saying this before so it's apparently only ok when anyone else says it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt I would like it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 05:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand I am doing a lot of generalizing and I apologize. I just want to know what some people have to say about this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 05:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ugh good point. ok how about this. are there jobs besides teaching for those who have graduate degrees in more abstract fields ex. topology, differential geometry, set theory/foundations of mathematics, maybe even string theory? what about PDE's which I suppose is a bit more applicable to the real world  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 05:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> holy shit im not the only one who does this? LOL! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 05:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes lol and I'm not totally opposed to that. but that seems to be the only option and I was just politely asking if there are any other options ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> is it really THAT difficult to find jobs as a pure mathematician? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 03:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this seems to be what everyone is telling me, which is a bit discouraging. applied mathematics to me just doesn't seem like something I would love as much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 14:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hm interesting I respect that argument  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 03:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just looked it up and it seems like unnecessary jargon to me. you're either depressed or you're not. sometimes people try to make things a little too complicated with all of these sub-types of all these disorders in my opinion  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would also like to point out how its completely socially acceptable for a woman to just outright insult a man by (example you calling me man baby) but the other way around? you get a fucking march on washington. you wanna be equal ? stop being hypocrites  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yea easy for you to say. you're a spoiled American woman. very typical.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to me it's about finding something to live FOR, which again for me personally is about finding something I want to be really good at, and better than most people at. competition keeps me going for the most part. Im more so depressed for social reasons  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
