<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3788</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can tract the logic. It's just one of those things. It's almost along the lines of the fetus being a tenant, the mother a landlord, and evicting the fetus for unpaid rent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What...the...fuck are you smoking? 

By far one of the craziest ideas I've seen on here. Lol! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 12:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Essentially, memos are a cumulative dump of information pertinent to a specific problem/issues that has been researched. Memos are a way to explain the actual law associated with the issue you're researching. 

Creating/proposing law can be different depending on many circumstances...so, it depends.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 02:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 00:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Water heater...hand wash those dishes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 00:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is how my professor had it lined up as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could/ should go speak with a real estate attorney in your area who practices real estate law. Seek out one that will give you a free consultation. There are many issues that can arise with seeking a liquor license. For example, some localities will set a cap on how many are given out within each zone. Things like this are very jurisdictional and will require some research to see what the current zoning laws are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the business?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Schools offer these to make themselves sound more competitive, when, in reality, these mean nothing. It depends on what types of jobs you'll be looking for post graduation. If your going Biglaw, they won't care what your certificate is in. But, if you go in-house/JD Advantage or small firm, then they may take your certificate as a plus because you've "concentrated" in a specific area of the law. 

All these things are is a way for a school to forecast what classes they need to offer. If you have 10 students going through X certificate path, then they know your going to have 10 students that need the required classes A,B,C, and D.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Secured Transactions..A9..thought it was going to chew me up and spit me out. Ended up Ace'n the class and fell in love with A9. 

Undergrad/background in Crim Justice, thought I would love Crim Law/Crim Pro/Evidence...hated them ALL! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If you need any other help I can work through the UCC (A2;A3;A4;A9; and the Bankruptcy Code) pretty easily. 

Just hit me up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * 9-109(A/1): Remember A9 does not apply to security interests (SI) in real property, this section creates an exception that, "AP applies to any transaction that creates a SI in personal or *fixtures*..."

* 9-102(A/41): Under the UCC there is a limited definition for Fixtures, which means "goods that have become so related to a particular real property that an interest in them arises under Real Property Law." This is quite vauge, and being that there are 50 states, all with different real property law--this definition does not help much. 

* George vs. Commerical Credit Corp. Case: The court in George identified a 3-part test to determine whether a good was a fixture. In order to be a fixture, the good must satisfy ALL 3 prongs, (1) Whether or not the good has been physically annexed to the property; (2) Whether or not it has adapted to the use or the purpose for which the real property is devoted to; and (3) The *INTENT* of the person was to make a permanent accession to the freehold. 

* Analysis the 3 prongs above

* 9-501(A/1/B): Remembering that traditionally to protect a SI the secured creditor files a financing statement at the secretary of state in which the Debtor is located. Fixtures are different, they must be filed at the County Registrar of Deeds in order to be effective, this is called a fixture filing. 

* 9-502(B)/Lewiston Case: Provides for the requirements for a Fixture filing-most important is the name or the property owner and not of the Debtor; these can be different if the Debtor is leasing. If the name is not of the property owner then the filing is ineffective. 

* 9-501(b): This is known as the *Transmitting Utilities Exception*, which has the effect to allow the Creditor to go back to the general rule for Finance Statements and file at the secretary of state which covers the entire state.  

* 9-334: Governs the Priority Rules regarding fixtures. The main battle the UCC is worried about involved the Creditor who has a SI in a fixture and has filed a fixture filing vs. someone (creditor/owner) who has a SI in the fixtures by virture of having a mortgage interest in the real property the fixture is located. 

* 9-334(c): Established the general rule that a SI in fixtures is subordinate to a conflicting SI of a mortgagee, or the owner of the real property, other than the Debtor. Where an individual is leasing the property to which a fixture sits, the SI will be senior to that interest. 

* Exception to the general rule: One big exception to this general rule is that where there are conflicting SI of an encumbrance/mortgage, if the Debtor has an interest of record in the real property, or is in the possession of the real property. An interest of record simply means they have recorded their interest in the real property and have perfected through a fixture filing before the encumbrance's interest was recorded. This is the basic race rule, whoever has done things first has won the basic priority battle. 

* 9-334(d): Exception to the general priority rule above, this is the PMSI Fixture Super Priority Exception. 

* 9-334(h): Exception to the general priority rule above, this is the Construction Mortgage Super Super Priority Exception. 

* 9-334(e/2): Exception to the general rule that a fixture may not be removed once its situated, if its readily removable.

* 9-604(d): Damages reimbursement; A secured creditor shall promptly reimburse any encumbrancer/mortgagee/ owner of the real property for the cost of repair of any physical damages caused by the removal of the fixture. Before the removal, assurances of payment/bond may be sought to protect the real property. 

* 9-334(e/3): Gives the rule where a Judicial Lien Creditor obtains a lien on the fixture property. After the secured creditor has perfected in the fixture by filing a fixture filing; under the general rule in 9-317(a) the secured creditor has perfected before the judicial lien attached, and therefore has priority over a judicial lien creditor. 

[Book Outline Photos](https://imgur.com/gallery/cUJc1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 14:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm talking about real estate brokers. 

If you have a broker that deal exclusively in buying/selling businesses...then you should be ok.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 01:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What type of business? Do you have licenses they want to buy too?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 01:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a lawyer. 

Brokers are in the business of selling homes, they do not have the specialized knowledge of selling a business. Have they bought/sold a business before? There is a lot of things that go into selling a business, let alone determining the accurate value itself. 

You said they are working with the buyer, how are they working with them? There are no professional rules to safe guard your best interest.You have to remember the Broker wants the sale, period, they have an internal and un-avoidable conflict of interest. 

I know some Legislature gives them the right to sell a business, but that doesn't mean they are the best professional to do so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you know for next time then. Just learn from the mistake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the typical response until your done with law school.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Typical response, you'll probably get an A.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well when you go into Trek your going to see how expensive this sport has become. It blows my mind to see bikes for $5-6,000 on their website, but they wouldn't be building them if people weren't buying them. 

I'm the same way. I'm super rough on my bike, my car, really everything. I'm not afraid to lien back and hit that jump; I've got the scars to prove it. It's one of those things that you want something that is going to hold up to what you throw it's way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in the same boat you are. I use to ride BMX 20in back in the day; a lot of flat land/dirt track stuff. Never had a mountain bike before. 

I'm actually going to the Trek shop today to test out their line. I had my eye on the Marlin bikes. I was debating on 4 or 5 because of the wheel size. The 27.5 feels huge to me coming from a 20, so I'm gonna test the 29/27.5 to see the difference. 

I'm a big guy (6'5 225) so I think I'm gonna go with the bigger size...because that's usually how it goes. Both bikes are $439(4) and $489(5)..but they are built to ride. My buddy has the Trek 5 2016 model and I took it for a spin and loved it. 

I'm gonna beat the thing up riding it so I want to get my money's worth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Halo 2 for me...gotta get that 50! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd assume the remote positions would be competitive. If you look at the job posting you should be able to see if there is a specific state required; again I'd assume it's employer specific. PM me if you want, I can maybe help with the search if you'd like.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's money. 

There is a self-infused stigma associated with these jobs, i.e doc review positions. The Doc Review places in my area pay $28-31+/hr to licensed attorneys. They also demand you work 40 hours a week, so your going to gross $60,000 ish salary wise. Usually they are super flexible with how you put in your hours as well and allow you to come in early, stay late, or work from home--all depends on the project. 

Do what's ever best for you. Even if it's a temp position, it's a lot better than having no position at all IMO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> C would not be able to sue A directly and would have to sue A. C does not have standing to sue under the contract because they were not a party to such contract; your correct on that. 

This sounds and feels like a Federal Rules of Civil Procedure question. Without specific facts/answers I can't answer it fully.

NZ's law will govern the legal issues because that's what they agreed upon; this is my guess. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking enigma over here. 

Edit: In all seriousness though, if that's how your brain can remember it, then so be it. Mine works in similar fashion, I usually just had to remember my codes, but when I could use notes I did something similar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So expensive. There are many other healthier/ less expensive options.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 13:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In elementary school I was taught to say "amen" after the final verse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 03:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anytime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Money Damages are the typical remedy in Contract/Sales Law. The overall goal: *Is to put the non-breaching party in as good a position as performance would have done, plus consequential and incidental damages, if any, less possible mitigation of damages.*

The two main ways to calculate money damages are: (1) Expectation Damages; (2) Reliance Damages. 

**Expectation Damages** are intended to put the injured party in the same position as if the contract had been fully performed. 

There are three major limits on calculating Expectation Damages: 

* (1) Expectation Damages MUST be proven with reasonable certainty given the P's position; Brand new or unproven business ventures have issues proving lost profits from lack of a consistent sales record. 

* (2) Consequential Damages are NOT recoverable unless the damages were reasonably foreseeable and contemplated at the time of the contracts formation (Hadley Rule)

* (3) Once a breach has occurred both parties must take reasonable steps to mitigate damages resulting from the breach. 

**Reliance Damages** are intended to put the party in the same economic position they would be had the contract never been formed in the first place. 

Reliance damages may be recovered if a non-breaching party incurs expenses in reasonable reliance upon the promise that the other party would perform; these are the steps the parties have taken towards performance of the contract. 

**A PARTY CANNOT RECOVER BOTH** Expectation and Reliance Damages--so you must choose what damages to seek. 

**Detrimental Reliance** is not a form of damages. Generally an Offeror is free to revoke any offer anytime before the Offeree accepts. However, the Offeror's power to revoke their offer is restricted under Detrimental Reliance because the Offeree has reasonably and detrimentally relied on the offer in a foreseeable manner. 

Damages are very fact specific. I don't remember a case with Det. Reli. in it dealing with damages. I guess you could for see a case where someone has tried/revoked their offer, but the offer was accepted and the offeree had incurred damages as a result of the offeror's revocation/their partial performance. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had at as a child and never gave math a true chance. Shitty part is it was my mother who put the anxiety in my head. My father, grandmother, grandfather, and aunt all were/are Engineers/Mathematicians on some level. I'm teaching myself from the start all over again because anything is possible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA: Do you use a printer/fax/copier? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Potential Security Risks](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iC38D5am7go)

After watching this short video I had to share it with this community. 

With privacy risks all around us, it's important to know how to protect your clients! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone has a trademark on Taco Tuesday...but they don't enforce it. I forgot who has it. 

Edit: [Taco John's Trademark Story on "Taco Tuesday"](https://priceonomics.com/the-trademarking-of-taco-tuesday/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say you should pay it off each month. 

How much is the interest rate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People do this all the time with land trusts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, great story. 

I totally agree with you. You put the time and effort in to write something original, screw him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so sorry. Things will get better just stick with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect! Great to know. I'd assume it goes by the upload date in its calculation. Thanks for the insight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No way. 

It literally could be 100% worse! Here are a few examples of how it could be worse:

* You could be dead;
* You could have failed out of law school;
* You could have failed the bar exam;
* You could have been rejected based on C+F;
* You could be stuck as some SUPER^super shitty job being under valued--like EVERY one of those jobs you applied for views you;
* You could be a whole hell lot worse off than you are now. 

You have to focus. Adversity is a gift, some may disagree, but you find out who you truly are when your on the bottom. What are your dreams, your goals, what is important to you? 

Drowned out all the other noise, even the bullshit your telling yourself. I was in a serious emotional/mental rut for about six months following the bar exam. I felt worthless, and that I was certainly doomed; I woke up. 

I'm not saying it's going to take place right at *THIS POINT* (Jedi mind trick). Maybe this message will serve as the seed planted within your brain which will enable you to open your mind once it festers and hits the right synapse. 

What ever it may be that your destined to do, your not doing it now. Put yourself in a position that will unlock the one door you've been working towards. Be honest with yourself and self assess. It's clique, but you can literally do anything you want right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't you go solo, or leech onto a mentor-attorney--do you have any contacts that could help you out?

Maybe these firms don't see that your going to provide them value if they take you on. I was in a similar boat, but I changed my mindset about what I was looking for, and once I was comfortable with different options things fell into place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 00:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have NEVER applied to refinance my student loans, nor have I given my information to anyone other than my school:

* How am I receiving all of these student loan refinance pamphlets in the mail? Do you think there has been a FERPA violation somewhere down the line? 
* Or, does FERPA not apply to my educational borrowing records, and solely to my educational records? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boom...question answered! Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Law Firm Blogging--How do you protect your blog content? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't seem to find anything on how to protect your original blog content. 

What's stopping someone from going to your blog and ripping off your original content to use for their own webpage?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regarding #6: True story. 

I packed my life in and shut everything out for three years. The journey was worth it, but you stepping into a new level of life.

Edit: Shift in priorities is a big thing to think about as well. Shut out everything that is not important to you, and manage your time effectively.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's a skewed example. To be a physics teacher at a college level will be different then at a high school or middle school level.

The necessary steps are the boxes you need to know and check in order to reach your goals. If you don't know what you need to do, then that's step one. 

Figure out everything you can about what you want to achieve and in the process you will know the direction you must travel. There is nothing simple about starting from the bottom. You have nothing but a goal, you've made strides towards your goal, but this is only the beginning--gain as much experience as you can and use everything you've learned to your advantage. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you've taken all the necessary steps and your ready to take the first leap!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said the same thing! You know there is some shit in those caves! I see two.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I can piggy back off this, try and get as much experience writing motions as you can. It's not something I was taught in school and only got to do two times while I worked at the small firm. In my experience smaller firms are geared more to transactional business and not so much litigation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd try for something that is a little faster pace. 

I worked at a small two attorney firm and I did a lot of what your doing. It's very good insight to how a small firm functions, but it's going to have it's downfalls. Get as much practical experience as you can and never burn bridges.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 16:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know nothing about this computer. 

I have 13 floppies and 8 of them will boot the system up. I can't seem to get the external floppy drive to read so I can't use two at once. 

Any suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 13:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
[My Weekend Estate Sale Haul](https://imgur.com/gallery/rEeXX)

Went to my first two Estate Sales where I lined up. I was #18   #8 for the sales, so I was the first wave in for both. I think I did alright, but I picked up a few tricks to improve my game. 

Everything will be on eBay soon! 

Took my wife as my bag/holder lady...worked out so well!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 03:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://imgur.com/gallery/vuiEL

Here is the link to the photos...you have completely turned my Harry Potter book world upside down. I've been using the CW numbers all along and didn't know about all this other jazz...and now I'm not sure wth this book is! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's weird. No price in DJ and the DJ has the red barcode back. 

But the book has the numbers on the copy write page. I always thought the CW numbers were the best identifiers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, crap. I've been going off the numbers on the inside. Well, again, I'm not gonna pass them up for $2.00 mint.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually don't pick up Goblet and later, but I couldn't pass up a mint first for $2.00! All of the Potter's are firsts/firsts, though. I just love cheap books...$2.00 each! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The estate sale itself, or what I bought? 

https://imgur.com/gallery/oZyWX

Here is a link to what I purchased.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://imgur.com/gallery/oZyWX


Looking at the photo with the blue circle, I thought that book was a 1st edition Black's Law Dictionary. It ended up to be a Michigan Legislature Book...but the trip ended up to be great as you can see from the first photo. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jeez, I personally think that's bullshit. I'm using my time and my money to drive to these sales...for what, someone to roll out of bed an hour after me to show up right as it opens to go in before me?! 

I'm just thankful I got everything I wanted. I could have taken a different route through the house, grabbing a few things as I went, but I was so focused on that damn book! Haha I could barely sleep!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GOT IT! 

Super^super pumped. I actually got a lot of other books I can flip as well. I will edit this post and provide a photo when I can. I got a super nice haul at this estate sale. 

I was talking to a lady before it opened and apparently the "usual" customers keep street numbers for their friends...this is the first time I have done this, but I have no problem telling them to go F themselves. 

Has anyone dealt with that before? People holding numbers for others not even there yet. I know it took place because their circle was standing around and someone walked up and I witnessed the number exchange first hand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You were right. Everyone ran in an went for the obvious collectibles and electronics. I had only one other person looking at the books with me and they were focused on a set of books. 

Man, I cleared those books out! I got the books I was gunning for AND MORE!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahahahaha...wth!? 

It clearly reads "Super Nintendo." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Family law, didn't you hear "board certified," she only said it 1,000 times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use to regularly move refrigerators by myself when I worked for a moving company. 

I'm 6'5 230lbs, though; I'm very abnormal. Haha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a buddy that will go to junk yards and find OEM parts and will basically legally chop up the car. He sells the parts on eBay after cleaning them up and testing them. He will also do this with cars he buys super cheap ($500-$600, or less). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 02:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The listing just says "Street Numbers honored at 8:30 a.m. Friday"

So, I'm under the impression it's up to the customers to hand out numbers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 02:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect, thank you so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 02:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it is an antique book. The book itself is not very ornate and you wouldn't know it was worth anything unless you looked it up or knew in advance; it's worth, depending on the condition, $500-$1,200. It's not your typical collectible. There is regular tin toys and other collectibles at this sale, but I have an unconventional taste; I've never found this book in the wild before. There is also a later edition of this book that sells for roughly $60-$100 at this sale as well. I have a few other things on my list too, but I'm going straight for the books.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Estate Sale Sidewalk Number(s) Etiquette </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm have never lined up and gotten to an Estate Sale/Garage Sale before it actually opens. 

Could someone explain how this works? I need to be #1 or #2 in line, there is three items I *NEED* to get my hands on for a potential HUGE^huge profit! 

Thank you in advance!

Edit 1: Left my house, 45 min drive, currently sitting in front of the house with number 18. Not the best IMO, but I'm here 2.5hours early. 


Edit 2: https://imgur.com/gallery/oZyWX ...the haul! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bankruptcy   Energy Law.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm striking out everywhere I look! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The next 90 students at each law school...

Or

The next 90 students overall state wide...

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (hahahah...*from the grave*) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In some way shape or form...we all know it's coming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PM me I can send some things your way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you looking for exactly? I have some power points and notes from when I took the class.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a riot. The *mother fu#king definition* of "riot." 

Look it up in Black's Law, my name is right under Res Ispa Loquitur. (*Insert sarcasm*)

I assumed you were asking for a current exam. 

Lol, just google the rule or look at the comments in the ABA rule book. Have you read the cases associated with the comments? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are federal loans from graduate school. I'm in the process of paying off/using some home equity to lower them. You can't just call and negotiate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I meant contract...my phone auto corrected my message. 

Ok, so your under no obligation to provide them with any commission. I think the finders fee is reasonable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My interests range from 7.65% to 5.59%, respectfully.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have any existing contracts with this company? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 12:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? You created a throwaway to seek help for an "*upcoming test*..."

I'm not going to sit here and argue with, what a 1-2L, who is lazy and can't search for shit on their own; it's super easy too by the way. 

Your request was vague and suspect from the beginning. Now, even with more information surrounding your test, I'm still not going to help you. 

Good luck in law school, your going to need it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could offer both services, really. 

You could offer face to face interactions, but also have some "buy-it-now" style documents on your website; similar to Legal Zoom/Rocket Lawyer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure, I wonder what year it's from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's called *cheating*...you have a *final* and are asking for help. I'm 99.9% sure it's against your school's honor code.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember...run! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh it's complete fraud. 

But, it's also a Federal crime because their industry is regulated by the FTC. 

They would be diving head first into an endless shit storm if they did so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Plain and simple, yes, but they are risking a substantial amount if they do so; they would be violating both Federal and State law. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't want to scare you more but it's a small reality that if it goes beyond what your approved for the underwriter could toss the deal. 

If you have been approved for more then what your paying you could roll closing costs into your loan amount, you'd being paying interest on them, but they wouldn't be out of pocket. You would pay them off if you throw down that 20% within the first year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, here is where the Reddit'ers jump in to save me. I live in Michigan which is *heavily* populated with "American" cars as opposed to "Foreign" cars; I'm sure you can make an argument they all are foreign now days, beside the point. 

I've read on here many VW and Toyota vehicles are great. I guess the only thing I'd have to add is the cost of maintenance. For example, where I live there is 10:1 shops for American vs. Foreign; which means it's much cheaper to work on American cars rather than Foreign. But, many places (California and Florida) are very much the opposite. 

That's just something to consider.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know a lot about a lot, and I'm sure if I don't I will tell you and some other awesome Reddit'er will chime in and help. Haha fire away! 

But, issue one is Craigslist...you *MUST* be super skeptical of CL.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is complicated. It's aimed to be complicated, the Govt. doesn't want everyone to take advantage of it because they would lose billions in interest. 

Regardless, read as much as you can and then take your questions either back on her or call the Fed. on that site. 

PM me if you'd like as well. I'm trying to find a municipality position so I can take advantage of it; I have $184,000 of student loan debt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [John Oliver: Retirment](https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=gvZSpET11ZY)

There is some great questions in here about what to ask your advisor. 

Key: Are they a Fiduciary? 

If not...run! They don't have any duty owed to you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to go to a Lawyer...yesterday. 

Find a local lawyer that will give you a FREE CONSULTATION!

PM if you need help finding one I will help you, bud. 

Good luck, regardless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, well technically you can enter into a legal contract on your own behalf. The contract would be *voidable*, but not void itself. 

Regardless, rough circumstances, good job being smart and mature about everything...seriously. 


Let's start with the bank account. If your parents are on it your going to need their permission to close it, take their names off, or do anything significant with it. 

To play into your cash option, which isn't bad, you could slowly start taking money out and saving it as cash. BUT, your going to want to really safeguard that cash. You should get a waterproof/fire resistant lockbox and store the cash in there. 

You could also check with the bank and ask if they could set you up with a bank savings account without a co-signer. 
Usually the co-signers are on checking accounts for security purposes if the primary individual bounces/overdrafts on the checking account. You obviously can't do that with a savings account. 

I think those would be your best options moving forward.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With that I would also question brand. 

For example, Chevrolet has a 10yr/100,000 mi powertrain warranty that is transferable; even if you buy it used with no warranty and "as is where is" from the Seller, it's a Manufacturers warranty. 

So, 2005 is out of warranty and 2015 is within warranty still. 

It really depends on many variables.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a slippery slope. 

You could take it, use it, and then they could bad mouth you behind your back or say you couldn't perform at that level. Two to three months isn't even 90 days which is the usual let go for under performing period. 

If your considering taking it I would suggest staying with the company for at least 6months if not 1 year. This will allow you to establish your position and show that you gained true experience; 2-3 months isn't even enough time to really engulf yourself with what your doing. 

Your boss is an asshat. Plain and simple. Just keep it to yourself and know their true character. Take the salary bump and perks that come along with it and use the opportunity to your advantage to take that next rung in life when it comes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Biggest factor: What are EACH loans interest rate? 


Regardless if you refi/consolidate, your going to want the best rate differential you can get, that's how you save money with these things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have another account in the same bank you were a borrower of they can do some called "set off," which basically allows them to whip out their loss by removing the money owed to them from your account which has sufficient funds. 

(They go this all the time). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, I can point you to you school's honor code, respectfully. 

Your request answers your question...no one on here will help you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, incorrect. 

*Very basic overview*: You need to qualify and then make 120 qualifying payments for 10 years. To qualify you must work for a govt. full time or a non-profit. 

 (12 payments per year for 10 years)

It's only for amounts you currently have outstanding. But the clock will start running as soon as the fund are dispersed to you. Regardless you more than likely (99.99%) qualify now and haven't even taken advantage of it. I read a study that more than 83% of outstanding FEDERAL student loan holders qualify and they are not taking advantage of the PSLF program. 

I would look into it ASAP for the loans you have out now. Go check out the [PSLF WEBSITE](https://studentaid.ed.gov/sa/repay-loans/forgiveness-cancellation/public-service). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vintage Texas Rangers Jersey Patch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weather channel didn't have anything? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
