<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject366</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 04:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did an AMA 3 years ago.  I really enjoyed it and would do another one, but I think that doing and AMA without being famous is a bit much.  I promise though, if someone actually gets a show about me made, I'll do another AMA.  https://www.reddit.com/r/IAmA/comments/1cz82v/ama_vibratorscom_founderpresident_tom_nardone/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 18:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks.  I was a little heartbroken when it didn't take off as well.  It was a really fun experience though, so I look at the whole experience as a "life well lived" type of thing.  It was fun to be flown to LA and to meet with a bunch of VP's from all of the networks.  I don't think many people get to experience that, and I'm thankful that I did.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 18:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a huge industry, there are only a few dozen companies and everyone is really, really nice.  Neal and I have been friends for a long time.  My kids think he is one of the funniest humans on the planet.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 18:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my travels I have met some people from Playboy.  I asked the same question at the time we were pitching and the production company answered by saying that channels like Playboy spend almost nothing on a show, that's why they stink so badly.  Since my company is in the Detroit area and I'm not a TV producer, director, or anything like that, we needed some budget to get it done.  Good question though.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 14:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!  Neal from Frisky Business is a good friend of mine.  He is as nice in person as he is on the show.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 14:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We did pitch FX.  They were very entertained by the pitch.  They were also really, really nice.  They just didn't think they could prosper from including our show on their channel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 14:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have an Amazon store as well, but for many of the products we sell, it is tough to compete with companies that are using fake reviews on the site.  Also, Amazon is a tough place to sell inexpensive items.  Have you ever noticed that some products that cost $2.99 in a store are $5.99 on Amazon?  That's because Amazon takes a large minimum fee.  Products on Bachelorette.com (our site) are often way less than they are on Amazon.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 14:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We offer a few advantages over shopping on Amazon.  The main reason is that we are experts in the items that we sell.  The adult products business for example is flooded with over 17,000 different toys.  Our team curates that industry and offers only the 500 best toys on Vibrators.com.  On a site like Bachelorette.com, the products are less expensive than Amazon and it is easier to shop when planning a bachelorette party.  Finally, since we handle all of the order processing and fulfillment ourselves, subject366 is more private than other adult retailers that use third-party fulfillment companies.  We aren't perfect, and we don't sell everything, but we are a really good choice for certain things.  I hope that helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 14:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe the show wasn't 100% real, because I'm not really that cool.  Thanks though!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 06:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Done twice in the UK.  But Brits are more liberal sexually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 06:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure!  Tom at subject366 dot com. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 06:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Troy, Michigan!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 06:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect except for the fact that we are competitors in our core business of selling stuff online.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 06:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup.  It is 100% real.  subject366 is a strange and wonderful place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 05:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my line of work that actually makes it more typical.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 05:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Netflix shows old episodes of a British show called Frisky Business.  Frisky Business actually is about my friend's company.  It ran two seasons on Lifetime in the UK and you can see episodes on Netflix.  It is quite funny and I'm in a couple of episodes.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 05:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks.  I didn't make the video though, I'm actually Tom.  This has suddenly gotten awkward because your comment has made me love you too.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 05:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess they weren't pitched because everyone thought that the show was sorta hard to explain to people and get them to find it on Netflix, whereas a regular network you would capture viewers hanging on from prior shows.  Also, at the time (2 years ago) Netflix wasn't spending money on non-celebrity projects.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 05:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks.  The lesson we learned is that the success of a show is more related to how many advertisers will buy space, not how many people will watch the show.  I appreciate the compliment though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 05:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe the team inquired with them and they didn't want to see the pitch, I believe they weren't looking for any reality programming.  But we pitched a whole bunch of networks, essentially anyone who was doing anything related to the show.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 04:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was involved in a pilot for a show about a company that sold sex toys and novelty items and all of its employees.  The employees were regular folks and the show followed their exploits selling truly strange products like vibrators, bachelorette party supplies, and anal bleaching creams while raising families and doing volunteer work.  We pitched it to 7 different networks and they all laughed and laughed during the pilot, but within a couple weeks we were turned down by everyone.  They all said the exact same thing, there was no way that advertisers would buy spots on a show about sex toys.  That's the day I learned that it doesn't matter if people enjoy a show, it only matters if advertisers will buy commercial time on the show.  I'll never forget that lesson.
I uploaded it to YouTube.  Watch it while you can: https://youtu.be/rUY6a2CQ13E </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 04:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read the book "How to win friends and influence people."  It's a great book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 03:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a Kickstarter running right now.  1/2 way in and Backerclub has produced $850 worth of pledges and I just met my goal.  So far it was worth it, but not a wild success.  I might also add that BackerClub.co said before the start of it all, that their average raise is about $1,400, so by the time I am done I will probably end up right about average.

Everything else I have done has been poor.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
