<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2519</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 06:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Planes do piss me off a lot but yeah AA guns are actually pretty effective already if you get a clear line of sight quite easy to finish one off  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grandparents are super religious parents pretend they are - all of us kids hate it and only I am a proper atheist. Pretty sure my two Bros and sis don't believe but they don't really think about it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I very much disagree with this. I have never had a mental health problem in my life. I have had a good life with good friends and I've have rationalised my own mortality and want to do something important with my life. It's not that I ignore my emotions of loneliness, sadness, isolation etc but for me it doesn't hamper me at all - and I realise I'm very lucky. I still care about people going through mental illness like some of my friends are-is it hard to get your head round ? Yes it is but everyone is trying and hoping people can overcome to help them survive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you have to kill yourself if you fail school? It's shitty I get it. My best friend failed school, joined the army got a bunch of qualifications and now has a good life. Not for everyone but your life doesn't end with school </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are any of us here? We are all animals at the end of the day-animals whose brains developed to believe we are special, that we are somebody, when in fact all of us are nobody. You don't need to add anything to anyone's life - you have a right to live  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exams are not the end of the world so just take a step back and have a little perspective. Really not worth killing yourself over even if it's just part of the reason  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like cock  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did u bend the screen?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg reading his answers hurts my soul  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha so you dodge all my questions so obvious that your probably from the countryside. Went travelling after uni and I currently live in Southampton I moved away two years ago but go back to visit fairly often. Anymore stupid criticism you'd like to throw my way...? Or more scary stories about nonstop acid throwing knife wielding teens? You sound like the scared one tbh.

And you can't be your own man if you have friends and family...?how does that work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 11:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in Hounslow which is mostly immigrants and immigrant descendants including me. People from here have joined ISIS and yeah there have been a lot of stabbings in my area through the years. Lived here for 21 years, went to school here and had a job here, and yeah generally found my generation are pretty agnostic. Went to a religious school were nearly everyone didn't believe in anything and pretty much is the same with our parents. Maybe because it's multicultural the young are just sick of religion, and most people who are religious don't let it define their entire personality. So yeah London is pretty tolerant in general, you can see how it's different through the way it votes in general and in the EU referendum. By the sounds of it your only been here once and just believe the stereotypes about 'stabbing' happening every minute in every part of London and acid attacks. (Funny I actually saw a daily mail headline talking about kids using acid instead of knives now-you probably just read that- I doubt you live here) 

Where I live is pretty bad for crime and poverty but it's still not like that - this real enough for you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 06:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty much one of the most tolerant places - and the best part is nearly everyone is agnostic and the press is currently destroying a leading politician who keeps avoiding the question if gay sex is a sin-can be pretty great here sometimes but hope it all goes okay with you in the US  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man those damn mormons -come back to London !  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fifa confirmed but not PES? Feel it would be easier to port </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a great story!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 22:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I much prefer running on a treadmill. Doesn't matter what time of day it is if the gym is open, the gradient doesn't fluctuate unless you want it too, you can measure your speed better, don't have to carry a bag, don't have to wrap up warm, or avoid cars, or pedestrians. Yeah it can be boring but running outside is good every once in a while for the fresh air and maybe scenery but I feel the toll it takes on your body (well mine anyway) is a lot worse). The road is pretty uneven where I live so it's not too fun   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I want talking about you op just Lord or whatever he's called  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How delusional and out of touch can you be!? King was fighting people like Trump and his dad  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She probably just thought you were off your face  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't bad trust me you're overthinking it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'See isn't he the best!'  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 07:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do know if you tell the college about your mom they will be more lenient with your grade right? I forgot what it's called exactly but it exists  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 07:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just tell her you don't want to hear it - she should probably know you don't like it. I've been with my gf who's never had a bf before for 4 years... I've never talked about having sex with my old girlfriend I just know not to  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 07:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you need therapy for a gaming addiction? If you genuinely feel everything like you've said about your girlfriend but still play Xbox over paying her attention you might be addicted.

I love video games have all the consoles and buy tonnes of games . I play a lot but I would never let it get in the way of my relationship. If I had to I'd give it up to maintain my relationship  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg you guys are so crazy and funny should all be comedians! I love this type of Reddit humour!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most lines on the map are pretty modern inventions as many new countries have been formed in the last 100 years - unless you guys did the history of Korea in 9th grade I doubt anyone wouldn't have assumed it wasn't a part of China at some point? The president should definitely know it wasn't though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't it used to be called Goguryeo? And china tried to conquer it many times but failed for the most part or when they did they couldn't maintain control  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the worst part is he didn't even try and look for a job in that time - leave him  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they felt quite embarrassed when someone from the cast of TFA was calling them out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When ever I hear cis the only thing I think of is the Confederacy of Independent Systems   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey thanks for watching and yeah that is a shame I do understand the audience want a certain type of thing but I think BF1 showed you can do something different and people will like it and yeah would love a cutscene or an on combat level in London. And we disagree on supply drops but that's fine I just hate that style of micro transactions I feel the weapons skins in battle packs on battlefield are better.

And yeah thanks for you critique. My only excuse is that the audio is actually from my radio show at my uni so it is infact broadcast live, done in one take, and I cut out that segment for my YouTube. While I have my notes reading from a script would be pretty boring for a live radio broadcast. I'm planning to make other videos that are scripted though!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Made a video on how WWII should differentiate itself from other COD's and World War shooters by making a mature campaign in lesser known battles and theatres of war </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 07:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Gaming Bible (offshoot of the Lad Bible) used a clip from by Youtube Channel, didn't credit me and claim they don't have to-who is in the right? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted a clip of me hunting on Horizon Zero Dawn. I posted to Reddit and YouTube and numerous gaming sites asked me if they could use it and they would credit me-Of course I let them. Now I received a message from a sub today telling me it was in the Gaming Bible without my knowledge or credit. Obviously angry I asked them why. Their response: 

''Because the clip is purely gameplay, and hasn't been edited, everything in it belongs to the developers and artists who created the game and in turn so does the clip. We always make sure we ask permission for clips that people have edited or narrated, but in certain cases it's not necessary''

The did say they'd put my name in now but the video has already got 600k views, 369 shares, thousands of likes and comments, which obviously generates them revenue. My clip was pretty skilful so a standard clip of Horizon would not have generated this much attention-who is in the right? It's standard practice to credit someone right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Battlefield does shotguns pretty well have a decent range and still hit people when they are at medium range even if it doesn't do a lot of damage  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are 18!! Dump him now! Sounds like a cunt trust me most guys are not like this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey at home I was very popular had a ton of friends. When I got to uni I just didn't click with anybody-I was from London and they were from other parts of the UK was had to connect in a lot of ways. I am in third year and have about 2 good mates-sometimes situation like this are just out of your control  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Medicine isn't a religion you don't just believe or not believe in it. It's factually proven to help treat illnesses physical or mental. So fuck his opinion just take them if you feel like you need it-he sounds likes a complete weirdo tbh  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think when you call your own girlfriend a whore it's time to end it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about no religion at all to make it fair? I was a catholic now atheist but if I was you I'd feel absolutely stupid wearing that stuff on my wedding day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sports games  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't seem off to me. Drack is 1,400 years old he rarely minces words. Obviously he is happy you saved his 3/4 of his men over one Salarian pathfinder especially since the Initiative fucked over the Krogan  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tim Farron is annoying - yay he supports marajuana legalisation, oh he is against abortion and gay marriage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah man anticipating going to Skellige was so great and when I got there it was amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha yeah I think religion is stupid its my opinion doesn't mean I hate all Christians  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 07:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So because I choose not to base my life around stories from 2000 years ago that have little factual evidence of actually happening I am hateful and non-understanding? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 03:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you part of the 'Christians are the most oppressed group in the West' club ? Newsflash Christians still control most of the powerful countries in the world  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 03:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg you are the exact type of person the Simpsons writers would love to offend. 'You can't choose your beliefs' seriously!? I was brainwashed as a catholic in my childhood realised it was bullshit and choose not to believe any of it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 02:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're both young so it probably won't get better. Divorce him your only 26 enjoy life with someone who wants similar things to you and makes you happy not this lazy slob.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Made a video on what the new Call of Duty should do to differentiate itself from other games in WW2-would like to discuss if anyone would care to watch! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he just used the wrong words-by Brazilian I assume he just used the wrong word and just thought he could substitute Brazilian for brown or black  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know you have to end it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's make everything wacky! That's what people want ! Yes please go back to 4's story telling each dogs 2 and GTA V are so annoying because the steroids feel so inconsequential  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 07:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He said she's mixed race and Brazilian  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 07:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cmon it was pretty harmless the best jokes are usually the ones that offend people  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 07:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't consider MD as a particularly safe drug especially when teens (especially stories in the U.K.) have died from heart attacks after a single use. Yeah most people don't get it but I understand why she doesn't like it.

As for weed I get it it's not bad but it fucking stinks so maybe it's just unattractive ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 07:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You dad sounds like psychotic and you seem to have 'daddy issues'. You're relationship seems weird if he cares so much about who you date and you care that he approves? Really who gives a fuck you and him both need to grow up  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not actually funny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did you get married so quick and so young?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol I can't fault the kid  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 16:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's funny that Christians have always used Easter as justification for slaughtering Jews. I guess they should not have wanted Barabas... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 15:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess in history religion is very right wing for the most part so that's why a lot of right wingers are religious and so are their parties (can you imagine May saying she was an atheist?). I don't think David Cameron was actually religious but he had to pretend he was.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 21:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the first order are way more extreme than the empire so that could be a factor ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 17:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean as a standalone mode that you select from the menu  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would you guys like to see a 1v1 mode for lightsaber wielding heroes in BF2? Similar to For Honor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 17:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A standalone mode searched from the menu. Like in For Honor 1v1 it could be first to three-feel they could do something similar for BF2 would be a nice change of pace  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> -only 21
-no family 
-one child already 

I know I'll also have lots of unprotected sex and hope that I don't get pregnant again. And if I do I'll pressure the guy into being a dad for my son.

Maybe you should be more careful. Even if you have a decent job I don't know how your gunna easily support three people by yourself  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Spoiler for U.K. HoC) Will Season 5 play out like the UK show in the 'terror' aspect? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the 1970's to the late 1990's the IRA constantly targeted Britain with bombs to try and get the Northern Ireland to be part of the Republic (although attacks on the U.K. Were on and off since 1867). Now in the U.K. HoC's Francis uses this to rid himself of opponents and blames it on the IRA. He kills people like Stamper and the Lucas Goodwin character with bombs and guns and then blames it on the IRA despite it being down by men loyal to him. Do you think Frank and Clare will now use he climate of fear, 'or terror', they have created to take down opponents and blame it on ICO? They could kill Remy and Jackie (especially because they have ties to Underwood they could sell it) and perhaps Tom. What do people think? This seems pretty likely to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 06:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> London was way better than Paris - cmon multiple different animation sets for kids playing soccer! Also it felt more alive - cool NPC conversations, bands playing music, jukeboxes, protests, people working in factories, carriages, people in pubs - Unity just has people walking around in massive crowds doing nothing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 04:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's great it basically follows a lot of the same story line as AC4 (Charles Vane, Nassau etc) but has some great characters and really good sets. If you like pirates at all or history it's really a must watch  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll make up my own mind thanks , a lot of shows final seasons are like that, reflecting on the events of all the show before the inevitable conclusion  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Season 3 is worth it to make season 4 better  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't you try talking in dms for abit then ask later? No rush  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mum would be pissed but more so wth my sister-something about girls and tattoos is worse for older people I guess  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Started watching Black Sails and now I have to start AC4 again... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean how can I not! The show has a lot of the same characters and locations!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 05:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just saying, if you're not out as bi and you're in a Heterosexual relationship is it really a big deal? Is it worth the risk of this relationship ending? If it is then I'd say you should definitely come out if it's how you want people to see you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She sounds awful in regard to your son. I know a couple of kids who had parents like this and they actually did a lot of worse shit because their parents were so strict. A lot of the time it has the opposite affect. Your son must be extremely embarrassed is there anyway to get through to her? What are her parents like? 

Also how do you have an amazing relationship outside of this? If this was me I'd absolutely hate my wife for what she is doing to our son, and it obviously affects his relationship with you both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because your bi and have a gf does it even really matter ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Intriguing but highly disturbing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can understand why he might be upset (I know my mum would hate my sister to have any kind of tattoos) but his reaction is abit extreme  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think you rushed things? I have a girlfriend of nearly 5 years, I am abit younger than you but moving in that soon and out of state seems fast  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not Jared Harris !? Camooon  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 08:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This made me lol it's a fucking video game it means nothing. Tell her to stop letting a game dictate her happiness and relationships it's fucking stupid - if you were married she divorce you for this? Ridiculous  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 08:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omgggg he said this to you at a party while off his face!? That is absolutely nothing I don't even know why the hell you'd bring it up after 3 years when you don't even talk to her!! Seriously it's nothing and you'll just look like a weirdo for saying anything. I don't know why you'd think about saying anything especially now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 08:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Soviet Union was absolutely horrible in its own way. Ethnic cleansing, anti-semticism, purges, secret police. It is like Nazi Germany in many ways so it's kinds of weird he fetishsizes it as it really does have 'bad connotations'. Does being exiled to Siberia because you're a Jew not sound bad? Or you and your family all working yourself to death in a gulag because you were deemed counter-revolutionaries by the KGB? Then again I'm guessing he doesn't know this (I hope) and he is just fetishising a stereotype - maybe sit down and explain to him why it makes you uncomfortable to role-play as a group responsible for senseless mass killing ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 08:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are very over-sensitive. He probably doesn't even realise he's changing his tone. A lot of the time my gf thinks I'm talking down to her ( or mansplaining) when I'm explaining something when I have no idea I'm doing it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 07:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It kind of sounds like you're schizophrenic - have you been diagnosed with anything? It isn't normal to think the world and everyone in it is out to get you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 04:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe see if he needs to get checked out by a doctor? You ranting about human rights shouldn't make you bf of 2 years sweat nervously lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 04:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe they didn't produce enough that was compatible with shells since they were on the offensive for most of the war?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes that what I was saying. But replace trump with Underwood and keep the story against him similar I feel no one would care. HoC universe is more like pre Bush jr sort of world  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is today's political climate-do you think people would actually care about Hammerschmidt's article on Frank? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm just thinking about the last year in US politics and fake news. If this story came out today about the current president I could definitely see it being swept under the rug as fake news as a lot of the other stories that have came out are worse than what Hammerschmidt wrote about Frank. Anyone else think if Frank was the republican (I know he's not but something about the Republican Party that would help him get away with it) president in today's office he could just label the story 'fake news' and get away with it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 08:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're gunna live together and he'll just leech off you for the rest of your lives?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 08:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> -overweight 
-no job
-wants to move to Korea

... you know what to do... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 08:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a dumbass have you honestly not even seen her since 2015!? And only text!?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 08:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We were on a break!!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 08:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is fairly common in a lot of relationships. I always notice people getting slot fatter as a results of the honeymoon faze. And the end of the day you are letting his lifestyle rub off on you (it's not as though you don't enjoy it) so you just have to change your mindset </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 08:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg the image of you grabbing another guys muscles while your girlfriend complements them... he must have felt so good about himself. I tell her you don't like it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 08:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regardless if they intend to do it or not, just saying it in a serious way is enough to indicate they are not mentally healthy. I can't even imagine ever saying that to my gf and meaning it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 08:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would never settle for this - can't stand people with no drive and/or ambition. Leave him the relationship sound shitty  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You probably were super annoying about something so trivial so he may have snapped because of this. If my gf did that to me I wouldn't care personally it's probably nothing just don't take it so seriously  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Erm you're an adult why are you constantly hanging out with them? Go out on your own and there is no problem  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol what is this shit!? It's still her and you know it is what is the problem ? If you don't like the dress up don't have sex with her while wearing it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 07:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I don't think military was the greatest place to go if you hated high school. English military where I am is so bad for taking the piss out of people and basically having no filter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 07:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha - maybe a lot  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 07:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry mate you bi at least. No shame in it just own it-you literally asked a man for a blowjob and enjoyed it -being drunk isn't really an excuse. It's who you are so accept it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 05:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously don't worry about it - most athletes give up everything. Wayne Rooney (England/Man United Soccer player) went pro at 16 for a big club full time. Most have to give up generic fun teen years but it's worth it in the end - I wish I had done it. My teens were fun but people still do all that shit when you're older anyway  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 05:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol why is this such a big deal? In England most people start drinking at 14/15 (nearly everyone). Yeah it's fun but most people know when to stop and control themselves. I'm sure you would too. You are your own person if you want to have a drink with friends at a bar do it-who cares if you gf doesn't like it? She needs to get over it every once and a while it's harmless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 05:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Focus on your dream-there is always time for girls later you are soo young. I have a ton of friends who went to all these parties and never got girls and now we are in our 20's and most still don't. So if you talented stick to basketball and try and make it. If you become a pro plenty of girls for you, if you don't you have a lot of time to chat/Snapchat whatever. If I could go back I would have focused on soccer and tried to go pro but I decided on social life instead. You'll regret it if you do this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 02:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've also never be woken up with someone who wasn't my girlfriend in my bed feeling me up...  pretty sure I'd be more alarmed then confused  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 02:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So she was drunk enough so she couldn't assess the situation but kept telling him to stop touching her and moving his hands away ... while he remained in the bed. I don't think being drunk absolves you of all guilt. He is in the wrong but they both hoped into bed together  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know he was very creepy but you didnt exactly kick him out after he groped you. You should stop being friends with him and be really grateful you bf is probably forgiving  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did you let him get in and stay in a bed with you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like what if you went out with a Hindu and it was serious but their family won't except you because you not a Hindu/Indian-no point complicating it and most western people are non-religious or not really practicing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck religious people, date someone who has similar beliefs as you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 12:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just listen to the youtuber Boggie to see how being overweight causes so many health problems  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 06:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why the fuck would he unenroll his son!? He wants to play football fucking let him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 06:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't keep your kid away from a potential serial killer you are a horrible parent. Never let you kid see him again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 03:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honesty I'd be pissed too if my gf suddenly told me she had done cocaine. People make weed an issue when it's not but Coke is a different story way more likely to affect your life negatively. I'm not saying you will be an addict or anything but he probably thinks in his own mind everyone has to start somewhere. I'd just apologise and if you want to do it every once and a while it don't tell him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 03:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No big deal really. The front is more comfortable and presumably his mother is a lot older than you anyway. He doesn't need to ask you - sounds like your jealous of her  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 03:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No he is a massive douche kicking you out. My gf loves food and would probably get abit mad if I took a big handful of fries like you did but she definitely wouldn't take it any further than a jokey argument. Him kicking you it and all that stuff is so uncalled for and he just seems like a dick. Reading this sub at times I don't know what the fuck is wrong with some of these boys, constantly treat women like shit for no apparent reason. Id leave him but whatever you want to do  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 03:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should you have called this other guy while your partner was about ? No. Does it mean you deserve a beating? Absolutely not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
