<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3359</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it is, his verse is godly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 01:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Danny Brown is pretty much a legend to me as well after his latest album. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 01:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Danny Brown - XXX

Lil Wayne - Tha Carter 1   2

Outkast - Stankonia

And others already mentioned


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dunkey in Paris </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't wait for the black dude to be our next president. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice cat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was wrong. Bogdan was right. Bogdan died for our sins. | Steel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> me to thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 15:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. Same goes for a lot of languages.

Pleonasme in Dutch, pleonasm in English. Sarcasme in Dutch, sarcasm in English.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 14:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/ThreadKillers lmao

Thanks for the list man! I've heard a few of the albums you mentioned but there's a lot of stuff there which I haven't even heard of. Gonna dedicate my sunday to listening to music :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the best albums from the 2000s? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 05:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I agree, even the young hip hop fans (like myself tbh, I'm only 16 lol) should listen to classics and essential albums. But I think it's a good thing to do these survivor things and switch between classic and modern hip hop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah you're right, probs buying the tickets today or sometime this week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ayy fam just go, none of my friends listen to hip hop so I'm probs just going with my bro but we could meet up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh in may? I should be fine then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude I hope tickets are still available tomorrow otherwise I'm fucked, can't buy them atm so that would suck so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He definitely did this when I checked his stream a couple of months ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 21:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That couch has gone through so much at this point lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 20:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg why is Aleks wearing a Tana Mongeau shirt hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 04:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 02:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd give Kano - Made In The Manor a listen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 00:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel the exact same way. It's way above my expectations and honestly not at all what I expected from the album. Definitely fits the album title. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 00:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah the singing doesn't sound bad at all, glad he's able to pull off both rapping and singing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 00:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To those of you who aren't able to listen to the album yet, you should be able to in around 30 minutes. (Midnight UK time)

Edit: Currently listening to the album and actually surprised to hear Stormzy sing in a few tracks, not bad at all.Definitely enjoying it so far and I'm about halfway through. Really glad he didn't just turn out to be a one-hit wonder.

Edit 2: So I've finished the album. Honestly way above my expectations and not what I expected at all. I recommend each and every single one of you to listen to the full thing to soak it all in. There wasn't any track that I really disliked, in my opinion they were all great. The title of the album also definitely fits it well. My personal favorites are Blinded By Your Grace Pt. 2, Return of the Rucksack, Bad Boys, Don't Cry For Me, Lay Me Bare and of course Shut Up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 00:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An EP, not an album but yeah. Ima have a listen to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [FRESH ALBUM] Stormzy - Gang Signs   Prayer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 00:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 13:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude ikr? I pretty much listen to Death Grips and Clipping. daily because of Fantano and have listened to loads of albums by smaller artists which I've added to my playlists.If it wasn't for him, I'd still be listening to mainstream shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 22:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't personally listened to the full album yet, but I'm enjoying it so far. Glad Fantano reviews things like this which not many people would find otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jonwayne - Rap Album Two ALBUM REVIEW | The Needle Drop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 21:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EnVy CS:GO - Short Q A with ScreaM </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 14:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 13:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When he turns eight, he'll start speaking in a British accent like Dex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CS:GO - Glitch | Clicky Crisp </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 23:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 16:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly, that's the only reason I found out about him lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 09:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Round literally lasting 15 minutes long, 2 players waiting for the other one to finally give up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 17:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yo this is awesome my dude, I've been working on my own playlist for the past two weeks and I'm already up to nearly 700 songs right now haha. I'm probably gonna scan through your playlist to see if I see anything interesting, thanks for sharing! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 13:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadokist has the best wordplay of any caster imo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 21:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly and that's what's so surprising to me! Their fanbase has been loyal since the start and there's no sign of the views going down whatsoever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah honestly, the subscriber amount seems pretty small compared to a lot of channels but the community surrounding it is in my opinion one of the greatest and most active ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah look at the OP, he was talking about Metuz in the first place lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 19:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbh Sly get's quite a lot of viewers on Twitch so it's not like he's not making a good living anymore or anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 23:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you forget about Uzzziii? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First Norman Jayden and now her, cmon Aleks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 13:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbf they did have to play against astralis in the quarters even though they're favorites to win the whole thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 15:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no bamboozles pls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 07:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hadn't seen this before so thank you very much for posting it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 15:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly I don't even care that it's a repost. This clip always makes me laugh so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't usually watch Dazed but it really surprised me how hard he tries as an IGL in pugs. This video really shows that. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 13:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 18:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FACEIT Season 2 LAN Finals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 15:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> give gif thx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 14:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These always crack me up lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hatris (dunkview) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 15:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 17:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your English is fine dw. But I thought you'd get skulls or something at the end of matches, but I get I'm wrong.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not getting any rewards? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 17:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got the game like 2 days ago and have 3 hours on it, I just got 1st place in a solo game but I don't get any rewards? I placed 10th and 39th before and didn't anything either. Do I have to have a rank before getting any? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not getting any rewards at the end of matches? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 17:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 04:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually do the exact same as the guy above and no, sounds in real life are just normal lol. But when wearing headphones I always wear them reversed because it does not sound normal to me if you put them on correctly since I got used to wearing them backwards for 3 years. I know it sounds weird as fuck, it does to all of my friends, but I got used to it and it seems correct to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 03:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mind sharing your decklist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 21:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey James and Aleks! First of all thanks for doing this AMA. Anyways my question is: Will Asher, Anna and the rest be moving to LA with you guys? It'd kinda suck if they didn't since they only recently started getting involved in your videos.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Enthusiastic Convert </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 15:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 04:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a person from the Netherlands with a group of British friends I can definitely agree with this. At first it sounds weird, but you get used to it quickly and even I now use this kinda slang when talking to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Noticed this while looking through my card collection... Piranaha Launcher? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 03:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/JQJyJzS.jpg

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 18:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a lot for the explanation! I played a few more matches and I was gaining more than I was losing so I guess I'll be ranking up some more before it all balances out. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 17:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Astounding! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uhm... Can anyone explain my rank? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 17:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So basically I just did my placements this season. I barely played in season 2, I just did my placements there and that was about it, I got played around 2900 SR. This season I did my placements and got 3250 even though I lost 7 of my placements, drew one and won 2. This doesn't make any sense to me, I heard there was something wrong with placements but is it really that bad? I don't want to brag but I did perform well in my placements, but with 7 losses I did not expect such a high rank. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 16:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel you bro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 16:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've played the deck a bit with Finja and Wickerflame. Wickerflame is great imo, a good counter for aggro. Finja I'm not too sure about, he's either an insane tempo swing, or he just messes everything up late game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 16:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shouldn't take out a pyro, if you're going to remove things then remove aldor, acolyte or one forbidden healing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Modified Mac and Cheese - You Suck at Cooking (episode 53) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 16:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 20:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even though Reno mage won't be the greatest, I think Inkmaster will be a solid card in the deck. Even with cards like cabalist's tome or maybe even a fireball it's great value imo. Oh and flamestrike of course. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 17:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He said it'd be up in 6 hours 12 hours ago, so hopefully his review will be up soon. He's gonna have an early stream too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 11:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe add leeroy as a finisher </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 10:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 15:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last time with the Old Gods release he was playing as soon as it came out, which was around 7pm CET. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 15:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Old Gods release took about 1.5/2 hours in EU, haven't experienced TGT, GvG or Naxx myself so I can't really say how good it was compared to those releases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 15:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good call, I'll try that out if I get him after my pack opening tomorrow or friday! =) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 13:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got a list for that? I haven't played rogue like at all but would like to play some fun decks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 11:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.hearthpwn.com/decks/622600-legend-reynad-tempo-rogue - Try it out! I feel like the list will be even better with small time buccaneer, it's not the greatest deck but people don't expect it and it's quite fun imo. I personally play it without Xaril and don't really think it's needed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 07:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reynad actually played an aggro rogue a few months ago and got top 200 legend with it, I've been playing it too and it's quite good. It's pretty much just about going face and you can have some insane burst with evic, cold blood, leeroy etc. Also put in 2 stranglethorn tigers for almost always guaranteed 5 damage.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 16:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's more of a control meta in the tournament then try out Renolock, it crushes a lot of control decks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 16:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it? I'm Dutch and we don't do that lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 16:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reno Shadowpriest will be so much fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favorite legendary in the game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 22:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine is Jaraxxus, I feel like even though he's extremely powerful he's still balanced and the emotes are 10/10. Rip "JARAXXUS IS... sorry" though :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 15:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt Rafaam will be used the next few months in a meta deck, it got used in Tempo Warrior for a bit, but that's about it wasn't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 15:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can definitely play top tier Druid decks without him, he was used in Token Druid, but wasn't a must have card. I'd keep him anyway though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 13:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EREDAR LORD OF THE BURNING LEGION!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 21:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4 months of amazingly fun reno decks, I can't wait dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 20:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's because of the new quests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 20:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and don't forget the guy who ate a dick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 18:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get fucked bogdan you absolute fucking smeghead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 11:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 07:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? El Manana is definitely one of my favorites on the album. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 21:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only watched this film a couple weeks ago, but damn it's good. Even made me tear up a little near the ending. Love Will Hunting as a character and how he develops throughout the movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 21:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/SeanGares </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where does it even go? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 20:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I feel like this is an appropriate time to post this video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 05:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm sick at home and feel terrible, do your worst and make me laugh (or cry myself to sleep) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 11:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watsky - Tiny Glowing Screens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 08:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ozzy Man Commentates iPhone7 Ads </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 14:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 01:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YOUTHFUL STEWART 2000 AT IT AGAIN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 01:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was fucking disgusting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 19:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my favorites: [Incorporated 2](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=o30lcEr49cY) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 04:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure it's completely random. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 18:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah shit I got that wrong, I'm not a native speaker either so yeah. Thanks for correcting me, I'll be sure to get it right in the future, I won't edit it just for the meme. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 06:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to be a dick but can you proof it was you? 

Edit: When you don't know how to grammar, I'll keep it like this for the meme I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 02:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing is, you can't do anything about cards like Yogg, Tuskarr or Barnes, they can just win you games on the spot and there's not really a way to play around them. Sure, there are cards like Ragnaros which are random but that's not the same.

Reynad made [this](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bdkGNrkJsII) video some time ago talking about good and bad RNG, because not all RNG is bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 20:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has also said on stream that he will most likely be banning Tuskarr Totemic from Tempo Storm hosted tournament, which imo is a great move since Yogg, Barnes are Tuskarr are way too random and could just win you the game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yogg Is Skill (Reynad Stream Highlight) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 19:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 06:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [BELUL](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p6-Psafv_Kg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 06:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then I've got no clue, the store was having trouble earlier today so maybe just try again tomorrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 06:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure you need the money on battle.net and not the google play wallet, I'm sure completely sure though since I deleted HS from my phone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 04:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First shot definitely hit, second one looks like it went just to the left of his head if you watch it at 0.25x speed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
