<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3183</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 08:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> true that. forget normal senseful approach </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 07:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks for the heads upon the 80d, just noticed it's around ~900.  
  
Then again 800 is pushing it so that's a dangerous game lol. But I'll keep an eye out.  
  
Lol, the FF boat? aka the pro photographer boat? I didn't know it was a thing actually.  
   
I'm trying to talk my cousin into giving me his 5d Mark II, he doesn't use it. One of those, I want to be a photographer! Shot a few times and that was it. I'm over here on the poverty rebel like...umm, please? 
   
I actually shoot on film with an older canon sometimes for fun. I think I'd...I know I'd appreciate a full frame sensor. The biggest deterrent for the 6d is mostly quality of life with video when it comes to the flip out screen. 
   
But it's low light would dope af. Most of the 6d's I saw weren't priced near enough to what I was looking for. But a little digging they do seem to be appropriate.  
  
Not sure if this has been a good or bad influence. lol, thanks again though, really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you were buying a used/refurb camera today what would you lean toward? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 06:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there are PTT apps that resemble the old nextel chirp!. 
  
So while it isn't a connection between a phone and a walkie talkie it turns your phone into one through the app for practical purposes.  
  
If his boss took to that it might be a compromise of sorts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kushner sold almost all of his holdings through legal advice that would create a conflict of interest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are actually. Big time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol...if it gets that high this time you better sell and recover your money.  
   
the profit here is to buy in and hold till 15-20 and partial sell. LTC is too volatile when it goes up. It always comes down. And often it's a pretty obvious big buy in and sell off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, morals, ethics, nor logic, really have  place in someone's mind when breaking the rules. At least from the perspective we're looking at it from.  
   
What may be more likely is that he though everyone cheats from the get-go and that's how you get caught. At 1764 if he had a strong rise through the tournament from the start he'd have more scrutiny. In general, winning from the start with strong performance draws attention. A couple losses then a wins between some last place participants, no one is watching those games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 03:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ahh excellent cherub example. 
   
cherubs...love searching me some cherubs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was kidding man. Takes 20 min to walk a mile. Push a car 10? Pfff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 23:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Waylan and Yutani's Final Frontiers: 
Ships for shipping, shooting, shuttling! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> based on where, are those guns? i imagine you'd want to be able to be looking where you're going to see enemy vs friend vs threat ahead of you? 
   
i could see the middle thing being a point but i think, as a rule of practicality, you'd have a harder time explaining to the 9/10 people why the cockpit is in the middle rather than the complaint from 1/10 that understands why it isn't there.  
  
and i mean from a psychological standpoint of pilots first probably being jet/astronaut pilots and being used to flying from the front. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Schwarzenegger runs out of gas on the Nicollet island bridge just north of downtown Minneapolis and then pushes his car to Mickey's Diner in downtown St. Paul about 10 miles away.

and? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Photoshop Tutorial: How to use sliders!!! Click Here! Pro's don't want you to know this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i guess house shopping is that point where you consider to stop throwing books out and start keeping them in anticipation of a library. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1880? clearly from the ghosts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol appropriately. i'd rather not have to guess where to find the booze.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 09:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, which is truly cruel. And by missing that the guy above shifts and focuses on the wrong thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 09:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're all missing the point here. Those people are uneducated. The ones that do seek education don't come back.   
  
Coal isn't their answer, they refuse to change, and refuse to leave. There are jobs in America. They just aren't there or in those fields. I'm sure Devos education plan will help secure their future as their shitty schools get shittier because they're shitty. We don't even need to teach these people college degree level shit. I just need to teach them photoshop or a coding bootcamp or AI.And get them to move. Clearly the state isn't pivoting on its own. And frankly that is their representatives fault for not forcing it in their best interest, even if they don't realize it.
    
Think it's about WV or some rust belt group that's all sorta of fucked with insane amounts of disability.
http://www.washingtonpost.com/sf/local/2017/03/30/disabled-or-just-desperate/?utm_term=.8c11d12a852e </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 08:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> jesus not all blacks live in the inner city nor are they poor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 08:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> depends what circles you run it i guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 02:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this has got to be the only mature and appropriately enforced place on reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No you can't. But you make choices like that everyday. Some people speak up about shot and some people don't. I know what I do. It's how I met my girlfriend actually.  

A guy took money out of her purse. I told him to put it back or leave cause when she sat down I'd tell her. He told me to fuck off. It escalated and I beat him up, essentially.

And please don't compare what you're talking about to animals. That's gross misrepresentation. Animals are food and if we were still hunting with Spears they'd be suffering more. Some people are well adapted to vegetarianism from their body types, blood types and what not. But generally saying we're at the top of the food chain but you need to stop! Isn't relevant. That said, should you consider it? Think about it? Arguably, yes. That said the way our society developed currently we have a system to provide food. If it wasn't that way we'd probably kill of animals to extinction to feed ourselves. Things would be a lot more fucked because we'd be competing for food. 

Enough about animals. I hear ya though.  And it's a fair point. But if you start out approaching the situation with 'oh well I'll be scared and join the common way of thinking' is no way to approach the issue

I also only eat red meat x2/month, mostly chicken when i do 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I don't know at a certain what is 'passive' turning the blind eye becomes actively choosing some fucked up shit. 
   
I've always been the kind of person to speak their mind. And I don't really stand for something if it's wrong, it's fucking wrong.
   
Then again, after they make a couple examples of people by shooting them...people aren't so keen to speak up. Not that you wouldn't have other ways to help. 
    
I also don't buy that shit that 'history shows we wouldn't.' Plenty of people choose to resist and fight back. And a whole couple nations worth of people thought it worth fighting for.  
   
I'm principled to a flaw. So I def could be that guy on the 'wrong' side of the fence if I took to some fucked up ideals. But I damn well end up killed before I lay down and let someone shit on values. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 05:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> once it hit the montage i was like...waaait. 
   
lol and this is coming off of a 2-3 hour favor shoot of this fundraising event for my mom. so i'm pretty tired, leg wise at least and it's late. 
   
not even lying here, bit proud i picked up on it that early haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fuckin cam.   
  
shit's funny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 20:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ironic username? seems like an all in premise </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I like the original quote but to a degree it almost doesn't tell people the point. That's the lightbulb came because he candle wasn't enough. 
   
#CandlesSuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> offering?  
   
lol, but you're not kidding. highly recommend it. 
    
to be fair though guys   gals   the curious:  
  
don't need to have gay sex for that (but why not?), or with another man period (so much to try!). 
   
hell or with anyone for that matter (flying solo fridays! or something...masturbation + creativity).  
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> shopify </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't be fooled. 
   
Oh I'm so confused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say something to her. And I'd watch my ass at work. I'd also firmly document everything and don't let them dick you out of that PTO. If it isn't compensated for, use it or some of it, within reason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought I was curious now I'm just full on committed to trying it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh, interesting. 
  
Now, to be fair though, most western nation kind of have things like that for certain people. In America we don't have mandatory service but we all have to sign up for 'selective service' which is the system or lists (in its most basic form) that they'd use for a draft in the event one was required. It's called selective service because a pacifist isn't forced into the military. Whether it's a religious reason or a personal one if you are agains the violence you aren't forced to do so. But the government will sometimes try to put you in a homeland civilian service that supports the war (working in a factory or something in the event of a draft). 
    
So, yes they are offered some protections but it's not so much just them or just Finland. It's a lot of Western countries that respect religion and the personal freedom of belief and expressing that belief. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well the helmet isn't going to do as much to protect your neck. unless i'm not aware of another protective piece there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah the USSR is fascinating. And, while totally dystopian, absolutely built on the backs of the people. It really puts in perspective the currency of human life too.  
   
and this is interesting about what's going on today... 
   
http://www.newyorker.com/news/news-desk/what-the-russian-protests-mean-for-putin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as the dog's loyalty to you is still strong and you can keep him in line I'll think we can overlook this.  
   
lol, it's actually pretty wild though. Scary to ~~think~~ watch democracy gone awry and the authoritarian nature of the Russian Government. (We're returning to Greatness Comrade! Uncle Putin is leading us back to our Superpower position in the world! We were first to space! We had nukes! We were feared!) 
   
When you think about it, and the book describes it a bit, that sentiment of working collectively as a country to be this 'great' superpower to then being where they are at now? It's gotta bruise not just the government and politicians but the average citizen who toiled in those factories.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really interesting. The book I recommend actually talks about things that are Samizdat, which was unofficial or dissident literature. There was another term, I think used to a degree for some official literature too. 
   
But yeah the whole thing was really interesting. And for the record everything out of the First Bureau(?) that was censored never was critical of the Soviet Government. They would never say, we only installed gas in Moscow or 3 towns or something, you know?  
   
But yeah all in all super interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well see, drain on society is some strong language there. They're also responsible for some decent contributions to freedom of speech/expression. Not saying you should be thankful or defend them. But not acknowledging that is ignorant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. Voices from Chernobyl (this is actually a documentary to clarify). She's a journalist and non fiction writer. Pretty awesome.  The book is also winner of the Nobel
  
edit: Joe Rogan has this clip where explaining his friend who asks "Oh you read it? Did you read it or was it an audiobook?" "..." "alright then so you didn't read it then. Just checking. You listened to it. Just wanted to clarify."  
   
Spent a few minutes looking for it. Didn't want to fast forward through the two or three I think it was from and 20 to turn to 60 but it's pretty funny. Probably from the De Franco or Will MacAskill episode...maybe the Neil deGrasse Tyson one. All three of those are worth listening too! 
   
Glad I could share though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not disagreeing with you. It's actually something worth thinking about. That adage that religions 200 years old are all cults? There's truth to it. At one point is it cultish and not something that should be protected? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 16:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah my GFS mom is JW. I'm not for them but freedom of religion is just that
 first JW's next who? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 09:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. The church stepped in to fill that void communism left. They jsut outlawed Jehovah Witnesses under their foreign extremists act. 
    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 09:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol right? like come on man, his answer his his answer, leave it be. 
   
It's like with le carre, people ask him shit all the time. he even once called because a friend of a friend was trying to defect while in London. They asked him to call 'his people.'  
   
I also, imo, wouldn't give as much weight to someone who didn't work during a time when electronic surveillance is at the level it is at. If we think, back then with the stories we read and year, that the gov't was doing a lot of shit...today it's probably ten fold or twenty what we can imagine they're doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 09:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna slip this in here. anyone interested in the USSR and how old vs young soviets look at the era and how they're looking at it now and, consequently, Russia today. Holy shit is this riveting, fascinating, and horrifying. and it's all told to the author who then wrote it down. It's firsthand accounts.   
   
https://www.amazon.com/dp/B018CH9ZVW/ref=dp-kindle-redirect?_encoding=UTF8 btkr=1  
   
Russia actually is currently claiming Jehovah's Witnesses enemies of the state.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Curious about the immediate building of the Berlin Wall and if there were any escape? Also are their figures for the amount of migration East to West Berlin preceding the wall's construction? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 09:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious how large of a population migration there was to prompt such a rapid building of the wall. My understanding of it was the border was closed and then the wall was constructed overnight. Did the creation of that border alarm East Germans? Even though it was overnight it strikes me as a large construction project, did people attempt to flee immediately prior to or during its building?  
   
I looked up some of the answers here in the past. They sort of mention some parts. The building escape where the border ran down the middle of the street, the rapid construction of the wall and the date it was constructed. None of it offers too much detail though. Any further reading on this would be fine too if you don't have time to source and answer. Sometimes I feel like this should just be the history book club/recommendation list. That'd make a great newsletter for this sub. Week's topic with 2 good articles and a book recommendation. 
  
  
Sorry, I have this horrible habit of phrasing questions as statements. I feel like, and in this forum it's more fitting, that posing a question on one niche topic sometimes loses sight of it within a larger context. Granted I can't expect you awesome people to write us encyclopedias (but if any of you are authors would love to read your book). 
   
Thank you very much for any response I get. It's much appreciated what happens here and absolutely love the sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 09:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wild how far back people held ideas that turned out to have some truth to them on such a large scale.  
  
Equally fascinating is the cult like thinking too. Man, human nature cray cray eh?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> soundcloud  
  
https://theartistunion.com/tracks/19400b </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 13:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i jsut saw this. but i think in general there's been a lot of really good competition in most matches. look at the NCAA men's basketball, there's some not to competitive games and some really competitive ones.  
   
Any tournament with 64 teams is going to have a few  bad teams. Multiple teams from one school would be confusing and in a way offer an advantage to that school to win it. In a way this is esports but it's also college sports. As for the sister team there's nothing stopping you from having an eSports club and fielding a sub/scrim team that participates in amateur tournaments/open division and helps you practice. Even if they're just a practice/sub squad.  
  
I think it's also important to realize the other squad was competing at a college level. And while I understand where you're coming from the nature of group/swiss or early tournaments are like there. Especially when you have such a large number of teams. A 4-1 gets eliminated and a 3-2 gets through. You can almost make the argument for any group stage. Well it's not fair! This really good team will move on and this one wont just because they were seeded based on when they won their spot or entry tournament. 
   
I hear ya though. Mostly I bet it's for confusion purposes too. Having two teams in it would be weird for viewers, friends, family...people wouldn't know who is who.  
   
It's really coming off as legitimate now and looks almost like the NCAA basketball tournament. That gives it a lot of credibility with people. And something to relate to. They know brackets and they know their school. So they know who to root for and who's 'their team'.                                                                                                                                                   
   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 09:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wikileaks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 10:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah different approach to society as a whole. Very much a we're in it together recognition of life rather than the let me get mine don't worry about anybody else mentality of America. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 08:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha it's not much more...it's absurdly more. 
   
10k's more. and if you don't have insurance you'll be in debt the rest of your life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've a heard a little bit of how it's calculated on a back end kind of perspective. I also think, appropriately so, that a lot of my experience is coming from AC. Compared to Vegas it definitely has more of a challenge to fill its hotels.  
  
IIRC the comp % per dollar spent fell somewhere around 30%. My personal experience is probably coming from around 2008-2011/2012 too, when they were getting crushed as a business and probably a bit more desperate to get people into the casinos/hotels.  \
   
AC is a different beast though compared to Vegas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha alright man. you're the one insistent on responding to me. 
   
suuuuuuuure, ya don't care! i get it. much easier to show it though, by not actually acknowledging my responses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 09:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a matter of agreement. Don't be upset when you do something stupid and someone calls you out on it. Especially when you choose to wear it on your sleeve as 'fun'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 09:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure they do. They also, usually, have a hotel to fill as well.  
  
No, a couple hundred bucks won't get you a spot. But it doesn't take much really. And the comped nights are rarely day of, but future dates they know won' be filled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 06:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What he's conveniently forgetting to add to his scenario, and this is where you know it's an actual issue worth addressing, is that he talks of 'effecting your life' and 'rewards.' 
   
If he wins 10, 20 or even 50 grand on one play, he's not playing 2500 anymore per daily play. His plays will up and up until he spends it all back of does some stupid short gamble and owes more than he's got back.  
  
I played horses for a year to earn a living. It wasn't easy, lol. But the point is if you really want to take on risk and make some serious money it'll involve some degree of work and self discipline. You manage a budget and stuff. There's an exact term for it, I forgot but it basically comes down to money management when you're actually gambling for a living. 
   
I want to tell all these guys to go play horses for a year and earn themselves a 50k net profit ytd. I'd like to see one of em do a profitable quarter, lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i think there's a difference though. gambling here isn't really gambling and it's just wasteful. like you could make some flag short calls and actually make some money, have some risk and still get a thrill. 
  
if you really want to gamble, i would go to a casino where you can win some real money. It literally is throwing money away because you don't even know what your payout will be or remotely near it. 
   
I played horses for a while. Semi professionally made a living off it. It was 'thrilling.' I'd never just put a bet down 'to have fun' with it. 
   
That's crazy. I get it, it's your life, you do you. But there's a point there and it's a valid criticism. An expected one especially if you're not just going to do that but either brag about the winnings or mope about losing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not sure if it's the arrogance or spoiledness that blows me away. 
   
i'm sure being raised feeling blowing $2500 "betting" *on a stock* is in some realm of normal and okay is also raising a perfectly well adjusted adult. 
   
lol these poor kids. or maybe not. they very well may never have to make a difficult decision in their lives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> actually not even man. you can play normal with a few hundred bucks in your pocket and end up with a comped room/stay.  
    
gambling 1250 in one night def get you a comped night hoping they can take the other 1250 before you leave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey wanted to let you know, that without any background, sure a copywriting course will help. 
   
especially without...any resume too i suppose. that said, you can definitely build a portfolio on your own. hmu if you got any questions and shit.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> holy shit that could be me. fuck.   
  
annnnnd looking down probably time to start working out again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 06:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I love art and design and all that. The calendar would make a cool product for fans. Merch can be a bit iffy as a 'revenue' stream though and, consequently, as an investment.  
   
You could play the pictures a few ways though. I thought a "Cards From the Front" idea would be cool too. And, not to give you any more work, but for a dollar, you pick one of ten cards (that are all done featuring you and the team, Indy at a general's desk, you as a communications/forward observor...sorry you know what i mean) and get a personalized social media message sent from The Great War twitter/facebook to their friend to help spread the show. or even for the person to use themselves in their social media as a background image or profile pic or something. 
   
My bad! Don't be to be pitching out of the blue. Just think there might be something there and I'm the type not to shut up. (My bad!)     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I'll find the episodes! That'll be plenty too! We love the decoration though, it looks great and sets a mood for sure.

The social media work is pretty spot on as well .

Actually, I do a bit of social media/digital media/marketing myself. And as a practitioner also a student. You're use overall is like a clinic on how to do it right. Especially with the interaction too. Great job.  
  
edit: i also thought, if you guys are considering merch, of making a calender with you, Indy, and the crew, posing in propaganda style shots for each month.  
  
or even just posters/t-shirts, etc. think it'd be 
great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They aren't on twitch, they're on Youtube and the show is 'archived' in  the sense that Youtube leaves videos up to be viewed when ever since they are uploaded rather than livestreamed, generally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey! I just started watching and shared the series with my girlfriend (she likes it too! win!). We're curious the set pieces and if any of them are historical? She noted the desk Indy sits at particularly. Where and when is it from?   
  
Please, we love history and items tell their own stories often within the bigger picture.    
   
edit: also we slightly debated whether it was styled after a trunk or actually made from a trunk? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 05:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and the team fight is a 9-5 or are they so weak that they're inconsequential? I don't know it seems an odd direction to go.  
  
Something like allowing him to control a zealot warped in for 8 or 10 seconds might be okay. Like an abathur clone functionality.  
  
people need to chill with the 'lore' stuff. Most of it being based on lore is about as good as it'll get. Thematically has a lot more creative flexibility.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 05:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think to a degree it's not a bad idea but people need to drop the whole "fitting into lore/fantasy" when repairing a hero. While it's important reality is needs to function first and foremost. 
  
I do think your idea very much comes close in both regards though and has the right mentality. I'm not sure it's exactly the fix. I think it might lead to a bit of power creep. Now we expand the pylons by one, so it's 3 total or the rifts replace a current one. And now it's borderline weirdly op or harder to use? 
   
Good thinking though. Better than anything I could come up with and very possibly the fix he needs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm super curious what kind of computers they use to calculate something like 3^3^3^3 like my computer can't do that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 09:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's got a sexy look to it on the that background  
  
 edit: just saw ur username...lol not by accident it gives that feel  
  
lol camera specs sexy too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 09:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> damn there's a hard twinge of envy there i think. 
   
that's *dope*.
     
  
all that whiskey too. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha true dat. 
   
Esp for the low light nature of weddings. I guess that's conditional too. More middle day/outdoorsy/well lit scenario you probably be alright anyway with some post. 
   
Trust me, I'm the last person to bash gear. I personally have a rebel, that's all I can afford atm, but have shot on a wide range of cameras from point and shoots to the high end Mark II/III/IV. 
   
Unless there's a real niche you're trying to hit/accomplish/, especially in todays world with Lightroom and Photoshop, gear really does not limit you. The right tool for the job very much comes down to your ability to take good shots at the end of the day. 
  
Or learning to do so if you think it's the type of camera you have.  
   
edit: and investing in a couple other lenses before the body. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's two sides to this coin though. Above the guy says 'shows up to shoot the wedding with a Rebel t5i.'

And he's right, depending on how well lot the wedding was. So you kind of need the right tool for the job to a degree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey! I use a rebel! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was my initial thought too. Oh that's gonna suck. The lighting seems weird and compared to the back ground its all off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 01:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i think it's really hard to distinguish what the 'correct' play is though. Down there at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah there's a lack of understanding here a bit about how these sauces are used normally. And to a degree how they're used on the show, minus the dab.  
  
When they mix a sauce for the wings at the further end of the spectrum they're using such tiny amounts to bring the heat up. I'm not even sure if they're good 'wing' sauces as much as they are for Jambalaya like dishes.    
  
When they do that dab, I'm like in awe because it's just not meant to be consumed like that, let a lone on a single wing to boot. 
   
I had it was either 357 or Blair's at a...beer convention? Or maybe a hot sauce thing. They had tortilla chips to taste sauces and then toothpicks to taste that one. 
   
Like, you slide the toothpick in and out. So it's barely covered. Of course, and I'm thinking it's the beer convention we're at, I take a tortilla chip and blob that shit on there and eat it. 
   
It legit felt like mustard gas or something. It's pain in the mouth, the face, the stomach, the esophagus. I actually helped my own alright. I mean I was fucked up but kind of tolerated it. It's a good 20 min of pain/discomfort though.
   
I don't really seek out the 'spiciest' kind of shit anymore. I guess after you do it it's like meh. I do enjoy my spicy food still, just prepared a bit more proper I suppose.  
   
edit: I'm also a guy who has been using Dave's regularly for years in my cooking. Not as much anymore because tastes change and I've turned more to using peppers directly to cook. 
   
That said, if people are curious and seeking this kind of shit out start with liek Dave's Insanity or something like that. It's, you really don't get it until you've tapped into that over the line kind of heat and you realize 100k or 500k? Why am I trying this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 19:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely. But I'm sure it isn't like a '30 foot training exercise with divers all around the sub like, 'we got you!' 
   
They're still probably doing depths where you'd have a hard time reaching the surface if anything happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 19:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes a lot of sense now. Still extraordinary. I'm not sure if it speaks more of man's ability to engineer, our stubbornness, frugality, or sense of resilience/perseverance. Suppose a bit of all of em. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 08:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm familiar with the tar/pitch process. And understanding it as, essentially, filling in the cracks makes this even the much more remarkable in a sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 08:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> of course man. but 70 years? wet wood last even shorter. 
   
i'm not surprised in a naive sense. i'm awed in an impressive sense.  
  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 05:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm not going to lie. a ship is a ship. it's basic design is to float and i'll trust a boat to float. 
   
a submarine...er...so it's 70 years old and is going to go under the water? with that pressure and just the whole diving process. 
   
I'd be a bit more than freaked out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 05:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> of wood? jesus. do they like tar her? like that kind of wood ship? that's crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 05:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whaaaaaaaat a coincidence?! 
  
absolutely not. the look on her face is solid though. she don't care. and to a degree it's one thing to have these shirts. it's another thing to put it on and then on the cat, at the same time in ur home and be weirdly cute. it's def another level to go out, in some capacity and take a photo of it. 
   
there's def a degree of weirdness going on here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> actually to be fair, i dont think people get this but there's a decent amount of oversight with these programs. the cia exists to protect us against foreign threats and generally with all the shit they are doing across the world don't have the resources to look at home. 
   
That's what the NSA does. I'm not naive but this is 100% used mostly in foreign countries and embassies and systems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh personally i would have it top 3 maybe, but there's def a few tracks better or as good. especially since it's individual tastes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha fa real. 
  
much more "when did my life meow?"  
   
edit: i also give big ups to the chick wearing the shirt and putting the short on the cat. no fucks given. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i just laughed out loud and almost spit out my drink. Oh my gosh this is too f'en good. Needed this after he last few days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it's a bit rough when someone publishes a book like that. On one hand though, for all the shit state facilities get, especially the forensic level ones, it really opens your eyes to the difficulties the field presents. 
   
That environment is near impossible to keep stable and that hurdle alone needs so many resources and support mechanisms to maintain it's like no wonder things aren't 'better' to an outsiders unrealistic standards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol nah Illmatic was dope man! I think a lot of younger guys on here don't have the appreciation for that old school sound, especially the largely NYC stuff that was so dominant then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very true, great point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Y'all need some SEO, writing or design be more than happy to help out.

I do 5 and 10 article packs but if you're hiring writers from the Philippines probably beats my rates. That said, a native English speaker for English SEO is probably worth paying for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I think a big part of it is recognizing is something is actually good or just trying to replicate that. His is the former by far and it reflects in his growth now. This wasn't born out of no where.

Different tastes though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Great* use of italics. 
   
Lol I'm kidding. But yeah it hurts. And it's like overall I can't help but think, if they could afford healthcare already, they would? Like you fucking moron. A health savings account?  
  
Like Gee, son, I put $25 whole buckaroos in your account! For when you break your leg. And get billed for $12,500. 
  
Like come on.    
   
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think, and I'm from NYC so, bias heavy 
   
maybe it's hard to get *not* being from NYC but striving for that standard is a worthy pursuit. To do it as well as he did, is worth celebrating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You act like they only started making music this year for this year. Sure it's a long year, I hear that side of it too.  
  
This shit is solid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Politics settles to the lowest common denominator. What's easiest. I didn't elect people to make easy fucking choices.  
   
It's not easy, it's not pleasant. It's sure as fuck expensive. And there's not much about that I like. But I inherently feel, both economically, and as an unalienable human right we need to provide healthcare for people. 
  
Right now, we provide it if you got nothing or a good enough job for it. And the only other option wants to be done away with. *When it's a private market oriented program!* 
   
They already killed it when they did that. Forced the private market initiative on it.  
   
Single payer is the way to do, hands down. IMO. Also no cheap. Not easy. But it's the most transitional and reasonable approach.  
   
Part of me hates the small businesses mandates of Obamacare but if you set that standard then people will consider it while starting businesses. It becomes a standard to expanding past a point and to me, that's kind of okay. 
   
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who the fuck is voting for N.Y. State of Mind?  
  
I mean i definitely might have when I didn't get what this is. But, now that I do... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is actually pretty interesting. This dude in Alaska still uses an outhouse and talks about his poopscicle.  
  
http://www.discovery.com/tv-shows/alaska-the-last-frontier/videos/everything-poop-and-outhouses/  
   
it's the third video.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to jazzfest a bit ago. It was kind of fucked they were all at one spot. Which def works in one way but also led me to believe there weren't any. 
   
That said, part of me still feels like I should live in NOLA for a few years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those three things are so counter-intuitive it's hard to reconcile that's anyone's approach.   
  
I think what we need is to cap costs for poor and lower income individuals, shifts the burden to insured, wealth people. Or just wealthy insurance companies. The problem isn't insuring the uninsured. The problem is the rising cost of health care. The uninsured getting pummeled by this is the symptom.  
   
I really don't have a good solution for this. Zilch in the idea department. Incentives for being healthy is a good one though. And making sure people use their bi annual or annual check ups. So they stop attending ER's for stupid shit. Throw in an educational campaign.   
   
Capping costs though really is what it comes to. I'm a fiscal conservative in most areas but healthcare is one that people should have access to in the 21st century. So rolling back medicaid doesn't sit well with me. Nor do I think block grants are going to be effective. Let alone cheap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Living well is the best, hands down. That said, I guess, it doesn't need to be out of spite. I think the point of that saying is that doing well for you is caring about you and not them.    
  
I try not to take joy in other's misery. I guess. When it comes to someone I look at as an adversary though, I guess that changes.  
   
Lol, yeah def does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might be decent book material if you write it right. Sounds like Gone Girl the real version. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to step in here and say addiction isn't the same. 
  
The options offered to our addicts are shit and based, largely, even therapist who hold medical degrees, on AA. Which is just absolutely bonkers psuedo science. 
  
And it's hard. It's *easy* in the sense everyone wants to help you. And thinking that person wants to keep on that path is really...it's a tough pill to swallow because it's not entirely true. 
   
Waking up one day and deciding to get yourself help can be a pain in the ass. Much much harder than just buying drugs again. Methadone clinics needs proof of past treatment attempts and suboxone doctors only accept cash, let alone medicare/aid.    
   
I'm not saying their aren't options and I'm not saying you should tolerate criminal behavior. And kicking them out isn't an easy thing to do. But wishing death?   
   
I really don't know many people who feel that's a normal sentiment toward addiction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah if anyone finds this topic interesting read behind the gates of gomorrah. forensic therapist at a state run facility. 
   
https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00GEEB17M/ref=dp-kindle-redirect?_encoding=UTF8 btkr=1  
  
from that book, iirc, they organized a softball game of some sort and there was something during it, maybe someone seized? and later the docor found out one of the patients, who had 'broke' their glasses a week before had sharpened a leg to stab him with it. 
   
it's part time, boredome, and craziness. when you got time you'll figure out the way to do what it is you want to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont think we should be throwing depression in with behavior that's clearly borderline personality disorder territory.    
  
or narcissistic territory.
  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh you poor thing that's not justice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and then shoot her anyway? yeah probably. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thinking about this is weird. Like to get software to do that you need to already have an internet connection. Obviously could have had it at any point prior. Then everywhere they go, they take a day to brute force wps pins? At least my understanding of why it's weak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 05:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said how you feel about it because all you replied to me with was an opinion. Nothing to back it up. Just because you feel like it wouldn't work doesn't mean it won't or you shouldn't try. 
  
Also, you're being dramatic again, Kidnapping? No, but they wouldn't be able to walk out of the store with the firearm until the background check cleared. The reality is, like a lot of security, the theater is half the battle. Criminals don't sign up for things that require checks or registration.  
   
But yeah I think your claims that it's unrealistic or a fantasy are just misplaced. You lack an understanding of how it might work. Hell, without trying we would really never know. Ultimately, I don't see why you insist that a criminal, with an immigration investigation, wouldn't come up when buying a firearm. Or if the FBI did get notified Mateen was buying an AR in Orlando that they might not revisit him since he was on a watchlist twice. 
   
Nor, when I suggested things a ten round magazine cap, federally, you just ignored it. Nor did you even begin to propose an alternative solution other than letting another shooting happen. 
   
And really, you're straw manning like crazy. A strawman isn't an attack on your character. The argument you presented, without facts and saying "It won't work because this isn't T.V." actually is a strawman because you provided no reasoning to back that up. Because I'm not proposing television. I'm proposing running names against watchlists we currently maintain and open NICS for assault type weapons. Hell, apply the same things to hadnguns we do to rifles, that simple.  
  
Dont' attack me. Your looking for calling what I said ad hominem which is also what you're doing by attacking me. I wasn't attacking you, because your argument was your opinion on something and isn't going to prove or advance any meaning in this debate. 
   
Christ man. Use google at least.  
    
And what kills me is the apathy. It's just you'd rather say, welp disagree! and move on! I offered yo ua shot to provide a different solution and even proposed shit like ten round mag limits. But you really just don't give a shit. You're worried about you and your ability to continue buying what you want to buy when you want it. It's selfish and immature. When there is 100% chance there will me another MCI shooting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 01:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah man. I guess I'm not a community kind of guy. The best thing you could do for yourself is a get an editor. It can be a friend, if it's the type of friend you'd trust for something like...telling you your wife is cheating on you. And smart/good writer/editor.
   
i know that sounds dramatic but it needs to be the type of person you want there to tell you the whole truth. No matter how shitty it's gonna be to hear.  
   
And the reality is people are always like, "constructive criticism" and I hate to be that guy, in the world of writing we tend to be pretty good at looking at each other as writers. Not black, white, asian, blue, green, man, women. But as a fellow writer. And in my group of writers, something we...partially opt to do by choice, victimization has no place. People need to hear shit like, get rid of that paragraph, stop going into so much background, cut this, and trash this character or rebuild them. 
   
You kind of just don't find that in people out here. And when you ask for it...well, it's still, "You know, overall it's pretty good. I don't think I can relate to the character though. I'm not sure it's entirely believable he would just leave like that." 
  
So what do you do? You go back and add a sentence "his cell phone rang, and he said 'I gotta bounce.'"  
   
And do we ever really repost it again for more follow up? Nah. Long term collaboration with a trusted editor is wear it's at. And whatever else works for you (so in that case is the community does, all the more power to ya). Just not for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 01:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit man, you don't let em walk out of you store with a gun until it's done, don't care how glacially slow the government is to do it.  
   
Sorry I touched on something a bit more real and jsut got back your solid opinion and a load of shit on why it wouldn't work. Sorry it bothers how you *feel* about it.   
   
So you're telling me the guy who was under investigation by ICE about a marriage for a green card and had associations with the guys arrested for planning to kill soldiers wouldn't pop up on a background check? He's the one who bought the guns. The other guy didn't because he was probably scared shitless of all the jihadi shit he was looking up. THe guy in Orlando's name had been flagged before too.  
  
It isn't every citizen, again, stop with the fucking dramatics. It's only if you want to take a damn similar gun home that our combat infantry use. You can walk out of a gun store with a damn near similar gun, with more dangerous ammo (HP), and more rounds than an Infantry man carries on a patrol. 
   
Except you're not in combat. And someone will, again, shoot up some fucking mall or something.
   
Come on man, you're killing me. You're suggestion is that because it might not work anyway we shouldn't try. Frankly, it's weak at best and just bullshit at worst.  
   
I'm sorry you're feelings are bothered by this. You're opinion that it might not work, so why try? Is no way to approach any fucking problem. Jesus. And don't call me an idiot. You've provided 0 evidence for this. I bet the same argument was put forth about the brady bill.
  
And part of, despite providing 0 evidence, what you're saying has a point. It won't stop everyone. It may not have stopped Orlando. The guy did buy a Glock and was background checked. In my opinion, it speaks more to the failure of the FBI to take him off their watchlist. It also incentives us to have stronger background checks. A federal law, a single one covering both handguns and rifles.  
  
What frustrates me is you argue against it without providing an alternative. You know. It's the lack of trying. If I'm wrong, tell me the answer. Not doing anything, to me, is immeasurably wrong and, frankly, not the type of person I am. 
   
For all the shit people put out here about being a gun owner to do something or a good guy with a gun beats a bad one. The lack of trying is hypocritical.   
  
Even a magazine limit to 5 or ten shots. 100% that cop gets a shot on him. 
   
And more so, even if Orlando happens because the background check sucks, San Bernardino probably doesn't. Cause the guy who bought the weapons was a criminal.  
   
edit: and that's the point. you're working in absolutes. the absolute right now is that another shooting will happen. 100% sure of that. We both are. But if we could reduce the chances of it happening? By 20? 30? 50? 75%? by creating a stricter background check, you wouldn't do it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> glad i wasn't the only one looking at that and thinking unoriginality </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No you have due process. If you want to own a weapon that our troops aren't trusted with taking home after deployment submit to the background check. Everyone does it for handguns because handguns are used in homicides. Now rifles are being used in MCI incidents, with some sense of regularity recently. Sure you could say the number of total people killed the last 6 years from these incidents is less than a 1000. You'd probably be right. Does that mean we shouldn't make it harder for he next guy to shoot up a mall and add another 50 to the list?  
  
Those lists you're talking about already exist. We lost due process with the establishment of our secret courts and the patriot act. I'm only looking to help weed out the few truly bad actors that are using legal means to create terror.   
  
edit: Trust me, I'm pretty torn about the current police state we live in. I'm reading articles about CBP forcing people to give the passwords to their cell phones and i"M like whaaatt the fuck man. On the other hand it feels like mass shootings are less common events but also events we shouldn't have to continue dealing with. Or attempt to hamper. Especially ones related to terrorism. It's not an easy pill to swallow either way. It's also incredibly important to maintain and exercise your rights. And to keep a keen eye on the law. Generally I like to think it isn't abused nearly to the extent it could be. Generally that seems to be the case. Most cops aren't the bad apples kind of argument.   
   
Then again when I hear Trump bash 'the media' and wonder if he's willing to attack the first amendment and undermine it with falsehoods at what point would it end? I'm particularly skeptical in this political climate of alleviating ourselves of any rights less we lose them forever, or the slippery slope is hit and we tumble down it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do want to thank you for being clear about that and pointing it out. Def makes a bit more sense now and I just want to reiterate how much I disagree with a lot of the reasons and things they ban on Assault Weapons. 
   
That said, generally illegal handguns are more expensive that counterparts that can be bought legally. Saying handguns are so widely available isn't really a good argument for it. Saying most homicides occur from handguns is, and it's to your point.  
  
I was mostly just talking through how it's presented to someone who is voting on a bill. The length of the barrel really isn't going to change shit. The place that this argument really gets dangerous is when people say, "Oh well, 5 round, 15 round, 30 round mag! It doesn't make a difference he'll jsut reload it!"  
   
Or handguns are prevalent and they have 12 or 15 round magazines, but you ban them from my AR? It doesn't make sense! 
  
And frankly that's bullshit. High capacity magazines are great for...putting more rounds down range faster. What's the purpose of that? Oh to suppress someone. I firmly believe that in Orlando if the guy was limited to 5 or 10 round magazine the cop would have been able to effectively shoot back rather than hide behind a pillar as 223 put holes into the wall and probably the thought to the cop that, if me, my vest too.    
  
And for anyone who claims home defense, buy a shotgun. Please. But if you insist 10 rounds is more then enough close quarters. Most people talk about this kind of shit without realizing these guns are designed to engage at 100, 200 meters. Let alone 20 feet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't you think the point of the background check would be to say, "He had ties o these guys we arresed in 2014 for plotting to kill soldiers. He just tried to purchase an AR with 1000 rounds." 
  
"Alright, bring his file back up, knock on his door, and check his communications."  
  
No then he gets arrested. Border Control? They're U.S. citizens. Come on, are you nuts?  
  
Saying it'll happen anyway is no excuse to not put the hurdle there. Especially if the hurdle involves a background check from intelligence/FBI/LEO resources. Get a grip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did a bit a of journalism a few years ago. mostly fiction now. had representation for a book, going to take another stab this year with it.  
   
got good feedback on it actually. just thought it might be hard to sell. i shopped it sort of after the circle came out and it's...not really similar but hits that BNW/1984 vein. Today? think it'll be great. 
   
I  half wrote that comment because I just don't like the peaches and cream description of writing. It always seems to fluff it up. And the idea of immersing yourself in your art or field, while sometimes necessary and always present to a degree is the exact opposite of what you need sometimes. 
   
In my opinion, some people can write and other can't. I writer better when I"m reading more actively and sometimes I can't write at all until enough time has passed because it's influencing me too much. It's deeply personal thing, fiction, and treating it any other way seems uninformed, least from experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 10:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's scary. And I'm a fiscal conservative. Pretty ashamed of the GOP and God forbid I think healthcare is a worthy cause. 

This fucking guy? He's no president. 

The worst is the ego by far though. But the lack of understanding he shows toward basic stuff, like the recusal, is crazy.

I've noticed that a lot of Trump supporters I know have begun passionately defending him. Angrily so. Especially the leak argument. And I'm like this really is how racism starts. Just blindly on the bandwagon. Even when I proposed a timeline like the IC gave it to him 3 weeks ago. When he didn't act they turned to the press. Because, besides being wrong, they were afraid he'd be blackmailed and being he lied about it once must have known it wasn't right.

They jumped down my throat. People who support him who I thought would say "Yeah pretty messed up Flynn was in the wrong." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 10:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Due process applies in the courts not in capitalism.

And don't be so dramatic it's not abolishment. It's common sense. Sure there's no direct correlation between the Brady Act and safer streets but neither of those guys bought handguns to shoot shit up. 

All I want is the hurdle to be there. And illegal guns are generally more expensive than their legal counterparts. Obviously. So let's add that hurdle legally for bad guys who, recently, looked at the legal purchase of a firearm to commit crime as the way to go. Let's make a guy who looks at Inspire think, will they know what I read? What I look at? Will they find those Facebook messages or that email?

Of course unless he's actually associated they won't but if he thinks it he won't bother.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 10:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus man. You're killing me. I'm agreeing, it's an absurd notion.

But by that logic the same background applications should apply to assault rifles. Because they're what people use in MCI's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 10:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, I kind of hate writing. It's not a pleasant thing it's work. Overtly challenging and fulfilling but not in a oh that's the problem let me take it on.

I don't even know if the base material I created is sufficient let alone the parts I feel might need changing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
