<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3191</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 03:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hat article is bullshit. Dan fouts was not the first guy to throw for 4000 yards. Joe namath threw for 4000 yards in a 14 game season </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 03:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Teams that dont have cheerleaders draft first in each round. Giants, bears, steelers top 3 every year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 03:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didnt the giants win that game? Wasnt it san diego that had such loser fans, their team went to LA? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 02:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are not talking about kissing Cousins. Dont get all horny on me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 02:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giants ahould use this to get odb to accept less money. Good for the salary cap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 02:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If your line is worse than the giants you should be demoted to the arena league </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 02:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much detail do you get for $20 ? There are more expensive tiers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 02:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats for professionals who need all the stats </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 01:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump can fire them. They dont get the same protections other agencies get and trump has started firing people st other agencies by layoff. They could also make them sign national security letters on the way out the door. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal Judge appointed by George W Bush orders Kris Kobach to turn over a documents from a Trump meeting to the ACLU by Friday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 01:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 01:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would requires non white people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 00:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lucky mama didnt charge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 00:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somebody has cat allergies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 00:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I see commy. You want to murder the mentally handicapped because they cant work effectively in state run industries. Goddam scientologist commy trying to spread the gospel of Xenu. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 00:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Report looks like they were scamming republican donors for profit. They would hold fundraisers without candidates consent and pocket it as fees. Alot of fundraising companies charge absurd fees and most money goes to them. CNN ran reports on this with charities in the last few years.

My only political point is that if this was some democratic fundraising firm scamming democrats it would be the lead story in right wing media because they use bullshit like this to distract from Trump scandals.

This does not appear to involve the republican party. It looks like some asshole scamming republican donors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do we roll our eyes up when we are exasperated? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 04:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 03:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You cant hide Commie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 00:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump would want to hire Hoover when he dressed as a women to piss on him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 00:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone paid putin to use some more bots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 00:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another scientologist claiming his religion is real. Goddam communist/scientologists. Bunch of child molesting communist Putin spies. We need to bring back the Conmittee for UnAmerican Activities and public hangings for traitors like you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 19:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Father Connor? So his molesting you is what made you turn from the Lord and towards communism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 19:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump is the most famous Russian spy and he doesnt have issues </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 19:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Explosions in movies are always so slow compared to real ones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 18:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was the republican party response to watergate before the very end when they turned on Nixon? Was it like they are acting today? Most defended him and called Watergate a witchhunt? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 18:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The chart for the size of your asshole in prison would go the other way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 18:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listen commy. They havent released anything because the investigation is ongoing. This doesnt mean there is no evidence. Atheist/Communists always lie. Commies like you have no morals .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 17:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Id like to see Isaac list his book recommendations in the blurb under his video and on his website sited back to his video.

Greg Egan also has some good shorter stories for free on the web. Go to his website. Isaac has talked about Wheel of Time also </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 17:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get frequent freezes and then i have to kill the process and restart. You can download easy task killer. I think my phone runs out of memory. I have a suggestions in another thread for options to lower graphics to use less memory.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 17:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You came in here lying. Then crybully about someone calling you on it. Trump has not been cleared. The investigation is ongoing. You are just lying. I am an optimist. No patriotic American would lie about Donald Trumps communist associations with Russia. So you are clearly a communist sympathizer or paid Russian communist troll trying to undermine our democracy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He doesnt havevto they will just kill it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paid by putin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Charles Krautheimer of Foxnews thinks Trump is Lying about why Comey was fired. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even Charles Krautheimer of Foxnews thinks this is bullshit. This story is on the foxnews front page.

http://insider.foxnews.com/2017/05/09/james-comey-fired-charles-krauthammer-trump-clinton-comments-july </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are lying. They have not said anything about the case. Must be another paid Trump Troll. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Getting optioned before publication is a big deal. The higher the cost of the option the more likely it becomes a movie. Most options are not for alot of money. Ridley Scott has been sitting on the option for The Forever War for decades. Back in the day they didnt have time limits.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wrote a really short story called the Egg that is very good too. You can find it on the web.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasnt ro e invaded by one of the hellenistic kingdoms before the punic wars? I think that is where the term Pyrhic Victory came from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You switched to russian? How much is vlad paying you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did they blow up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Id be surprised if the koreans call their naval special forces seals also. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comey was uncovering something about Trumps ties to Russia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New York State attorney general should get a subpoena and raid trumps accounting firm and seize his tax returns.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Democrats had a majority in the house back then so they could run the investigation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the way things are going trumps son will be king and he wont let it continue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fbi will go silent and say nothing about the russian investigation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This a coverup. If you fire the fbi director while you are under investigation its absolutely done to shoot down criminal activity. The next fbi director will shutdown the investigation. Flynn will plead the fifth when subpoenad 

New York State attorney general needs to get a subpoena on trumps accountant and seize his tax returns and all records wirh him. Then subpoena and new york banks or investments that he has and take all records. Then subpoena all of his vendors. 

Hall his 2 adult sons in for questioning as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Game in a very unbalanced state and is Kelsonk abandonong the game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the facebook page Kelonk wrote that he is burned out and no more design updates indefinitely. The game is currently in a very unbalanced state and if this forum is any indication the fan base is leaving. If balance isnt brought back, I think it will die. 

I did not play before the recent changes a few weeks ago wen progress was really fast. I am not comparing to that. I am level 90, on NG 2 and bought 6 clicks a second plus the XP bonus. I have not progress reset yet. In a post yeaterday, Kelsonk said I should not progress reset and should go until the game sloes down. Its a crawl. The only way to progress is to manually tap for hours or root my phone and install an auto tapper. Even then its slow.

1. The finger does not appear to click 6/times a second. As soon as I tap, my gain goes up alot. I cant tap 6/times a second so something us wrong. If its a performance thing, its may be better to just o one combined tap every 5 seconds so I would get a 30x tap every 5 seconds.

2. As soon as you make a mysterium and upgrade your boats, sailors are totally useless. On NG 2 a basic galley set to go for 1 hour, that has 5 level 37 sailors will reduce time by 2 minutes.

2. Workers in generally are useless. Its multiple days with 10 workers to clear out a mine. This means they are useless.

3. The only way to harvest/build/refine is to tap for hours. There are only so many tap bonus items I will get. I have spent some money, but Im not going to spend hundreds of dollars to progress. No one will. If you want people to spend more money you have to give us a reason. For example the finger auto tapper length should be upgradeable with gem stones at a reasonable price. 7 minutes when it now takes 2 hours or more of tapping to clear a mine.

4. The increase of 2300x in cost for every NG is arbitrary and is way too large.

5. Whole Cities give such a small bonus they dont do much of anything. I git several levels in the one that increased my ship and its not noticeable. Did you even test this? 

6. Price increases on buildings like Dragon Forge, Kinetic Rune factory, university  is so huge it does not allow the game to scale with the absurd 2300x cost increase.

7. Time for ships isnt that big of a deal. I didnt play before, but people complaining seem to want this to go too fast. That being said sailors and whole city bonus to speed are totally useless.

8. Why is the progress reset static? You get a set amount. That standard in games is that prestige increases are based on some formula of what you did. Its also not clear that if you progress reset and rebuild your guilds do you double your multipliers again? So they dont go down when you you lose NG?

Can you put some thought into a good progress reset mechanic? 

9. Progress reset should say exactly how many NG you go down. Not a few.

10. The time of the Auto tapper should be increase to be increased with gems and achievements. It should be like 1 minute for 10 gems. This is an idle game. It should go up in 15 minute chunks. It should work offline. I dont want to run my phone in a game all day. Ill wear down my device. Also as said above, its not tapping at the correct speed or its not getting the full amount. I dont want to be tied to the game. If it takes a while to mine or build, I need to be able to run offline and workers are totally useless. 

11. Return in banks is so low and take so long they are totally useless for anything other than achievements. 

12. Bonuses from artifacts are basically a who cares for most of them. Per the wiki page a bunch dont do anything. So why have them? 

Lag issues: playing on a samsung S6. 3 years old. Only thing running. People dont buy new phones every year.

1. Game freezes after a period of time. Maybe due to running out of memory. Allow a low res mode that gets rid of graphics, sjowing tap and worker values and workers spinning. 

2. Allow an option to only collect auto tap and workers every few seconds. Maybe a slider. So if its every 10 seconds you just get 10x.

3. Game seems to pause fir half a second at intervals with workers. Adding 1 and 2 should help with that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 09:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What engine are you using now? I havent seen any release posts from you in a long time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Become a cop. You can arrest asshole customers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont use linkd in. Been in IT for 20 years. I dont want my life on the inteet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its not lazy. People dont want to pay you as much. Half the people in the world dont have enough to eat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Family emergency. Or you are sick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your lucky your office doesnt block reddit. Most block social media </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im nit going up fast. The coat increases are enormous compared to my build/mine rate. I looked at older posts. You have really nerfed progress. Im not sure the last time you tried playing.

Do I lose the cities? If I do, I should plunder them before I reset. What about lumber. If I keep my lumber and my lumber yards reset, I will have more lumber than I can hold. Do I keep that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is your financial situation? How hard is it to get another job? I job hop alot. I have never asked fir a raise. I tell people when I interview that I want more money. Your CEO sounds like an asshole. Asking fir more money is dangerous. He might go out ad hire your replacement then fire you. 

I would push back on the workload and not be willing to increase my hours. However, I have alot of experience and live in a good job market. I would not ask for a raise. Good job market doesnt mean I can find a good job right away. 

If the ceo, pushes you too far try to find another job at more money. Put all the increased responsibility on your resume. 

Always be ready to get a new job in IT.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Erdogan an Islamist or is he just playing them to set himself up as a dictator? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Name the country, when you went to it, etc. if not your just a racist troll </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And which country dis you go to? Or are you just a troll? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By palestine do you mean Israel, the West Bank, or Gaza? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors who live in, have lived in, or travelled to countries with Islamic law, what is it like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors who have gone to North Korea, why did you go and what was the experience like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Followup question. It says you keep your resources. So you dont keep your mines right? So its a good idea to mine everything out before doing a progress reset? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When should I progress reset? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am resding older posts. There seem to have been alot of changes to progress resets the last few weeks. I am on NG 2. I can now progress reset. Should I progress reset or wait? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Post the name of the youtube site in the title.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you imagine how much a guy would get trolled if he wore 56? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yankees are going to run out of numbers. I cant see anyone wearing babe ruth and all the other famous number again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one will ever wear 56 again. I dont think that was officially retired.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are there any sites that outline the plotlines? Wheel of Time has a wheel of time encyclopedia which is a big wiki with out of every chapter. Links when characters and special things are mentioned so you can go to a timeline.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Permanent brazilians? As an aging guy Ill take permanent ear hair removal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are they allowed to take your house for not paying water? They shouldnt be allowed to do more than turn your water off, send to a collection agency, and potentially sue you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No she is too attractive for Cleveland. She would need to lose 20 pounds to get that Cleveland Meth look </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1986 giants knocked qbs out in 9 consecutive games through Montana. It was why they were so dominant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My grandfather never had money and for a time owned a camera shop. There were lots of cameras in the 1970s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Odell Beckham. You haters never talk about him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michael Jordan. Wide Receiver </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anne Coulte as cheerleader. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1986 giants only gave up 3 points and scores more points too. Beat Joe Montana, Jerry Rice, and the 49ers 49-0. We wanted the bears for revenge that year, but they choked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He made Elite money for a mediocre player </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is he hof in deliverance county. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one hires Peyton Manning or Brett Favre </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You stole my thunder.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vatican dating site for priests and nuns </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I looked at some videos of this guy. There will be a thread in the future where this guy has been killed. He rolls around and puts his arm in their mouth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was greek fire exclusively used in naval warfare? Was it ever used in land battles? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why all the red roofs? Are they required to use the same tile? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its not the middle ages. Its 1600s tech without guns. Jordan said that. People are too rich even then. This is common in fantasy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alot of authors would love a AAA game developer license thee work to make a game and pay them lots of money </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wht are his other games? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What sub is this on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are his other games? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the US wanted to kill Castro, it would not have been that hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking Seth Rogen should be prosecuted leaking classified information. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone wants their Almost Famous moment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need the source. How bad was he hurt? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wants the big contract. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only assholes want to be called sir.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jay cutler on any nfc east team not named the giants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He signed a deshaun jackson contract. Time to sport the bling like jackson </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you get a reset stone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont even see it listed under stones. Im on droid. Latest version. I saw in a thread I can craft under the other tab. I dont see it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got a university in new game 1 after I made a library. I am now researching an observatory in my second library. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happened to southern slaves immediately after they were freed during the civil war? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this question is broad. Was there a sense of what do we do now? They did t own any possessions. I know eventually sharecropping became a system that replaced slavery. What happened basically right when they were freed. Were they given land or anything? Did the plantation owners immediately start negotiating with them to farm their land? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When my cobra ran out and I needed health insurance I was it n hipaa for allergy shots by Aetna. Hipaa was very expensive shit insurance that did not cover allergy shots. Aetna denied if you had more than 2 things. I had shots and 2 generic allergy medications( which i did not need all the time). Both are over the counter. I asked if they could give me a plan without hipaa or allergy coverage( wasnt alot of money). They said no. They used Hipaa as profit centers to just get money out of people. My only option was the $2000/month with $15,000 deductible that covered basically nothing. 

Its not just pricing you out, its how bad the insurance is with hipaa. Unless you get into a car accident and just die suddenly, everyone will need expensive medical care eventually.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> During the 1300s life expectancy dropped  beyond child mortality. Famine and the black death. Plus the little ice age ( google it) caused crop yields to go down. Middle Ages is a 1000 year period. 1300s people dropped like flies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chair isnt effective. Put barbed wire on a baseball bat and name it Lucille.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they lay hands on you and are larger grab lucille and go Neegan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hotelgate. Don Trump junior runs an international child molestor ring out of the Trump international hotel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They turn a blind eye to the Armenian genocide and they were Christians. Back during the start of the Iraq war several democrats finally called the Armenian genocide what it was a genocide. Right wingers were goi g crazy with why now? 

"Who now remembers the Armenians?" Adolph Hitler </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This times 100 in computer games </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Say hello to my little friends </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the red god will raise donald trump from the dead? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jonny cash shot jfk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about they develop georges last 2 books with him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God. The man is a homicidal maniac. He drowned the entire planet, destroyed sodom and gamorrah, enslaved people and requires people to worship him. Fucking psychopath </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put their home address and phone number on the billboard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marketing department doesnt pay what a coach makes. Do you have to live their in that job? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mcadoo only ran 11 personal alot last year. Not so much before that. He admitted in an interview that was a mistake. I expect it to change. There is plenty of room for 2 slot receivers on the field. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Engram... You can scheme for 2 alot receivers. There is plenty of space. I think the giants long term hope is he becomes an outside WR.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In pittsburgh you would rather just have sex with goats </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He will be the Joe Thomas of the Browns defense. Shit team. Wont win anything. All pro every year. Buys house next to Lebron and Lebron lets him shine his rings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its when you are good that matters. Ill take rings for his qb rating </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its not legal everywhere. Most teams in states where its illegal will argue it gives teams in states where its legal an advantage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somebodys got a rent check due </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How s that 19-0 trademark working out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LT should be #1. He was defensive player of the year as a rookie. Was the gunner on special teams. Giants made the playoffs for the first time in 17 years. Defense gave up 150 fewer points.

There are clips buried on youtube of opposing coaches calling him the best linebacker they ever saw during his rookie season. 

Dickerson had a great rookie season, but the rams hadnt sucked for 17 years before he got there. He had a decent, veteran qb too. He also wasnt hailed as better than Jim Brown as a rookie. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is high school coach in the south who onside kicks every time and never punts. Won a bunch of state titles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bowl games exist to get the school paid and justify coaches salaries. They are not paid. They owe the school nothing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bunny Ranch will be selling groupons </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoever NO drafted with Pats pick. Its the bad karma fro trading with Satan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Engram TE Giants. Im. Fan. So I am an optimist that McAdoo will figure out how to use him. I think if he can catch, he will move to outside WR after the short interlude with Brandon Marshall. At 234 he is too small to block effectively. If he bulks up he will lose speed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cutler is a dick. No one wants and old dick who cant get hard easily </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only 1 baby mama right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All 4 giants superbowl wins came with bellichek.

Defensive coordinator for the 2 we won
Opposing coach for the next 2

All 5 giants superbowl appearances came in the coaches 4th or 8th season </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who knows? Offseason rankings are meaningless </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think guards tend to have shorter arms than tackles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> April is Unprotected Sex month </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do they draw the line on whether something from an illegal search will remain admissable? Does it matter on how serious the charge is? If someone is charged with murder can any evidence no matter how its aqcuired  be admitted?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do those do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This slightly off topic. I got declined by Aetna for insurance and placed in Hipaa in 2007 for allergy shots. I had always had company plans. I stayed in IT, but most of the work was contracting (temp work with no benefits). Cobra ran out after 18 months. So I needed insurance. All I had were allergy shots and 2 generic prescriptions for allergies that I did not need that much. Both of these are now over the counter. There are a bunch of antihistamines and nasal sprays that went over the counter in the last few years. I think the total cost on all this plus 1 allergy doctor visit a year was maybe $1500 total if that much. Most was shots.

The shots were not optional. Im allergic to everything and prone to sinus infections. Took several years, but they helped alot. I had a permanent stuffed up nose and nasal drip plus cough before that. Had surgery twice to relieve constant stuffiness at that point.

Not life threatening, but sucked and not expensive treat.

Aetna automatic declined everyone if they have more than 2 things. Back then the regulation was that if you got declined you went into the Hipaa high risk pool. It had a $10,000 deductable, $2000 a month, didnt cover allergies or much of anything else. So i was in the same category risk category cancer.

This is massive profit fir Aetna. I would only need insurance if something really bad happened. I asked if they could just remove allergy treatment from the regular plan and was told no. Aetna used Hipaa as a profit center. Move as many people as possible to it to make money.

Health insurance is a yearly contract. So if I got Aetna then went on allergy shots/medication automatically to Hipaa. Fucking ridiculous.

I eventually got a good plan from BlueCross. 

It was stressful. I didnt expect any issues getting medical insurance. You had to pay to apply. So there is a dicentive to apply to multiple companies at once. Technically you get the money back if you dont take the insurance. It took like a month to get approved.  I had to scramble and get bridge insurance until I got approved by BlueCross because if I get into a car accident or something, I am bankrupt without insurance.

Total fucking bullshit. I have an employer again who provides health insurance so Im fine. Unless I get cancer, cant work, and Cobra runs out in 18 months and I either have not died or not healthy again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are there different types of resets? I did one to get to new game+ and all it did was let me build better and more expensive buildings. I could lower my new game level to use the older buildings. I did that at level 50 and dont regret it. It was as soon as I got it.

Is there another type of reset?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to find a fancy city? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a quest for this. Is this dependent on distance? How long until you discover one? I have a quest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a basic refinery in new game 1. Can you eventually upgrade your refinery buildings and get better rates? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joe Montana didnt develop Steve Young </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who the duck makes walmart out to be a dream job? Rednecks living in trailers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is the job market where you live? If you lost your job how hard is it for you to replace? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean refuse to build housing? They zoned to deny housing construction? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Silicon valley needs to move. There techies all over the country and people will move for more affordable housing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
