<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3386</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 00:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how the number of broken pieces is reduced as the stairs climb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 04:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once again, you have made my passion for history even greater. Thank you kind sir </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use at your own discression </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, you can't be a fireman then. Your peers won't be able to tell the difference between Jose and Hose </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pinche bato vete a la mierda. Jk I have no problemo with you mate  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 13:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should have said "No pinche wey " </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like jumping on the ground after being on a trampoline. It sucks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did not hit her, I did not. Oh hi mark </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow that was good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 78 77 76... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Automatically read: "Beating: 72 months". Seems about right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok. First of all, I'm going to stand by my original point of view which was of elaborating raw materials YOU ARE GOOD AT. Or is your phone's brand "El celu", your car "El carro"? Stop trying to bullshit me with all the "screw the people who ruin national industry" because most probably, you don't even care enough about it. If you think a reason why the military came was to power, was to debilitate the national industry, i think it is quite far fetched.
Also, the money which goes to the landowners, then goes to the rest of the country. Be it thanks to taxes, salaries or even buying consumer goods. Being the "granero del mundo" was amazing for Argentina in those years. Should it have developed industry in bread, cereal, etc.? Probably yes. Should it have looked for new markets to develop? Yeah, why not. Now, why would it have wanted to produce cars, chairs, light bulbs, if Japan or any other first world country already did it 10 times better? Why buy an "Anasagasti" when you could buy a Rolls Royce? 
By saying "other informal economies" I don't really know what you are talking about. 
(Plus, we actually agree on the fact that the military didn't randomly took power, and that before them, the conditions weren't all that greater when talking about terrorism? Because that was the only thing I was aiming at. What I hate, is people blaming the military for all the events that occurred back then. Persecuting them only for the "atrocities" they caused all while the "montoneros" are not even questioned for the crimes of "lesa humanidad" they sure also committed) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has to blow up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 03:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really know where this popped up, but I would rather say that a country must focus on generating value on the raw materials it it good with. In the video you showed, it basically states that argentine chair fabrication isn't good, which is true. It isn't its specialty. For this reason it imports.
The agrarian class in argentina is actually not the one in control of political power. This is why there is a lot of tension between the agricultors and politicians. In 2008 there was a "reforma 125" which you could look for if you are interested in the topic. Basically it raised the taxes on the agricultors and it even made them stop production in its entirety.
I'm sorry, but I don't know if I answered your question because I don't think I understand what it is exactly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 02:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I prefer "Tesla, by Elonmusk" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One guy (bottom of the pic) is way ahead of his time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hence my username </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 05:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The wealth of nations by Karl Marx. That would be interesting  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 05:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Aleph by David Foster Wallace </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 05:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> David Foster Wallace is way too hard to "cover" in my opinion  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
