<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1989</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 07:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CGP grey


VlogBrothers


Crash Course


JennaMarbles


ASAPscience


Big Think


Epic Rap Battles


Harry Potter Folklore


Last Week Tonight


List25


Matthew Santoro 


MinuteEarth


MinutePhysics



SuperCarlinBrothers


TomScott



TED


TED-ed



WatchMojo.com




VSauce


ZAGAT


Zefrank
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What slang terms do you use that cannot be found on Urban Dictionary? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 07:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Honey, one more time, how do you do the helicopter thing without a penis?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there is actually one for armadillos in knitted hats, that be really cool. But considering that every post in n this sub is automatically marked nsfw, I'll let you put 2 and 2 together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 09:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not trying to undermine, over simplify, or finesse a square peg into a round hole here. If I'm not a good fit, I'm not a good fit. I think there is research out there on how hard it can be for first generation Americans to be able to navigate certain systems like universities and such. But regardless of what the literature says, I know that's been my experience. And I get that the plural of anecdote isn't evidence, but its ironic to see that in the name of inclusivity and non-judgement, you can find people still so willing to judge a book by its cover. I haven't been given everything on a silver platter just because I'm a white guy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 08:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you say I *feel entitled* as if I don't get it. This program is targeted toward helping college students from "traditionally underserved backgrounds". Yes, that includes women and people of color, but last I checked, it also included immigrant populations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some good Instagram accounts to follow? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 08:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 08:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look, I get it. Millennialism and the convenience of tech and all that, sure. But no one else is being the squeaky wheel here and God forbid a student in a leadership role at this university ends up in an actual politically influential position and thinks electronic ballots are a scalable idea. 

That said, go vote. However you want. 

Edit: I too  Tom Scott a lot.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 07:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was born in the states. English wasn't my first language but I went to school here so you wouldnt know it by listening to how i speak or write or anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I, a white male, earn an internship through a diversity program that claims the market is too white and too male? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 07:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My family is one of immigrants. I think that fits the diversity bill quite well. But it was uncomfortable being the only white man in the informational meeting listening to the speaker tell the rest of the audience (and myself too, I guess) that the employer's their company works with aren't looking for "someone like me". *emphasis on the air quotes there* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 06:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well yeah. And I'll even concede that some of his points obviously don't apply to student governments....but nonetheless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On account of ASOSU elections....Relevant. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did you celebrate International Women's Day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It takes me longer to read something from someone I know because I have to make sure I'm hearing it in my head in the way that I think they would say it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 10:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "My name is Sugar Spice AndEverythingNice but you can call me whatever you want... Professor ;)" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Ted Talk topic that no one expected to make it on stage. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 10:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 06:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eye wanna see how that plays out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 05:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a similar note, I would like to see some variety pack options. The one I built for myself consisted of taking a small box to a local shop and telling them I have a budget of x and no taste preferences yet whatsoever. Filling that box up was fun but innefficient.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 05:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Meeska Mooska Mickey Mouse!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 04:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 04:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See the definition of misnomer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'A for effort' is a misnomer because 'effort' starts with E. Lets award the person that came up with the phrase an A for effort. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 03:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are there diagnostics I can run to be sure?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 08:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you're not wrong but you're not right either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] A natural Pothole. Not in the road, but in the earth. When water fills into it, you have a puddle, but what is the divot in the ground itself called? (With or without the water?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 08:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 08:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in the PNW and some of my days started so early and ended so late that I literally did not see daylight. 

Edit: That's a testament to our spring, not to my busy lifestyle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors who moved to a place far from home for a 'fresh start', how did that work out for you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 07:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How can I check weather or not my laptop suffered from non-obvious, light water damage? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 07:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had it in my backpack in the rain, not knowing how long I would be outside. I pull it out and wet paper is stuck to it but I am able to brush off a tiny pool of water off the bottom side with my hand. I don't *think* any got in and ruined anything... but how can I be sure?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How have you used the 'student' card to your advantage? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 07:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I don't mean your literal Student ID, and neither simply asking for student discounts, but when has being a student been an advantage in getting your foot in some kind of door that would otherwise be much more difficult.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scholarship-granting institutions should still award money to graduated students. Just because we have moved on from school doesn't mean we don't have student debt to worry about. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 06:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If your loved ones treated your open-casket funeral like a personalized time capsule. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 05:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please help me understand how big this community really is and how to be a bigger part of it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 05:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mainly follow the YouTube channels like vlogbrothers, sci show, crash course and the rest. I also know about vidcon, nerdcon, and all the books John wrote (which I am counting as part of nerdfighteria until corrected.) I know that the Hank and John have done so much more. But how much more continues to elude me. Help me build a list in the doobly-do?

Edit: [Found it](http://www.nerdfighteria.com/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Combinations of country names and objects that sound like sex acts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 05:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> B-E-A-Utiful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What kind of professional certifications can complement a business management degree? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm familiar with 6-sigma. What else is out there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An ' On This Day In History' book that is a single contiguous timeline, page after page, that plots to the highest degree of accuracy possible, when historic events happened all in relation to one another. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 02:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Putting ALL famous births, deaths, happenings, and events together and splitting the volumes up by time increments instead of by subject. It could help people understand the interconectedness of history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 02:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice tits. Mark it nsfw.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [DISCUSSION] Where do the jazzy licks that reviewers play come from? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 02:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Duscussion] Where do the jazzy licks that reviewers play come from? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 08:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 07:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are Apache Attack Helicopters allowed?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 07:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's delicious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Freudian slip is a biological autocorrect. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 06:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 01:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hosts usually have administrative access to everything they host. Google can see everything you do on chrome and it's other products, your company and school can see everything you do on their network, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 01:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm no scientist but something tells me that there is a reason they don't put magnets near microwaves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The inside tab of the Crayola pack helps me know exactly where each colored pencil goes when I'm done. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 23:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE check up on matches on Facebook if it shows that you have mutual friends? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^ You're the real MVP. Unintentional puns FTW.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is doing those workouts in concert with practicing the stunting *not* counterproductive?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm not going to be winning any need-based scholarships anytime soon. How do I still make sure I graduate debt free without entirely relying on family support? Am I allowed to graduate with a net possitive in scholarship and grant dollars in the bank? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a few years of college under my belt but it has taken to just about now to start being eye-poppingly expensive now that I'm at university and not in my home town anymore. Work is an option I have but they call free money just that for a reason I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need help not injuring myself. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a but of ballroom background and I've dated a dancer or two but that's really it. I started stunting recently for a side project and I be yet to not lift a girl yet but at the cost of my back. This is something I am going to be doing for over a month and I don't wanna put myself out of commission durring practice. Advice? Reesources? Please and thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 11:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe. I didn't know gentle was in the vocabulary of any Christian sect do themoreyouknow I guess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: If your student email account is a gmail account, you have unlimited data storage and backup space. Don't pay for what you don't have to. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 09:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: If you have a student Gmail account, you have free unlimited data storage. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 09:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 09:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My college roommate does this and I never understood it. Have yet to try it myself but that's just how he reigns in the weekend sometimes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 09:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're having minivan sex instead of sport scar sex, you're too old for car sex.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 09:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just wanna be efficient here. u/hummus12345, u/RatBatBusinessCat, u/chem_dog, u/Grootheidswaan, and u/RPDRNick. All those terms came up when I put 'non christian into the thesaurus. That's still not the term that's on the TOMT.

Edit: #onthetomt  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] Infidel is to Muslim as Gentile is to Jew as _____ is to Christian. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 09:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> e.g. nonbeliever. I am 99% sure there is a specific word for this but my Google attempts have yielded nothing. 

Edit: so heathens are non believers, agnostics and atheists are defined by their stance on God's existence, what I'm thinking of is specifically a synonym for non- Christian.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does a student Gmail account really, honestly, actually come with unlimited Google Drive data storage space? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 07:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what several friends, articles, and FAQs say but it's just one of those 'too good to be true' moments and I don't know what's real anymore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 06:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MDMA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 06:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Summer of 69 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 06:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 50 shades darker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unconventional ways to get out of a speeding ticket </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 06:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 02:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Good morning class. How was your superbowl weekend? I hope you all studied for this midterm!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tweets from celebrities that no one ever suspected came from a fake account. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 02:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Easy A? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 01:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't need the credits, just the check boxes for baccor. Specifically in Cultural Diversity, Western Culture, Science, and DPD categories. I would also appreciate something that's not a huge time suck and fun is nice. I like fun. What unicorn classes can you recommend?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 23:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Owned and driven by Jean-Luc Picard when he worked for Hewlett-Packard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE think that vegan cheese either is too expensive or doesn't hit the flavor mark? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 23:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What stories or anecdotes do you keep in your back pocket? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 08:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't drive a manual. My roommate does. He always does this and I never understood why.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 04:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But goddamn it's second to none in terms of back scratching options.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Easy A' baccalaureate core? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 01:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not one to count my chickens before they hatch but I just have 8 credits worth of classes left to take next term until I'm in pro school. I'd like to really experience an easy course load for once so lay em on me. What's the easiest class you've taken? I don't need the credits.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Text] "Stop thinking about what you should do and start thinking about what you can do because what should be done usually requires more resources than you have at your disposal." - Annonymous </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 01:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Stop thinking about what you should do and start thinking about what you can do because what should be done usually requires more resources than you have at your disposal." - Annonymous </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 01:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook should start using facial and text recognition software to let you toggle specific kinds of posts from specific friends. Not even because you might not want to hear about politics, but because live updates of a newborn doing newborn stuff isn't actually that exciting. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 23:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right. That's just how the rule of thumb goes. Venomous snakes and alike usually only bite defensively.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That video actually brought me here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 17:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> venom is actually quite expensive in terms of biology to make.  



True BUT venomous things try to eat you and poisonous things are eaten.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How were certain foods discovered to be edible? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 09:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did older civilizations just have a bunch of guinea pigs and village idiot food testers that would eventually give them enough data to realize that chicken and even certain plants should definitely be cooked or that certain parts of certain plants are edible while other parts of the same plant definitely aren't? And what about animal organs? Not wasting a thing is all well and good but were they not affraid of using intestines as sausage casings or putting other parts into dishes? I see the village idiot hypothesis being just as likely as 'desperate times call for desperate measures and good for you if you get the luck of the draw.' hypothesis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 09:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically, the features of other languages that don't exist in English make a statement as simple and cut and dry as "To be or not to be, that is the question." potentially ambiguous at times - giving translators a lot of latitude with interpretation. But moreover, from the context, that line is only an exerp from a monologue that is meant to be more ambigous as a whole when you consider characters and themes in a larger sense. But that's what makes Shakespeare the OG of the linguistic form to this day.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What shoulder angels do when you aren't faced with an ethical dilemma. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 08:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What physical atributes do you feel self conscious about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 08:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When the person that addresses the elephant in the room definitely makes things worse. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 07:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 10:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saaaaaaaame  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 10:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This belongs in r/art </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Autocorrect gone wild </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 10:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 10:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Nigerian Prince uncle needed help to get himself out of a shifty situation and I never heard if he was alright again but it cost me only $5000 for the peace of mind.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 10:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not well enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There are 2 types of sex changes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 10:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lopitoffame's and Addadicktome's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 06:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all, if anyone else is thinking about reading the replies to that tweet, don't.

I only read them because you wrote this. What a bad mistake. Seriously, don't do it. 

Now I only read them because you wrote this. You were right



choo choo motherfucker. Lets keep this train of regret going..... Don't read it. I did tho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the difference between searching in ALL and r/ALL? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 06:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bad times to ask for the password. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 01:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> World Peace and other 4th Grade Achievements </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 01:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 01:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/crappydesign </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree - I guess I could have worded the post somewhat better. How about "What are some milestones or goals I can set for myself to both look good and perform, regardless of how interlocked the two lists are?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Go, hoe. Zero /zero </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh great. Lets make a shitty product spicy. That'll turn people onto it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the data is, in essence, you. Otherwise it wouldn't be valuable to the advertisers trying to expose themselves to you. Call it a proxy, a metaphor, or whatever, but just because it's not you in the strictest sence and you aren't prostituting yourself doesn't make the data less accurate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Data scores and data reports just like credit scores and reports but for the data up you generate via your digital footprint. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You are not Google's customer. You are the product. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Shit. Rock again? How about best 17 out of 32?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, mom and dad, I love you

But I'm dropping out of school

It's just a lot of hard work

And I'm a lazy fool

But if you need peace of mind

That I'm going to be fine

Here is my sugar daddy

His name is Ryan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *full Tetris sound plays after every kill* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gee. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just read </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 09:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to Coachella!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some good goals for someone who wants to just be healthy and physically well rounded? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 09:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So a beach body would be nice but my main goal is to stay healthy and fit enough to have sex with the lights on. I'll start off the list with the gimmes that I know.  

6 minute mile. 

100 pushups. 

... Idk what else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Being publicly drunk is something you might be able to get away with. Being publicly disorderly may not harm many except uncomfortable bystanders. But being both drunk and disorderly in public simultaneously is a crime. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 09:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 09:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry. I posted and didn't check back. Bad habbit, I've even gotten a CMV post taken down because of how bad I am with checking in sometimes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] The game that a man developed that children can successfully finish and adults can't. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 03:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a game that models real life socioeconomic, geopolitical, and military decision making and the man who invented it may have been a Ted Talks speaker. 

Edit: Top comment solved it. John Hunter was the teacher and speaker. Not having seen the film, read the book, or played the game myself, I'm REALLY curious to know what those 50 interlocking problems actually are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm looking for visio templates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 02:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Specifically one for business model canvases. Can someone help me out please? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My gut reaction was just "ooooh pretty"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am crazy.  Can confirm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wonder what it says about a person who prefers to go sock, shoe, sock, shoe over sock, sock, shoe, shoe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Music video deleted scenes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 02:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why is golf the sport/ leisure activity of choice for politicians and businessmen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 02:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 01:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/crappydesign </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help a business major out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 01:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Accounting is not my major, minor, strong-suit, or passion. But it is an interest of mine simply because I understand how important it is. And I hugely respect the kinds of minds that  this stuff comes easily to. I have struggled through my accounting classes and I have even struggled to find a simple business plan template online that can succinctly cover the financial plan section. Every time I try to tackle it, I run into a cluster-expletive of KPIs and accounting terminology. Any suggestions? Study tips? Resources?   

Please and thank you. 
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you keep your laptop clean? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 01:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The chasis on my laptop is just a fingerprint magnet. I don't have particularly oily skin but judging by the look of my laptop, someone who didn't know better would beg to differ. How do I maintain a clean laptop?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 21:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That strap tho  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There are simply a lot of attractive people in this world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 11:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A video that I can't find </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 10:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a shower threesome that starts with the guy in the shower followed by one girl, followed by the next. One of the girls was a skinny, busty brunette and the other was a mature blonde. I've tried all sorts of combinations of tags searching for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Procrastinating works if you are good at making up excuses. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 09:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What villages did with their virgins before they had volcano gods. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 09:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 08:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do one of these for every knot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 08:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Yes sir. The truth, the whole truth, and nothing put the truth." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What did you take for granted as a kid that you don't now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 05:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doubt kills more dreams than failure ever will. Suzy Kassem in Rise Up And Salute The Sun (2010) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 01:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [source](https://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/List_of_misquotations) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [no](http://www.mlive.com/news/saginaw/index.ssf/2015/01/75-year-old_woman_goes_back_to.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any good shops in town? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need mechanic recomendations. I'm using yelp and the other sources but wanted to come here to ask as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 09:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The new helmet looks cooler but doc says we shouldn't expect any less brain damage." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 09:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We are getting through here absolutely fine and conditions are clear for miles but ya know what? Who am I to ruin such a good kill streak?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 08:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rogain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 08:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Each fraternity at each college is slightly different. At the end of the day, you are choosing a group of friends to call brothers so read them out and make sure you like the guys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 08:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Practicing putting a condom on and not wasting it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Clip' means both to attach and detach. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 08:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: If something keeps popping into your mind and distracting you, start taking Adderall. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 08:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've heard that every culture has it's own rice dish and it's own soup dish. What's your favorite? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 07:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've heard that every culture has it's own rice dish and it's own soup. What are some of your favorites? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 23:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] Where do I remember 'Elephantamous' from? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 22:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it a movie or tv show? I vaguely remember hearing it in a kid's voice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 22:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> suddenly became inappropriate in other settings.   

ummm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 21:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to this week's episode of 'Can they Kama Sutra?' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 08:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^^^ This guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 08:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Octo-clitoris.  
21-developong neighborhood.  
The Lion prime minister.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 08:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Noah, for the last time, we overbooked this damn boat. Tell the penguin they are either gonna have to learn to fly or swim!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 08:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Humpy Smurf
Hempy Smurf
Smergi
Smurfer bro
Smurfette of the month </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 08:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Excuse me sir. Just because this is a potluck doesn't mean you are allowed to sneak your own food in. I'm going to have to ask you to throw that away." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Shut the hell up Felicia. You don't know what you're talking about." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My heart will go on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh boy! Cereal! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Honey, that's not what's happening in the picture. All I know is every time we do this, there are extra parts leftover and you end up with a hurt back. Maybe I get a professional to do it next time." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If the things you're not supposed to do in a movie theater suddenly became inappropriate in other settings. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do porous surfaces like paper, fabrics, and rock look darker when they are wet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 22:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do porous surfaces like paper, fabrics, and rocks all look darker when they are wet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 22:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that scientists have mapped out the perfect road trip that takes you through all 48 contiguous states. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 19:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grant Puerto Ricans and Washington D.C. voting rights, abolish the penny, commission more street art, set speeding tickets and similar fines proportionate to your income, grant internet access the same legal status as utilities, and allocate some of the discretionary budget to a second space race. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 10:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMP] A brunette playmate with a softball bat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 09:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sometimes getting on the computer in front of your family is risky </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 06:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 02:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  have always wondered. He wears this one a lot (all the times I have payed attention to it).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 02:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright. Well, again, thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 01:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But if I let them buy it, are we looking at a similar price range or do shops but parts at a different price point than the people that hop on Google?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 01:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for being awesome with the explainations. The AC compressor needs replacing. I've found them online for $100-200. Any idea how much time and labor we are looking at? Just a rough idea so that the shop doesn't rip me off completely. I am still looking for a place to take it to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Working on memory </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 19:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So mine isn't as great as I'd like it to be.  I've got a note-taking system that works most of the time and I've thought about actual exercises or medicinal approached to help me not need the notes as much as I do. What's worked for you guys? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMP] Not an orgy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 07:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for a video that I can't find.   

Details: 30-ish minutes long. Involved one blonde pornstar and several men having sex with her one at a time. They were all hanging out in a living room at the beginning of the video but the sex happened in the bedroom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the 'retry' button for? Computers can't just try harder the second time, can they? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 03:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do the movies get wrong about what you do for a living? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 20:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what she said </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everything anyone has ever thought of you or said about you behind your back is recorded anonymously and you get the opportunity to read it all. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 07:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe annually. Maybe it'd be a once-in-a-lifetime deal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If someone handed you a box full of everything you have ever lost </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 07:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE just make random noises when you remember something embarrassing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 06:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fact checking sites should sell desktop software that acts as a text reader and gives you pop up warnings when you are reading lies. (especially on Facebook) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 03:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 20:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is also the more subscribed to of the two so I thought I would capture a larger crowd.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] When you talk about Judaism with someone, what are your personal responses to some of the more Frequently Asked Questions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 20:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some quick remedies for allergy-acne? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Consulted: A reality TV show where a panel consisting of experts in areas ranging from medicine and law to economics and psychology rate contestants on how 'well' they live their day-to-day lives. There are no winners or losers - only report cards. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 10:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Little known scenes from popular movies that got left on the editing room floor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 08:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 08:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) that's what I thought.  

2) This is probably me just being a bad car owner but I'm not sure if that's possible with what I'm driving. There is an auto setting that turns the AC on, an off button, temperature buttons, then 4 settings that allow me to control the air once the system is on. But it seems like we are going all or nothing here - what combination of settings do I want that won't cause smoke and noise and parts-destruction? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 08:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good explaination! Just some follow up questions.  

1) from what I understand, weather or not I mess with the clutch, as long as the ac is off, the alternator should be fine, correct?   

2) Tis the season where I might need to defrost my glass every now and again in the mornings... How would I go about that in my current situation?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 07:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 07:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm truly sorry, but ELI5 please? We're really pushing the limits of how much I know about what we're talking about here. hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Consulted: a reality show where a panel consisting of a experts in areas ranging from medicine and law to economics and psychology rate contestants on how 'well' they live their day-to-day lives. There are no winners or losers - only report cards. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 01:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If what you are thinking is what's pictured in the link, then yes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 01:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disconnect the clutch? Would I not just be able to drive around with the ac off?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 00:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No dash lights whatsoever and my buddy had a code reader and volt meter verify that everything is alright. We Just took it for a drive and replicated it. The smoke and sounds only start when the ac runs.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 23:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We replaced the belt and everything seemed fine until about 2 miles later when I heard a noise, the car started shaking, and the smell of burnt rubber was coming from the engine compartment. The new belt is in tact and I don't know what happened. My buddy took a second look at it and didn't see anything wrong. Nothing seems seized up.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Publish a book with 10 different endings and print each one with varying levels of rarity without saying anything. When fans figure it out, announce that there are eleven. Pop some popcorn. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 19:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: I'm not trying to repost, crosspost, or thieve. I think I may have seen this on my  Facebook wall once a while ago and stored it in the memory banks, but honest mistake. If someone wants to find the original Tumblr post and link it, I'll give credit where credit is due.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Calling all former debates. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 09:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am one myself - just wondering who else is out there. What bigger and better things have you moved on to?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sooooo Adderall. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 09:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 08:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/crappydesign </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 08:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I was gonna say how familiar it looked.](https://www.reddit.com/r/personalfinance/wiki/budgeting)   

https://i.imgur.com/CcEVQAV.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 08:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HMF a woman who is getting a French horn blown into her. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 01:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a piece of art work. I can't really pin the medium because I found it on Slash's Instagram account and he has a lot of stuff like this but that one in particular is one that I haven't been able to find and I have tried several times. Rote scrolling isn't doing it for me.   

Oh yeah - and I'm only asking for a friend. ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you think replacing 'excuse' with 'explanation' in your vocabulary is valid? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are definitely times and places for excuses but do you think people are actually willing/able to hear the difference and understand that you are not trying to use circumstance as a cop-out for not having completed a task?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Organ donation should be an opt out system instead of opt in. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 09:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Race and massacres come to mind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 09:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard that you can/should work abs daily. I haven't been but that's purely lack of planning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
