<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2257</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 03:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Oh Jesus Reese your puffs are *so* good" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 03:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Grow 6" in 2 weeks with penis captivus!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 03:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, you have subscribed to Mammalian Nipple facts! Please press unsubscribe if you would like to discontinue this service. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 03:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So much for the Germans making a perfect race </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The same reason cum is sticky, it's all interconnected, man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, you making that face really shows you're desperate for attention. I mean, that is why you 'came out of the closet,' right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's so gold then give the man gold you worthless cumguzzling waste of air </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 08:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a royals fan, all I have to say is you're welcome  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 03:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always thought DTD's were idiots at my college, but this confirms that they're idiots everywhere </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit, 6 hours later and she deleted her account, what a *dramatic* person </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they had just had enough of killing everything in WWII and decided to call it quits for a while </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> twisted sex appeal

Yep, kind of pinned you as a rapist as soon as I saw you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] After a close call with extreme overpopulation authorities throughout the world have taken extreme measures to control the population -- of puppies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After a close call with extreme overpopulation, authorities throughout the world have decided to take drastic measures in order to control the population -- of puppies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rae Sremmurd, Migos - Look Alive (Remix) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 03:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 04:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good to see the arrow hasn't come back. Would've been devastating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While they probably aren't the best ever, the family guy Star Wars episodes at least deserve an honorable mention </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 02:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just like they said they'd give me 250 Mbps, they can kiss my ass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today marks the 4th anniversary of what is widely considered the most gruesome sports injury in television history. Viewer discretion is highly advised. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 20:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Sir, the drone has crashed in Stockholm and we are unable to find the Ebola specimen."

EDIT: sry, I thought I read Swedish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you had one nuclear bomb and you HAD to drop it somewhere in the world, where would you drop it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 05:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 01:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YEEEEEEEEEEEEEROOOOOOOOOOOOOOH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you really pronounce Gyro? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 01:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 00:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it rather Strange that only 1 senator was not paid off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People who have helped out a real Nigerian Prince, what did he do to pay you back? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After the market downturn for student athlete memes, national social media account makes creative play; is there this market prime for a comeback? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but what if you asked it while married  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you heard the man don't blatantly insult women </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heartily second this, works every time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Don't freak out but-" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most hurtful insult anyone has ever used on you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to protect him, I grew up eating orange slices and not peeled oranges. Peeling is for tangerines smh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/wholesomememes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> she had it coming tbh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This wasn't one singular continuous irrational fear, but when I was about 6 or 7 years old, I once thought I woke up from a nightmare, and I looked over at my dresser, and there was a four foot tall dime that was leaned up against my dresser, and FDR was starting right at me with his stone cold, nickel plated eyes. Because I thought I had already woken up, this scared the absolute shit out of me and I was a sobbing inconsolable mess.

tl;dr: I was scared shitless by a four foot tall dime watching me while I slept. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 05:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> smh if they were gonna kill him off they might as well done it right and make his head explode </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 05:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Panty raid? You're talking about girls, right? Girl girls? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 05:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YOU ARE FAKE NEWS, WENDY'S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *OP ironically receives gold after calling out a gold advertisement* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 00:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> get yelled at for cookies

Welcome to marriage, man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I believe we have found a suitable Queen for our King Jaden Smith </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That last part about wife and girlfriend was redundant. It was already implied as soon as you said "Magic the gathering." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, we have literally the exact same list of cars here at my university </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's Sir Patrick Stewart to you, OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And crippling anxiety! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It may not be a very meaningful album, but Sremmlife. That thing is full of bangers, and here's not a bad song on there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations! You win! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To put my own input here, I've noticed that on every campus I've been on there are always these Asian nationals who walk around in packs, smoke a shit ton of cigarettes, wear super nice clothes, and drive absurdly nice sport/luxury cars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is one thing that EVERY college campus has? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was once at a concert, and a few high school acquaintances had walked over and we were talking to them. One of the girls we had just recently met at the concert asked if me and one of the high school acquaintances were dating, and she got this horrified look on her face, and with every ounce of pretentiousness in her body gave the most disgusted "*Nooo*" I had ever heard in my life. She, and she precisely, can go fuck right off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Chicago, you'll see a gun followed by "give me your wallet motherfucker" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too bad they freeze easily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should hear some of the other regional vocabulary we have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GUNS EAGLES MERICA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll have a chocolate watch, thank you very much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have any photo evidence </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 16:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun fact: Warren Buffett still lives in the home he raised his kids in, which he pays $13,000 in property taxes each year. With the Nebraska tax property tax rate sitting around 2%, that only values his house at $700k, despite being **the second richest man on earth** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 16:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *BREAKING: Angelina Jolie rumored to have adopted a penguin* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 16:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have any proof of Cena visiting these kids, like a picture or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 16:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have proof of him doing this? Like a picture of him with the kids? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 16:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gateway drug into...?

EDIT: Does OP now chew 5 packs a day? I MUST KNOW WHAT IT WAS A GATEWAY FOR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 07:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's what she said </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 02:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't get over how calm the CNN anchor is after a gun being fired just feet from him. Honestly, it's borderline sociopathic how little emotion there was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 02:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Day 1: the first day of the rest of our lives.*

*Well Diary, it's been a wild 24 hours, one filled with uncertainty, pain, and eventually uncontainable joy. Going into the day, I was still nervous as me and the hubby have yet to pick out a name, but after our experience with some of these innovative parenting books, we decided to wait until after the birth to choose the name, and simply choose whatever came to mind first.*

*Anyway, labor rolls around and I'm screaming in intolerable pain, and at that point, I frankly blacked out, and thank the lord I did. That pain was so excruciating, I couldn't have handled it one more second.*

*It took the rest of labor and then another 10 more minutes for me to recover, but the first thing I remember was opening my eyes, looking at the doctor and the contents in his hands, and being more certain of anything I had ever been. Despite many people thinking them to be ugly, I thought it was beautiful, the dark, smooth little nugget in his hands. At that moment, as I sat in admiration, I knew immediately what I would name the baby: it would be named after what lay in the doctors hands. *

*Welcome to the world sweet Placenta, your father and I love you.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 01:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry this may not get the attention it deserves because it came late, but this is fucking hilarious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 01:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *ahem*

We're looking at you r/CrohnsDisease  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 01:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This comes from another person who gets anxious while peeing in front of others, YOU CANT FORCE IT, IT ONLY MAKES IT WORSE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 01:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Percocet... Molly Percocet  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What once reliable brand has managed to maintain its reliability throughout its growth? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 01:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 01:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 7-11. They practically invented the word slushee, but after going into QuikTrip a bajillion times, I feel disgusted every time I walk into a 7-11. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know K-State fans are jealous about him and Oregon's coach making it, but this is too far, even for the fan base that regularly chants "Fuck KU" in non-KU games </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm sorry son, I don't drink Miller anymore. We're a Pabst Blue Ribbon household now." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Navalny found dead with gunshot wound in back of head* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 08:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *family gathers around*

"Guys, we need to have a talk. Your mother and I are getting a divorce," Mom #1 solemnly tells the family.

"What?"

"How?"

"But you guys haven't argued at all!"

"Is it my fault?"

"No honey, don't worry, it has nothing to do with you," Mom #2 replies.

"If it's not us, and you haven't been fighting, then why are you getting divorced?"

"Well honey, it's, it's-" Mom #1 chokes out before she begins to sob.

"-*it's for Reddit, honey*," Mom #2 finishes, as tears collect in her own eyes.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 01:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came here to look for tito's, was not disappointed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 22:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> City records indicate that Leite billed the city and was paid $103,504 between Nov. 7, 2014 and Sept. 21, 2015

Mom, dad, I'm becoming a plumber. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well he is a good dog </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 07:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [are you thinking about one person in particular](https://imgur.com/gallery/wvQXF)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 07:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Missouri is that wild card: no one knows what to expect, so no one really talks to him. Some say he's a pretentious asshole(St. Louis), some say he's a hardcore druggie (anywhere in Missouri), and some say he won't shut up about sports(KC). Regardless, most everyone forgets he's there and he just does his own thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 06:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kansas is that hick who drives the hopped up 1998 Chevy Silverado that has no muffler on it, and spends his days revving his engine in the parking lot making sure that everyone knows that he has a truck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 06:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found Becky </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 06:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Midwesterner here, the blue ones are cool too  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 06:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're so full of shit, both figuratively and literally </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 06:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or during shitting season, which last 365 days a year for them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 06:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plot twist: the cockroaches have continued their ridiculous evolutionary progress and now have learned how to use Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 00:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> relevant username </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 00:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the catch: you weren't a teenage boy, you were 11. What else are you hiding dodgingartfully? Where's the ark of gm he covenant? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 06:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/shittyaskhistory </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 06:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Popped My Cherry Gold

Another terrible crayon color name! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would a water gun made out of M M candy shell that shoots hot oil really work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 06:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 06:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Corn dog: first a tasty snack, then you sharpen the stick and you've got a shank.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *black screen at end triggers another episode of uncontrollable existentialist dread* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You won't look us in the eye just the same you won't look any of your problems, especially that haircut, in the eye </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, more like fappy disks, *amirite* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frankly, it was just something to do. I've been in a couple relationships where it's just dead end from the start, and I've re organized that there is very little chance of long term success, but I was just so bored with my life that I said screw it, and kept dating then anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FarmersOnly.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [well are you gonna do something](https://imgur.com/gallery/Z4w0C)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The other guy is probably straight too now after what you made him go through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Update: attempted to build full-scale jet engine, couldn't quite get it. 3/7 for this video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, he's just like my father.

*Too bold* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With so many questions being asked directly to the Police Officers of Reddit, what are some good stories the rest of you Redditors have about with your experience with Police Officers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With so many questions asked directly to the Police Officers of Reddit, are there any good stories that the rest of you Redditors have about an experience you've had with an Officer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 08:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 06:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the hell are you doing walking in the middle of the road </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 00:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next is shower orange.

After a long day, rip apart an orange and let its juices flow down you as you are in your fit of primal feeding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 22:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IMO the amount of neck tattoos is rather disturbing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In the days of Ancient Greece, did their stone tablets also have touch screens? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 22:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors who married one of your best friend's siblings, what was the story behind it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 22:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 07:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> congrats on the sex </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 07:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cooler full of Keystone and Pabst Blue Ribbon

FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 07:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/wholesomememes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 06:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Undoubtedly, the first thing to happen would be Kansans would run over the border and go shit on Missouri. They've had it coming for 160 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 06:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Answering this question for real, Texas would undoubtedly win. Not for obvious reason, but because there's only three power grids in the US: East, west, and Texas. With access to power, they would demolish everyone because of superior means of production. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 03:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wasn't this an episode of greys anatomy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Definitely the yellow. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 02:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I swear, she's got the mind of an adult!"

"YOU'RE SICK!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 18:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> COOL CATS DONT LOOK AT EXPLOSIONS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 09:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've driven through. It was so bad it was just depressing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this well actually the Grand Canyon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My flight to Arizona takes 50 minutes, but the one back takes 5 hours: why do they slow down so much on the way back? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THE DAY THE MUSIC DIED </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 07:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is going on snapchat, Facebook, Instagram

Welcome to Reddit, friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *something something nikolaus something something dues vult* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a thought: 

*The French are stupid.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
