<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3428</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 12:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /uj I have never seen people turn on a movie the way they turned on Avatar.  It is probably no worse than Batman V Superman, but people treat Avatar like it's cancer and BvS like an underated gem.

/rj  Nolan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 12:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> uj/ just started the Black Ops 3 campaign and there are so many new features that will have to be removed to make it WW2 again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hate cod. Where is my karma? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 12:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 09:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yousa could be sayin dat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya their were some other cool features, and with rising amounts of digital sales maybe Xbox was onto something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 01:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ON </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 01:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I please get some boots on the ground. Please God can I get some boots on the Ground!

In Geraldo's name, Amen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looks like meat's back on the menu, boys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have never been that into the single player of Call of Duty, but I did play through Advanced Warfare's campaign and it was pretty fun.  I hear Ininite Warfare has a good story, and I hear Black Ops 3 storyline is really crazy.  You should be fine playing any of them, and if you have an Xbox One you can play 2,3, World at War, Black Ops, and Black ops 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I might be one of the few people who actually likes the future games better than the BOOTS ON THE GROUND gameplay.  People kept on saying how every call of duty played to similarly to eachother and the second they changed it up, people hated it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 13:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Snyder's name, AMEN. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guess which one is winning boys? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 08:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These people are all prety crazy.  If Titanfall 2 had been made by Ininity Ward and been called Call of Duty Infinite Warfare people would have hated it.  I don't think they realize that a good game can be made in a future setting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE COD Sucks and can do nothing good!!!I!!II! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 22:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It has begun. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 07:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saitama's feats include being able to defeat virtually any enemy in a single punch and also being virtually indestructible. He is a comedy character.

lol wot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I litterally thought it was Mark in the thumbnail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is arguably the strongest of the three. Going by Dragon Ball Super anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 23:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am pretty sure the Dark side is like a corruption of the force.  Which means that balance isn't like a scale, but like a pool of water.  The light side is when the pool is calm(or balanced) and the dark side is when it is out of balance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 08:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want the gold
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Strange people trying to become a wizard: from 2009 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /ujLet me play as Hayden Christensen, or I am not buying it.

/rjLet me play as Hayden Christensen, or I am not buying it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 11:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /uj maybe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 00:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /uj  It is because most people thought that the prequals looked to much like video games, but that makes them a better fit for video games than the original trilogy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me show you an example.  There is a character who has defetead every enemy without showing his full power, but that character has only fought against ants.  Should we now consider his max power to be infinite? And if so why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't mean he has infinite strength. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saitama vs. Superman, Iron Man, Batman, and Captain America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: In character

Round 2: Bloodlusted

Location: Uninhabited planet the size of earth.

Inspired by [this](https://np.reddit.com/r/OnePunchMan/comments/63tdeo/disaster_level_saitama_by_woo_chul_lee/?sort=top) post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vs. debates don't take into account authorial intent, otherwise protagonists wouldn't lose to villains. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you think he wins simply because he is a joke? Why does that override feats? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a no limits fallacy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 02:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am sort of the inverse. Being a fan of Superman, it made me upset that Batman steals the show after he already had the Dark Knight Trilogy. The fact that Batman has to clearly win the fight with Superman because of Batman's extreme popularity. Even though I am not a fan of Batman, I didn't like how he became a killer either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 02:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also with losing Hans Zimmer I have lost more faith in the movie. Junkie XL might do a fine job, but I thought Hans Zimmer was one of DC's biggest strenghts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 01:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To each his own. I only kinda liked 300 and Man of Steel, but I hated Batman V Superman and thought the Justice League trailer wasn't up to snuff with trailers for his other movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zack Snyder's thoughts on superhero dialogue show why he might not be the best choice for Justice League. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 01:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 10:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I am going crazy. I have no idea why I thought Poe said it in Force Awakens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 09:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HEY! No sequel quoting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But he had just killed Ray in one hit before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 09:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We start at 530,290. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 09:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We start at 530,290. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I suggest new leadership is needed. Put the Senate on r/place </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 08:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
