<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject398</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 01:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will try this but it does sound strange. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 15:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saltine crackers and the butter dish for the dip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 01:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep got that one wrong twice. Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 01:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks and believe me I am too old and not senile enough to fall for these scams yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 01:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, bad planning on her behalf. But I've made mistakes in life and people have helped me out so I just continue to pay it forward. She is an artist and has been doing Workaway from Mexico to her present place. You would be impressed if you knew how little she travels with and how little it costs her. She is 58 and out there doing what I don't have the balls to do. When we were in El Salvador staying at the same place for 6 weeks I once bought her tooth paste (the small one, she didn't want o carry a big one) And gave her $20 US you would have thought I gave her the world. She is proud and stubborn. She has never ask and that is all I gave. She is doing what so many want to do but like me are afraid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 00:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they're </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 00:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conversation has been exchanged that verifies her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 00:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a scam, a friend with many mutual friends. I can't believe how many people think something is up. This is sort of disheartening for me. I guess she is on the street for the night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 00:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I offered. I like helping people live there dream. She has turned it down many times until now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 00:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She has support from home but cannot connect with her father right now. I know her well enough and we're only talking $20-30 here. Just a couple nights in a hostel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 00:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am sure it is her. I helped her out in El Salvador and have told her a number of times if she gets into a pinch I would be glad to help again. She has never asked, I have always offered and now she needs a hand up. I can also tell it is her by her broken English.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need to get some money to a traveling friend, now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 00:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made a friend while traveling and have kept in touch through Facebook. She is out of the long haul on very little funds. Right now she is in Cuenca, Ecuador and in dire need of a few dollars. I tried Xoom earlier today but the bank there would not accept her passport as proof  and told her Xoom was only for locals. She hasn't made friends with any locals yet so can't use that route of sending it through a third party. How can I get some money to her quickly. I am from the states she is Russian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 16:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This brought tears to my eyes just thinking about
it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 15:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Locks only keep honest people honest anyways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 04:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I understand, you are looking for salespeople to give children a "sample" lesson and then close the sale. Am I correct? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 23:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to run an automatic circumcision machine at the hospital. Didn't pay much but there were a lot of tips and a chance to get a head.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 15:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree! Came here to say this. I HATE when people try to make "it" better when I have my expectations set on the non-fancy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 04:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> El Salvador for me. One bite of undercooked pork and 3 days later I was wishing I would just die and get it over with. My local friends laughingly say "You got the amoeba." go get me some pills. Two days later I'm good as new. That is how I learned about Mebendazol. Now when I travel I take a low does almost every day. No more problems even with others going down from eating the same foods as me.
Edit: words and stuff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 03:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a skunk that pays visits to my backyard every summer for a few years now. I know it's the same skunk because if the windows are open he can wake you up at night with your eyes watering he stinks so bad. I believe he has a damaged butt sprayer and get himself when he sprays. Also, I have a dog (you know what they say about skunks and dogs, there are two kinds of dogs the ones that learn on the first spray and the ones that never learn). I have the later and this skunk fellow will spray the old fat bastard but never gets a good direct hit. It has happened at least 3 time over the years. A bath with a little peroxide and Dawn dish liquid and the smell is faint and dissipates in a few days. Peroxide to open the cuticle of the fur/hair and Dawn to wash the oily residue away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 03:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a pet one in the 60s, yep, always had a musty smell if you didn't keep him clean. I think it was the urine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 21:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrong, chlorine over time will lighten your hair. Copper sulfite is what turns your hair green in most pools. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 16:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but I do everytime I poop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How far can you walk into the forest? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 12:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Halfway, then you're walking out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 15:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP, I see you are using this post to harvest email addresses. What is your current hussle you are/will be using these for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
