<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3065</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you buy a developing kit or did you piece the stuff together?  Also did you scan it yourself? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sir, your down votes prove your point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm gonna start a foundation to help homeless children" Ned Nederlander </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sucks when pets die.  Maybe you should get a parrot next time, a Kakapo can live for 95 years! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been surfing porn for years and never ran across some shit like that.  Don't want to either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joined the military, learned a good trade, met the love of my life, traveled the world, retired and getting paid for the rest of my life! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually quit drinking for a while until I got stationed in Germany.  I had never had wheat beer before and it was awesome!  Now I'm back in the states and German beer is expensive here, it was so cheap over there for the same brands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't say anything.  Any time this person tries to get into the conversation slowly work you way between that person and the rest of your friends.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I learned that day how to play cool and not let somebody fuck with me, which is what he was trying to do.  In the end he got the message I didn't want any trouble but I wasnt scared of his ass either.  I rode the bus several times after that and didn't have anymore problems.  It was on grey hound between Louisville and Chicago I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A person traveling by bus definitely gets to meet all kinds of people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The hardest part for me is realizing I'm in a downward spiral.  Sometimes I won't notice for days.  By that time I'm feeling like crap and really don't care to change my mood but then after a while I'll get sick of being in a shitty place and do things to change it.  I remind myself that I have won the lottery of life!  White American male with a loving wife and kids, what else can you ask for?  Also exercise really helps me from starting the spiral to begin with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was 19 at the time and riding the bus...Had a big black guy try to intimidate me into giving him my shoes.  I was able use humor to get out of the situation...But I also had a big ass knife in my pocket for back up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I visited part of the Verdun battlefield.  There were two occasions where I got the heebeegeebees, first place I was out in the forest where part of the battle had taken place.  I found some old period correct ruins of a large building and was checking it out when I heard distant voices talking.  It was probably some other people out walking the trails but it was time for me to move on.  The second time I was inside Fort Duaumont walking down the empty hallways all alone.  I came to an area that had exploded and killed several German soldiers who had been occupying the fort.  The atmosphere of the entire place and the echoing sounds of dripping water and muted voices from other tourists who were in other areas was haunting.  Unfortunately I didn't have time to, or better yet, didn't want to stop and see the ossuary after being in the fort.  I had enough for one day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is true.  I was stationed in Germany for 4 years and toured WWI and WWII battlefields, went to the Ann Frank House.  I'm a history buff and seeing all this stuff was fun.  I didn't want to go visit the concentration camps because that would not have been fun and I have seen plenty of documentaries on the subject. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before you buy a bike make sure you are getting the right size.  I don't know anything about either bike but can you find a used bike where you live?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like riding a jackhammer if you do it wrong!  Good ole taint buster lol! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started riding back in 97 on a rigid GT Outpost, fully rigid with the crappy old cable brakes not the fancy V brakes.  Anyway, I learned how to pick the smooth line (or suffer the consequences) and I've been told on several occasions that I ama very fluid rider.  Then I stepped up to a Cannondale with 80mm of front suspension travel and a seatpost shock absorber.  Eventually I went FS but I do miss how well you can climb on a hard tail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started riding back in 97 on a rigid GT Outpost, fully rigid with the crappy old cable brakes not the fancy V brakes.  Anyway, I learned how to pick the smooth line (or suffer the consequences) and I've been told on several occasions that I ama very fluid rider.  Then I stepped up to a Cannondale with 80mm of front suspension travel and a seatpost shock absorber.  Eventually I went FS but I do miss how well you can climb on a hard tail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $10-$20 tops...Nobody is going to use it, just hang on a wall </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yea, forgot to check the sidebar...Lots of great info in there thanks for reminding me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heck yea!  I got a Minolta Srt 101 off eBay for $35 and a sweet 50mm 1.4 lens for around $25.  The camera was made in the late 60's and it still works great!  A roll of film costs around $12 and another $13 to develop...so $25 a roll all together which works out to .70 per shot.  A new Sony a3000 costs around $600...that's 857 shots on film.  I shoot landscape and I don't take the shot unless the conditions are just right so it's going to take me a long time to burn through that much film.  If that makes sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the link! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My local processor wants $25 a roll...Will definitely mail it out!  Thanks for the tip! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently shooting 35mm and have been looking at medium format cameras because of the better resolution for making large prints.  I'm tired of digital cameras, they break easily and cost a ton of money.  Then you have to mess around in Photoshop for hours on end to make it look close to what you want.  I've got an old Minolta Srt 101 that works great and was made in the late 60's and film comes out looking good with no fuss...call me old fashioned.  Where is a good place to mail film to get developed?  I'm near Ft Worth TX  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok thanks for the reply!  Glad to hear it's not dead yet.  I like to do landscape and used to get good results with Fuji velvia a long time ago.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Slide film question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking about getting back to shooting some slide film and my local film processor is telling me they have discontinued making the development chemicals necessary for the E6 process.  Is this true?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 455 BC, Aeschylus, the great playwriter known as the Father of Greek Tragedy, died in a most unexpected way. He was said to have been killed by a tortoise which was dropped by an eagle that had mistaken his head for a rock suitable for shattering the shell of the reptile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been riding trails for 20 years...Never needed either one.  I could see where you would need one if you were doing a lot of down hill.  Do you currently have a problem with your chain popping off or bending you chainring on rocks or something?  If not then I wouldn't worry about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or you can get a good deal on last year's model at the bike shop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it's fine like it is.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 06:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the law here in Texas but nobody cares...Germans are all about following the rules </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 05:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lived in Germany for 4 years and saw the light.  It's awesome when everyone does it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When passing a car on the highway I GET THE FUCK BACK IN THE RIGHT LANE so others can pass me if they want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This site has some other products made by the same company with possible dates of manufacture.  The first pic of the bench grinder on the site was made in 1952 and the companies name has already been changed from what you have which suggests your drill was made before 1952.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok thank you, just making sure I wasn't smoking crack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you just called Americans gay!  Well guess what?  Canadians are gay by association! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most definitely!  Probably want to make a new acct for that though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whatever man, it's a free country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would take my wife to Diego Garcia and live on the abandoned side of the island in the old coconut plantation house.  Civilians are not allowed on the island unless contracted by the military. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> High end drug dealer...Literally take out the competition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The old guys from Muppet show were the best! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I second the slut part!  You can start by posting to r/gonewild </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $83k...I fix trains and also collect military retirement from my previous life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There you go </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chicken fried steak smothered with white gravy and mashed potatoes on the side also with gravy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> German bratwurst is way better than the Johnsonville "bratwurst" we have in the US.  I really like your fleischcasse mit brotchen und mustard from the Globus store! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol he was a baby in his crib when I was in my Slayer and Napalm Death phase. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> World war I was still in full swing so probably a bullet proof set of body armor...Or an A-10 Warthog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure they're not straight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the study found that the participants VO2 max increased by 4.126.0 points?  Is the +/-6.0 the error factor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone have any ideas about the temperature spike? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lived in Shreveport when hurricane Katrina hit.  We had a massive influx of people into the area and we saw first hand the effects of the migrating population.  We called them Katrina people because we noticed how all of the stores were trashed out after they showed up.  The locals resented them and the refugees acted like they were entitled to more than they were provided with by the government.  It was a bad situation all around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I Flew for the Furher is a good read.  It's from one of their fighter pilots.  https://www.amazon.com/dp/B06XGR2BCX/ref=dp-kindle-redirect?_encoding=UTF8 btkr=1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 06:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a good reason to upvote, never really thought of it that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 06:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because of decreased activity.  You need to burn more calories than you consume. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 06:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has to be good for me to upvote.  I make lots of comments though.  I'm more interested in making conversation than casting meaningless votes that have no real purpose besides karma whoring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you still there?  I'm at work and need to pass the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dropped the Mother Of All Shits MOAS bomb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They already know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People driving slow in the fast lane and not moving over after they pass someone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had this guy that worked for me in the military.  Everyone knows not to be late or its your ass.  This guy was an awesome worker, never had to worry if he was gonna get his shit done.  He came in late a few times and couldn't explain why he couldn't wake up.  Said he woke up with head aches and felt tired all the time.  I had heard of sleep apnea and it sounded like he might have it.  I told him to go get checked out and that was his problem.  They gave him the mask to sleep with and he wasn't late again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 02:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not scared but thought it was a fart...Recently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 02:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going outside to play.  I grew up in the country out in the woods and the neighbor kids would all come over to play with me and my brothers.  We would take the dog and go bird hunting with our pellet guns or shotgun.  Have sniper shot contests.  Build forts and play war.  Put on our camo and face paint then go on recon patrols to the neighbors house.  Kill frogs in every imaginable way...Yes we had fire crackers and an electricity generator.  Catch snakes and have the dog kill them.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 02:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Chinga tu madre" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 02:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I put it as far back as it goes and stretch my legs out under the person's seat in front of me.  Sometimes I have to kick their under seat bag over to one side but they don't even know.  I also stuff their seat back pocket with my stuff and constantly raise and lower my tray.  If it's dark I'll turn on MY light so I can read my book.  If my neighbor is not using their air I'll steal it by pointing it at myself when they aren't looking.  Sometimes I quietly let a fart slip and fan it away.  I always get a window seat and never offer to trade to anyone.  I ask for extra drinks when mine runs out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 02:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think 60 FPS is the upper limit that we can process.  TV's are 60 FPS.  Less than 60 things look choppy and any more than that you can't tell the difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 02:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And light switches </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 02:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or stay and bang. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 02:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My grandfather grew up during the depression and he told me that it's not what you want to do in life, it's what you can do.  That's all he said but I take it to mean that not everyone is meant to be a doctor or a lawyer or even go to college.  It's more about seeing the opportunities around you and acting upon them.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking more along the lines of our own citizens killing each other.  Such as the gang related attitude of "getting mine" by selling drugs and controlling their part of the market. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget about fracking!  That really knocked the bottom out of gas prices and broke the choke hold OPEC had on us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So efficient that we have them killing each other! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We didn't really see them too much until KFC started marketing the idea.  I know they were around before then but KFC brought them into popular culture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa there buddy, I eat the aforementioned food items on a regular basis and I am not suffering the effects of diabetes or obesity.  Maybe you are eating too much?  Next time don't get the super size shake and maybe go with the kid size.  It's about the amount of calories you consume and hence burn.  Ideally to lose weight you intake less calories than you use in one day.  Conversely, to gain weight you of course eat more than you burn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's because you bring them free refills.  It cost the price of another one to refill in Germany. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I always envision myself there when telling a story.  You have to describe the location first then explain the action happening as if you and the person that you are telling are there right now.  Put them in the moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 17:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you turn this into a Trump bash?  It's a guy making moon shine.  Take that shit to r/politics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 17:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Canada is my second favorite country! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 08:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are at the center of the observable universe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 05:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't have a BEST friend in highschool.  Allen smoked meth and still lives with his mom.  Talked Nick out of suicide and now he's a truck driver.  Rich went to jail for selling drugs, got out and joined the Army then got medical discharge.  Rudy married Mindy (the hot girl).  Never seen Bill again, heard he got some kids.  Mike got new teeth and he is a truck driver.  Craig inherited the grocery store when his dad died, still smokes weed 3 times a day.  Different Nick molested his step daughter and got caught.  Dennis is still in prison 20 years later.  Jason works with my brother at the factory.  Different Dennis joined the Marines (he wasn't my friend though).  Todd finally got married to a bleeding heart liberal.  Chucky is still a retard.  Different Jason works at a shell station.  As you can see my friends were fuck ups, that's why I joined the Air Force and got the fuck out of there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok then, yes, North Korea is causing the power outages with their cyber weapons.  Are you happy now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sanfrancisco was caused by a faulty circuit breaker which caused a fire at the substation.  I'm an electrician and sometimes circuit breakers fail.  Highly unlikely NK had anything to do with this.  They would have to get a person inside to tamper with the CB.

https://www.google.com/amp/sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2017/04/21/power-outage-shuts-down-barts-montgomery-station/amp/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What power outages? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea that is strange how China has an appendage between Russia and NK.  Thanks for posting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe made by a company called Tramontina?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First time I've really ever heard about space law.  My first question, are there space lawyers?  Turns out there are in fact space lawyers.  Not sure about the space prison yet... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been seeing a lot more sexy nerd girls with glasses...It didn't used to be that much of a thing until fairly recently.  Amber Hahn as an example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would be nice to just hop on a plane and go where ever you want when ever you wanted to, for free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would never go to work again!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try deleting your cookies, it might stop it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing.  They have to experience it for themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really?  I've been to the gym several times (military for 20 years) and never felt as if I were cumming.  If that were the case I'd be ripped!  Please tell me you are joking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last I heard, Snowden is still guilty and will be imprisoned if he ever comes back to the states. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 04:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still guilty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 05:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ideally, NK hands over their nuke program and let's UN inspectors in to verify.  If they do this, China has their back again and the US has no reason to press the issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 02:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the xl12 chainsaw and it's awesome!  Paid $20 at an auction for it and only had to replace a gas line.  I want one of those circular saws!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 13:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, yes it does make him guilty and he knows it, that's why he can't come back because he will be prosecuted.  It's fairly obvious that you are the one trying too hard by creating your parody account that's only one day old and trolling people with your BS.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 04:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean YOUR parody account that is only one day old?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 04:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So that's why they are letting him back and all is forgiven?  Oh wait, he can't because he would be imprisoned...because he is guilty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you saying he is not a traitor guilty of treason?  Myself and a House Intellegence Committee beg to differ.  https://www.google.com/amp/amp.nationalreview.com/article/440113/edward-snowden-report-house-intelligence-committee-not-pardon  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is Ed's attempt to stay relevant, he's played out his hand but still trying to stay in the limelight in order to not be forgotten.  Go Ed go...Traitor! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
