<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3535</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoilers] Your opinions on the new Superman continuity? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 18:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just read Action Comics #978 and I really like the retconned continuity. I like what I think is a 70-30 split between pre N52 and post N52 continuity as well as the reasoning for how the N52 stuff (the armor for example) fits in with the pre N52 stuff.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 17:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he landed in the middle of Chicago and was fished out of lake Michigan, he'd probably be like his grant Morrison version from the New 52. Not as much of a boy scout, probably would not wear his traditional costume, and would have the 'stand up for the little guy' mentality he had back in 2011. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 16:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the warning. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 06:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone clarify this for me: I remember asking in thread a few months about transferring to the 75th Ranger Regiment as an MI officer and was told that the 75th had a program specific for those in the MI MOS. Is/was this a real thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 04:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One other leader I forgot to mention is Robert E. Lee. I feel like he either gets overlooked or a bad rep on account of the side he was on during the Civil War, but I think he was a much better officer and overall leader than Grant (and this is coming from someone who's half  African American) especially in regards to his dedication to his men. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 00:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the book on Travis Manion and Brandon Looney, right? I picked it up in a Barnes and Noble a year ago. I liked the sentiment, but the writing wasn't the best and it kinda distracted me from getting into it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 18:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sean Parnell, right? I got as a birthday gift in high school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 17:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the correction. I've only ever known Machiavelli to associated with politics so I just figured he was a politician at some point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 17:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a commandant back in high school who used that phrase when talking with the senior cadets that were in leadership positions, but I never knew it was from a book. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 16:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its by Pete Blaber, and you're right, the advice in it is excellent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 16:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Machiavelli was probably the most cutthroat political figure to ever live. Why would someone looking to become an O want to study him, especially since being political can be considered a negative trait for Officers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 16:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. I'd heard about Gary O'Neil, but never paid any attention to him because I thought his stories were too wild to be true, but if its legit, then I'll definitely check it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 09:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would second the first point, which is why I loved Deriliction of Duty by H.R. McMaster. I think in regards to leadership studies, it's important to learn from what not to do as much as what to do. That's why someone like Herbert Sobel is such an interesting case to look at.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 08:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the recommendations. I hadn't payed much attention to the Liberations trilogy, and I already own a copy of Horse Soldiers, but I haven't the time to read it. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 08:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are there any books the focus on McChrystal's leadership? I've only seen The Operators. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any leaders you'd recommend studying? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 07:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are there any leaders, both military and non-military, that you guys would recommend someone looking to become an officer should study as examples of what to and not to do? Recently, I've reading up on the leadership styles and actions of both Dick Winters and Hal Moore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any leaders you would recommend studying? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 07:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are there any leaders, both military and non-military, that you guys would recommend someone looking to become an officer should study as examples of what to and not to do? Recently, I've reading up on the leadership styles and actions of both Dick Winters and Hal Moore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 05:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently in my sophomore year of college going into my junior year this fall with the intent of applying for OCS soon before or after graduating. However, I'm unsure about how to go about it. Are there specific recruiters for OCS, and if so, how do you contact them? Also, what would be the best time to contact a recruiter about OCS? 

Also, one of my goals is to eventually apply to SFAS and become an 18A. What would be the best way to go about achieving that in terms of MOS branching, schools to attend ect.? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that some Canadian police officers would punish drink drivers by playing Nickleback in their cruisers once they were arrested </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 04:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 03:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting point of view. How would there not be enough content? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [COD] What would you guys like to see in a Vietnam set COD? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 18:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aside from WWII, a COD set during Vietnam is very high in demand. If either IW or Treyarch sets the next COD in Vietnam, what would guys like to see in it in regards to story, characters, multiplayer modes, events you'd like to play through, stuff that BO1 touched on that you'd like to see continue? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [COD] COD:WWII and historical accuracy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 18:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 14:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully, they don't throw the baby out with the bathwater and get rid of everything from Andromeda, as a lot of the mechanics and ideas were good, but just needed to be tweaked and polished. I liked the idea of opening up the environment, but not to the extent to where its a full scale, GTA type of open world. If a middle ground can be found where we get worlds filled with content but are open enough for legitimate exploration, then I'm ok with that. 

Also, given the current state they are in, I doubt Bioware would put all of their story related content behind a pay wall.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 13:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying that DLC will be delayed or outright stopped, but I was thinking that since there isn't going to be an immediate sequel that they would try to close any remaining storylines with DLC, something the team at Bioware probably didn't plan on initially.  

And by "soft reboot", I meant a shift in direction back to the OT, hence the term "soft", not a full restart of the franchise, but slight change in tone and direction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 13:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't trying to. Just trying to get my thoughts out there and see what others think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ME:A Spoilers] How will the recent news about Bioware affect future DLC/next installment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 13:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the news that Bioware has put the ME franchise on hiatus, its got me wondering how will this change the content of future DLC as well as what the next installment would look like. 

In terms of DLC, since we're not going to get a sequel to Andromeda any time soon, will the content be changed in any way in order to wrap up the remaining storylines. I think we might get expansions that are along the lines of trespasser that cover things like [Spoiler](the Quarian ark, the benefactor etc.) 

In the long term, its probably too soon to guess where the franchise is heading, but I wouldn't be surprised if Bioware decides to have a sort of soft reboot of the franchise in order to, similar to what Call of Duty is trying to do with WWII, take Mass Effect back to its roots.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 06:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could see the Reapers intending to invade but are wiped out by the Phoenix Force in dark space, and the Milky Way has to contend with a Phoenix invasion. 

Or what if instead of the crucible, the only way to stop the reapers was to track down the phoenix force and have it inhabit one of Shepard's crew. 

I could also see Apocalypse using Protean technology as opposed to Celestial like in the comics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers]What if the X-Men were integrated into the ME universe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got the idea for this from a combination of two posts I made the other day. I know the ME universe has something similar to mutants in the form of biotics, but for the most part, biotics have been accepted by the ME universe. Would the same thing apply for mutants, and how would the rest of the galaxy treat the Alliance when they have access to people like mutants?

Also, what other superhero/villain teams would you want to integrate into the ME universe?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And neither does the Council, unlike the Federation who always seems to let whatever the Romulans did slide. I could totally see a Cold War scenario breaking out between the two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Liara is the Broker 

Wrex is the Warlord 

Grunt could easily be his Superhero name

Jacob is the Priiiiiizzzzee 

Ashley and or Kaiden could also be called the Spectre since they're the only other ones with Spectre status 

Miranda is The Cheerleader 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While SE empire may be riskier, can you tell a point in the last few years where Cap hasn't been altered in some way, shape, or form. If he's not getting aged in Dimension Z, he's getting his mind wiped in Hickman's Avengers, getting the Super Soldier Serum drained out of him in Rick Remender's run, being old man Steve for however long, and then finally having reality be rewritten to where he was Hydra all along. And even before that, he's gotten Assassinated post Civil War, became a wanted fugitive during Civil War, and after all that he gave up the shield to Bucky. 

The point i'm trying to make is that Cap's been in a constant state of change since 2006, and while change is key to good character growth, Steve hasn't been Cap for any extended period of time without some kind of circumstance effecting him or going to effect him. I would like to see them play it safe for once and just let Cap be Cap.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a matter of opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would they replace element zero as the source for biotics or are you bringing the force to the ME universe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A krogan developing a Salarian and Turian specific genophage is such a good idea, I'm kind of disappointed it never happened in the OT. 

A Hydra designed Cerberus would have been the ideal portrayal of them. Can you imagine the Citadel attack resembling the Hydra takeover from Winter Soldier? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I appreciate someone arguing for the other side, I would have to disagree. Captain America can be a reflection of the times, but he should still remain true to the concepts and ideals at his core, the best of  American ideas and values, and in turbulent political times, Cap should be there as a reminder of what we strive for as a nation. The biggest mistake of Secret Empire is just that. It compromises the core of Steve Rogers just make a political statement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Just one big yes. I love the John Carter Of Mars series, and Would love to have a 4 armed Green Martian squadmate, holding a weapon with each set of arms, with me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The key word in your post being "versions". Like I said in the OP, you could draw a comparison between Secret Empire and Superman in the Injustice universe, but the big difference being that Injustice Superman was an alternate version and was not being sold as the Superman of the main continuity, unlike Cap.

Furthermore, I don't think the huff and puff over this is entirely unjustified. It goes without saying that Cap represents a lot of things to a lot of people and to see him betray those things and the ideals he stood for struck a cord with people, not to mention they feel like there's an unnecessary political message in what's going on with Cap.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amen to that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What DC Rebirth Superman can teach Marvel and Captain America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before I began, let me preface this post by saying that the purpose of this post is not to start some kind of flame war in the comments, nor am I trying to belittle Marvel. Captain America is a character that means a lot to me personally and Rebirth Superman is my favorite thing going on in comics right now, and I think there's a lot Marvel can learn from what DC is doing right now, particularly with Superman, going forward.
 
Now with that being said...

I've always been a believer in the fact that every comics universe should have a sort of 'gold standard', someone that sets the example for what it means to be a hero in that particular universe. The character of Captain America has been among one of my biggest influences during not only during my teenage years, but also recently as I've become an adult and am making my way through college. Whenever I've had trouble figuring out the right thing in a situation or have trouble with adversity, I've always looked to Cap's example to help figure out a solution. Recently, however, I feel like Superman is beginning to take that slot. 

With what's been going on leading up to and during Secret Empire, Marvel has essentially compromised their gold standard. And while yes, almost nothing in comics has that much of an impact and everything will probably go back to the way things were in a few months and,that a parallel can be drawn between what's happening with Cap and what DC did/is doing with Superman in the Injustice series, but DC didn't make the Superman in Injustice the Superman of the main continuity, unlike Marvel warping the fabric of the MU in order to justify the change with Cap.

With Rebirth, DC has managed to give readers fun, refreshing, interesting stories for Superman without changing the core of who he is. With Marvel Legacy, which is looking to become their answer to Rebirth, coming up in the fall, I hope Marvel learns that a character doesn't have to be fundamentally changed in order to have interesting stories.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a fair point and while I'm not the biggest fan of it, I will give Marvel credit for going as far as they are with Secret Empire and Hydra Cap. At some point though, you have to go back to Cap being the gold standard, and when they do, I hope Marvel looks to DC and Supes for influence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last part would have been amazing, especially with David Tennent or Matt Smith's Doctor. I could see just a handful of Time Lords wipe out the entirety of the Reapers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can have Steve go through adversity without having him do a complete 180 character wise. 

And just out of curiosity, what about Rebirth is pandering or boring? Not trying to start anything, its just that I haven't heard anyone have that opinion about Rebirth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. The same can be said for Cyclopes as well. Bring back the first X-Man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who's to say that won't be the case in Legacy. Remember the basis of Supes current continuity started out as Lois and Clark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly, so why can't Marvel do it for Cap? I hope Marvel pays close attention to the success DC is having with Supes and applies the lessons learned to future Cap books.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have loved to have orbited Endor and found out that the Ewoks have held off the Reapers that same way they did the Empire in ROTJ.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely agree. As a matter of fact, I think Akksul and the Rokaer should have been the primary antagonists with the Kett being the Reaper level threat looming on the horizon. I think the Rokaer would have been a more sympathetic and complex group of enemies with motivations we can understand (defending your home from invaders from outer space is the basis for most modern science fiction)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Rebirth era Superman can teach Marvel and Captain America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before I began, let me preface this post by saying that the purpose of this post is not to start some kind of flame war in the comments, nor am I trying to belittle Marvel. Captain America is a character that means a lot to me personally and Rebirth Superman is my favorite thing going on in comics right now, and I think there's a lot Marvel can learn from what DC is doing right now, particularly with Superman, going forward.
 
Now with that being said...

I've always been a believer in the fact that every comics universe should have a sort of 'gold standard', someone that sets the example for what it means to be a hero in that particular universe. The character of Captain America has been among one of my biggest influences during not only during my teenage years, but also recently as I've become an adult and am making my way through college. Whenever I've had trouble figuring out the right thing in a situation or have trouble with adversity, I've always looked to Cap's example to help figure out a solution. Recently, however, I feel like Superman is beginning to take that slot. 

With what's been going on leading up to and during Secret Empire, Marvel has essentially compromised their gold standard. And while yes, almost nothing in comics has that much of an impact and everything will probably go back to the way things were in a few months and,that a parallel can be drawn between what's happening with Cap and what DC did/is doing with Superman in the Injustice series, but DC didn't make the Superman in Injustice the Superman of the main continuity, unlike Marvel warping the fabric of the MU in order to justify the change with Cap.

With Rebirth, DC has managed to give readers fun, refreshing, interesting stories for Superman without changing the core of who he is. With Marvel Legacy, which is looking to become their answer to Rebirth, coming up in the fall, I hope Marvel learns that a character doesn't have to be fundamentally changed in order to have interesting stories.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] Comic book fans in the sub, what comic book concept/organization would you want to see in the ME universe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any comic fans in the sub,what comic book idea/concept/organization would you want to see in the ME universe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few of the other races I would want to see are: 

1. The necromorphs from Dead Space: Imagine a marker being brought to Omega, the Nexus, or the Citadel. 

2. The Skrulls from Marvel: This technically counts as another Sci-Fi franchise I think, but I would love to see a the Skrulls infiltrate the citadel council and the Spectres ala the Secret Invasion event from Marvel

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I want Liam to be replaced by Wookiee now. Don't care how BW does it, I just want a badass Wookiee partner riding around exploring Andromeda with me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, man. The Scholastic book orders. My friends and I would have an entire trade network based on what we got from those pamphlets. The cool spy toys had the highest value, sci fi/fantasy books were second, books for girls were last. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
