<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3415</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 13:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean you can always just Snapchat then your ass cheeks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 13:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but they don't have the swan police to come along and lock them up for 5 years for public indecency </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 13:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They certainly are but it doesn't change the fact that more violent crime is perpetuated by the black community. I'm not saying that as my opinion it's true. 

People in the system are racist but the system itself isn't. You can post articles like this that I half agree with all day long but the reason more black people get arrested is once again...they commit more violent crime.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 13:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to statistics you are. 

Then again that isn't what I was arguing. 

I'm pointing out that besides the racial prejudice shown by some government officials and officers it's a fact that the black community commits more crime and not because their arrests are higher but because they in fact commit more murder, assault, abuse, etc whatever it is the crime stats are there. 

Now I don't think skin color should play a role in how punishment is doled out but it's ignorant to think that the only reason there are more black people arrested is because the system is racist. The people in the system are racist and black people happen to commit more violent crime. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 12:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They upped the jump scares. They had a director who wanted to honor the book but he was replaced with a more "Hollywood friendly" director because they didn't think the original script for the reboot would make money it was considered too psychological. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 11:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget it's 8-bit with an all new shitty track by some artist you've never heard of.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 11:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you less likely to be arrested for drug offense because you're white or because you participate less in crime?

I understand there are many attitudes towards certain communities but one undeniable fact is the crazy high crime rate in areas populated by black people. 

Is it because cops just arrest them more OR is it because they actually do commit more crime? Having lived in the hood I'd say it's the latter. Being black is one thing but slinging crack is another. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 00:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happened to me, sniff, whole nine yards, dog gave no indicators and yet they insisted I had a "roach" in my backseat and when I told them I didn't they all began to yell and scream at me like in those videos where you get shot. Scared the piss out of me and I haven't trusted police since. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 22:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Twice is way too much? :3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm learning so much today, we're all calling three or four different things the same thing and we're all like "No you're wrong!" hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dead Island </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Daddy_longlegs

You're right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Explain clock overflow in 2038. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Daddy Long legs aren't spiders they are a species known as harvesters you'll find they only have one ~~two~~ body segments as opposed to a spiders ~~three~~ two.

Edit: I guess a lot of people believed this fake fact too, lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's not kid ourselves, anyone who seriously prescribes to any religion has to be truly ignorant on some level. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The work ethic of the older generation was fueled by the fact if you didn't work your ass off you were likely to die.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see, so it came from behind the monitor, hit the Anthology that your monitor was propped/on top of, stopping it before it would of entered your chest? 

Well damn lucky you. 

Did you get to keep the bullet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really, he said the bullet hole was to the left of his monitor. He makes it obvious it came from the left side. The bullet came near him but it hitting the game did nothing to "save his life" that is just a click bait title. 

It'd be more interesting and truthful if OP's title was "A bullet hit this man's Elder Scroll game through the wall!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/d3puns/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 05:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I want to ban a specific type of post. I think it's silly we see the same "Rare with a pun name." post every day. It's low effort and adds nothing to the sub-reddit. 

Fluff has it's place and it's purpose but this kind of fluff sucks. If we banned things or posts I didn't like there would be a lot more banned than just sub-par puns, this isn't about my personal likes and dislikes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Popped up in my "People you may know!" feed. Um...no... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks like OE.Cake with a tank, not truly innovative but really interesting at the same.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be rather odd if the constant loot grind was actually canon. 


"And then the Nephalem found the exact same piece of armor, except this one was shinier and slightly less dented!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must not be reading my message correctly. 

I don't want it banned because I don't like it...if we banned things I didn't like we would barely have Reddit at all lol.

I think it shouldn't be allowed because it's a low effort post copying a joke that has been told a thousand times already. That's my reasoning, don't put words in my posts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? Because I have an opinion? 

I don't think it's funny, it's super low effort, and gets upvoted to the top every time. It's old, it's done, I've seen it a thousand times. 

It's my opinion and that is all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know people come here to discuss Diablo, did I ever say they didn't?

And I never specified what kind of posts should be posted only a particular one I think shouldn't be allowed because it gets posted every day and the joke is old.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how you think me disagreeing with the general consensus is me being condescending. I'm perfectly chill, I just literally think this is low effort posting and shouldn't be allowed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I wouldn't and I stand by my statement. 

Repetitive jokes and meme culture are not my bag and I think they are low effort jokes. 

It's cool when you're with friends but to log in to Reddit every day and see a slightly different variation of the same fucking joke over and over again is ridiculous. 

The community may not agree with me but I think it's lower than low effort and should not be allowed. It's like reposting but worse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This joke has been around since vanilla...can we ban it already?

I don't look forward to my daily "Haha this Rare has a name I can make a pun into!"

"Guys, have you seen my ultra rare The Ring?" HAHAHAAHAHA SO FUCKING FUNNY.

I swear man... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I don't understand is how come with have this law but it doesn't concern everything unprovable. 

I understand people have deep religious feelings on the subject but these feelings are comparable to people who see ghosts, aliens, the future, etc. 

This is like making a law where you're not allowed to make fun of someone's imaginary friend because it might hurt their little feelings. 

Guess what? Everything points to god/gods not being real, we're not being mean we're being realistic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 14:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're going to get a game tattoo make sure it looks good and is simple...you did it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 05:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yo honey done used a load of honey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A close up would of shown you have fake this is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are many things that can't be proven to be true and the general rule of thumb is to not believe them without sufficient evidence to do so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm dumb I thought you meant you were winning each match in under four minutes I was like damn this dude must really be something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
