<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3093</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 00:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UPDATE:

http://imgur.com/Pw1yADn

Ugh how fake can he be!? His tweet of praise is STILL up  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spoiler :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was with you all the way until the last sentence :l </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how she thinks morality   legality are the same thing #SoDeep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think she thinks "mentality" means mental state  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 09:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He refuses counseling... :/

He's told me he's feeling really dysphoric,   that the lack of sex is making it worse (?)

but I can't get myself to give him only that aspect of things...I feel zero sexual attraction to anyone ever without the emotional aspect being tended to first   foremost ya know? :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ftm boyfriend   emotional changes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 07:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My boyfriend   I have been together since September, though I've known him for years. We met as "lesbians", though he's been on T over a year now   I fully recognize/respect his male identity. We were long distance until a few weeks ago, when I moved in with him. Before that, the last time we saw one another was mid January. i was generally the more dominant one, making the moves. He liked being held, cried sometimes   was openly sensitive. Within that last month apart, there have been a ton of biological changes. His voice is much deeper suddenly, he's growing a mustache   in general, he's passing SO much more. Now he pulls away from most affection...he has a suddenly new dislike for cuddling, holding hands etc. Even if I simply rest my head on his shoulder, he complains that I'm treating him as though we're in a "lesbian relationship." Even touching his thigh or offering him back massages [which he used to beg for] now seems to offend him. He told me straight up, I need to learn how to appeal to a MAN physically   that touching him where I do turns him off now... His lack of affection has made me scared to initiate sex   that lack of initiation on my part, has in turn angered him. we even broke up because of it.... but we still live together   are trying to mend things. I just feel at a loss for how to move forward from here. How can I validate him while still not catering too heavily to toxic gender roles? Anyone else ever gothrough this emotional hault of sorts...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree...idk enough about circumcison to say whether I agree or disagree w/ it BUT I do know most people at least BELIEVE it to be medically beneficial-not just cosmetic.   that is where it greatly differs from other body modifications IMO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 18:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kail reaches out to the press   stirs shit up on Twitter. Chelsea genuinely keeps to herself... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> cis gf seeking advice for ftm bf </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 08:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I will probably post this on r/mypartneristrans but it's not nearly as active as this subreddit   also tends to be more mtf oriented. I'd love to hear from you guys on the following;
My boyfriend has been on T for about a year now,   isn't often misgendered anymore. But saturday was real rough... [first off, most of his family still calls him by his dead name   misgenders him pretty routinely]. We went to a family get together so the day already was probably not exactly easy for him. He's too shy   sweet to correct anyone   I don't really feel comfortable correcting his family since they're just now meeting me [i just moved in with him last week from across the country]. Anyways, the real discomfort came later into the night. we agreed to see his cousin perform at an open mic night/stand up comedy. We arrived a few minutes late   had to sit in the very first row. One of the comedians blatantly made eye contact with my boyfriend   loudly butchered his pronouns. Immediately, my bf left the room   headed to the bar for beer. I followed after   he said he was fine, but "too sober" for such an experience. I understood   we headed back in, enjoying the rest of the night. That is until he was ONCE AGAIN called "she" by ANOTHER comedian. My heart fucking broke for him   again he headed to the bar. This time when I asked if he was okay, he "jokingly" said he'll probably avoid being in public for a long while   will be pretty emotionally fucked up. He continued just drinking the night away   not really wanting to acknowledge the pain of it all. We haven't really talked about it since   I just know he's hurting so deeply, even though he jokes. What can I do to help him feel loved   respected for who he is? Should I intervene when he's misgendered in very public situations/  or by family members? I sure want to...I just don't know if that's helpful or makes it even worse. I've asked him   he tells me that's up to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 07:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cringe is real </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 07:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Sober </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 00:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 weeks seems...excessive 

Sorry but idk if you have room to be judging other people's parenting \_()_/ 

Edit: let the downvotes begin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 14:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Von douchebag would be a great flare  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can this PLEASE be my flare btw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 19:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kitten cat fighting a doverman  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 22:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget that it sat there for MONTHS while he was in jail. Didn't he supposedly come back home to it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 04:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Farrah promoted Trump... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 06:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> now I KNOW this is a troll account  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 19:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 17:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently she also went missing in 2013...http://starcasm.net/archives/268956 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 19:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just really liked him calling a button PUSHER a "button pressure" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 16:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely. I used to babysit for an orthodox couple whenever they went skiing. Even THEN, the wife wore a skirt  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
