<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2472</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump expresses support for French candidate Le Pen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time to get multi-pass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gary Lockwood: They did the [first] pilot with Jeffrey, and Ive heard seven thousand different versions of why it didnt sell. I dont like to speculate on things I really dont know. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's an imposter sent here by the Outspacers!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I updated the list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TNT's The Alienist: Brian Geraghty Replaces Sean Astin as Teddy Roosevelt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TV Showrunners Speak Out on Possible Writers Strike: "Anybody Would Be Crazy to Want" One </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good riddance  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where in the world is the USS Carl Vinson? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Entertainment One   Palomar Team For Gaddafi Series From Gomorrah Writer Roberto Saviano </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The semi- sequel short story 'Jon's World' was great as well.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oops, my mistake.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the cinematic adaptions were based on his short stories:
 

* Total Recall (based on We Can Remember It for You Wholesale) 

* ~~Blade Runner (based on Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep?)~~ 

* Minority Report (based on The Minority Report)

* Imposter (based on Imposter)

* Paycheck (based on Paycheck) 

* The Adjustment Bureau (based on Adjustment Team) 

* Next (loosely based on The Golden Man)


Edit: Added 'Next'   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope they will get to do something based on 'Explorers We' or 'A Little Something For Us Tempunauts' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Amazon and Channel 4's upcoming anthology series Philip K. Dick's Electric Dreams is rounding out its cast. Mireille Enos, Greg Kinnear and Steve Buscemi have boarded the sci-fi drama, which consists of 10 stand-alone episodes. Enos and Kinnear will star in "Father Thing," while Buscemi will be in "Crazy Diamond."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good riddance  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't let the door hit you on the way out you POS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazon's Philip K. Dick anthology series 'Electric Dreams' adds Greg Kinnear, Steve Buscemi and Mireille Enos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Krypton Trailer Reveals Syfys Superman Prequel Series </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not according to Memory Alpha:


 Paramount Pictures produced Star Trek , Star Trek Into Darkness and Star Trek Beyond under license from CBS Television Studios.

Edit: I mean, you guys can downvote all you want, it's still a factual statement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Paramount can put them on any service they want without needing to consult with CBS.

Not accurate. CBS owns Star Trek copyrights, including the movies.

From [Memory Alpha](http://memory-alpha.wikia.com/wiki/CBS_Consumer_Products):

 CBS has licensed the right to produce Star Trek films to Paramount Pictures, but CBS Consumer Products remained the sole entity responsible for the marketing and licensing of the Star Trek product line for both the television as well as the movie properties, instead of farming it out to Paramount's own division, Paramount Licensing, Inc. 


And if you go to CBS Consumer Products website and check the [List of Properties](http://www.cbsconsumerproducts.com/properties.html), you will find listed under Star Trek:


* Star Trek: The Original Series
* Star Trek: The Animated Series
* Star Trek: The Next Generation
* Star Trek: Deep Space Nine
* Star Trek: Voyager
* Star Trek: Enterprise
* Star Trek: Discovery
* Star Trek (2009)
* Star Trek Beyond
* Star Trek Into Darkness  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shatner   Lloyd Set To Share Senior Moment: 'Star Trek III: The Search for Spock' adversaries William Shatner and Christopher Lloyd are set to reunite for the romantic comedy 'Senior Moment' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Ansara: Good Guys, Bad Guys   Guys in Between </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Netflix Tells Analysts It Will Be Hurt If Writers Go On Strike </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 03:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should 'Star Trek: Discovery's' continuous delays alarm fans? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mark Hamill Wishes Luke and Han Had Final Scene Together in 'Force Awakens' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 18:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll need to pay more for their non-commercials plan:


 [Hulu](https://www.hulu.com/nocommercials): Choose to watch your favorite shows through our new No Commercials plan for $11.99/month or through our existing Limited Commercials plan for $7.99/month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CBS Not Tied To Release Date For Star Trek: Discovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 16:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 22:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The Times](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Times#Related_publications):


 The Times is the first newspaper to have borne that name, lending it to numerous other papers around the world, including The Times of India (founded in 1838), The Straits Times (Singapore) (1845), The New York Times (1851), The Irish Times (1859), Le Temps (France) (1861-1942), the Cape Times (South Africa) (1872), the Los Angeles Times (1881), the Trenton Times (1882), The Seattle Times (1891), The Manila Times (1898), The Daily Times (Malawi) (1900), El Tiempo (Colombia) (1911), The Canberra Times (1926), Times of Malta (1935), and The Washington Times (1982). **In these countries, the newspaper is often referred to as The London Times or The Times of London, although the newspaper is of national scope and distribution.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 21:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  As group organizers put it, people suddenly had an unsettling sense that the United States wasnt as welcoming a place as it once was. The result was a wave of withdrawals. Getting those cancellations all at once, that was startling, said Russ Hedge, chief executive of HIU, which oversees 52 hostels across the country. Weve never seen something like that. From hostels to major hotel chains such as Marriott, tour group operators to outfits that cater to business travelers, the toll of Trumps proposals on the nations tourism industry has been swift. Some say long-term damage has been done. And it could be compounded by recent reports of Trump administration plans to implement extreme vetting of foreign travelers. Visitors  including those from allies such as France and Germany  could be pressed to turn over mobile phone contacts, social media passwords and financial records, according to a Wall Street Journal report. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 21:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you in principal but with news of yet another possible delay I cant help thinking that CBS is not handling the production well.

Edit: A word.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 20:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just three posters right now, 'The Matrix', 'Blade Runner' and 'Star Trek: First Contact'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CBS Not Tied To Release Date For Star Trek: Discovery: Were not tied to any specific release date. Itll be there when were ready to do it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 20:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 19:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just in time for D.C. march, how convenient! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 19:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  President Trump has requested a ride with Queen Elizabeth II in a gold-plated carriage during his visit to the United Kingdom this October, according to a report by The Times of London. [...] While President Obama chose not to ride in such a carriage during his U.K. visit, other world leaders  including Russian President Vladimir Putin, Mexican President Enrique Pea Nieto and Chinese President Xi Jinping  have taken such carriage rides during state visits. [...] While the carriage is well protected by nearby security and has some protective features, security officials say it is more risky and more vulnerable than other options. The vehicle which carries the president of the United States is a spectacular vehicle. It is designed to withstand a massive attack like a low-level rocket grenade. If hes in that vehicle he is incredibly well protected and on top of that it can travel at enormous speed. If he is in a golden coach being dragged up the Mall by a couple of horses, the risk factor is dramatically increased," a source told The Times. There may well be protections in that coach such as bulletproof glass, but they are limited. In particular it is very flimsy," the source added. "It would not be able to put up much resistance in the face of a rocket propelled grenade or high-powered ammunition. Armor-piercing rounds would make a very bad show of things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump wants gold-plated carriage ride with Queen during UK visit: report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 19:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Vulture: I have to ask you about Star Trek: Discovery. Its been delayed a bit, and you parted ways with Bryan Fuller. You still havent announced a premiere date, or even a launch window. Where is that right now? And how big of deal is that going to be?

* CBS Interactive president Marc DeBevoise: Its going great, Ive actually been up there [to the set]. It is, you know, phenomenal. It is huge. And were very excited about the content, the creators, the actors, all coming together. As you said, were not tied to any specific release date. Itll be there when were ready to do it, and when we feel its in a great place. Were not worried about anything here. Were excited, and well have more specifics as we get closer to what will likely be the release dates.


* Vulture: Is it likely going to be the fall?

* CBS Interactive president Marc DeBevoise: Were not stating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CBS on 'Star Trek: Discovery': Were not tied to any specific release date. Itll be there when were ready to do it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A conflict over North Korea could break out at any moment, Chinas Foreign Minister Wang Yi said Friday, warning there would be no winner in any war as tensions soar with the US. The sharp language came after President Donald Trump said the North Korea problem will be taken care of, as speculation mounts that the reclusive state could be preparing another nuclear or missile test. Lately, tensions have risen ... and one has the feeling that a conflict could break out at any moment, Wang said. If a war occurs, the result is a situation in which everybody loses and there can be no winner. [...] There are reports of activity at a nuclear test site in North Korea ahead of Saturdays 105th anniversary of the birth of the countrys founder Kim Il-Sung, which have fueled speculation it could carry out a sixth test. But Beijing has long opposed dramatic action against Pyongyang, fearing the regimes collapse would send a flood of refugees across its borders and leave the US military on its doorstep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conflict could break out at any moment over NK: China </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still hope that Netflix will revive 'Rubicon' one day, seeing that they have working relationship with James Badge Dale and AMC as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A writers strike could slow or stop production on Fox, CBS, HBO series: CBS All Access Star Trek: Discovery, HBOs Divorce, and Netflixs "Marvel" dramas would all be immediately affected if writers refused to work in the middle of production. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the [Chinese Foreign Minister Wang Yi](https://www.bloomberg.com/politics/articles/2017-04-14/china-warns-of-war-risk-as-trump-rattles-saber-at-north-korea) himself seems to agree with the ex CIA chief: 

 China warned that a war on the Korean Peninsula would have devastating consequences as the U.S. threatened military retaliation against North Korea if it proceeds with a nuclear test this weekend. As U.S. Vice President Mike Pence heads to Asia on a 10-day trip that will include South Korea, Chinese Foreign Minister Wang Yi urged all parties **to stop provoking and threatening each other and not to make the situation irretrievable. Once a war really happens, the result will be nothing but losing all round and no one could become a winner,** Wang told reporters in Beijing on Friday, according to the official Xinhua News Agency.

And yes, China took some steps to  rein in NK, however they are worried that things might get out of control: 

 Even so, China is getting increasingly alarmed at the brinkmanship. The situation now is similar to the time before a storm, and this kind of dangerous situation worth of our attention and we must be alert, Wang, Chinas foreign minister, said on Friday. No matter who the nation is, if it continues to provoke wars in the Peninsula, it has to bear this historical responsibility and pay its price. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Rubicon' - The gentleman to my right is a remarkable intelligence analyst ... his greatest asset, for you, is that you don't know him, and he doesn't know you. He doesn't care about you. Or your feelings. He just knows what your tie looks like. You can trust him. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These aren't the droids you're looking for.


Edit: Here is the trailer for ...  [The Last Jedi](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zB4I68XVPzQ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They fit Riker and Troi into a show set 200 years before TNG. it was horrible, but for some reason they still did it.

Well, at least we agree that it was a horrible decision. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If it is an abject failure, like his other forays into military matters, he will say he didn't have anything to do with it and someone below him will get the blame. 


Yep, we're going to see another "They lost Ryan" comment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The reboot movies are also not in the Prime Timeline, Discovery is.


The 3 reboot movies are about TOS characters.


 We don't know how much we'll be seeing Sarek and Mudd during Discovery, but neither of them were heavily featured during TOS. 

You're ignoring the point, these are not new characters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WGA Video Urges Yes Vote On Strike Authorization </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We had 3 TV series and 4 movies detailing the TNG era, and its characters. 

Well, we had 9 movies (6 TOS + 3 Reboot) and 2 series (ENT + TOS) all set pre-TNG. 


 we're getting new characters and a whole new story. 

We're also getting old characters like Sarek and Harry Mudd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  According to legend, the memory wall is the great lost sequence of Star Trek: The Motion Picture and was cut only because it was impossible to complete the necessary effects in time for the movies December release. The truth is that, although it was incredibly expensive, the sequence was abandoned because it failed on many levels. Director Robert Wise rejected it during postproduction and replaced it with Spocks spacewalk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Star Trek: The Motion Picture - Producing the Memory Wall Sequence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carter Page is the living incarnation of Ben Swain from "The Thick of It'. As Malcolm Tucker so aptly put it he was like ["a sweaty octopus trying to unhook a bra!"](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GV_SaxVgY5o) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Reverse-Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ridley Scott tends to take on lots of new projects that at one time he might find himself in need of a clone to carry on half of his future projects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, and they made the initial series announcement in *November 2015*, that's 18 months ago! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [CBS Says STAR TREK: DISCOVERY is Already Profitable](http://trekcore.com/blog/2016/07/cbs-says-star-trek-discovery-is-already-profitable-ahead-of-production/)- July 28, 2016



 **We also struck a significant international deal with Netflix for Star Trek, licensing our new series Star Trek: Discovery to 188 Netflix countries around the world  virtually everywhere but North America.** In addition, we licensed all 727 previous episodes of our Star Trek library. Plus, we struck a similar deal with Bell Media for Canada. **As a result, Star Trek: Discovery, our new series, is profitable  and we havent even begun production.**


And on December 7, 2016:


[**Moonves: Netflix international sales pay for entire Star Trek production cost**](http://www.fiercecable.com/online-video/moonves-netflix-int-l-sales-pay-for-entire-star-trek-production-cost):


 CBS Corp. chief executive Les Moonves said the broad-reaching international sale of his companys new Star Trek incarnation to Netflix paid for the shows entire production budget. Netflix just took it off the table for the rest of the world, Moonves told media investors at an annual UBS conference Monday. **Basically, Star Trek is going on CBS All Access for free.** [...] The back end is now becoming more important than the front end, Moonves added, noting that  CBS couldnt enable this model without back-end sales of the shows to buyers like Netflix.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> iirc Netflix is footing the entire bill for DSC to the point that Les Moonves was bragging that the show is profitable before even filming a single frame! 

However, that was back in July of last year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Even M. Night Shyamalan Thought the Original Ending of 'Split' Was Too Dark </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Its a little disconcerting that CBS and Paramount would reportedly offer Dorn, one of the most iconic actors in the entire series, 0.65 percent of what hed previously made on Star Trek (seriously). That would suggest they either dont value the original characters enough to make it worth the actors while, or the pockets on this thing are way too shallow to turn out something solid.


I wonder if the constant delays led to budget overruns or something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Sutherland to Star as J. Paul Getty in FX's Danny Boyle Anthology 'Trust': The first season tells the story about John Paul Getty III and his 1973 kidnapping. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just your typical debriefing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair he did use [voluptuous](http://www.nydailynews.com/news/politics/donald-trump-objectifies-voluptuous-ivanka-howard-stern-chat-article-1.2822826) at one time to describe his daughter Ivanka!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "I was sitting at the table, we had finished dinner," Trump told Fox Business host Maria Bartiromo. "We're now having dessertand we had the most beautiful piece of chocolate cake that you've ever seenand President Xi was enjoying it." Bartiromo then said it was "brilliant" that the missiles were "unmanned." "It's so incredible. It's brilliant," Trump agreed.


"missiles were unmanned." FFS Bartiromo sounds as dumb as Trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Brags About Eating the "Most Beautiful" Chocolate Cake During Syrian Missile Strike Decision </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  CBS probably does not want to invalidate a whole series of books either

That makes no sense, the current books are not part of Star Trek canon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was just a sham to appear that he and Trump are not that friendly after all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, yeah. Their [previous statement](http://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-syria-putin-tillerson-idUSKBN17C13K) was just for show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  columnist Michael Wolff told Trump's counselor Kellyanne Conway

Weird coming from Michael Wolff, the same guy that went on a rant against journalists for their continuing coverage of Trump lies, [telling them to just report what Trump says and not to fact-check him.](http://www.mediaite.com/online/michael-wolff-says-journalists-covering-trump-should-just-transcribe-what-he-says/)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't I read the other day that Tillerson is only meeting with Lavrov because Putin was so "angry" that he cancelled his meeting with the T-Rex?


Edit: Found the news source.

 [Kremlin, angry at Syria missile strike, says Putin won't meet Tillerson](http://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-syria-putin-tillerson-idUSKBN17C13K)

I guess it was all part of a plan to make it looks like Trump and Putin are not that close. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I'm not a witch](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uxJyPsmEask) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  [20 minutes later @SecretaryCarson is freed from stuck elevator at Courtside Morning Apts. Alonzo Mourning looks more relieved than anyone](https://twitter.com/ReneMiamiHerald/status/852140325871259649/photo/1?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw ref_url=http%3A%2F%2Fmiamiherald.typepad.com%2Fnakedpolitics%2F2017%2F04%2Fben-carson-visits-miami-housing-development-and-gets-stuck-in-elevator.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ben Carson visits Miami public housing development -- and gets stuck in elevator </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not surprising to see Glenn Greenwald's outlet at it again deflecting and defending Trump and the Russians.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just like he approved the failed raid in Yemen over dinner!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe he read 'Term Limits' by Vince Flynn and is scared shitless that it's coming true. /s  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too many fucking reds there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is an excerpt of [Entertainment Weekly interview](http://ew.com/tv/2017/04/11/stephen-king-the-mist-tv-series-first-trailer/) with the showrunner, beware of major spoilers in the full interview:


 I wanted to be respectful to the source material, but my feeling was there was already a great adaptation out there by Frank Darabont, says show creator Christian Torpe, referring to the 2007 film with the infamous gut-punch ending. The novella is 200 pages and one location, and we needed to change that to make an ongoing series. But we wanted to remain faithful to the heart of the story, he says. Gone is the grocery store, where residents of a small town take shelter from the beasts outside and unleash the sinister qualities within themselves. The series will be spread out over several lockdown locations, including a church and a mall where hundreds have holed up against the monsters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From reading an interview with the showrunner it's going to be very different from the movie. Not sure how I'd feel about that. 


Here is an excerpt of [the interview](http://ew.com/tv/2017/04/11/stephen-king-the-mist-tv-series-first-trailer/), beware of spoilers in the full interview:


 I wanted to be respectful to the source material, but my feeling was there was already a great adaptation out there by Frank Darabont, says show creator Christian Torpe, referring to the 2007 film with the infamous gut-punch ending. The novella is 200 pages and one location, and we needed to change that to make an ongoing series. But we wanted to remain faithful to the heart of the story, he says. Gone is the grocery store, where residents of a small town take shelter from the beasts outside and unleash the sinister qualities within themselves. The series will be spread out over several lockdown locations, including a church and a mall where hundreds have holed up against the monsters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The question was always, how do you basically visualize and dramatize the idea that the island itself is all that separates the world from hellfire and damnation? said co-creator Lindelof. And the answer was the volcano. The volcano had been dormant for the duration of the series, but based on moving into this endgame, the island had become unstable and the volcano was going to erupt. We were going to have lots of seismic activity, and ultimately, there was going to be this big fight between the forces of good and the forces of evil, which ended up in the series manifesting as Jack and The Man in Black, in the midst of magma. Magma spewing everywhere! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Lost' finale almost featured a giant exploding volcano </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Based on story by Stephen King, the 10-episode series follows the residents of Bridgeville, Maine who find themselves engulfed by a foreboding mist containing a myriad of inexplicable and bizarre threats that put their humanity to the test. As the eerie fog rolls in, a family is torn apart by a brutal crime that suddenly cuts them off from the rest of the world, and in some cases, each other. Family, friends and adversaries become strange bedfellows, battling the mysterious mist and its threats, fighting to maintain morality and sanity as the rules of society break down. [...] The Mist premieres Thursday, June 22 at 10 PM on Spike.  

[The Mist trailer](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kya_uqiSQOY t=3s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Mist Trailer: A Mysterious Fog Puts Humanity To The Test In New Spike Series </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tillerson Asks Why U.S. Taxpayers Should Care About Ukraine: Why should U.S. taxpayers be interested in Ukraine? Tillerson asked foreign ministers discussing Russias intervention there at a Group of Seven gathering Tuesday in Lucca, Italy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 01:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must be Alex Jones from the mirror universe! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Holocaust centers"

The White House's SS moron at his "best" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mattis: This time we will send 120 Tomahawk missiles to destroy two airbases. 

But dont worry; well give your Russian overlords a 48 hours advance warning so you can get your personnel and pilots out of harms way! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, keep him. Clueless Spicer is the perfect face for a clueless administration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Honest Trailers - Rogue One: A Star Wars Story </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Weve agreed to come Monday to begin a conversation. If we were to strike  and were many steps away from that  every writer would put their pens down, and even if something is in the middle of production, the writers will stop writing. Some of the shows that would be affected would be Netflixs Marvel dramas and One Day at a Time, HBOs Divorce, Star Trek: Discovery, and FXs American Horror Story. The WGA will poll its members for a strike authorization vote, with online voting to run April 19 to 24. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Writer Strike Could Affect Star Trek: Discovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really. I dont like the fact that Discovery is set Pre-TOS but Ill give it a shot and see what they will come up with. We have no idea if it going to be a turd or not before we watch at least couple episodes. 


As a fan I have no real power to change the views of CBS. We can express our dismays by posting here on Reddit and other forums; meanwhile I will keep hoping for a Post-Voyager series.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dont know about the rest but having nifty ships and futuristic tech is not really the reason why I want the series to take place Post-Voyager. 


Watching the various Trek series was in a way like watching future history unfolding in front of your eyes. From Kirk's five years mission and first contact with new species. Open conflicts with the Klingons and the Romulans in TOS era and so on. 


Then we jump to the 24th century, and see how the Federation evolved economically and politically. Making new alliance with the Klingon and meeting new enemies like the Borg, the Cardassians and the Dominion among others. By the end of the 24th century the Federation was reeling from non-stop conflicts with the Brog, the Dominion and the Romulans. 


I, for once, would love to see whats the Federation is like after facing all these major challenges. Will they continue looking for new lifeforms and expand the Federation, or will they hunker down for a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Since President Donald Trumps inauguration, Democratic voters hostility toward the new administration has been evident in national polling, in rallies and protests in cities and airports, and on social media. But outside a handful of small legislative races over the past four months, there hasnt been a true test of the new, Trump-driven political dynamic at the ballot box. Tuesday, however, begins a series of special elections that will examine whether increased Democratic enthusiasm can deal Trump stinging defeats and reshape the narrative a year-and-a-half before the midterms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democrats hope to deliver Trump stinging defeats in special elections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps if Discovery is so successful CBS/Netflix will greenlit spin-off series that takes place post-Voyager. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Rubicon: A conspiracy series that was very similar in tone to the 70s movies like Three Days of the Condor. 

* Flashforward: It started well and then the plot was all over the place. However, episodes such as The Garden of Forking Paths   the finale gave us glimpse of the series potential.

* Virtuality: It was planned as a new space/mystery show by Ron Moore but Fox changed its mind and they made a TV movie instead. It ended with a mysterious revelation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You see whats going on. You see the numbers, Trump continued. Weve created over 600,000 jobs already in a very short period of time, and its gonna really start catching on now because some of the things that weve done are big league, and they are catching on. Already, weve created more than almost 600,000 jobs. Its unclear where Trumps figure came from. The president has in the past spouted information that is inaccurate and at times demonstrably false. The White House did not immediately respond for comment. According to Labor Department data, the U.S. economy added a combined 317,000 jobs in February and March, the first full months Trumps presidency. About 98,000 of those jobs were added last month.


"Its unclear where Trumps figure came from." How about his ass? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump overstates job creation numbers under his administration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if Star Trek Had Never Existed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's still alive? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Qusay Trump is as dumb as his brother Uday.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The actor confirms that there were a couple of conversations with producers last summer about a possible Star Trek: Discovery role. Those discussions lasted a couple of weeks, however they never led anywhere and there are no plans for him to appear at this time on Star Trek: Discovery.



So they talked with him after all. This might be just them trying to keep it under wraps for now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Alabama Gov. Robert Bentley (R) was booked into Montgomery County Jail on Monday evening for two misdemeanor charges related to campaign finance violations. Bentley resigned on Monday evening, after reaching an agreement with both state lawmakers and law enforcement officials. The agreement comes on the day of impeachment hearings were set to begin, allowing Bentley to avoid the public spectacle.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alabama gov. booked into jail for campaign finance violations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since they said that 'Discovery' takes place in Worf's past timeline, he's either playing an ancestor, or there is some sort of time travel involved and he will play a descendant of Worf from the future.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 23:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Dorn did say that Trek fans would in fact get to see him appear as a guest star in the upcoming Star Trek: Discovery, as a Klingon **ancestor** of Lt. Commander Worf, saying, . . . the first episodes of the new series center around the Klingons.


Then:


 Dorn indicated that the producers from Star Trek: Discovery approached him about a year ago to see if the actor would be interested in guest starring as a **descendant** of Worf in the new series, which Dorn admitted he thought was a fun idea


Did they change their plan or this is a mistake by the website/Dorn? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The links are not real. First link is broken and the other one is the home page of PBS website.

From quick googling, it is clear that [Obama administration made the visitors log available to the public.](http://thehill.com/blogs/congress-blog/politics/326447-release-of-white-house-visitor-logs-important-for-transparency). 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are you defending the Trump administration then? 

Edit: You provided a broken link to support your fake outrage. [Here is reality check for you](http://thehill.com/blogs/congress-blog/politics/326447-release-of-white-house-visitor-logs-important-for-transparency):


 **The Obama administrations decision to publish nearly 6 million visitor names during his eight years in office was not unprecedented. He simply utilized 21st-century technology to provide the public with the tools they need to hold him and those in his administration accountable**. After all, the American public elected him to serve them in our countrys highest office. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But a closer look reveals that the last two months have not been characterized so much by what has happened but by what has not. Near-daily controversy over executive orders or tweets does not represent substantial policy changes but instead masks an almost complete lack of movement on many issues. Fiscal policy is among the most striking. **By this time in 2009, then-President Obama had signed 12 bills into law**, including the American Recovery and Reinvestment Act ($663 billion), the 2009 Omnibus Act ($410 billion) and the Children's Health Insurance Program (CHIP) Reauthorization Act ($73.8 billion), totaling roughly $1.1 trillion in spending. No doubt these bills represented the foundation of Democratic priorities at the time. **In contrast, President Trump has thus far signed a grand total ofone bill with significant spending implications  the reauthorization of NASA.** Indeed, the Congressional Budget Office (CBO) has opted to score only only two of the laws enacted this session. Officially naming clinics in Center Township, Pennsylvania and Pago Pago, American Samoa may be worthy efforts, but they hardly represent a heavy lift. **And while the House has voted on eight bills with spending implications, the Senate has yet to address a single one.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cable News Loves War: Nobody projects network war delight better than CNNs Wolf Blitzer, whose metallic and nasal shrieking lands on virgin zones of mental irritation in these times. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 01:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 21:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He said the U.S. will "continue to talk with" Russian officials "about how this undermines any hope of improving relations not just with the United States," **but suggested self-reflection will be a stronger deterrent than external pressure**.

Is he really that dumb or just playing a game here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tillerson: Election Meddling Something 'Russia Needs To Confront Themselves' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 21:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 21:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She [sounds insane](http://talkingpointsmemo.com/edblog/mcfarland-out-at-nsc): 

 while she was running against Hillary Clinton for Senate in 2006 (actually making a failed bid for the GOP nomination to run against her), she claimed that Clinton was so worried about her candidacy that she'd sent secret helicopters to surveil her house in the Hamptons as well her apartment in Manhattan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And she is insane too.

 while she was running against Hillary Clinton for Senate in 2006 (actually making a failed bid for the GOP nomination to run against her), she claimed that Clinton was so worried about her candidacy that she'd sent secret helicopters to surveil her house in the Hamptons as well her apartment in Manhattan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Following reports of a chemical attack in Syria, the U.S. military bombed a regime air base in Homs. Since the bombing, Syrian warplanes have continued to take off from that base. "Here's what I think Assad's telling Trump by flying from this base: 'F you.' And I think he's making a serious mistake," Graham said on NBC's "Meet the Press." "Because if you're an adversary of the United States and you don't worry about what Trump may do on any given day, then you're crazy."


Assad knows that Putin is the key player and not the orange buffoon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Graham: Assad telling Trump 'F you' by still using bombed Syrian base </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How JUDGE DREDD predicted the future </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 02:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 01:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [It was a $60 million publicity stunt](https://i.redd.it/fgf30pulubqy.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not even a day, the airbase was attacked Friday morning (Syria local time) and it was operational again by Friday evening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The airport is operating as a first phase, Homs governor Talal Barazi told Reuters. Planes have taken off from it, he added, without saying when. Asked if it was true that Syrian planes were now taking off from Shayrat or that the air base is operating, a Pentagon spokesman referred questions to the Syrian government. The Syrian Observatory for Human Rights, a UK-based organization that reports on the war, said warplanes had taken off from the base on Friday and carried out air strikes on rebel-held areas in the eastern Homs countryside. [...] A senior military source in the alliance fighting in support of President Bashar al-Assad said the airbase had been mostly evacuated thanks to a warning from Russia, which has deployed its military to Syria in support of Assad. The senior military source, a non-Syrian, said only a few out-of-service jets were destroyed. The United States warned Russia ahead of the attack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syrian air base bombed by U.S. cruise missiles resumes operations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A US soldier was killed Saturday while conducting operations in Afghanistan against ISIS-Khorasan, the local branch of ISIS there. The soldier was mortally wounded late Saturday during an operation in Nangarhar Province, Navy Capt. Bill Salvin, a spokesman for the NATO-led coalition in Afghanistan, told CNN. A U.S. military official separately told CNN the fallen service member is a special operations soldier. [...] There are about 8,400 US troops in Afghanistan. This is the first US combat death in Afghanistan in 2017. The number of US casualties in Afghanistan has fallen sharply since the end of US-led combat operations in 2014.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US special operations soldier was killed today in Afghanistan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 18:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Game of Thrones.

* The Expanse.

* The Man in the High Castle.

* Flashforward.

* Outlander.

* Hannibal.

* The Leftovers.

* The Last Ship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 18:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What consequences? 


The single airbase that was attacked is still operational. The Syrians and the Russians are continuing their airstrikes against civilians and Trump doesn't have a clear policy regarding the conflict in Syria.


So again, what consequences are you talking about?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 17:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump's own National Security Adviser disagrees.


 [National Security Adviser H.R. McMaster says the strike in Syria did not stop Assad's ability to carry out future attacks](https://twitter.com/CNNPolitics/status/850177474365448196)


Not only they failed to disrupt the [operational capability of the airbase](http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/syrian-planes-shayrat-air-base-homes-us-air-strikes-syrian-observatory-human-rights-bashar-al-assad-a7673511.html) but the Syrian regime conducted [new airstrikes](http://www.cnn.com/2017/04/08/middleeast/syria-strikes-russia-donald-trump/index.html) against the same town that was hit with chemical weapon.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 17:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, the Russians supplied [the Syrian regime with chemical weapons since the 70s](https://fas.org/sgp/crs/nuke/R42848.pdf).

 Syria began to expand its program in the late 1970s and early 1980s. Declassified U.S. documents indicate that the Soviet Union supplied Syria with chemical agents, delivery systems, and training related to chemical weapons use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 16:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Now that Obamas poll numbers are in tailspin  watch for him to launch a strike in Libya or Iran. He is desperate.](https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/255784560904773633) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You betcha!

 [I wish everyone, including the haters and losers, a very happy Easter!](https://twitter.com/realdonaldtrump/status/584647721883148288) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Trump in 2012](https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/255784560904773633)

 Now that Obamas poll numbers are in tailspin  watch for him to launch a strike in Libya or Iran. He is desperate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not surprising giving Russia involvement with [Syrian chemical weapons program](https://fas.org/sgp/crs/nuke/R42848.pdf).

  Some analysts point out that Egypt provided Syria with a small number of chemical weapons and delivery systems in the lead-up to the Yom Kippur War in 1973. Syria began to expand its program in the late 1970s and early 1980s. Declassified U.S. documents indicate that the Soviet Union supplied Syria with chemical agents, delivery systems, and training related to chemical weapons use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sonequa Martin-Green didn't quit The Walking Dead to do Star Trek: "It did not happen that way" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's still a puppet, nothing changed on the ground. 


[National Security Adviser H.R. McMaster says the strike in Syria did not stop Assad's ability to carry out future attacks](https://twitter.com/CNNPolitics/status/850177474365448196) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys should amend the Submission Rules to allow subtitles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Mitch McConnell in 2013](http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2013/09/10/syria-vote-mitch-mcconnell_n_3899989.html)

 **Syria Vote: Mitch McConnell Opposes Strike, Slams Obama**: I will be voting against this resolution  a vital national security risk is clearly not at play, McConnell (R-Ky.) said in a Senate floor speech Tuesday [...] The limited scope of the proposed authorization to use military force was meant to reassure Americans that the nation would not become entangled in yet another Middle Eastern war, while still asserting the U.S. claim to moral leadership in the face of atrocity. But McConnell said Tuesday that such a limited plan made no sense. Although the measure also calls for the administration to present a broader plan within 30 days of the resolution being enacted, McConnell said there simply were too many blanks that need to be filled in. There are just too many unanswered questions about our long-term strategy in Syria, including the fact that this proposal is utterly detached from a wider strategy to end the civil war there, and on the specific question of deterring the use of chemical weapons, the presidents proposal appears to be based on a contradiction, McConnell said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joachim Rnning To Direct Micro, Last Michael Crichton Novel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Things escalated fast. Last Friday, key administration officials UN Ambassador Nikki Haley and Secretary of State Rex Tillerson publicly acknowledged that they would no longer seek to oppose the Assad regime. On Thursday evening, the Trump administration fired 59 Tomahawk missiles at a Syrian airfield in response to the Assad regimes use of chemical weapons on civilians. Whether or not you agreed with this specific decision, the complete reversal  in only six days  of the Trump administrations policy on Syria should worry anyone who cares about the future of U.S. foreign policy. For starters, the new president seems to be prone to making snap judgments on the use of force. In his early days in office, Trump ordered a Navy Seal team into a risky mission in Yemen, resulting in the death of one U.S. soldier and several civilians. He apparently made that decision over dinner. Trumps secret plan to defeat ISIS may remain unknown, but he has chosen to escalate U.S. airstrikes, resulting in substantially higher civilian casualties, and has sent thousands more troops to the region. [...] Yesterdays airstrikes are a case in point. They were primarily symbolic, barely denting the capability of the Syrian military. And they certainly sent a message, proclaiming, as Donald Trump did, that it is in this vital national security interest of the United States to prevent and deter the spread and use of deadly chemical weapons. But the administration appears to have given little thought to what happens next. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 0-to-strike in 6 days: Trump's snap decision on Syria should worry US </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheating? She won the primary by more than 3 million votes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They didn't. Your guy lost by more than 3 million votes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  U.S. employers added just 98,000 jobs in March, the fewest in a year, though the unemployment rate fell to a nearly 10-year low of 4.5 percent.[...] Last month, construction companies added just 6,000 jobs, the fewest in seven months. Retailers, suffering from the shift to online shopping, slashed 30,000 jobs. Education and health care services added the fewest jobs for that category in 15 months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Job growth tumbles as U.S. employers add just 98K jobs in March; unemployment rate falls to 4.5 percent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Wrong](https://fas.org/sgp/crs/nuke/R42848.pdf).

  Some analysts point out that Egypt provided Syria with a small number of chemical weapons and delivery systems in the lead-up to the Yom Kippur War in 1973. Syria began to expand its program in the late 1970s and early 1980s. Declassified U.S. documents indicate that the Soviet Union supplied Syria with chemical agents, delivery systems, and training related to chemical weapons use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Coming back to the first point, Russia was alerted beforehand of the bombing, thus limiting the danger of escalation. If this was the case, it raises the question of just how committed Putin is to defending Assad, and of whether Trump might just be able to have his cake and eat it too. That is, he might be able to win the trifecta: distance himself from the slur of isolationism, placate the interventionists, and keep his budding alliance with Russia. A jump in oil prices as a result of the bombing will make Russia and Tillerson happy. And perhaps this is all a test run for the real game: figuring out a way to drive a wedge between Iran and Russia. Then Trump can have Moscow and McCain and Schumer can have Iran.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Real Targets of Trumps Strike Were His Domestic Critics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, he warned the Russians hours before the strike and they in turn most likely warned the Syrian forces. And the strike was limited to just one military airport.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [JUST IN: National Security Adviser H.R. McMaster says the strike in Syria did not stop Assad's ability to carry out future attacks](https://twitter.com/CNNPolitics/status/850177474365448196)


What was the fucking point then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The US warned the Russians ahead of Syria missile strikes: Official](http://www.cnbc.com/2017/04/06/the-us-warned-the-russians-ahead-of-syria-missile-strikes-official.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kong: Skull Island Crosses $500M With China Audiences Help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 01:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 01:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. I have not gotten the chance to watch 'Fargo' yet, might as well give it a shot this summer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 00:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carrie Coon is without question my favorite cast member on 'The Leftovers', I hope we will see more of her in future shows/movies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter Sues U.S. Government Over Attempt to Unmask Anti-Trump Tweeters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wesley Snipes Sci-Fi Thriller 'Armed Response' Lands at Saban: The story follows a team of highly trained operatives who find themselves trapped inside an isolated military compound. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  With Nunes stepping aside from the Russia probe, Trump has lost the latest in a string of allies  real or perceived  who occupy positions that could have been used to shield him from scrutiny over his and his aides ties to Russia. 

Or as [Jim Sciutto](https://twitter.com/jimsciutto/status/849990023428624384) puts it:

 So far Russia investigation has led to recusal of AG Sessions and House Intel Cmte Chair Nunes and firing of NSA Flynn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Trumps perceived Russia allies keep dropping </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So, at least we still have that.

For now! 

Who knows, DOJ might come up with their own list of banned "extremist materials"   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking at the [Twitter account](https://twitter.com/ALT_uscis?lang=en) I don't see any threats against POTUS as far as I can tell.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Twitter Inc said in a lawsuit on Thursday that it had received a demand from U.S. officials for records that could reveal the user behind an account opposed to President Donald Trump and that it was challenging the demand in court.


Are we living in the fucking Russian Federation? 

Edit: Here is the [Twitter account](https://twitter.com/ALT_uscis?lang=en) in question.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Conaway, an accountant, is an unlikely candidate to be a bipartisan healer. He was elected to Congress in 2004 to a heavily Republican district in midwest Texas, and has since racked up one of the most conservative records in the Capitol.[...] But Conaway has at times also sought to elevate the House above partisanship. In 2013, when he accepted the chairmanship of the House Ethics Committee, he told his hometown paper that his goal was to "improve the view the public has of the House and how it operates." 
And Conaway, who did not endorse Trump for president until after he had forced his rivals out of a contested GOP primary, has previously criticized Trumps posture toward Russia. In April 2016, after Trump called the NATO alliance obsolete and said it inadequately focused on terrorism, Conaway had choice words for the GOP frontrunner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet Mike Conaway, the new sheriff on the Trump-Russia case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Get Out Leads First-Ever MTV Movie and TV Awards Nominations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makes sense, will edit my comment.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gareth Edwards on Rogue One, Darth Vader, and What Happened to the Death Troopers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The high cost of protecting President Trump and his family is leading the Secret Service to make cost-cutting concessions in order to keep up with their protective mission, according to a Thursday New York Times report. Dozens of agents across the nation are being pulled from their criminal investigation assignments to protect Trumps family in two-week shifts, including at the presidents Trump Tower in New York City, where first lady Melania Trump and their youngest son, Barron, are living for the time being. Under the Trump administration, the Secret Service is facing much higher costs. They now must cover a large first family including Trumps adult children as well as their spouses and children. The Trumps' far-flung international trips and other travel are adding to the agencys expenses, particularly Trump's frequent visits to his Mar-a-Lago resort in Palm Beach, Fla. In addition to the presidents family, Trump has also requested top aides like Kellyanne Conway, national security adviser H.R. McMaster and White House chief of staff Reince Priebus receive protective detail.


The ~~SS~~ USSS is undercutting criminal investigations in order to protect the Grifter-in-Chief.

Edit: An acronym.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Secret Service strained by protection of Trump family: report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Writers Guild Promises Strike on May 2 If No Deal Is Reached </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 02:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet that various foreign intelligence services are excited by this opportunity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sonequa Martin-Green Addresses Her Star Trek: Discovery Character, Show Format, and Canon : Its going to open up so much potential for new storylines because not being the captain automatically gives you a different perspective. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 23:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) says it has deported a man convicted in federal court of conspiring to act as a Russian agent within America. Evgeny Buryakov, a 42-year-old formerly of New York City, was removed to Moscow Wednesday, the agency said in a statement. Authorities had probed Buryakov, Victor Podobnyy and Igor Sporyshev for suspected ties with a Russian spy ring, according to a 2015 court filing. Reports emerged Monday that a former adviser to President Trumps election campaign met Podobnyy three years before the 2016 race. Carter Page, who was then an energy consultant, purportedly passed documents to Podobnyy during a 2013 encounter in New York City. FBI Director James Comedy said last week his bureau is probing Russias 2016 election meddling, including ties possible collusion between Moscow and Trump campaign officials. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ICE deports convicted Russian spy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He who controls the spice controls the universe. Can't wait to go back to the Dune universe for the 3rd time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sonequa Martin-Green Addresses Her Star Trek: Discovery Character, Show Format, and Canon : Its going to open up so much potential for new storylines because not being the captain automatically gives you a different perspective. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Contact Day: 11 unforgettable first contacts in Star Trek </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The most important part of it for me was when they told me we would be going back to the early days of Jack Ryan. The character starts as an analyst, literally at a desk. Thats where you find Jack Ryan in this. Hes just a numbers guy. Hes crunching numbers for the CIA, and he stumbles upon something. And so, you get to see this incredibly wild arc of a guy who thought he was basically pencil-pushing for the CIA, and then hes brought on this incredible adventure because one of the things he was researching turns out to be real. You get the whole spectrum of everything, and I think that thats really cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jack Ryan: From Analyst to Badass, John Krasinski Lays out the Arc for His Title Character </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Walking Dead's Andrew Lincoln Hopes to Appear in 'Star Trek: Discovery' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From Spider-Man to Alien: why does Hollywood keep spoiling its movies? Blockbusters keep getting spoiled before anyone has a chance to watch them thanks to plot-filled trailers and loose-lipped directors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  [spoiler](#s "Nope"). Season 2 premiere was good but then the show went back to the boring family drama. There were some interesting episodes but the series overall is not that great. Peter Jacobson as the former proxy Snyder is the only interesting character in the entire series IMO.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When good TV goes bad: how The Walking Dead started to stink </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buckle up everyone, we're going to get a [younger, edgier version of Star Trek!](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5HeNZBItzps) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 02:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite quote from the original [Buzzfeed](https://www.buzzfeed.com/alimwatkins/a-former-trump-adviser-met-with-a-russian-spy?utm_term=.bcN2zdb6Kk#.vjyxVloBDN) article that broke the story:
 

 The court filing includes a colorful transcript of Podobnyy speaking with Sporyshev about trying to recruit Page. [Male-1] wrote that he is sorry, he went to Moscow and forgot to check his inbox, but he wants to meet when he gets back. **I think he is an idiot and forgot who I am**...He got hooked on Gazprom thinking that if they have a project, he could rise up, Podobnyy said. I also promised him a lot...this is intelligence method to cheat, how else to work with foreigners? You promise a favor for a favor. **You get the documents from him and tell him to go fuck himself.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, in an interview with [The Washington Post](https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/post-politics/wp/2016/03/21/donald-trump-reveals-foreign-policy-team-in-meeting-with-the-washington-post/?tid=sm_tw utm_term=.27c786463c4a)'s editorial board on March 21, 2016

 Trump began the hour-long meeting by pulling out a list of some of his foreign policy advisers. "Walid Phares, who you probably know. PhD, adviser to the House of Representatives. Hes a counterterrorism expert," Trump said. "Carter Page, PhD. George Papadopoulos. Hes an oil and energy consultant. Excellent guy. The honorable Joe Schmitz, [was] inspector general at the Department of Defense. General Keith Kellogg. And I have quite a few more. But thats a group of some of the people that we are dealing with. We have many other people in different aspects of what we do. But thats a pretty representative group."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Star Trek: Discovery' writer [Bo Yeon Kim](https://twitter.com/extspace/status/848945518688452608):


 Yes, her name is Michael. And yes, she is our Number One! Welcome (officially) @SonequaMG! #StarTrekDiscovery </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Star Trek: Discovery writer [Bo Yeon Kim](https://twitter.com/extspace/status/848945518688452608):


 Yes, her name is Michael. And yes, she is our Number One! Welcome (officially) @SonequaMG! #StarTrekDiscovery </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sense a distressing lack of enthusiasm on your part.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Star Trek: Discovery' - Sonequa Martin-Green Finally Confirmed As First Officer Michael Burnham </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Star Trek: Discovery writer [Bo Yeon Kim](https://twitter.com/extspace/status/848945518688452608):


 Yes, her name is Michael. And yes, she is our Number One! Welcome (officially) @SonequaMG! #StarTrekDiscovery </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sonequa Martin-Green Confirmed As First Officer Michael Burnham in Star Trek: Discovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After the same write, Eli Lake, wrote an article in February defending Gen. Flynn and then went on [CNN](http://www.mediaite.com/online/chum-is-in-the-water-bloomberg-writer-says-washington-swamp-wants-to-destroy-donald-trump/) to defend Trump as well, Trump returned the favor:

 [Thank you to Eli Lake of The Bloomberg View - "The NSA   FBI...should not interfere in our politics...and is" Very serious situation for USA](https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/831842652085686273) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, watch the clip for yourself where he was defending Gen. Flynn and ended it defending Trump:

 [I think as a general rule, not just Democrats but I think I do think a lot of permanent Washington  the swamp for lack of better word, and Im part of that swamp  wants to destroy Donald Trump](http://www.mediaite.com/online/chum-is-in-the-water-bloomberg-writer-says-washington-swamp-wants-to-destroy-donald-trump/)

And Trump was so happy that [he tweeted](https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/831842652085686273) this about Eli Lake:

 Thank you to Eli Lake of The Bloomberg View - "The NSA   FBI...should not interfere in our politics...and is" Very serious situation for USA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, 

* Villains from the past: Nero (24th century), Khan (20th century)  and Captain Edison (22nd century).

* Motivation: REVENGE.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 16:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eli Lake was ranting on CNN a few weeks ago defending Trump and claiming that Russia investigation is a hoax. That was before the Comey hearing where he announced to the world that Trump and his associates are indeed under FBI investigation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 03:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a great idea to get the news from inquisitr.com. The site is known for recycling very old news and repacking them in new "articles" as something fresh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris Pine Wants To Know Whats Going On With Next Star Trek Movie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 02:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
