<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3297</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 03:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's also charismatic in Justified </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 23:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually hate her because she such an annoying character, contributed nothing to the story, and wasted screen time with stupid story arcs that have absolutely nothing to do with anyone else or the rest of the show. 

We already got the dichotomy of questioning what's right and wrong with Walt and Jessie's dynamic. Which includes how far they're willing to justify their crimes and sins. Marie was an unnecessary annoying character 

Post-edit: so is anyone who is downvoting me (which means you think I'm not contributing the conversation) actually going to actually respond to my criticisms? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 21:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually think writing got better after Sorkin, especially for the Republican characters as they would usually be relegated to being scary boogie man or crazed maniacs, but it's clear they didn't know what to do with Will, so they try to expedite his story as quickly as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 21:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marie in Breaking Bad. How did this version of the character ever make it past the first draft? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 21:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Spider-man: The Animated Series, Electro and Rhino team up to take down Spidey.

Spider quips with: "Electro AND Rhino? Where did these guys meet? Computer dating?!"

It's...so awkward just because NO ONE calls it that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 19:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 2002 adaptation of The Count of Monte Cristo. The timeless story of a man wrongfully imprisoned, and his plan to bring vengeance against those that imprisoned him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, Jesus said he was the son of God, so if you're going to break some rules and taboos, go big or go home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I consider them still running unless they've been cancelled, ended, or not have any future entries in the series planned in the near future  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cowboy Bebop: [Spike's Memory](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nQXtsFFgr3w) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I thought that scene was good in terms of writing and performance, but most of the claims he makes [have been debunked](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qOhDFCcmgvY) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Wish we had more horror shows

Scream Queens, Hannibal, Bates Motel, The Exorcist, The Walking Dead, Fear the Walking Dead, Penny Dreadful, The Strain, iZombie, Outcast, From Duck Till Dawn, Ash vs Evil Dead, Stranger Things, Attack on Titan, Santa Clarita Diet, Scream: The Series, The Mist TV show is coming out, Bitten, Sleepy Hallow. 

I mean, you can argue the quality of each series and if they "count" if they're not currently airing, but there's a LOT of horror related programming on right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's just a minor distinction as it's the best TV show "currently on" as in a TV show that has premiered, will be having more episodes come out, and hasn't been cancelled or ended. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Legion is fantastic by the way. Best comic book related show in TV currently.

For me, it's still Daredevil by a country mile for best superhero show on right now. I think Legion is the best FILMED and EDITED show on TV right now, but in terms of narrative and writing, Daredevil has my vote as it's honestly one of the best shows on right now (in my opinion).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But, they got free doughnuts and coffee afterwards, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Books Were Reviewed Like Games (Lord of The Rings Edition) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the first one had the Nazi-Lovecraft-occult stuff in it.

Man, I wish Del Toro could have filmed a Hellboy 3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd give Daredevil a try. It's half a vigilante/superhero story, with the other half in law and order. It's one of my favorite shows ever made </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Police Squad!, Smart Guys, the first three seasons of Family Guy, Childrens' Hospital, Brooklyn 99, Chozen, Moonbeam City, 30 Rock, Arrested Development. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Daredevil, The Expanse, Jericho, LOST, Samurai Jack, Cowboy Bebop, Prison Break, Stranger Things, and Band of Brothers.

 The Young Pope (made it to episode 5, too religious for me)

That's too bad. I think it really is a great series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 30 Rock and Arrested Development are great.

I'd also recommend the first three seasons of Family Guy (absolutely terrific, unlike the "post-cancellation" seasons), Smart Guys (it's an online series), and Police Squad! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd recommend:

Daredevil, The Expanse, Jericho, Band of Brothers, Cowboy Bebop, Justified, Arrested Development, Legion, Samurai Jack (new season is incredible). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw...I like TellTale games </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Copyright laws are broken as Hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a wonderful moment in time. And economic boom while everyone was terrified that nuclear war would be coming the very next day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Books Were Reviewed Like Games (Lord of The Rings Edition) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. I thought the pay-off for that moment across the entire episode was fantastic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 02:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely loved this film. I will fight anyone who besmirches it's terrificness. It's so damn cheesy and good as it's LA Confidential by way of the Rocketeer. It's an early 20th century crime seriel where the good guys are good, the bad guys are bad, and it's got some snappy dialog.

"I'll make em shine like the moon, Jerry! Like the moon!"

I'm going to rewatch this movie again tonight because I love it so </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In multiplayer as a constant feature instead of a set piece?

Also, wouldn't that mean that COD copied off of Halo, especially after the Modern Warfare series? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He'll let millions die so long as he doesn't pull the trigger.

Sacrificing yourself at the alter of other people's whims. FOR SHAME!!!!!! :P /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Evidently "angry Scottish" isn't an option that developers have focused on yet.

Well, clearly they're doing something wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ANCHOVIEEES!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hitchens was a good debater. Just because he was overly assumptive or wrong in one sense doesn't take away from the strength of his arguments that he was able to prove through argumentation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Pay attention ,I was reading an Alberta Report "years ago". I no longer have the magazine because if I kept every article that interested me I would have to move out of my house.

So, you don't have the evidence and your argument is "take my word for it."

 The Catholics will always defend her because a religion founded on lies will always defend untruth. But if you do the math it adds up to a possibility.

Well, A) you haven't actually proven that's true, and B) you seem awfully quick to judge an entire group of people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have vehicles and shields in COD? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, maybe. I mean, Halo is an influential series, so maybe that is the case. I'll play the game in the future and see if it stacks up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two weapon limitations, vehicle utilization, energy shield recharging, weapon styles and tactics, armor abilities, radar, regenerating health, and Iron sites say otherwise. LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I read a report years ago that stated mother Theresa was directly responsible for more deaths than the Nazi camp system. 

Which report? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure. I think it could be a cool idea to have a "Xbox Arcade" game with Spartan Ops across the Halo galaxy taking on different threats and targets to galaxy stability (remnant, Insurrection forces, Banished, etc.) with story elements that showcase the rest of the galaxy.

There's a lot of interesting spin-off potential for Halo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Well Halos starting to look the part again but will Halo ever play like Halo again?

Yes. It has been for the last 7 years, even with minor changes. Please stop being so sensitive and hyperbolic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I dont really like 343s shiny plastic look.

That really only seems to be a problem with Halo 5 (which, to be honest, I didn't really have a problem with). I do think that this version of what the Elites look like is a good compromise between the two. They look like what "Covenant Elites" would look like in Halo 4, if there were any. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You are arguing pure semantics here.

Uh....I'm arguing the semantics that atheism is a belief (which it is, and it's not an inherent mark against the ideology). 

 The burden of the proof is on YOU for that

Yeah...for my claims....just as it is for yours. That's not what I'm arguing.

 "Atheism" is just a lack of belief in said theory.

No. It's a belief system. Specifically, claiming that you merely don't have a belief in something *causes active beliefs*. It's like you STILL haven't read the arguments.

Here's one from the article:

A further drastic problem arises if the atheist wishes to claim that his statement there is no God is not a claim or a beliefif it isnt, then it cannot be true or false. The problem is that only claims can be true or false. It makes perfect sense to ask whether a claim like It is raining today or The Maple Leafs lost again is true or false. On the other hand, it is meaningless to ask whether the colour blue, a small off-duty Czechoslovakian traffic warden, or the word Wibble are truethey are not claims and thus cannot possess a truth value.
So heres the problem for the atheist. If atheism is not a claim of any kind, then it is simply meaningless. On the other hand, if the atheist wishes to claim that his atheism is true, then that must mean that atheism is a claim, and claims need to be defended, evidence provided and reasons given. 

or even this one which ties back to the :

The first problem is that the statement atheism is just non-belief in God proves too much. What do I mean? Well, on this definition my cat is an atheist, because it does not believe in God. (I sometimes suspect cats believe they are God, but thats another story entirely.) Likewise potatoes and small rocks are also atheists, because they, too, do not possess a belief in a deity of any kind.
When I have pointed this out to atheists, I usually receive a response along these lines: But a potato cant believe anything. To which I reply: So youre now saying that atheism is the lack of belief in God by a creature that has the ability to form beliefs? This is a different claim entirelyindeed, its a positive claim. The atheist is now claiming to believe that the external world really exists (thus she is rejecting metaphysical idealism), that other minds exist, that the human mind can form beliefs, and that our cognitive faculties are broadly reliable. Each of those is a hotly debated area in philosophy.
Suddenly what looked a simple statement of non-belief (I dont believe in God) has sprouted a whole series of positive claims, popping up like mushrooms after a rainstorm. I have not yet encountered an atheist who believes that positive claims do not need to be argued for (indeed, atheists are fond of crying Evidence! whenever confronted with a religious believer) and so it is the atheists job to give evidence for each of the philosophical positions they are encamped on. If they are not willing to do the hard reasoning, well, then, they can take their place alongside the cat, the rock, and the potato. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy Macks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude! What the Hell is wrong with you!!! This is a public place!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But does it come in black? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HERE AT APPLEBEES, WE ENJOY RUINING THAT WONDERFUL MOMENT YOU WERE JUST WATCHING.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, that looks the dopest album dropping this year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You would literally have to construct an entire story to be that bad from the word "go" concerning to be worse than the animated adaptation of the Killing Joke and their romantic relationship in there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DISTRACTIN THE MONSTER WITH STEAMIN! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Written by: Quentin Tarantino </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually loved that it was awkward and understated for most of the episode and that last moment of sappy music and making out being totally earned, especially after all they've been through and how they've become peers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Why not Walrus-berg?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dug the Hell out of this episode. That ending was one of the funniest moments I've ever seen in television history with these two getting together. However, I also enjoyed their relationship and it felt like this romantic angle is a natural step. They've been fighting with one another with them becoming peers. Not to mention they've both faced incredible hardships since the beginning of their lives and they are able to find someone supportive in each other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Fallacious argument, there is no cold hard proof that there is a god (like there is of Sweden existing)

Okay, I think you probably didn't actually read the article, because it's about merely saying that atheism is a "lack of belief in a God" means that it is actually a belief, especially in the suppositions that it creates in it's wake. 

 Person A: Do you believe aliens exist?
 Person B: Not really

Yes. And this is a belief that Aliens don't exist. I can't prove aliens don't exist. Can you provide evidence that Gods and Aliens don't exist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   He would've had even less of a shot if he had ran Independent. He attacked the party too, he's not a saint.

Yeah, God forbid he criticizes any group he's apart of in intellectual honesty. He also played by the rules that the DNC stipulated, and he still got screwed over. Running as a Democrat in the short term doesn't give the party the right to screw him over like that.

 You're not exempt from it.

In FUCKING what?! I'm saying that the generalized "you're with us or against us" mentality is stupid. Group politics often runs afoul of actual logical and ethical arguments. 

 For example, at the Presidential debate, Trump told 37 lies, and Hillary told 4. That's not comparable.

Okay, I think you missed the part where I said that she lied more when NOT compared to Trump and compared to any other candidate. She's still a horrendous liar (sniper fire, anyone?) and her record in terms of supporting her stances chances with the softest breeze. 

 You know the Benghazi stuff is mostly a right-wing fueled smear right?

You know that's not at all true. Right? She lied about the Youtube video being the cause of the attack, she lied about who [she hired for security](https://www.louderwithcrowder.com/clinton-state-dept-terrorists-benghazi/), and she lied about "[not losing a single person](https://www.louderwithcrowder.com/clinton-on-benghazi-we-didnt-lose-anyone/)".

She's a liar, will blame anyone else for her mistakes, and she was a terrible candidate for President.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  atheism isn't a belief, it's a lack of belief

No, it isn't. [It's a belief](http://www.rzim.eu/the-scandanavian-sceptic-or-why-atheism-is-a-belief-system), and atheists shouldn't be ashamed that it's a belief. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listen, I voted for Hillary, but she was a terrible candidate. Outside of getting the ambassador and American soldiers killed (and constantly lying about Benghazi as well as the lie about Obama's knowledge of what happened), she has a habitual problem in terms of lying that only looked normal compared to Trump, her associations with Wall Street (saying things to them like having a "private" and "public" persona), her hawkish nature as secretary of state, her lack of getting anything done as a senator of New York, her constant backstabbing in her own party, and the clear collusion between her campaign and the DNC when she claimed there was none was enough to get people to choose anyone else besides her.

This "me against you", "us versus them", "we are right and you're wrong" mentality is what gave us candidates like Hillary Clinton and Donald Trump. 

Once again, I think the candidates for the 2016 presidential election were absolutely terrible. And no, I don't think being the lesser of two evils is good enough anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Terrence Howard sitting in the theater seeing that they replaced Cheadle with Downey Jr. for Rhodey going, "Oh, come on!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He's.. he's not wrong though.. lol

I would say he is, but that's just my personal stance, and I believe he's fully entitled to say it, because it's not encouraging violent action against people of faith.

 Why should I respect a capricious, mean-minded, stupid god who creates a world which is so full of injustice and pain?"

I would argue that it's because He's created a universe of laws, both moral and physical (with objective morality and rational intelligibility of the universe that even the most stringent of atheists put blind faith in), that dictates the possibility of this world, including the chance for joy and happiness. I do respect Stephen Fry. I think he's a smart man. I don't agree with him here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cowboy Bebop: "Ballad of the Fallen Angels." Absolutely mastercraft work in storytelling. An excellent and poignant moment for Spike as his conflict with Vicious reaches Biblical proportions with Spike facing the realization of how far he has come since his days in the syndicate, and how far Vicious has fallen. 

Daredevil: "New York's Finest". Rarely does a show talk about morality in such stunningly brilliant detail that makes me reflect on the nature of morality, yet Daredevil pulled it off brilliantly. Matt and Frank come to blows on the rooftop with their fists and wits and they argue the merits of their own ideologies in a very real way. The rest of the episode is excellent character work with Foggie and Karen, which so brilliantly sets up how the absolute chaos going on in New York because of the actions of the Punisher and Daredevil. Season 2 of Daredevil is SEVERELY underrated, and this episode proves that it's one of the best shows on TV.

Jericho: "Why We Fight". An emotional roller-coaster of conspiracies and small town survival as the townspeople of Jericho begin their fight against their New Bern neighbors. Lives are lost, lines are crossed, and an intense battle of spirit begins as the cast of characters say "nuts" to their misfortune and prepare to fight. 

Fullmetal Alchemist: "Words of Farewell". A gut-punch of an episode that blindsided me in a way no other show has done before or since (even with Game of Thrones' shocking plot turns). This series is great, and this episode cemented it as one of my favorite anime series ever made.

Trigun: "Live Through". This entire episode is dedicated to the crushing ending of the previous one as Vash recovers from his physical and mental wounds. Coming to terms with what he has done, and how he's broken his own stringent philosophy on life, Millie and Meryl try to help Vash heal while at the same time come to terms with all the tragedies they too have faced. It's a raw episode full of suffering, self-reflection, and despair, but ultimately clears the path for redemption and hope. You don't need to have a gun battle to be an engrossing tale.

Band of Brothers: "Carentan". Showcasing the chaos and harrowing feats made during war, this episode cements Easy Company as the men in the war who leaned on each other to make it through each battle. Intense action scenes, great character moments, and an excellent analysis of what people are willing to do and lose for the sake of winning a war. 

LOST: "The Constant". The metaphysical journey of Desmond as he travels across time and space is both narratively and thematically rooted in his attachment to his love for Penny. A moving episode that experimented and played with both the storytelling tools and sci-fi tropes the show employed while grounding it all in amazing character moments. 

Samurai Jack: "The Tale of X9". A somber noir story focusing on a grizzled robot tasked with hunting down Jack to save the last thing he has any attachment to. These "side-stories" are amazing, but this in particular is so impactful by making such an endearingly sympathetic (and yet layered) character with such a bittersweet ending. "Lulu...sweet thing."

Arrested Development: "Top Banana." You'll be hard pressed to find an episode of this series that people don't love, but this one (for me) is the perfect amalgamation of everything perfect with this show. Besides the hilarious visual and dialog driven comedy, the story manages to find the sweet spot of mocking family structures, while at the same time lovingly supporting and embracing it....even if it drives one crazy to be apart of.

Family Guy: "Brian Wallows and Peter's Swallows". Season 1-3 of Family Guy is among the best American comedy ever produced. I will stand by that until my dying day. The episodes coming back from cancellation?...not so much. This episode delivers hilarious laughs in all forms (flexibility of telling jokes was one of the biggest staplemarks of early Family Guy), but the personal stories of Brian dealing with an old shut-in and Peter contending with raising three baby chicks in his beard come to surprisingly emotional conclusions about losing people and enjoying the time you have with them while you can. 

The West Wing: "The Supremes". While "Two Cathedrals" is most recognized for its emotional impact, I love "The Supremes" in analyzing the fact that while Democrats and Republicans play off of each other like bickering enemies, at the end of the day, they really just want to help make the best kind of country possible. And the only way to ensure a good future for the politics of America is through healthy debate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wolfwood from Trigun, especially in showing who he kills towards the end. He questions his life and wonders if they things he had done were ever justified. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think just the idea of tolerance for other people's viewpoints on life is the most important lesson we can learn right now. I believe in a God, but I respect other peoples' opinions on the matter, including if they straight up believe in atheism. 

I personally disagree with Stephen Fry on a number of issues, but I think he's more than entitled to his opinions without blasphemy laws coming into effect. I'm glad that I live in a country where freedom of speech is cherished and valued, and I will fight to the death for someone's right to express their opinions.

Post-edit: I'm supporting Fry in this instance, and I genuinely think that this enforcement of a blasphemy comment is stupid. Am I seriously being downvoted because I'm expressing the fact I believe in a God, or that I sometimes disagree with Fry's personal opinions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hold up now, these are priests, not public school teachers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok. I'm not really big on the overall story but I just LOVE how it's filmed and edited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Marie, Walt Jr, Meth Damon, etc never have primary, focal storylines, but they are focal characters and have secondary, sometimes incomplete stories because those stories help either bring exposition, help us understand the main cast, or help drive a secondary plot point to move a primary plot point in a way that's required for the story to make sense without it simply being a point a to point b equation.

I don't have a problem when their used for effect, my problem is when we spend so much damn time on them and they add so little to the actual overall show. It would be one thing if they were reoccuring characters in supporting cast roles, but these were MAIN ACTORS that they struggled to find relevance for in a rather small cast. 

The difference with something like Game of Thrones is that it's a massive story, but uses the characters are long as they are effective in the story, and then they move on. One of the reasons the Dorne storyline gets so much hate (besides being poorly written) is that there were too many characters and sub-plots that ended up being pointless or underwhelming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (In no particular order)

Daredevil

Smart Guys

Arrested Development

Family Guy (The original run - first three seasons)

Band of Brothers

Cowboy Bebop

Trigun

LOST

The West Wing

Stargate SG-1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Legion is a good series, but I still don't consider it to be the best superhero show out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, not really a fan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Somewhat true. The GOP said the Dems rammed it through, but they meticulously worked on it, with both sides for nearly two years.

Didn't they say you could keep your original coverage and that it wouldn't be a tax? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see that it's a well-made show, but the slog through the first two seasons as well as superfluous characters that don't really add anything to the show (Marie and Walt Jr.), as well as some really questionable character moments (Skylar), keep me from loving it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anchovies.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mike Tyson Mysteries is a hilarious and creative series, and I personally prefer it as a send-up to the old Hanna-Barbara cartoons over The Venture Bros. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You made this...? ...I made this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I AM the Jedi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Isn't that a bit silly and self-fulfilling?

Only if you assume a position without actually investing time to look at the evidence. 

 The existence of followers is the proof that what the followers believe is true? 

Not the existence. The EXPLOSION of followers that flourished under the prejudice and violence of the Roman empire, the likes had never been seen before or since. 

 There's ample evidence that things lots of people have believed have been wrong, 

That's a very general statement, which could also apply to old scientific axioms, like the universe always existed instead of being created (which was something that Christians had championed for the longest time). 

 I would say the more rational explanation is that after the death of the historical Jesus, his followers all wrote books, which were able to spread his ideas further than one man giving speeches and in-person preaching could do.

I'm not doubting that his followers spread the word after Jesus' death to as far as they could. What I'm pointing out is that many of his followers were LEAVING him when he was being hunted down by the Romans. Why would they suddenly become intense advocates after a painful humiliating death of their messiah. I know there's the tendency to think of our great ancestors as far beneath in terms of intelligence, but I don't believe that 'hysterical insanity' would make any more sense then as it would now in terms of people suddenly laying down their lives for a small, unproven, moderate, peaceful way of life without seeing some kernel of truth in it. 

 You might be interested in the concept of intellectual contagion,

Which is an unclear, unproven concept which basic idea is that "ideas are contagious". That being said, that idea in itself can be thrown in any direction towards any ideology rendering it either so completely destructive that NO idea could ever possibly be salvaged (as anything from vegetarianism to what we agree the word "blue" should mean to assuming most men can't pull of mustaches means that it could be subject to "intellectual contagion"), or that it's a word that can be misconstrued to banish away any idea that people genuinely latch onto a like as a part of "herd mentality". Also, looking online, there doesn't seem to be too many places that it's discussed in a scholarly manner. 

But, let's look at it seriously. Intellectual contagion in it's forms that I've been able to find, usually relies on the idea coming from larger influential groups - not 12 guys and a dude who claims to be God. Also, these would be insolated communities with no pre-existing ideology being usurped by such a tiny and publicly reviled (by the Roman authorities) ideology. 

 but it seems like the idea of the force existing is taken for granted even by non-adherents to the Jedi belief system. 

The Force is apart of the entire universe, but it takes the faithful to be able to actually use it. Even people who have only a small devotion to it are able to utilize it if they have a theology concerning the the mystic, not if think they can quantify and use it in a scientific method. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked how they used the antagonists in the story, but I respect your viewpoint  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here you go, boss:

"Food+Time=#2" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Up with mini-skirts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And then he made ice cream have an orgy and implied anyone that's not Hereronormative is a sex-fiend. Classy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a very interpretive use of the word "information." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The key difference you skipped over is midochlorians can be measured objectively in the real concrete world. sure you have to study the force in order to harness it, but you can't deny its existence regardless. 

Well, allow me to pontificate on that. We can do science, but we still have a consistent belief that science is something that we can DO. We hold to a belief of rational intelligibility of the universe. We place faith that we can understand the mechanism of the universe through our senses and rationality (which already postulates several hotly contested areas of psychology). 

 Just because the Jedi don't understand the science behind it well enough to explain it in terms above "trust the force" doesn't mean its not just a natural scientific phenomena.

The Force isn't a superpower (which I feel that The Force Awakens just gets wrong). It's an intangible myetaphysical concept that extends beyond the realm of "the Real". Yoda's own perspectives on the force is that life exists beyond the physical existence. And the Midi-chlorians are apparently general indicators of the Force. Imagine the canary in the coal mine - the canary only alerts us to the affects of the coal mine, but it isn't the coal mine itself. Lucas, in his wisdom, wanted to make something that was universal and crafted a source of power that was both spiritual and science - of this existence and beyond it. Things like the dream sequences of Luke and Anakin, the ability to see the ghosts of the dead, and the concept of 'sensing' beyond your current area of situational awareness (across the galaxy) treats itself more like a divine gift rather than a scientific algorithm, especially with how vague and abstract the ideas become to both the characters and the audience. But I can see the other side of the argument too.  

 The Christian lord and savior cannot be scientifically measured in the real world, nor can any of his supernatural or spiritual effects. 

That's true since we don't have anyone to test miracles. My Christian belief has come through analysis of historical affects of Jesus, the claimed resurrection, Christian apologetics, the historicity of the Bible as a source of information (including archaeological discoveries), philosophical axioms I believe to be true that are apart of the Christian doctrine (including the concept of inherent morality), third party sources confirming the existence of Christ and his influence on the ancient world, and the rather sedate (very much scholarly) writings of events in the Bible relying on eye witness accounts and details of the mundane rather than expansive stories of the fantastical nature of Gods (like Greek Gods among the mortals), though there are stories of Jesus' miracles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I think it's better explained by the psychology of cults and radical political movements.

Well, there's distinct differences between religions and cults. 

 Past a certain point, adherents to fringe ideologies tend to make their beliefs inseparable from their selves. Even in the face of persecution, death, and contrary evidence, they hold onto their beliefs because they no longer know how to live without them.

These people were turned to a particular point of view when they were adults. It's not like the indoctrinating affect of raising children into particular lifestyles. They also openly questioned Jesus' teachings and were leaving him when the Romans began hunting him down. That doesn't sound like unwavering devotion. These people also weren't grown in a petri dish. They lived their lives and were exposed to the politics and religions of that time. It's not a hidden commune in Waco, Texas. 

 Now, transplant that same belief system to 2000 years ago, in a time and place where proper skepticism was not quite vogue, and you can imagine that it might catch on even quicker, perhaps even becoming a major world religion of some sort.

I don't believe that to be the case because this is so out of the ordinary even for THAT time. Why would a poor carpenter bring such fury and anger against him at that point in time in history (the crucifixion of Jesus is historical canon at this point, which automatically raises a boat-load of questions), be condemned to one of the worst deaths imaginable through a humiliating process, and have THAT story be the rallying cry those once skeptical followers of Jesus were now crying through the streets at the pain of death. If they thought it would just lead to their lives ALSO ending, that wouldn't make any sense for the evidence, but if they had witnessed the resurrection, that would be a believable reason for the sudden uptick in both the community exponentially growing (which is unheard of for any other religion rather than a slower process of growth; including the story of the 500 people seeing Jesus post-death without any previous knowledge of the guy) as well as the disciples becoming fully indebted to the teachings of Christ where they were willing to suffer those same pains of death for something that they were terrified to be associated with, and didn't fully believe in when Christ was being sent off to die on the cross (if they were abandoning him).  

With Scientology, it IS a cult. It's exclusive, secretive, controlling, coercive, totalitarian, and seclusive. Christianity was known (even back then) for being inclusive, open, encouraging values of brotherhood, peace, and forgiveness, and the main symbol of the movement was a man who openly accepted his death and never commanded others to fight for his survival (even quoting the famous "live by the sword, die by the sword" mantra).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay. I respect your opinion on the matter for that. For myself, it was a more character based look at these people rather than some of the more eccentric fantastical superhero stories in the FOX, WB, or MCU library. I enjoyed it in the way that it focused on smaller character moments being the larger triumphs rather than a Maguffin or plot element being the big payoff for the cast.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boy, that's a stretch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From a certain point of view.

^Dew ^it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is this a specific response to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Whole lot of fast talking"....what? Are you saying that the apostles of Jesus were literally content with proclaiming their religion and being put to death after they had began leaving Jesus before his death because of....fast talking? And what do you mean by "fast talking"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except the Book of Mormon's inaccuracies in terms of archeological discoveries have disproven a great majority of the book, whereas the archeological of the ancient world have done nothing but vindicate the Bible's accuracies: [here](http://www.equip.org/article/biblical-archaeology-factual-evidence-to-support-the-historicity-of-the-bible/),  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  not Jesus as the son of God, of which there is no objective proof. 

I would cite the explosion of devout believers in the face of being executed for being Christians as a pretty darn good indicator for the resurrection (among other pieces of historical evidence like ancient scholars remarking on Christians), especially after his own followers were abandoning him towards the end of his life. Looking into history, there hasn't been anything yet that proves Christ's divinity and resurrection, there's a whole lot of evidence in history regarding the Christian following after his death that would really only make sense if the resurrection took place. But, that's just my perspective. 

 The difference being that it isn't really a religion since it requires no faith to believe in, only scientific and objective proof.

Actually, it requires the study of the force with an ethical doctrine leading in terms of understanding and harnessing it. Midichlorians can be measured, but it seems like they're general indicators of the presence of the force rather than measuring the force itself. 

In A New Hope, Luke is only able to destroy the death star because he gives his faith over to the force (his spirituality) and not his targeting computer (his technology). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Are we blind?! Deploy the upvotes!!!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Dumb and Dumber sequel as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved The Amazing Spider-man films but I respect your opinion on the matter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, Christianity is a religion and the evidence for Jesus has been on the side of him being a real, yet it's still a religion because you're following tenants of morality and a specific doctrine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, maybe Luke since Obi-wan and Yoda were still tied to some unmovable beliefs in "Return of the Jedi" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And then the Senate murdered all the Jedi and the ruling government hunted down the survivors </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10/10 would Idris again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That means he's on the frontline, not hiding away behind barriers, like a real console warrior :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For myself (I may be in the minority), I thought Jessica Jones was the "worst". It had three really solid first episodes, and then went kind of nuts in a bad way towards the end, even moreso than Luke Cage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For myself, I think Iron Fist is just....'okay.' It's competent enough not to be bad, but not interesting enough to be good. Just a perfectly mediocre show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's absolutely fantastic in both seasons of Daredevil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He just seems to be responding to the claims made in "The Newsroom" and arguing against those points. He doesn't seem to making his claims as the source of his self-worth. He does admit when the show is right in terms of listing and clarifies why America is in those particular rankings (like life expectancy and technology). 

Your argument seems to be based on ad-hominems against the guy rather than his actual arguments. I disagree with your assessments that he's anxious (seems particularly calm and composed to me) and he seems slightly agitated at most, but I wouldn't even come close to calling it hostile. He's not Alex Jones in anger or Bill Maher in terms of self-secured smugness, and cites all of his sources and reasonings in the video. 

  that a 5 minutes fictional speech that raises very valid criticisms 

Are you saying that because it's a fictional speech that he shouldn't take it seriously? But you then say it raises very valid criticisms. Are you saying that the show should or shouldn't be critically addressed for the real world claims?

 hostile against anything not American or left of centre.

How is addressing directly claims made by the show "not America or left of center"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How so? He didn't seem very insecure to me, especially for someone putting a video out for the public. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 06:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell even West Wing fantasized both sides of the aisle. It might be liberal fan fic on the whole, but John Goodman and Alan Alda are like your archetype of the well liked conservative.

Yeah, but with Alan Alda and William Fichtner, those character came after Sorkin's departure, and Goodman's character was seen as overly-authoritarian, war-mongering, unsympathetic, and unfocused (for as good as Goodman is in the role), and finally got better when season 5 started up as a more well-rounded character.

Even Steven Crowder dissected the [infamous Newsroom scene](https://youtu.be/qOhDFCcmgvY) in which Sorkin's political leanings become more obvious, and that's partially because Sorkin is a great writer, and has his politics deeply engrained in it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 05:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really mad that the Unforgiven remake in Japan has an all-Japanese cast instead of reflecting the American story. 

Oh, wait a minute, no I'm not, because I'm a sensible adult and understand that remaking stories in a different country can change races and story elements and I don't need to throw a temper tantrum about it. 

Also, we already have the best version of "Journey to the West" and it was called "[Enslaved: Odyssey to the West](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Dhcj827385w)" and it even had the amazing Andy Serkis.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 05:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I almost woke the house up with how much I was laughing at this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kingdom of Heaven was an all right movie, with a better directors cut, but I felt like it really misunderstood the crusades </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Crusades. Just reading Rodney Stark's "God's Battalions" made me see just how complex the beginning, middle, and end of the Crusades were and what really caused everything to happen.

In my opinion, "Kingdom of Heaven" (even the directors cut) was a disservice to the actual events that happened, and completely missed the intricacies of both religious and political motivations for the war, as well as the context of the history that was going on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same with G4.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To accuse someone of being guilty because he is being accused, and not when he's actually gone through the courts. And claiming that settlements and the number of accusation further solidifies his guilt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The amount of money, time, and public viewing high profile cases like this is pretty high. Settling out of court isn't an inherent admission of guilt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Yeah I haven't finished 2 yet but 1 wrapped me up pretty great. 2 also kept using the "fetch 3 of this thing" and it got kinda repetitive.

I felt the total opposite. I thought that that was one of the biggest problems with Darksiders 1 with 2 really changing things up, but I respect your opinion on the matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe have character swapping like with "Arkham Knight" or "GTA V". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Guess who didn't get kicked out?! THIS GUY!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DmC: Devil May Cry could be a good template if they decided to mimic Dante's combat style for Strife. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
