<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3288</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 13:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. So very much. Red dradgon is borderline impossible to play online because of all the leavers. Right now I think most of the leavers in SD (including myself) are related to crashes and bugs, but the lack of any leaver punishment makes me fear that ST will turn to Red dragon pretty fast, where 60 % of your team leaves during the first 4 minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 13:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not quite what you are looking for, but Steven Runcimans "The fall of constantinople" is a great book about the final years of the empire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 13:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Besides the rts games you mentioned, like total war and Age of empires 2 I don? think those games exist. As one pointed out there AC revelation but after the fall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 13:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, do you even game of thrones?
If Meryn trant can say it so can I! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 14:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 11:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the unknown edges of the world are some of the most interesting places in planetos, like what is beyond the wall, annd the islands of the south and along Sothoryos, The ibbenese and such. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 23:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The reason I said "other than Silmarillion" is because I have already read it /though many years ago).

And if my memory serves me correctly that books covers the creation of Arda and the first few ages and the rise and demise of Morgoth.
Right now I just want to know if there are any books about middle earts general history and race info akin to books like "The world of ice and fire", "The world of thedas", "The world of the witcher"... (Honorary mention of the world of kong, a natural history of skull island as well)
So, art, general lore about lots of things I what I`m after. And it bothers me because, as I said earlier, I know these books exist, my old school had them and I was stupid enough to never read them because I was caught up in Game of thrones at the moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 13:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if we will se any game like it in the near future. This game is the new game benchark for me. It stands a king amongst titans.

Side note; i really hope we will se more of the witcher one day, perhaps to ofir (?) really liked the few bits we got in hearts of stone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 13:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, thx for the heads up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 13:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. I actually found something that peaked my interest,the books call "The complete guide to middle earth" and "The people of middle earth". I`m looking for those compendium type of books, that give a good overview of all the racees and locations  (and history) of the middle earth universe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any lotr/middle earth lore books? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 12:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are there any lore books covering the history of various races, peoples locations etc for the lotr universe? I`m not looking for the silmarillion, but books more like "The world of ice and fire" and "the world of the witcher" style lore books, preferably with art.
I remember my old school having 2 such books, but I can`t remember their names and searching on the internet didn`t help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 12:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IMO the best lotr game there ever was. Still looking for it whenever I see a game store selling old ps2 games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PLS fix all the online crashed related to Disconnect or desynch, I can`t even finish an online game withouth having some sort of crash of disconnect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yout have been disconnected from server </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get this message constantly, "You have been disconnected from the server: Your computer is to slow to play the game"

Which is just silly, i play on hight setting and play Wargame on ultra (and this game does NOT look better than red dragon)
It always happens during the last 10-5 minutes of a match, and prior to the Disconnect There is no lag og any kind. Bug? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 13:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Darthmod, no doubht. Takes everything you love and improves on it by far, but still retains the original feel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. I for one want more micromanagement and controll, not less. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 13:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IMO the frontline system is one of the best new additions to the rts genre i years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good, I`m gonna buy it then. Love tropico. Too bad there are no other games like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Game crash when iditing video options </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can`t add images to text for some reason, but the craash happens when I tried to change video options. It says : Critical error: Could not (re) init graphic device. Reason: changemod failure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So i also includes epic meltdown, hostile takeover and paradise lost? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is included in the tropico 5 complete collection on ps4? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 11:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The text really doesn`t tell me much, I wanna now I it includes all the tropico 5 dlc or just a few. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 11:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AMD. Happened to a friend of me too, just random game shut down without any error message. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 11:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nah, you can get just as close, if not even close, in wargame.

On a side note: What options to I have to change to remove the grun trails and the oversized unit and bombs when zoomed out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 22:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The graphics are a surefire downgrade from wargame, and the explosiosn are as lackluster as it gets. Sound should be improved as well, though the sound of distant battles occuring on the other side of the map in large mp battles is badass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 22:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Need a bit of polishment (and online stability fixes)

Kinda miss all the detail from wargame, loved the fact that I could learn everyhting I wanted at a the info deck. But there are also some improvements in SD that I love, like the fact that U can urder your troops to move in deployment phase, and that u can press c to see waht areas are visible or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had one game drop me 3 minutes before the game was over because my computer was to slow to run the game or something (BS, everything ran fine), and just now the game just random crashed on my without any error message whatsoever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 13:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 12:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice, downloading the game right now so time to get some tips! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, and the next time somone makes and fps pls remove the fps part! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That could be pretty cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 09:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, I read about mazdamundi i the lizardmenn army book and the abilities he had were way toned down from the crazines describes in the lore. He can shake the ground to stun enemies, destroy specific buildings (could be usefull in seiges to destroy towers) etc. A bit of a let down but if the could summon a vulcano uner your fett people would go all cry baby. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 09:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More content doesn`t mean it has to be called a sequeal. It`s a game that expands upon the fist, thus an expansion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 22:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then it seems the total war fans must endure the most dreadfull og all conflicts, the fanboy wars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I didn`t really understand how many hisotrical fans there were out there. BUT, To be honest I`m more astounded by the warhammer only fans. Total war is first and foremost a historical rts franchise, and most of the old fanbase play the series because of that. I bet many of those fans are wondering how their beloved franchise went from featuring mount horse combat to dinosaurs riding dinosaurs and flying magical toads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? To be honest I`m more astouned by the warhammer only fans. Total war is first and foremost a historical rts franchise, and most of the old fanbase play the series because of that. I bet many of those fans are wondering how their beloved franchise went from featuring mount horse combat to dinosaurs riding dinosaurs and flying magical toads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Warhammer only fans don`t stand people with different opinions ( that is the total war historical core fanbase) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sales have nothing to do with the community wanting a total war game. It just shows that there are a lot of warhammer fans out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2018? Never heard of that. Source? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 40 buck price tags would be perfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
