<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1565</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 13:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hiking  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stockhouse is full of jerkoffs like that, which is why I started coming here for discussion. I am hoping like hell they stay where they belong, which is anywhere but Reddit, but I am seeing more and more comments like that appearing here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You could sell sauted raccoon's assholes on a stick, and Americans would buy them and eat them."

- George Carlin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at the charts. Draw trend lines and view the company chart relative to moving averages.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only role oil has in this is related to the CAD. So if you are going short any Canadian stocks based on short-term fluctuations in the CAD you are playing a very dangerous game. Currency changes direction on a dime. Not to mention a number of the weed stocks just bounced off support, so they have technically just confirmed the end of the recent downtrend, more or less. Lastly, since when does a merger automatically result in a negative stock price? Last I checked, accretive mergers structured with attractive financing can be a positive for the stock price. 

Short with caution.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 13:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your Oma reminds me of the teacher from the movie A Christmas Story.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blazing Saddles.....the entire movie really, but specifically the scene when The Waco Kid is waking up upside down in jail, and first sees Sheriff Bart. 

Bart: Are we awake?
Waco Kid: We're not sure. Are we...Black?
Bart: Yes, we are.
Waco Kid: Then we're awake, but we're very puzzled.

The way that Gene Wilder delivers this short scene alone is proof of just how wonderful an actor he was. The rest of the movie is just as good. A true classic!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
