<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3640</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [META] Here's a way to backup files to other cloud drives so you won't lose them permanently. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 13:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I should have probably posted this sooner but I never got around to it. I dont post anything so I have no idea how this works but basically this is basically about MEGA link takedowns and how you can kinda save the file before it gets lost to removed. Also saving the hassle of submitters who lose their uploads.   

Theres a site called [Multcloud](https://www.multcloud.com/) It allows you to send files to yourself on other cloud platforms. 

For example you have a Dropbox account (I have 50gbs on my dropbox account but normal users have 2.5 gbs :( , but dont worry theres plenty of other clouds that also work with it) and you want to download say a movie but its a bit too big say 10 gbs (really hate encountering a movie I want thats over 5gbs, but hey its free, can people please maybe separate them into 1gb files, not everyone has great internet speed, or maybe its just us Australians with crappy internet speed) 

Back on track again, say your internet is too slow or the place you are in say a library doesnt have great internet speed and you really want the file but you cant download it cos youre in a library and its illegal (its illegal at home as well...I think). Well guess what you can now copy it to another cloud and then copy it back when you can finally downloading it. 

It takes about an hour per gb(for me), but if you do it overnight you cant even tell.

I really suggest someone getting a Baidu account, there was a promotion or something going on last year where you could get a 1TB account for free if you signed up or something last year, never got around to it as I was too lazy, even now Im avoiding work by typing this up :( 

Back on topic by getting a Baidu account you can copy movies from MEGA over to Baidu so you have a backup copy of it even if it gets taken down. And also! It makes the request thread easier to fill if they want past movies that have been taken down. Annnnnnd also it saves the submitters time if it gets taken down, so all they would have to do is copy the file from Baidu back into MEGA and whoalah the file is back on Mega and the request can be filled. 

P.S I really feel like there should be more likes on posts, like this subreddit has 31, 404 people and theres only 12 upvotes? What? Im sure theres more way more people who downloaded the file. But idk nvm whocares, the OP does thats who, right?

tl;dr Theres meant to be some kinda tl;dr thing right, which sums all the stuff up with less waffle.
MultCloud which allows you to backup files to other cloud drives and move files around to other cloud drives. [Multcloud](https://www.multcloud.com/)

Want to save MEGA files online?
1. Connect another service to multcloud
2. Move files back and forth.
3. Voil

Thank you /u/TheGoodSheep for telling me to shorten the article.

Im sorry for all the waffling ( i'll edit it maybe) but since this isnt summative for school, I typed out my thoughts as well. 3 

edited: links and tl:dr
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
