<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1143</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New Zealand

Correct, even spelled it right

in order: syria, egypt, iraq, yemen

Adolf Hitler, Joseph Stalin, Leon Trotsky, Joseph Tito, and Sigmund Freud

correct

[this](http://y1.ifengimg.com/644db11e181e00f8/2014/0219/rdn_5304b5491e4f1.jpg), pronounced 'biang' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> updated, three more questions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which country has the highest sheep to human ratio?

What do you call the fear of long words?

[Which](https://qph.ec.quoracdn.net/main-qimg-4837b1a0a44f0e617e5c5f4879608bf2.webp) flag [is](https://qph.ec.quoracdn.net/main-qimg-d4466fd43fe323544cbef51dca66b3c8.webp) the [flag](https://qph.ec.quoracdn.net/main-qimg-5c4ec7944407564b573faf5db220f030.webp) of [Egypt](https://qph.ec.quoracdn.net/main-qimg-ca73577adff95999633f3d0c9d74b6c1.webp)?

In January 1913, which famous people can you find in Vienna?

What do you call the type of nuclear reaction that happens near room temperature?

What is the most complex Chinese character/symbol? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 02:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a question tho. If you only use three rooms in your big house, and live somewhere else half the year, why did you buy that big house? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's this little mountain range... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, if the elves took off the rings after they discovered sauron's plan, why did galadriel have her ring on in the fellowship? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they're fine for entertainment. I know the reputation of reposters are bad but a lot of the stuff I do find entertaining. So I don't care if they are shills or not. If I want serious discussion, I go to smaller subs like this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best mobile CSS I've seen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. It's like a breath of fresh air. The logo is so simple and elegant, I love the different shades of purple going on there. The way you represented CSS with the brackets is pretty clever, and the background is nice and clean, it kinda reminds me of kurzgesagt.

...That's all I have to say. You can hurry along now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I learnt that from the hunger games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't seeing infection in your veins blood poisoning? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to call it hard knowledge and soft knowledge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, you better start soon, cause Antarctica's melting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh. What do your bakeries sell? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So is the only real benefit of using credit cards scam protection? I don't see why otherwise. It seems too easy to give in to temptations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 01:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Put the engine in reverse!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 01:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why isn't it sold in a bakery? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 01:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried to help someone who wrote 0x8=1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have never been religious, but I can understand the sediment of an afterlife, like even if I fucked up in this life, if I was a good person there will be a better life waiting for me, and this time it's eternal. It's like a safety net, and when it gets taken away you get anxious. 

I don't know, never put my hopes into gods and all that. I just try to build my hopes on real things, like family and friends, and food. One day I'll have to return what I've borrowed. The way I see it, you're gonna die either way, so why stress over it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually it makes me realize what little time I have, and it makes me appreciate my family.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Humans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, more logic than grammar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 03:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instrument. It would make me incredibly happy, and I can work as a musician in basically any gig.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 03:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also that really old book with lots of pictures that no one knows what it means. People think it's about biology. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We had too many of those recently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u/PaulsRedditAccount </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favourite villian quote? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am not who you think I am; I am not who I think I am; I am who I think you think I am. -Thomas Cooley </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google. They're just bidding their time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *walk* into mordor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey, it's not how many times you fall down, it's how fast you get back up again that matters. So don't be afraid to fall. Sometimes you have to, but someone will be there to catch you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you hide it so well though? It's so hard to imagine someone perfectly well and happy by day, and a wreck at night. And why? Why do you crash without trying to get help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Contact them, and ask to schedule a lesson. See if their price, personality and such match up to yours, if their times are convenient ( if they go to your house, when are they available, etc). The first lesson is just to test the waters, and it's fine if you decide not to continue. 

My personal opinion - I'm a relatively beginner also - is to find a teacher who's really serious and attentive to detail. Posture's really important in the beginning, and you'll want a teacher who'll set you in the right path early, and not leave a bad habit that'll come back and bite you in the butt years later. My thought is that a bit nitpicky is better than leaving things unsaid. Also heard from my friend that Russians are good teachers; supposedly very serious and strict.

Please use common sense when taking my advice. This is coming from a half-arsed pianist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does it work on mobile? I can't seem to win </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a P-115, and used a P-45, and I can honestly tell you... They both don't feel like a real piano.

Just kidding, no there's no difference, buy the P-45 if it's cheaper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah, heard of violins and maybe piano(?) that sounds better as it ages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 02:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't want to jump to conclusions hastily, but this is queer. I had a good impression of the WP mods, but now... I don't know, further research is needed. I've been wondering why you haven't been showing up at writing prompts recently, guess I now know why. It's a shame really, I think their ban is a bit extreme. You can still respond to the prompts I guess, just not there. Here's to a swift two months passing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yuo hav weird road in palau... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> White on panel 3 is what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some things that get better with use? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An example I can think of are some leather suitcases, the leather gets softer as it's more used. What are some other things that get better with age? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 03:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am not know what saw but is beautifu 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 03:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 25C is wayyy too hot for comfort, 15-20C is my zone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 03:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know. I'm here, might as well make the most of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 03:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's never enough time to do all the nothing you want. But hey, a year or two later you'll look back and wonder why you've stressed out so much. Everything is minor in the grand theme of things. Don't set your expectations so high you fall flat on your face. Nothing ever goes exactly according to plan, so just roll with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I love lord of the rings for its music... enjoy! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 00:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 02:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant xkcd: https://xkcd.com/1803/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The CIA headquarters has 231 reviews on google maps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 02:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 01:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why was it called the Holy *Roman* Empire then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 21:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the detailed answer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 21:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever you go out of doors, draw the chin in, carry the crown of the head high, and fill the lungs to the utmost; drink in the sunshine; greet your friends with a smile, and put soul into every hand-clasp. Do not fear being misunderstood and do not waste a minute thinking about your enemies. Try to fix firmly in your mind what you would like to do; and then, without veering off direction, you will move straight to the goal. Keep your mind on the great and splendid things you would like to do, and then, as the days go gliding by you will find yourself unconsciously seizing upon the opportunities that are required for the fulfillment of your desire, just as the coral insect takes from the running tide the elements it needs. Picture in your mind the able, earnest, useful person you desire to be, and the thought you hold is hourly transforming you into that particular individual Thought is supreme. Preserve a right mental attitude  the attitude of courage, frankness, and good cheer. To think rightly is to create. All things come through desire, and every sincere prayer is answered. We become like that on which our hearts are fixed. Carry your chin in and the crown of your head high. We are gods in the chrysalis.  Elbert Hubbard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 16:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 16:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> should totally post this to r/watercolor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I stream music but mute it, will it still use data? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 16:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 15:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It reminds me of what Earth was like before we grew up!

Is she a goddess then? This sentence kinda reminds me of 'the egg'. Your story gives me a nice vibe, I like it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll look into that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What colour scheme would you recommend? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
