<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1137</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 08:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im hyped af! Hope it turns out awsome! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 19:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> really hard to take 2 seconds to give me a tip, i hate these kinds of subreddits, fuckin shit. Fuck you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Want to buy a new laptop, need help! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 22:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 10:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the computer trying to boot on something? Or does it simply restart everytime it starts up?

Does it stop after you've done this a couple of times, or is there no way of entering the PC?

If you have not tried this, try and get into Your BIOS settings when the computer is starting up. Im not sure wich button Your computer uses but it's usually F9, F10, F11 or F12.

Then when you're in the BIOS, check Your Boot settings. Check out the boot order, is it looking weird? Is the pc trying to boot on something that does not exist? 

You could also try and reset the boot settings to default and see if this helps.

Hope you'll solve the issue! :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 10:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god, im at a Windows Server Course RIGHT NOW, and I we learned binary yesterday and our teacher just said this joke hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 10:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends if it is in another Country. 
I could have moved somewhere else here in Norway and that would probably be fine with me, but to move as far as to another country, I doubt I would be able to do that. But that's just me. It is different for everyone :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahahaha oh my god this is perfect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 12:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! :) I'll try and do my best :) Im not sure if it matters, but I was kinda drunk the whole weekend too, (I remember everything) but I still felt like shit on sunday :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First relationship </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 12:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, i've never posted here before, but if this post does not belong here feel free to tell me.

I need some advice, I've during the past month gotten into a relationship with this girl. On sunday i woke up with her, etc etc.

BUT, why do i feel so uncomfortable thinking about the whole situation? I just have this uneasy feeling everytime i think of this. Am I scared of actually going into a relationship? I've wanted a GF for a long time but when i finally meet one i just cant shake off that feeling.

I've never been in a seriois relationship before, this is new to me, could that be why? Am i scared of commitment? 

Have anyone else felt this before?

Right now i think i will just let it flow and see what happens. Hope someone here can have some advice for me. Thanks!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 01:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck off faggot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How can I deal with my new annoying co-worker? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 12:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 08:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds pretty nice actually :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For alle som vil se en som roaster norske youtubere </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 16:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 10:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I collect gasmasks and CBRN gear, i also enjoy taking my rifle up to the shooting range, just to shoot for a few hours. Its fun and challenging! :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 00:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you but i managed to fix it! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 00:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha yes they do enjoy floating </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sitting in a chair is overrated! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 20:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 19:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Warriors! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 23:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice, thanks! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 12:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds awsome! I'll fix this right away, thanks! :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 08:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love dr pepper! This sounds perfect!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 23:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you guys so much for the help! Really appriciate it! :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 22:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao hahaha okey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
