<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2840</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 15:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can eat as much as you wish in front of Muslims, you are under no obligation to fast with us.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 15:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fahad
Laith
Faris  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 13:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The GE shows prices of yesterday, so it probably just ridiculously increased in price the day you sold it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 08:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also find it very easy. I do not understand why it's "hard" is just inconvenient for me. Why wait 45 mins for a movie to download when I have it already for me to watch it on Netflix?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 08:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to swear by torrenting. After I got my brother's Netflix, I haven't looked back since. Being able to watch basically anything without having to find a torrent and waiting is magic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 07:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well how often do we really light fires? I make maybe 7 fires a year, nowhere near enough to learn how to do it without fluid. I just wanna get it over with and chill with my fam.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 07:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where the fuck do you teach? How do people not know this?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 07:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There: a place/what to use if the other two don't work. Ex: look over there!

Their: someone's belongings. Ex: Give their things back Johnny I don't wanna deal with your shit. 

They're: they are. Ex: They're out by the tower. 

Your: something that belongs to you. Ex: yo pass me your phone. 

You're: you are. Ex: you're so good at eating hotdogs! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 07:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Manual cars for people who like driving: more immersive and fun way to drive. 

Manual cars for people who want to get from point A to B: more work, more annoying. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 07:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There: a place/what to use if the other two don't work. Ex: look over there!

Their: someone's belongings. Ex: Give their things back Johnny I don't wanna deal with your shit. 

They're: they are. Ex: They're out by the tower.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 07:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. I couldn't run for my life a few months back. Hit me like a ton of bricks. I've been running regularly and it feels great! At first I kept thinking I'm not making any progress, then I realized that a distance I couldn't run became cake. Changed my life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 07:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you holy shit this is so true. Whenever I'm debating with someone and I find out I'm wrong, I back out and accept defeat. When they're wrong, they ratfuck their way into making it look like they won. They don't like debating with me because I don't play their little charade or enable them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 06:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus fucking Christ this right here. I was debating with a friend about bashr alassad. I said he's an asshole and shit leader, he thinks he's a saint for backing Russia(?) and he kept saying "no you're wrong, that's all propaganda" even when I pull up different sources and REAL LIFE PEOPLE FROM SYRIA!!! He still denies that Assad did anything bad and is a saint.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 17:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Say yes to the good things in life, say no to the bad. Only one of my friends who has never smoked or done shisha(hookah) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 16:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "A relationship is 60/40, with both sides trying to give 60" -I forgot who said this. And it's paraphrased.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 06:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just don't try to chase girls or show affection in public(dont kiss is what I'm saying). You should be good to go, the country is nice to foreigners, be friendly and don't worry lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 06:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try to get your time down as much as possible with the current meothod, then explore other algorithms. I did this because when I got my time down to 1 min and 15 secs I understood how the cube operates. Learn F2L when your time is really down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 06:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try to get your time down as much as possible with the current meothod, then explore other algorithms. I did this because when I got my time down to 1 min and 15 secs I understood how the cube operates. Learn F2L when your time is really down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow great job! I'm so glad that I've actually inspired someone to learn it! I found a few sneaky loopholes in solving the cube, so if you need anything, pm me yea? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 21 degrees is the temperature that our bodies are used to. When the surrounding air is 21 degrees, then you won't feel especially cold, but you won't feel hot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [LPT] never set your ac under 21 degrees Celsius, it'll last longer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My AC guy told me that if you set it below that, then the compressor will be constantly on, which is a very bad thing if you want it to last longer. If it's at 21+, then it won't need the compressor. I don't have central heating/cooling, so it might only apply to single units.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [15/M] Guy from Bahrain wants to talk to literally anyone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 10:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heyo I'm Saeed, and I wanna talk to you. I don't care what about, as long as it's intresting. Some of my hobbies/intrests are:-
History
Art(can't make it for the life of me but I love seeing art lol)
Playing cards
Rubik's cubes
Books
Politics

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 10:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm here for you. If you ever need to rant or vent to me, don't hesitate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
