<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2621</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was staying at a buddy's on campus apartment for the night because my car broke. A roommate said I could use their bed since they would be staying at their girlfriend's dorm. The ra caught him and sent him back to his apartment and he forgot I was there. He got naked in the room and started crawling into bed when he woke me up and I saw everything. Tall slim mocha twink, 6pack starting to show. Long dark as night soft cock dangling. He said fuck, put boxers on and told me to scooch over. We cuddled together and slept the rest of the night away. I woke up to his wood poking through his boxers. Went to a take a shower and jerked furiously  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What could a guy do that'd immediately melt your heart? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Oh crap I wanted to keep this conversation going because I have genuine interest but I suck at starting conversations via text. Wanna help and choose a topic?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 05:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't lie to people about yourself...why does this need said.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 05:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always notice the messages I just have more important things to do at the moment or not m just not in the mood to be flirty. Sometimes it's because I haven't made up my mind if I like you yet and you are trying to move too fast.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beds  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An ever living shit ton of Vicks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zack your girlfriend is still in love with me and is planning to dump you right after college. Also Zack, I hate you and your alt-right ways, you ruined my best friend with your tiny dick, yeah she showed me the pictures.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Second play-through with all my gear and skills  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hamburger  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Coming soon to own on VHS" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hamburg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite bar is becoming popular with gay people, they are ruining the place...and I've slept with a lot of them so it's weird lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't do anything today that can't be undone tomorrow  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it's when someone touches my neck unexpectedly. I was kidnaped when I was four and don't think about it a lot, pretty much just let that go but the moment someone touches my neck in surprise I'm back to being a scared and confused four year old.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 06:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah they do but everyone says I have a many voice in person...it's weird </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much. It helped make me who I am and on good days I really like me so it's all good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would you describe it as being misplaced?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get my degree in august, I'm poor as hell right now and looking for a new job. My gpa is absolutely shit but I have a plan. I want some finical stability then I'm going to start taking online courses to boost my gpa so I can get into a masters degree program. It'll be hard, but my family does it's best work when the odds are stacked against us.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THIS

I suffered from fear of better options and let a guy get away (we became friends later and learned it would never work out) and there was another guy that I liked and he liked me but he wanted to play the field some more. He just called me and we had a very emotional conversation about how he thought I wouldn't be able to move on without him and he thought he'd be able to just step back into my life. He is worried that he threw away all of his meaningful relationships for one night stands. 

Don't let fobo get the better of you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend owns an old Boy Scouts camp site with a big pool, obstacle course and all. Everyone gets naked there at night; gay, straight, bi, anything. I've only gone there a couple times but it's always amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trolling really makes me sad. I am not interested in your trolling, I clicked the link because I wanted to see what you think about an issue or to offer some advice and possibly learn something. 

When you post something on the internet you get a chance to come into a strangers life and for a few moments you are changing them. Please post what you really think and feel, not this trolling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The upper level classes get ya sometimes. Plus you have to remember that there are some people taking 20 credit hours a semester with two jobs (60hours a week) just so they can afford college and at the same time take care of a dying family member, but that's just my experience... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was kidnaped for about 15 minutes when I was four. The land lady can running out when she noticed what was going on and was beating on the van until the guy let me go. I don't remember much of what happened it my parents tell me about it every so often. If someone touches my neck when I'm not expecting it I freeze up and don't feel right for the rest of the night. The guy was caught, apparently he kidnaped kids, raped them and then most were never found again. I'm very lucky. I don't look up anything about him though because it took me a long time to forget his face, I don't want it in my dreams again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm bi and have the problem that women always think I'm going to leave them for a man and men think I'm going to leave for a woman. straight people call me gay. Every single person I hang out with thinks I'm into them and my friends that are couples keep trying to sleep with me (this one is a big issue). I just want to hang out with my friends and get drunk with them without the fear of them trying to fuck me. In my friend group the gay guy doesn't get picked on because they say it's not right but they hold nothing back with me. I constantly hear someone say go sit on a dick and then they chuckle. It's really annoying, plus every girl I've ever dated "takes credit" for me coming out. It's none of those rude women's credit. I came out because a wonderful friend I almost dated helped me get there. She was wonderful and supportive of it, even though she is a manipulative bitch lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 01:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol the guy I'm seeing now is just under 5'4". It's definitely interesting  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just tell him you thought he wasn't down for the date and you made plans with a friend who is excited to see you so you can't cancel. Then say something like "what other day are you free so we can get the date set and this doesn't happen again lol" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes you have to swim upstream through a river of shit to get where you wanna be in life. If blowing him is going to make your path a bit easier then go for it. Don't hate yourself for it, you do this for you and your dreams.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm bi and find that women like being my friend, though they are really protective of their husbands or boyfriends around me... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, especially after he says something dumb lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is gonna sound weird but I'm always uncomfortable when someone else makes plans for the first meet up. I like to ask the other person out, when I get asked out I have a couple moments of panic deciding if I like the guy and how far I'd be willing to go. So while I'm panicking I'm a bit wishy washy about the plans. After I've thought about it some more I almost always say yes. 

I suggest you go on a date with the tinder guy and make plans for some other day with the other guy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad you are alive. Stay safe out there. you made it out of this with a great story, it could have gone much worse. Go smell some roses and eat your favorite sweet, if you weren't as lucky then you may not have been able to do that anymore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't judge him m too harshly. He's in uni and is trying to come up with ideals of his own. The best thing to do is to keep asking him questions and make him defend his opinions, hopefully he won't be too prideful to drop wrong ones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's nice for checking out if the cute guy at the bar/gym/college/restaurant/party/museum/library is gay. I use it to double check my gaydar  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a bad habit of talking back to people who are homophobic around me. For context I'm 6'4" and a pretty decent size. I usually just say smart ass remarks...until, I was dating a guy who is around 5'6" Mexican scrawny, pretty much a twink. We were walking through town when a guy around my size in a camo hoodie shoulder checks my date and says "fuck homos". I turned around and gave him a flat tire and said fuck you. He punches me in the chest. (For this part you should know that I grew up in a trailer park in a shit part of a city, I've been fighting since I was old enough to leave the yard) I stomp on his foot punch him in the face and hit him between the legs. Then my date and I ran. He chased us for a bit but I used to go jogging every night back then and that fucking twink could run lol


No idea why I told this story, was just reminded of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keto is great at loosing weight, one of the best diets out there for sheer simplicity but it's not good at keeping the weight off. When you come off keto you have to slowly add carbs back into your diet at the rate of 5carbs a week. Do this until you stop loosing weight and stay the same on the scale, if your weight starts going up then you need to cut back 5 carbs and that becomes your new normal. (Advice from my doctor friend to my friends starting the keto diet). 


My advice: momentary diet changes will not counteract a lifetime of poor nutrition. You need to find a diet that you can stick to for the rest of your life, it shouldn't be too strict and you need to be able to forgive yourself for screwing it up every so often. 


All that being said, you had the mental fortitude to loose 80lbs on keto, you are definitely made of stern enough stuff to change your life. Good luck out there, though with determination like yours, I'm not sure you need luck. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking good, but smile in your pics :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So glad you posted more. You look wonderful dude :)

Ps I love the hair  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like having sex and there is nothing wrong with that. If asked how many people I've been with I tell them I'm not sure but under two dozen guys and about the same women.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was dumped for my past once. We went to a bar (not really a gay bar but a bar where gay guys often hang out) and a few guys came over to our table to say hi to me. Apparently while I went to the bathroom one of them told him that I've slept with almost every guy in the bar. 

He asked me about it later and I told him that it wasn't true but I did sleep with the guys that came up to us, he asked me how many guys I've been with and I told him I'm not sure (I'm really not) but less than two dozen. He had only been with five and said we wouldn't work  :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Men are so much easier  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 06:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck people :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are both me lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao xD  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People keep saying I look like him lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I weigh about the same in these two lol 
I just look very different with a beard  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The head of mine is a bit thicker than the rest and the whole this is just pretty lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to smile guy :)

Also I don't think facial hair is for you, you don't look bad with it but it doesn't really make the face. I think clean shave would be a lot better for you. 

You should only have facial hair when it really changes the face and there is an obvious improvement. Here is me as an example  http://i.imgur.com/8bJCFHB.jpg http://i.imgur.com/aUGlBji.jpg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love your glasses...they wouldn't work for me but they look wonderful on you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm that kinda guy and occasionally do jerk to myself lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations! You two have fun but feel no need to rush things. When I'm with a guy that's going too fast I saw "I want to take my time falling for you, I want to take this in as small of steps as possible, savoring every one. Because if we're lucky, we'll never fall for someone new again." 
That line has worked for me every time ;)
Also if you're nervous about the kiss just wait till you're sitting in a car together and curbing that awkward silence where you are both getting situated say to him "this is the part where we start kissing"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol yeah  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me  http://i.imgur.com/FBoVJSW.jpg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help with summer wardrobe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a bit larger and sweat a ton. I'm pretty good with my winter and fall fashion. For the spring I usually just roll the sleeves up on my button ups.  I've never been good at finding a look that works for me in the summer. Please help me. I have a picture of me in the comments if that helps.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it was interesting. I called my ex (he sells cologne in Chicago) and asked him about the three colors thing and he told me it was something he was told by his boss and coworkers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't listen to norm, you look fine and have a very earnest smile  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 12:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awwww :)))) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 12:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol thanks :))) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 12:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You two look so cute  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 12:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They all look good but I like middle one the most  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
