<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2746</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They aren't part of the problem. Stop being nasty. Grow up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Earbuds are not Buy It For Life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 04:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're asking about earbuds, I think you're in the wrong sub. In five years, any pair of earbuds will be outdated and obsolete. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. Thank you!  I will definitely track down your information.

EDIT:  Found it.  Thanks again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 01:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not out to kill any kind of flowering weed, definitely.  I don't mind those.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I desperately need to treat for weeds in my lawn, but my bees are about 45 meters away. Is there a bee-safe agent I can apply to my grass? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 19:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is MS/Bing maps app available on Android? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Windows Phone F1 Fans Still Have an Updated App! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 13:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 03:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, considering how long it's taking me to get my PhD, you may be wrong about that horse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course I have bills and pay a large corporation for the car that I drive.  But I did not go to school to "literally just . . . to learn how to work for other people."  I went to school so that I could work for myself, which is what I do, and I do it quite well, actually.  I could not have done that without university.

If you're truly unable to fathom "why anyone goes to college" then this is probably not a debate I'm ever going to win . . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, no.  I was having to work for other people until I got an education, where I learned how to work for myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 01:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A chaotic evil goat druid! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 22:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure my character could use a little goat wisdom every now and then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that a goat in Pathfinder has a higher Wisdom score than my character. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 22:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 03:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The text implies that the system uses 1d100, so all tasks are resolved as percentage chances . . . ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PRINT THE LEGEND - a new RPG of the American Southwest. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 23:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 03:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My live tile is stuck. Luckily, it's stuck on Freddie Mercury. But still, it's annoying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you were binding books, like, as part of your job? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you think about spiral-bound RPG books? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 04:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all own many lavish hardcover rule books, and they're lovely.  But I recently took my Shadowrun main rule book to the office supply store and had them chop off the spine and replace it with what they call a "comb binding."  The book lays perfectly flat on the table, and I like it a lot!  Maybe it doesn't look as nice when vertical on a bookshelf, as the title is no longer on the spine, but so far I have no regrets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 03:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your reply!  I think editorial choices make more of a difference than a director's choices of how to shoot to scene, but that's just my personal and somewhat uninformed opinion.  Character development is another story entirely.  Everything in TFA just seems really straightforward and basic.  I agree that the opening minutes of R1 are all over the place.  But most of the scenes are composed with more maturity.

One bit of camerawork in TFA that I DO love is Finn's long run through the battle outside of Maz's cantina.  That's a great shot.  Otherwise it just feels clunky to me.

But this is not meant as a critique of TFA specifically.  I'm looking more at Abrams's filmography and wondering why it doesn't match up to his popularity.  He's the go-to guy for reboots and sequels . . . and that's about it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 21:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the reply!  Could you elaborate on how Abrams is improving as a visual director?  I've been analyzing THE FORCE AWAKENS and trying to produce a compare/contrast with ROGUE ONE--which seems to be a much better film, at least from a technical standpoint (cinematography, editing, directing).  Thanks again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I would like to make some criticisms of J.J. Abrams in this subreddit, but I don't like conflict. : ) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 21:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need opinions outside of my film class.  When I look at the feature films that Abrams has directed, everything is a reboot or a sequel or--in the case of SUPER 8--intentionally derivative.  Further, his directing style seems pretty basic compared to some of the example scenes from other directors that we watch in class (such as David Fincher).  So Abrams has directed nothing original, and there's nothing innovative about his directorial choices, so why is he so popular? 

I really hesitate to ask, because I'm not trolling and am looking for some serious discussion points for our next class meeting.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Frequent Insider updates are cool, but eventually the hardware will simply be too old. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 17:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 950 is a year old and still performs well, but just like my five-year-old laptop is now laggy, my phone will one day need a refresh. So surely Something New is on the distant horizon . . . ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 15:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grow up.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas Beekeepers Against 85R House Bill 1293 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 15:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Ferrari's involvement is integral to the sustainability and success of the F1 business model. They receive payment based on their value to that model."

Yes, we all understand this.  I was asking about a comparison of numbers, which other Redditors graciously provided. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 19:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the answer I was seeking.  Thanks for explaining! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 19:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually that's not the "simple answer."  In fact, it doesn't answer my question at all.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 19:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, but the question remains.  I need a ELI5 for the F1 payout structure.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GPUpdate quotes South East Labour MEP Anneliese Dodds as saying, "Smaller teams are unfairly punished by an uncompetitive allocation of prize money that will always give the biggest teams more money, even if they finish last in every race." Is that true? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 19:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lets say that both Ferrari cars retired in every race of the season and they scored 0 points.  At seasons end, would Ferrari still receive a larger payout than Sauber?  What if the Sauber cars finished 1-2 in every race and they won both championships?  Would Ferrari STILL receive more money? 

Sorry for the somewhat n00b question, but the F1 payout process has always baffled me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 22:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for all of these wonderful suggestions! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can you suggest any active beekeeping YouTube channels? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 15:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your recommendations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 15:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, thanks for the info. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You had to write a dissertation for your bachelor degree? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 01:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 21:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Munchkin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 21:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heroes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has Merc announced the details of the Bottas deal? How was Williams compensated? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 17:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 23:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That game is supposedly "the Second Edition that Gary Gygax would have published had he remained at TSR," based on the author's interpretation of articles in DRAGON and other sources.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It seems the damage from my frag mines has been greatly reduced. I deal those mines to my enemies like I'm dealing cards at a poker table, so this makes me sad. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 16:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have two ranks in the Demolitions Expert perk, and for quite some time my frag mines and grenades have been doing an extra 50% damage.  Now the mines have returned to base damage.  Grenades haven't been reduced.  I searched for known bugs on the issue but came up empty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 20:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like I'm 5? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 20:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like I'm 5? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 05:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there really a difference in friendliness between the two places?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
