<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1417</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Trigger Happy | Episode 1 | Cycle Lanes   Bad Beards </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 17:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have I Got News For You is back! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 18:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 15:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Ants....Thants </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 Diabolical Zorak Moments | Space Ghost: Coast to Coast | Adult Swim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 10:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had the exact same thing from an abusive ex. I laughed and told her I fucking hope not. Luckily now I've got someone who knows how to love me without the need to physically attack me when i'm asleep. Good times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Last year a man threw a glass at me whilst I was hosting a comedy night in London. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 11:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 Awesome Guest Stars - Rick and Morty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 02:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Revealed: PSGs 160m Neymar transfer approach </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 17:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two Irish men try to get through U.S Immigration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 12:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 23:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And to think, after this they went on to win the game.... nah, just kidding. They lost 15-9 and England won the Grand Slam. Still, lovely voices.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 7 Great Rick Sanchez Rants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 17:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 13:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I hadn't noticed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chosen (2009) - "This BAFTA award winning film deals with a subject often whispered but rarely spoken about - the sexual abuse of boys by teachers in Britains private schools." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 10:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 12:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I love the outtakes from this scene.](https://youtu.be/xECmmlNIu40?t=2m57s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 6 of the Best Eric Andre Monologues | The Eric Andre Show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 10:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 6 of the Best Eric Andre Monologues | The Eric Andre Show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 10:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> YouTuber does 75 impressions in 5 minutes. Really impressive. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 16:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 17:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My day made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 16:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's it like being global sex symbols?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Best of the Sheriff | Mr Pickles | Adult Swim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 11:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> George Dawes - Peanuts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 10:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A year ago today Adam Hills made this impassioned speech/rant live on TV. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 11:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 11:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now in the space of just a year the UK government have gone from fucking kids to fucking everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you do to kill time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 19:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Adam Hills' moving speech about the murder of MP Jo Cox on The Last Leg. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 17:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAVID BRENT: LIFE ON THE ROAD - OFFICIAL TRAILER [HD] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 12:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heckler Throws Glass At Comedian </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 12:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 17:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, what was surreal is how everyone else was so unfazed. Like it was the norm. It was in Canterbury too, it's not even that rough a town. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 17:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His expression after checking his watch is amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 00:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That I had my arm chopped off by a chainsaw!

I used to work as a barman at Uni and as a favour one night I covered a shift for a friend in a really rough pub in a dodgy part of town. At that time I used to have long hair down to my shoulders and as I walked into the pub before I could even get behind the bar a local shouted that I needed my hair cut. I joked with him and asked if he was willing to do it for me, he shouted back he's got a chainsaw and is willing to do it with that. Thinking he was just kidding I told him to go get it and I'd let him give me a trim, I get behind the bar the punter leaves and my mate looks at me with a really worried look on his face. I asked what was wrong and he explained that the local was a bit of a nutter and also an arborist. I looked blankly at him and he then explained what an arborist was and I shit myself. Moments later the guy comes back into the pub waving around a roaring chainsaw and screaming "It's time for a trim!" Everyone else in the pub is laughing and I was truly shitting myself. I told him if he put the chainsaw down I'd buy him a drink to which he agreed. He left the pub, put the chainsaw away and came back in for his free pint.

I considered calling the police but my friend told me that it'd be more hassle than it's worth and the guy had had his fun. So I just went about the shift as normal. Also in that shift a 14 year old kid threatened to stab me because I wouldn't serve him and the police did actually turn up to the pub at one point to let me know one of the punters was meant to be in a mental health care centre and hadn't returned by his curfew. (This turned out to be a different guy from the chainsaw guy). After the shift ended my friend and I had a lock-in and got fucking hammered. I never worked there again.

Months later I was asked if I heard about the barman who was attacked with a chainsaw in the pub I'd done a shift in. Apparently he'd upset a local, the local has gone crazy, gone at him with a chainsaw and he'd lost an arm. Once I'd checked that there wasn't another incident I realised the story was about me and in typical 'Chinese Whispers' style, people had retold the story enough that it now ended up with me losing an arm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 08:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do love seeing 'The Actor Kevin Eldon'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 18:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I remember this. If I remember correctly between each film showing there was a round table discussion where celebs/comics took bets as to which monster would win in each film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 18:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 18:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually I do but I was MC'ing and it was literally going to be just a couple of minutes before I brought the headline act on. I'm gutted I didn't have it on during this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 16:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So am I.

Cheers, there's a bit afterwards that I took out because the audio had finished. Another audience member gave me their drink and as I drank it they tried to charge me for it, I joked they were the worst audience member I'd ever met. Was a crazy night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 16:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair there was a 5 minute build up which isn't caught on the audio. The guy kept trying to insult me and I kept putting him down, even his friends turned on him. He got more and more angry and offered me out for a fight several times but I laughed it off and kept going. When he realised I wasn't going to bite he snapped. 

There actually wasn't any security on that night which was scary. I knew this but knew if I buckle at any point I've lost the room and he'll win. I'm from the same place as him and knew the exact type of person he was, it was all posturing. Normally a person like that would've been kicked out earlier so I just held my ground until the manager acted and removed him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 15:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers dude, appreciate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 15:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said "And you thought you'd had a bad week!" It was a reference to another audience member I'd be chatting to beforehand who had just been dumped. I'm gutted there's not audio for the whole thing as the bits before and after were really funny but I've had to make do with what I have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 13:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha so specific. Ok I'll keep that in mind next time I'm attacked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 12:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair I still had glass in my back. How bad did I need to get hit before I could call it a glassing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In October last year I was glassed whilst performing in London. Here's the footage. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 10:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Frankie Boyle's David Attenborough joke on Have I Got News For You. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 17:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 15:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that John C Reilly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 12:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very good point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This guy is why you don't want to go to prison in South Africa. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 11:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Homer Simpson's bee rant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 12:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 10:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has been an on going debate with a friend of mine. She's horrified that ducks gang rape and constantly tries to stop it. I feel this is a waste of time, there are bigger social issues out there than duck rape. Don't get me wrong I'm no pro-duck rape but I'd say I'm more anti-actual rape. 

Call me crazy but I just feel like policing sexually deviant ducks isn't time well spent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 13:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks pretty good, I love the idea of Olivia Coleman and Julian Barrett in a dark comedy together. Will be checking this out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Andrew Jackson is being taken off $20 note. If you didn't know, he was kind of a dick! Here's a short history my mate made about him. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 11:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dude does a Backflip over a Formula E car (shot In 360 degrees) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 10:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 11:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I've just realised I don't talk in enough Kanye quotes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A VR Body Suit for Gaming and more... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 18:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 18:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 16:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soooo anyone fancy giving me some context on this one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Jon Snow Dead? Kit Harington Takes A Lie Detector Test </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 11:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man Shot 7 Times By Islamic Extremists Paralysed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 18:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British Couple Suspected Of Terrorism For Drunken "Destroy America" Tweet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 10:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wi-Fi: Will It Ever Catch On? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 10:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 22:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love is a one way street... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tom Hiddleston pee'd on Tom Hollander after Jellyfish Sting - The Jonathan Ross Show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 17:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Best of... Batman | Robot Chicken | Adult Swim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 14:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 15:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are 12 of these and they're all amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rick and Morty REMIX (by Eclectic Method) | Adult Swim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 12:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who knew a video tutorial about RV bathroom basics could be so funny? Love this guy! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 22:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 16:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is amazing, so layered. You can see more of the artists work here - https://www.instagram.com/jumpinkmonkey/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A friend of mine did this insane Rick And Morty fan art. It's like a trippy acid dream. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 16:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mugged </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 19:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mugged </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 19:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 23:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw this in Edinburgh, one of the best things I've seen live. Amazing stage show and really really funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British Mum Turns To Prostitution To Feed Her Kids </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 17:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bloody vegetarians! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 13:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 14:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd tell you but he does't like to be quoted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Best of Brock Samson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 16:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jez Compares Hitler to Jesus - Peep Show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 18:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 20 Sided Die </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 12:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ellie Goulding Boxing With Gordon Ramsay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 10:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One Minute to Christmas - Robot Chicken </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 16:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 13:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I was joking but ok... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 00:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too soon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
