<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3323</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 23:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The husband only gets to have sex two times a year with his wife. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hate how on Easter people say, "Jesus is a zombie!!!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 23:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the last time, he's just really really high. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was feeling really lonely recently, so I bought some shares... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 19:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After that, I decided to watch porn and jack off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My physics teacher told me that even though I may feel down, that there's always an upside in life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So she pushed me into the pool and begun the lesson on buoyancy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An apple away keeps the doctor away... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 05:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> omg same! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> triggered! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any creature that eats mosquitoes is alright in my book. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 09:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I managed to contact them, turns out they're very responsive on Facebook. But they loved the video and reposted it on their feed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 09:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Baby coffins are only a one time payment, while raising a child can charge multiple monthly fees. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 09:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Fucking Repost </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So what happened to the doctor? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 09:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good news, he made it to his hospital.

Bad news, he was the patient. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 06:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For anybody who actually thought Dad was referring to the dog, did you seriously just assume that dog's gender?!?!?!?!?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Daddy are you okay? Are you okay Daddy?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 23:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dad: "No Hungry, I'm just Dad". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I put all of my crops and produce in wheelchairs... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That way all of my vegetables feel special. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Food kabobs make me feel like a primal warrior who just went out hunting with their spear. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> School shooting: 4 severely wounded, 6 minor wounds, and 17 left with PTSD. My uncle said it's the worst school shooting he's seen in years... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dumb-ass terrorist couldn't even kill a single person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hate how melee attacks in most video games do nothing, yet in real life one punch could knock somebody back or out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 09:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If time travel is real, then there must already be a line of strict protocol rules for preventing paradoxes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 08:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 08:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indiana Jones stared at the perverted thief, then said "THOSE AIDS BELONG IN A MUSEUM! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smart people read books that look complicated and are pretty big in size. So I brought some books of my own to school, just to look more smart. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 08:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone was so mesmerized when they saw me go through my third "Where's Waldo" book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was gangbanged by an orchestra </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First the flutes came in, then the trombones, then a heavy ass piano, finally the violins came in last. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ohhhhhh thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So wait, is the assassin gay or straight? Who's he sparing here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi-Chews are just higher quality Starbursts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 08:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A cashier is ringing up a customer... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 01:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Customer: Alright here you go $6.43, perfect change!

Cashier: CONGRATULATIONS! You're the 50th person to pay in exact change, you know what you get now?

Customer: No, what?!?

Cashier: Nothing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fucking repost </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just don't get Spanish girls these days... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whenever people say "I enjoy all kinds of music," they usually don't like country music. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I like women like I like coffee. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 22:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I once got raped by a gang of mimes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 05:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They fucked me up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a kid, when I rode my bike I wanted to go faster and faster, speeding up as I went down hill. Now that I can drive, I want to slow down more and more, to be careful. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 05:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 07:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Repost </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 05:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I can't wait to send them a message now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know how to contact this band? I made them a fanimated music video... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 08:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The band I'd like to contact is The Royal Concept, and honestly it's just to thank them for everything they've indirectly done for me. Their music helped me find confidence over myself, and create new ideas for me as an artist. So I thought it'd be nice if I made my first animated music video after one of their songs. I know it may not be the highest of quality, but I'm still in high school so bear with me. 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T7sG5_2LjYk

This video has resulted in nothing in but a lucky streak for me as a student. It won me first place for a Film Production in the Student Recognition contest(a local thing in my area, but it's real search it up). I was the first person to enter an Animation and win first place, and that's only a big deal to me because there's no classes in my highschool that teach animation and no real artists in my school are willing to take the time to learn animation. After that the overall creation of this music video has been a great way for me to start conversations, meet new friends, and finally have the courage to talk to a crush I've had for a while. 

I feel this band should know that their music has inspired this change in me, it lifted my depression and gave me a reason to find new self worth. I really just want to thank the band. I could care less if they told me to take the video down, as long as they watched the video I'd be content.

Thank you for reading this, and if anyone knows how to contact the band please help me get this message across to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 01:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is literally a repost from /r/antijokes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My favorite AntiJoke </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 23:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is on /r/antijokes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boss:How good are you at powerpoint? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 08:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me: I Excel at it.

Boss: That's the wrong software you dumbass.

Me: Word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 07:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just couldn't say gofundme... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I had a dollar for every time women called me ugly. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 07:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I might be able to pay off the insurance bill I received after just losing my legs to a horrible car accident. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm not allowed to feed my sister's baby anymore </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 07:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was feeding her son Cheerios. She told me to try playing with her son a little to convince him to eat his food more willingly.

So I said "Here comes the airplane...OH SHIT 9/11"!

And ended up punching the baby.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 07:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/showerthoughts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 08:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Repost, but atleast it's a good one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
