<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1101</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump supporters partying that Johnny Rotten of the Sex Pistols says Trump's presidency has been a "joy to watch". Too bad he was saying stuff like this less than a year ago. Could he just be looking for attention? Very sad. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 23:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 22:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the amount of people currently on that episode's page </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Glitches in Weezer songs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are some minor studio foulups in Weezer songs that you know of?

For example, 3 seconds into "The World Has Turned and Left Me Here", you can hear a squeaking noise. Happens again about a second later, this time a bit longer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The original comment is a real thing that happened (Coolidge was known for, despite his wit, keeping to himself and not saying much). The replies are just jokes imagining what else he could have said in this scenario. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 19:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty funny that both of those were unrelated. #BadLuckNixon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 19:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think there was meant to be a moral, it was probably just to show shit was gettin real </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 08:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speak for yourself, IMO Pinkerton wouldn't truly feel complete if Butterfly wasn't the closer. It addresses and ties up all of the themes from the previous songs and its bare instrumentation is the perfect contrast to the rest of the record. Longtime Sunshine is one of my favorite Weezer songs ever, but I definitely think it only works as a closer to SftBH. Tragic Girl should've just been on the album in general, it's a fantastic song but I don't see it as a closer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 08:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Fall Together, it's one of the few songs on Maladroit where Rivers' attempts at meshing hard rock with the Weez actually fully comes together. Maladroit's worst for me is easily Space Rock. Generic instrumentation, terrible production, and godawful vocals. Probably one of the worst tracks to ever be on a Weezer album </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 06:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As far as I know, all the annotated episodes are based on lists that are up on http://www.annotatedmst.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really cool and good the guy who deemed this a shitpost didn't bother to click the link to find out this isn't a picture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "A picture of Obama"? It's a link to a tweet... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not like the London killer wasn't born in England... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadiq Khan has said he believes the threat of terror attacks are part and parcel of living in a big city and encouraged Londoners to be vigilant to combat dangers.

The Mayor of London revealed he had a sleepless night after the recent bombing in New York, and said major cities around the world have got to be prepared for these sorts of things to happen when people least expect them.

Nothing is more important to me than keeping Londoners safe, Mr Khan said at the time. I want to be reassured that every single agency and individual involved in protecting our city has the resources and expertise they need to respond in the event that London is attacked. 

The terrorists are evolving their tactics and we have got to evolve our response to them all the time. I am afraid the consequences of a terror attack are very very scary. They want to kill. They want to maim and terrify. It is my job to try to make sure that we are as safe as we can be.

This is from the article Don Jr. tweeted about. I may be a libtard cuck but it seems pretty nonoffensive to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got a question. Who are you referring to with the "one confirmed SJW" in the cast? Like, you could characterize several of them as that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol as if Bill Frank and Kevin weren't super liberal already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 03:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh? Isn't 5'10 above average? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, I think if the lyrics weren't vaguely creepy nonsense it would be a high point. It's a simple track but the melody is pretty catchy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 05:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends. What'd you think of BTTS/TGFG? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it weird that the first thing I took notice of was the background? Looks great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imo both EWBAITE and White were great, so it makes this new crappy song hurt just a tad more, because it seemed like they were slowly on their way back up to the top. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a big fan of Back to the Shack and I like EWBAITE. I don't like TGFG and I love White. I detest this new song so I guess that means I'll LOVE Black. That's how it works now, it seems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 09:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After single #2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 08:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Space Jam has a wacky concept and executes it surprisingly well. I don't think it's a great movie but the fact that the production is fully competent for such a zany premise adds memorability. Back in Action though is pretty paint by numbers despite its live action/2D concept. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 06:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say I like Seven More Minutes, but it's kinda inconsistent. The first three tracks are great. Then The Cruise hits and it's just pretty annoying and kills the vibe for a bit: Barcelona and Say Goodbye Forever are kinda fillery. I really like Overlee, but Big Daddy C is pretty grating. Keep Sleeping and The Man with Two Brains are both great but as the album hits the home stretch it kinda gets more and more susceptible to filler: I kinda tune out when it hits Must Be Wrong, Insomnia, and the It's Alright reprise. It does end on a high note though, I really like My Head is in the Sun and Jumping Around. Overall I'd say it's good but it doesn't really need to be an hour long; you could chop off a few tracks and it definitely would increase my rating. Lost in Alphaville is a lot better imo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 05:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was actually expecting something like the Rentals when Rivers promised some synth heavy weez, not what we got which is kinda blah.

Also for anyone who hasn't heard it Return of the Rentals is the shit. Rivals peak 90s Weezer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pat's thoughts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 01:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, he did make [this](https://twitter.com/JeffFlake/status/793503341108002816) good tweet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey SCREW you bud </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/im14andthisisfunny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well those were both on White Deluxe, which is already out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alec Baldwin on Playing Trump: 'I'm Not Going to Do It Much Longer' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 04:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alec Baldwin on Playing Trump: 'I'm Not Going to Do It Much Longer' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 04:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this really that impressive though. Maybe if it was from the top posts bot, but I'm not all that stunned a FULLCOMMUNISM bot put together something about capitalism/socialism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 04:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty good. I gotta give props to Yassir Lester. Never heard of him but he's pretty likable and funny in this. My only major complaint is that the pacing felt a bit uneven; you're kinda thrown into the major conflict pretty early and as a result it doesn't really feel that urgent. Maybe a few episodes of setup before the big cliffhanger at the end woulda been better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow all those Trump cabinet refs. Very topical. Although it's Jefferson, not Jeffrey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Err, did you mean to post that 9 times? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah like he's been going on Ellen and Kimmel in the past few days laughin' and having a grand time. And I'm like "2 years ago, no way he gets away with this." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 06:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought they got rid of him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HIM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 06:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno I wouldn't call Bill Burr really right leaning, at least not in the sense /u/porkslapchop was implying. He wouldn't really be what I'd call an alternative to Stewart because he's made it clear he despises Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 07:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At first I thought you just fucked up Warren Beatty's name really badly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 03:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 21 actually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 17:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh? Feingold is from Wisconsin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 07:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As far as I can tell most liberals on Reddit don't really mind Bush Sr. and he's been out of the spotlight for quite a while so I couldn't see that one getting too messy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 17:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 16 days before mine! April births unite 8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 00:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some guy on those_ronalds said "The book sales just got 10% higher." I don't think that's how it works, but ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's in luck, Dallas is very liberal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 22:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does Matt play bass, though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 05:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **LOCK HIM UP** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://twitter.com/Joy_Villa/status/796137229294964736 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The only tweets by Joy Villa (the singer who wore a Trump dress to the Grammys) about Trump prior to this stunt were ones MAKING FUN OF HIM AND HIS SUPPORTERS! TOTAL DISASTER! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 03:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/post-politics/wp/2016/02/19/25-quotes-capturing-donald-trumps-final-pitch-to-south-carolina/?utm_term=.bde34c2a7e43 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 23:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's very swampy, contrary to what Trump promised. You've got completely unqualified people like DeVos essentially buying spots by giving large sums of money to Republican senators. Iirc most of these folks were yuge donators to Trump's campaign, and were terrible choices. So basically he passed over qualified people with experience in favor of billionaires willing to loan him some bucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 00:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ARE YOU TIRED OF WINNING YET </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 00:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't Dina Titus running?

Also, I thought Hatch was retiring. (Of course another Republican would definitely win that seat though.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not always that simple. Most Republicans in the Senate just want to support the party. Don't wanna be the senator who votes against their own party, that's bad for votes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember Bush. I was only a teenager (and not even a US citizen) but I despised the man. The new memes about how he's actually a wacky likable guy still get me salty (he might be, but he fucked up America, not a very likable move!). Hopefully those never happen to Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 02:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt it. His Twitter is pretty standard alt-right stuff. He only veers into crazy dumbass territory occasionally (like this). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 23:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...what's the issue? Looks like a good post for the sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 23:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'm going to opine this isn't a shitpost. It's sufficiently mildly interesting and so fits the sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rob Stewart, "Sharkwater" director and star, dead at 37 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 01:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best part of this song is the yelp Stipe does in the chorus after the "laughing" part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I audibly groaned when I saw this nonsense reposted, but I was pretty glad to see that top comment again. If Reddit agreed this time that this was a thing, I woulda sailed out a window. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 18:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hm. Off the top of my head, maybe Jeff Kessler. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 18:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah, I wasn't being entirely serious there, he seems like a pretty standard WV democrat. Better than Jim Justice anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 18:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Manchin makes me cringe. Can't we just get an R in his spot and drop the illusion? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 15:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit doxxing rules </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 20:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wooooooooow..........witnesses describe 2 men in ski masks.

One is an arab with an arabic name, the other has a french canadian name.

They're putting it all on the french canadian named guy so this doesn't conflict with refugee plan.

Holy shit.....Canada is in trouble.

oh lord </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 00:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, he's 36 right now. He'll be 37 in February. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 00:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we just talk about how sitcommy of a name Kevin Levin is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 22:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you an R.E.M. fan? ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 23:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can tell all that just from the (surprisingly few) videos and pictures of him? From what I can tell Barron's behavior seems pretty normal of any other 10 year old suddenly thrust into national spotlight. I mean, come on, he's 10! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 14:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alt fact. Obama had 5 million more votes than Romney. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 11:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would've been the purpose of giving Perot any EV, though? He didn't win any states and Clinton still won both the popular vote and the electoral college rather easily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 19:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh I'm kind of lenient with Melania because it doesn't seem like Donald likes her at all, but it's insanely hypocrtical of her to preach NO CYBERBULLYING when her husband is Donald Fucking Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 01:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cancer, right there in the first paragraph. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LOW ENERGY DON Falls ASLEEP at Inauguration. SAD! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 00:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 23:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But... but... the karma!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 20:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So how old were you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama smoked the weed as a student, got taken to task, and gladly owned up to it as opposed to other folks who got caught like Bill Clinton who just go "I ACTUALLY HATED IT AND NEVER DID IT AGAIN" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New anti-Trump Green Day music video prompts /r/greenday user to declare that "christ sake guys, racism is not a major issue in America, nor is islamaphobia, and neither is police brutality". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 23:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 21:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rob Schneider is a joke. He used to be a Democrat but became a Republican because "California has too many Democrats". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 16:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you're a star, they let you rip the baby out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 05:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that's true, just saying that it didn't have anything to do with the legitimacy of Bikers for Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 05:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is the post retarded? Sure, Bikers for Trump may be going to the inauguration, that's not what's in dispute here. What is is the fact that this person took a completely unrelated two-year-old photo of motorists and slapped LOOK AT BIKERS FOR TRUMP GOING TO DC WOO!!! on it. It fits this sub perfectly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 00:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Went over to Donnie's subreddit, and there are already a handful of upvoted comments asking him to let it go. Sad! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 21:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ben Garrison's personified wet dream. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 08:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh sorry, I interpreted your post to mean that there was a shortlist (?) of nominations out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 06:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, I just... why on earth would Booker vote to confirm this guy? I was assuming that he's been prepping for a 2020 run but this would shoot all that in the foot instantly.

Also, I'm thinking Heitkamp goes yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 04:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And they say they're ok with it

They are? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 22:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 22:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are those? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 20:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, there's a similar one with an MS paint Adolf going down a rainbow iirc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 14:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember the "Everyone I Don't Like Is Hitler" meme that Trumpers love? Well... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 05:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something similar, Garth Brooks hosted the show as himself and did the musical performance as Chris Gaines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 02:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dear OP,

Good title. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The allegations documents of Don's ties to Russia include a section on him hiring a series of prostitutes to perform "golden showers" in Moscow's presidential suite </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 00:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 17:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not an emmy expert, but wouldn't Donald also win one since he's EP? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 23:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guess we can add Shkreli to this meme now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 19:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No he brought her up when talking about Don't Let Me Down but she's not actually on the list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 07:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a good album. Berlin is pretty great and IMO is up there with some of their classic IRS-era songs. I think my biggest beef with the album is the production, a lot of songs have this weird blaring quality that makes them hard to listen to. I'll put a few songs from it in an REM playlist and I always have to rush to turn them down when they come on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 06:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They met when he was 68 and she was 29. Does not check out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 19:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> T_D circlejerked over a Donald tweet from a few years back that said something like "I've never seen a thin person drink Diet Coke", and they kept babbling about how much Trump owned the hamplanets, ignoring the fact that he's a big fat fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 13:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your grandad seemed like a pessimist. Average year of death (in the US at least) is what, 78? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
