<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3318</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, a light just went off in my head.  I get it :)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hyperfocal focusing - I understand the concept and how to figure out the hyperfocal distance. I am interested in the workflow of shooting the picture using this example...... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For this example, I am standing in front of a field of rocks and boulders that goes to .  My hyperfocal distance is 10 feet.  Here is the question Do you folks find something on the ground that is ~ 10 feet away and focus on it, then lift your camera for the shot or do you frame your shot first and focus so the stuff ~10 feet away looks in focus.

To paraphrase  look down and focus and lift? or Look out and make sure the stuff at the bottom of the viewfinder 10ft away is in focus?.

Thank you
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does the satellite radio companies and TV cable companies know how many people are tuned in and to what station? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Satellite companies can control your radio and cable can control your TV.  Since we know there is two way communication, is there a feed back to the company that goes to a number readout? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!  I'm trying to get some work done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where is Al Sharpton and Jesse Jackson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Havent heard from them in a while.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did the prisoners in German concentration Camps ever try uprising and taking over the camp? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The dog breed is Chow Chow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 03:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RADAR, COMMS, hangers, and planes I imagine.
Here's a good Tomahawk 101

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8sa7ZX58Kk4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 03:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now the fun starts. Time to crawl in, wash it, sand it down, prime and paint.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 03:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hardened runways can be repaired in a matter of hours.  Not a valuable target. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 02:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you tell me why it is bad for portraits?  I put the single spot right on their nose.   I am not challenging you - just want to learn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: I saw a movie and the credits rolled by at almost supersonic speed. Why bother showing them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just bought a 1Ds MKIII - paid about $1200 at an online store.   Bought a little better grade and the camera looks brand new.  Came with a money back guarantee and a small warranty.  Gave me insurance against buyers remorse.
Moved up from a T5.  Boom - thing is awsome. I can't believe the quality of the pictures.  The autofocus is great.   I don't need more than 5 frames a second and you probably don't either.  Shooting in RAW will slow down any camera.   The thing is sexy and a workhorse.  
A small reason I went to the 1D because of its size (I have huge hands).  I am just overwhelmed by the quality of the pictures. 
I know I'm not going to do movies and the onboard flash was a nuisance to me on the T5, so It doesn't bother me to not have them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 15:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard the Easter Bunny hides Eggs because he does not want anyone to know he is having sex with the chickens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 03:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, never seen them.  Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 02:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to confirm this works.  I pay 30 or so for 6 months.   The catch is you need to call and renew or cancel before the 6-month mark or you a charged the full price automatically.  I just make a calendar reminder.  When I call to renew the deal I am aways pushed for a full year.  My response is "you can have 5 a month or nothing". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 01:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
