<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject322</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> e ratott hgg luea 4"a aesrbv </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched the anime up to when they're running through the field with a lady titan chasing them or they're chasing her? It's fuzzy.

Anyway. The entire time I found the writing stilted and very generic "anime". That isn't to say you're wrong for enjoying it of course. But I've been watching anime since I was born and the characters just so often seemed copy and paste. I couldn't get invested when "Generic Anime dude #3" got eaten or was freaking out because he let other people get eaten. I had already seen him in so many other anime that I just couldn't invest. Ya know?

The stoic, emotionally dead characters hardly ever resonate with me, and that was basically their cast.

Take full Metal Alchemist. There's an anime with nuanced characters. Or more recently, One Punch Man. While having those same generic anime tropes, One Punch Man leans into them, mocking them and taking them apart. I love it.

Again. I LOVE attack on Titan's concept. It's animation is top tier, the music is stellar and the voice actors are great. But it's the script that loses me. The thing is, I can see why people would love it, because back in the day. I loved Inuyasha. Which has the same problems and strengths. (Though I'd like to think the Inuyasha characters have slightly more personality, that might just be nostalgia talking though. haha) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With 2.0 Coming out I would like to share my insights from a few months ago (With some edits) on my favourite map, and one of the most Unique Heroes of the Storm has, Towers of Doom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This post originally came about because I was frustrated with people's attitudes towards the Boss on Towers of Doom. It is a momentum sink and can actually lose you a game that you've been leading.

 Basically, if you wipe the team and it's a question of taking lanes or taking boss? **You always take the lanes.** Because the lanes will give you more damage on your towers. (Boss does four, but 3 extra lanes + 3 towers = 9.)


 Even having two extra towers and taking two shrines **you get more value**.


 BUT it also sets your enemy back. They cannot safely run up that lane now to escape you, they need to take those forts back to be able to do damage with the objective again, and while they're taking one back you can take another. Taking just**one fort removes 1/4th of their damage.**


 Let your split pusher split push while you defend a tower. **Just poke the enemy, don't engage. Keep them from getting that shrine as long as you can.** Build that momentum. Then when the enemy has four points left, take the boss for the win.


 But there is **almost** no instance where taking boss is better than taking a fort.


 Azmodan, Gazlowe, Slyvanas, Zagara, Hammer, Xul, Murky, Abathur and The Lost Vikings thank you for your time. Pushing really does win games on Towers of Doom.


Also. I would like to add too this that your core health is a resource on this map. As long as you have 1 health, and your enemies have 0 you win. Do the math. Are you able to sacrifice a few early objectives to get yourself a siege lead? If so, it may be worth it.

Also, if you help someone take a merc camp, don't leave that lane. Walk the mercenaries in to the buildings. Only leave the lane if you're using the Mercs as a decoy to pressure another lane, but fill your allies in on what you're doing. The mercs are fragile and only get value from either hitting your opponents buildings, or crossing their no mans land and dealing direct core damage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 02:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. Purely fan art. Those two characters are basically dead inside. 

It's a horror story of sorts, set in a kind of feudal steampunk Japan setting. It's a hugely UNIQUE concept just not incredibly well done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 02:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Attack on Titan fan art.

It's not cute at all. Very gory. Was super popular for awhile.

I found it was kinda poorly written.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 02:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. You've got to consider all of his abilities and qualities. 

His W, will wander off if it doesn't detect an enemy, his laser has a small engagement range but he can chase with it and it can be talented to grow.

His health pool is as enormous as he is, boasting one of the highest health pools in the game, under Cho'Gal, Full Soul Diablo, and Avatar Muradin.

His W is there to deal some damage, block skill shots and disrupt channels. He is there to block skill shots that are heading into the back line, and provide a body to watch the back of his tank/bruisers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 02:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Level 20 Azmo here, there Azmodan wasn't so much on point with his timings as using the globes on cooldown. Luckily he had his minion's spawnign from it to provide a second layer of poke. But he is the one who lost them the game. 

Look at that team fight at the start of the video, he's barely in it at all, his health stays pristine until his team starts to fall.

Azmo is a mid line character. He's big with a big HP pool and autos that hurt a bunch, plus his Laser. He should always be between the front line and back line, but he was way back line where his HP pool, his autos and his lasers weren't worth anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most often Bottom is the solo lane, most of the time because of saftey, the rest of the time out of habit.

There are some maps you'll see top lane solo, but really the maps are super balanced so it doesn't matter too much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are rare and far between and someone looking for Abathur tips will not be able to recognize them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, Bushes aren't the only place to hide. Often there are curving walls and what not you and hide behind, feel free to either spread your mines out for scouting info if you keep an eye on a mini map, or fill your hidey hole and the area leading too it with them so someone coming to gank you get's surprised

Also. Monstrosity is terrible compared to ultimate evolution. Your locus will push just fine and you'll be more valuable in team fights. Especially with heroes like Jaina, her trait will combo with clone jaina.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to have a comedic bard NPC for my allies to encounter, what's some good DnD/ye old timey esque humour </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One on the front page

"What do you call babies born in a whore house? 

Brothel Sprouts!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And of those Skins The Lost Vikings still only have their original nine. T-T </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Azmodan player here, 10/10 would use exclusivly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neat. Googling the "air date" for the episode just comes up with speculation about it coming out in summer. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Myself. I'd figure out a bunch of different winning Lotto numbers for like the past three months before I went back, win the lotto a bunch of times, probably place bets on high profile games etc.

Continue living my life but now as a rich dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What makes you think it's tonight? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Lost Vikings. Because if I'm stuck on one hero, I may as well play the one that's the biggest challenge.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 23:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remeber to get your refer a friend code, so they get free stuff*raynor and Slyvanas) and you get free stuff (Portrait and mount) and tell them about the Mechano spider mount of facebook
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 07:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is.... Is that a thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 07:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because its a repost too you doesn't mean ya gotta be a Debbie Downer. Down vote and move on if its that offensive too your sensibilities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 07:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope this doesn't get taken down. Its a silly rule to not list thoughts about redditm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 07:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too. Came here from rising. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 07:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guys, his relationship isn't 2 months old, he used the printer 2 months ago.

Op. Its just stress. That being said, you need to sit her ass down and explain to her it is not okay to talk to another person that way despite her stress level. This is going to be the rest if your life, every time she is stressed if you don't communicate with her and help her improve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can also pick your domain first, and then find which gods use that domain. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She sounds quite lawful too me!

You see, lawful isn't "Following the law of the land" it's following a strict code. Your code is two fold.

1) Never murder an innocent
2) Serve your master (In this case your "master" is your addiction. You do what ever you can to serve it.)

You could easily play her as lawful, and that might add some fun flavour for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 03:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in Toronto, I'll grab a beer with you sometime </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 01:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Veterans deserve more stuff

OR

Veterans deserve nothing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pure random. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Optimum Order for maximizing 2.0 unlocks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, grab yourself which ever mega bundle you so desire. Ideally the one with the most heroes, but it's up too you. Because even if you get a hero out of one of your boxes, you wont get shards for getting the mega pack. But if you get the mega pack, you'll get some of those dirty filthy shards that you're going to need to get the things you actually want.

Second, crack open those sweet sweet legendary veteran packs if you have any, then re roll as often as you feel you need too. You are garunteed to get one legendary in these. By doing them first, you have all your gold and can re roll as many times as you want.

If you get a legend that you sort of want, but want to reroll for something you REALLY REALLY WANT? Don't. You wont get the thing you want. Take the thing you sorta want.

Then, from there. Figure out how much gold you have in relation to epic chests for rerolls. 

250 x number of chests = amount of chests you can re roll once. Do you have more gold left over?

500 x number of chests = amount of gold you need to reroll twice once you add this number too your first number. 

And if you still have more gold,

750 x the number of chests add it to the other two numbers, do you have enough gold to reroll everything three times? Groovy.

If you don't have enough to reroll three times, just don' reroll many, if any three times. Since the price is so high, just re roll cheaply. You'll want to have some gold for future rare/epic chests. Don't be tempted to reroll on commons. They're a gold sink so you cannot buy new heroes as they're released. Don't let common boxes trap you. (Unless you're like MFPallytime and have all the gold the game has ever generated. )

Then your common chests. Don't open them. Ever. Ignore them. They're not worth your time. They're a dissapointment to their parents and all who have loved them and come before them. Look on them with pity and shame.

Then open them anyway and someone get eight legendaries out of two of them, then post on reddit for some sweet Karma.

And that's how you maximize your 2.0 launch experience.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is all Cho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a gameplay reward for everymode just like gold for winning is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Playing the game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah. Common's give like, five shards I think? One rare duplicate gives 20. So /u/madmax569 did the math and it turns out that you're doubling your chance to get rare's in all of the boxes with one reroll. As opposed to a 39% chance or something like that with the extra box.

One rare duplicate is worth the same as 4 common duplicates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/madmax569 did the math on it in a comment lower down. Check it out. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because that's not relevant to the conversation at hand? Brawls should have been giving XP from the start in most people's opinions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I figured that would be the actual value, double that is too say. But I wasn't sure of the math. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't, because it's random.

But you can compare the average value of one extra loot box, vs four re rolls.

The four re rolls win everytime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The new Brawl reward is worth less than 1/5 the old one. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a hypothetical. You've got 0 gold, and four Loot boxes. You play the Brawl and get a Fifth loot box. Neat! 

Or, you have four loot boxes, and you then get 1000 gold.
You can use that 1000 gold to re roll each of those four loot boxes once, so your chances of getting something good, rather than increasing by 1/5th with the extra loot box, is increased by x2! 

I'm sure someone else can do the math here, I think it comes out to being 1/10th the value? Although you do get 4 extra items you wouldn't get before. Gold is, in the end more flexible because you can also get heroes with it. 

This new loot box reward is not the way to go for people who want to play F2P.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What might the world have been like, if Homo Sapiens were on one continent, and the others, Neanderthals and the such were on another. Thus not eradicating each other in our early fledgling states? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they were they same guys supposed to move in with me, but they got lost on their way here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was supposed to get Three new roommates, but they got lost on the way here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If a man is undoing his belt before he even gets too the bathroom, some serious shit is about to go down. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah. Just like on Warhead, you can hold three nukes.

Each Viking has their own "F" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not true. I've played as them and each one can hold an item. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 05:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man. TLV are amazing on this map. One player can rush a payload to the otherside on their own, or they can split push/soak with two, guide a payload on their own and enable their team to kick ass.

They can grab three items, dropping turrets and heals left and right.

You'll see TLV grouped up more often than usual on this map, that's for sure. But at the same time, it's because they're hitting camps, ganking someone solo (With how small the map is, it's super easy for TLV to gank finally. Very few heroes can handle all three vikings. Very few people realize this though, which makes ganking so easy.) pushing carts, scouting vision, taking out a fort. Etc etc etc. It's so cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 05:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like all those things you're bemoaning, but as someone who LOVES The Lost Vikings, I might be biased.

This is my new favourite map because of how busy it is. You're honestly doing it wrong if you're in lane for most of it. Even pushing seems a waste of time, and I have a level 20 Azmodan so I love my push.

It's hectic bombastic, and off the wall fun. 10/10 would play Hanamura again and again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 04:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always saw that as more of an easter egg/cheat. Because of the effect it has on the final boss and all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 04:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> correct me if I'm wrong, but isn't there a Nordic version of Death metal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 02:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lonely Redditor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 02:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Potato Pete </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 02:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beautiful Furry Goat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 02:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Baby Battle Axe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 02:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sober Brew Master </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Community builds a card! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 02:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay so, all top level comments participating will contain a name.

"Orgimarr orchard guardian"

"Dingle dangle Doggo"

"Gnomeish Dragon Eater"

Etc.

Then, the people replying too it will give it it's stats and abilities. Whomever get's the most upvotes wins! The most upvotes! Isn't that exciting? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 02:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the exploit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 02:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd do Megaman X personally. I know where every item is and in which order to get them (Chill Penguin, Storm Eagle, Flame Mammoth, Sting Chameleon, Boomerang Kuwanger, Sparkmandrill, Armour Armadillo, Launch Octopuss.)

You'll be able to get all items without backtracking doing it in that order.

Shit. Don't join my group of 100 people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 00:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, since they didn't even get a tint. I 'unno. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would our generation's "We didn't start the fire" have listed in it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 00:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is anyone else sad that as far as additional swag goes, The Lost Vikings have been forgotten? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 00:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that having a TLV "Announcer pack" would have been Amazing. Eric, Baelog and olaf just like, not actually commentating on your game, but rather arguing the entire time about it.

**Olaf**: "Dat was a triple kill!"

**Eric**"No you dumby, it was a double kill?" 

**Baelog** "Are you kidding me? The player Just died!"

**Olaf and Eric** "Oh. Right."

And like, there are so many awesome skin ideas they could do.

**Star Craft**

Protoss Olaf, with Zerg Baelog, and Terran Eric

**Diablo**

Demon Olaf, with Angel Baelog and Nephelem Eric
**Warcraft**

Taurn Olaf, Blood Elf Baelog, Goblin Eric

Night Elf Olaf, Dranai Baelog, Gnome Eric

**Overwatch**

Omnic Olaf, Strike Commander Baelog, Reaper Eric

And so many unique ones they could just come up with from outside their franchises. 

I mean, now that it's all loot box nonsense, could we please get more TLV skins? Like... Maybe even one more tint? They've still got the same nine skins they started with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What should I do with my new found fortune of one Gems? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blizzard was kind enough to give me an %AMOUNT% of Gems equal to one! One whole Gems. 

http://i.imgur.com/Ywz9KTJ.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. This guy gets it. You need someone who wont be kited while chasing the Vikings (Because at least 2 will be hitting you while you're doing no damage chasing one) and you need a way to keep yourself alive. 

I'm happy to see someone popped in here to back me up against people spreading miss information. 

Kael is only good against the Vikings in that he can out lane one viking really really well. Kael is good as PvE not PvV! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man. Blizzard needs to give you a job already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just Like Zeratul. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I mean. A Vikings player with any level of Micro will not be bothered by Living Bomb at all. I've not had an issue with it since like, level 8.

I don't even take Jump anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kael is one of the worst at fighting a good vikings player. His abilities require an uncoordinated team to get the most effect. And neither Dehaka or Arthas can do enough damage to land a finishing blow.

If you've your heart set on 1v1ing a clump of Vikings, someone like Illidan, or Thrall or Sonya. People with Sustain and decently high damage are what you need, because the Vikings will out last you. Though I'd recommend against Illidan and Thrall if you can help it. Thrall is better off than Illidan though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a level 19 Viking in the old system( Not sure what 2.0 level I'll have) there are very few Heroes that can take on all three vikings at once with the minimum of Micro you'd pickup from the starcraft training missions.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 05:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 03:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm "Alabaster" and my Friend is "Monkey"

Together we are "Mon'ster" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But since he wasn't evil he was breaking the sterotype? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. That's awesome. I don't know when I last tried it but it didn't work. I'm glad they added that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? how? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd just be happy to be able to sort by class, then search Melee or ranged.

Sometimes yiu need a melee assassin and it'd be nice to have them all grouped up so yiu could decide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your Azmodan skin reminds me of one I've always wanted to see, Dark Archon Azmodan. 

Like, it'd be his face and hands in a Dark Archon body. I don't know if you play starcraft or not.

But yeah, long story short. I'd love to see that Old Gods Azmodan skin in game. Day one buy for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Az'guldan didn't stop Gul'dan from getting in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 06:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol Very nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The mightiest Sorcerer in my in game world is just my name spelled backwards.

Also, all the faeries in my game are bananas and I love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> United Airlines Pilot training </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 23:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. I especially love being last pick, and throwing on my Master Skin as TLV and watching either their last pick panic because they locked him into support and they have no TLV counters, or just knowning that sitting on the other end of the count down is a team of five salty mother lovers haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the thing that makes your statement true. 

I avoid watching the trailers. (Made the mistake of watching the spiderman one and basically saw the entire movie.) So I had no idea what the context was here, I didn't even see the subreddit it was in.

Saw "SingleKirbyTear" and thought, oh. Kirby the video game character.

What makes that a perfect costume, is without seeing the subreddit, without getting the context, and without knowing she was in Thor Ragnarok, I knew that was Marvel's Depiction of Hela.

Their costume work is just top notch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but how? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. That's one of my favourite things about this game. It is SO team oriented. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't delete anything. 

And I never said HotS was all rainbows and unicorns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, whenever I play TLV I always say "The secret of a great TLV player isn't the play, it's how good his team is at playing with TLV"

Like,I will push the shit out of every lane and carry the entire game to victory if you let me. But that's the thing. You need to let me. I need a talented gank squad backing me up or I can't do anything at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Because the game is the toxic thing and not the community. 

Contextually it's obvious, but I am sorry I did not perfectly craft every line of my post for your sensibilities.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did not bash another game. I shared an experience that made me appreciate HotS more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played four games of dota and they were all awful. I say that in the original post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually I think Phantom Assain was on my team. The username was egg something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 05:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a fun play is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 05:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was really stressful. You get a troll or two in hots sure, but the amount if abuse I received for two hours was unrelenting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DOTA2 Is so toxic oh my goodness. HoTS has me spoiled </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 05:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had over 100 extra levels. Wow. 

I didn't know, thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 05:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. That is garbage. How can they allow that to happen too their fans? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 00:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doomsayer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. I'm fine playing against and losing too any kind of deck other than a OTKO deck. And even then, once in awhile it's whatever. My complaint is this same deck has come up four times, and I have not enjoyed playing against it at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And don't have dirty rat lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I run a Murlock Shaman deck because its fun on a bun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. The deck doesn't require any secrets to function. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that's garbage that there is literally no setup that I could potentially counter here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This new "Exodia" mage meta is unacceptable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I've run across maybe MAYBE 3 or 4 OTKO decks over my years of playing. Paladin Murloc dealy bopper and that Purple genie guy build.

I also know, that there have been more styles. 

BUT I have seen this mage thing four times TODAY. I won against it once, and lost twice. Losing against it is not fun. At all. Everytime I play, I out play them keep their board clear keep mine healthy etc. I was at 30 life. Then in ONE TURN (Two, I suppose because of the quest card) the wipe me out. Nothing on the board for me to counter, no way for me to defend against it. Nothing. It just feels awful to play against.

And apparently people are getting ripped off with duplicates? What's all that about? (I myself got the "Discover a Murloc" murloc in about 15/25 boosters. But I didn't really think much of it at the time.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 02:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't watch the video. What is Project Scorpio? A new game console? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys. My laptop has finally aged out (As in I can no longer play modern games like this one) and I cannot afford a new computer. But it still makes me happy to see the community pushing on. As a poor gamer, piracy has been the only way I could ever really continue my hobby. 

I just wanted to give a shout out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> go for the vetran chest. I need 35 levels and I'm going for it. Much better value. One extra item and it's legendary guaranteed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another fun thing to do, is not grab Metamorph. Instead grab the hunt and pick off anyone dumb enough to solo lane. There are very few characters that can Take Illidan 1v1 and quite often he can get a kill and escape during a 2v1. (Though, going after someone like Kael when they have ETC with them is just dumb. Pick your battles.)

But yeah. I love both Sonya and Illidan, and I choose Illidan if I want more kills, I choose Sonya if I want more damage. 

Think of it like this, Sonya is way better at setting kills up for people like Valla, Lunara, Kael etc. Illidan is better at sealing the deal after an enemy has been poked down enough.

He's also awesome at supporting out of position allies iwith "the hunt" 

Oh what's that? Zeratul is harassing my out of position support? "You are not prepared" and Illidan is one of the few people who can chase zeratul down after he blinks away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't be able to run a 10v10. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is very exciting. I'm very happy what Blizzard has done in regards too their veteran players. One thing I'm concerned with is the gambling nature of this whole thing. I get that it makes money, but I'm uncomfortable with the loot box system in general. Many players have already discussed the perils of gambling addiction in their own lives and the lives of family.

My question is, how frequently will be be able to buy the skins we want? To reduce the need to gamble for them?

Obviously this is not the Q A before someone climbs up my arse. But I might not be here for it, and if someone wants to post this question that would be great. I've got two more questions that are more personal I'll post below here, but they aren't as important.

The Lost Vikings... Where's the love? Are there ANY skins in the works? Even just extra colour tints? Getting an ETA on it would be great, but I'd honestly just really like to know if something at all is coming our way. I love those guys. Their games helped me learn to read when I was young! They've got a special place in my heart. 

And another quesiton, each other modern Blizzard game, Hearthstone, World of Warcraft, and Diablo III all have Heroes of the Storm mounts you can gain by progressing in game. I was wondering if Starcraft or Overwatch would ever get something like that? (I understand an Overwatch Mount might be tricky since we're obviously never shown anything, but something silly like a Unicycle with a junkrat wheel would be awesome. You can use the Treasure Goblin mount stature for it.)

So yeah. Neither of these two questions are important. But I think the first one is. If someone could be swell enough to ask these questions for me in the Q A that would be very nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 01:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh nice. Yeah thats the kinda idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 23:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love that song and as one of the "whiners" I would just like to say, you're welcome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 23:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does superstition do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bulwark, another kind of Shield </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just thinking and maybe we could get another HP shield kind of thing. I'd use the word armour but it's already used. 

So while this extra hp bar is up, you take less damage from Auto's (Extra armour? Maybe max?) but you take 200% damage from spell damage. 

I think it'd be interesting to throw that on Johanna in place of her unstoppable shield (Keep her unstoppable.) Make her even more of a anti auto attack tank. 

Just an ideal idea. I'd love to hear more discussion about this and maybe other kinds of shields. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was one of the people complaining. This makes me much happier. Thank you Blizzard. For listening too us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The big bad corporation didn't deserve all the pressure it got oh no.

You know what? I love Blizzard BECAUSE it gives into pressure. Few companies do and it makes Blizzard a better one because it listens. 

Guess what? If a bunch of people complain about something a company does, it's not your place to tell them they're wrong and entitled. The FEEL wronged for a reason, and the company made them feel that way.

This? Right here? This is Blizzard doing it right! Thank you Blizzard for stepping up for the little guy. Not many companies do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah i got 16 common boxes on beta and after a few games and more bixe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Find heroes with a common theme but have different qualities.

Illidan, Diablo and Kharazim are all similar in positioning, but different in use.

Learn how to use them, then learn how to use others like them.

Illidan can help you learn greymane who can help you learn other ranged heroes.

Diablo can help you learn etc or even rexxar.

Kharazim will teach you when you need to use your heals and on whom, which translates into other supports.

Of course, thats just what worked for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 07:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, if you like playing the PTR at all I'd suggest it. It'll give you a head start building stuff up. It's a good way to test to see if you'd do better on a Smurf account as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm always with my team post like, 13.

But my generals do work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 07:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah. Drop it into their back line and it wrecks havoc. They need to commit resources to clearing it and tanks can't peel it.

And if they don't it gets kills
 Hones truth. You should try a few games with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 07:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I even prefer Invasion. It often catches folks off guard. I also take the talent at seven that promotes a minion with your general. Love the split push.

Again, obviously I'm not in competative levels or nothing. But at Plat I see huge sucess running him this way. (Though everything else is the same. I obviously take the forced recruitment at 20. Double super catapults on core while you're all fighting on obj will win a game easy)

But that's neither here nor there.

Great post at the end of the day. Was just surprised to not see Azmodan on the list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 06:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose I'm only in Plat. Not quite at competitive levels, but I often go a W build and it works out amazingly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 00:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like Azmodan might be someone you're missing from this list. Getting him to 20, he's a very dominate Solo laner </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was the stupidest thing I've ever seen.

I loved it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again we are in plat. I'm not saying anyone is great but my azmo is level 20 so I'd like to think I play him above my level with other heroes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They honestly don't. I'm only plat mind you, but I've not been bullied out of lane by only one hero as Azmodan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 16:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They said they read the 2.0 feed back? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 05:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It honestly has not been a problem for me yet. Slyv is an awful solo laner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 05:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can beat anyone in lane as Azmodan. But I'm level 20 with him so I've got a bit of practice haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 01:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a bad tip! The shards you get from a master skin, as a "rare" skin are only 100. You get much more value from your gold for re rolls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 23:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't like him using their cereal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 22:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this a mobile game or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 03:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used the darkest orange for the edge, like the spirte
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 23:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is... Is this a thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 23:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By that I meant, like. It SHOWED me doing a lot but it didn't stick around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 23:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah. mine glitched so I was able to do alot. She's got one pixel enough space not to touch crono. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 23:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @OP can you edit your post to mention Marle is in production just too the left. I've got her pupil/hair line started. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 22:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started her awhile ago too. I did the front of her face, eye to eye with Chrono (Distance for the arm) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 22:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started Marle. Her eye and front of face are right across from Crono </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 22:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. If only </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 22:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right? I'd preorder it right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 22:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been participating without even seeing this thread. I am glad to have found the image though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Square's April Fool joke looks better than most games that have come out lately </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Team for star making a Jim Reference </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will HoTs 2.0 need to do that then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, it's not even sacrifice a few to save thousands. IT's sacrifice a few, so thousands can get free goodies. 

That's garbage in my opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the wAsp! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
