<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2129</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I made a mistake making beef stew. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 18:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I made a huge pot of Delicious beef stew the only problem i didn't add enough beef.

Now i have a big pot of gravy with no beef in it, my question is can i just sear more beef chunks boil them in beef broth till tender  and add that to my original gravy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 15:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Up too the 3 minute mark, I get that you made the track quickly so i understand it's not mixed all that well.

I do like the base layer not sure about reversing it near the end but thats how you make music you try out different things and see what sticks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 15:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I harness a powerful feeling and just let the music make itself.

That's basically all i do, I actually have no idea what i'm doing ; 0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 15:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stand with you, also I liked some of the progressions in your idea here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 15:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Parts of it i really like </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 14:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP can I hear these textured sounds that your making?

This board is on my wishlist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This seems fake, what do you guys think? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 02:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 01:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You would think Trump would denounce this kind of stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 21:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 19:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> link to episode ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 17:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 17:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good news is you have hard wood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 16:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So you're suggesting it was a heat issue

No, I thought perhaps it was just a bit flimsy compared to that of a consumer version.

I do agree with you. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 16:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a guess, I bet it's not the same kind of windscreen that's used on regular cars? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 16:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe a little delay,some wight noise and some sailing chords that span over 2 measures? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 13:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm betting if he owned the restaurant he'd most likely get the most he could from the customers, serve crappy food and pay low wages.

As far as i know he didn't even tip the waiter, if the shoe was on the other foot I don't think he would like being treated like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 12:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes are in my opinion has to be the band with the most flourishes,layer after layer of these little tack on's and production experiments.

If you listen to there music on a good pair of headphones you can hear all the little bits they'd layer there tracks with, it's so well done it feels oganic and natural, brilliant!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 12:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He started out debating philosophy on Youtube years ago....

Back then Youtube was very small and people weren't getting paid for content, it was kind of like a chat Vlog, Arguments would go back and forth for months and Thunderf00t was king,however,most of the people he was debating where idiots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 04:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude nailed all the synth parts! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 04:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say play slower, find sounds that move you.

I could be wrong but I see a talented player that is caught in the details.

Anyway don't take anything i say too heart, do what you want.

Edit: Here i think is a missed idea https://youtu.be/aPpbDnlyS-k?t=2m11s here you have this nice sounding patch, it could have been layered with a wonderful string section...something emotional.

Anyway I encourage you to keep at it.

I remember not too long ago i'd post tracks here that were so bad the mods deleted them so i'm not being a snob, just trying to give you my thoughts.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 00:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know what guys and gals we always need to be patient to people like this, she is obviously a little OCD and did something out of her normal routine and is obviously freaking out about it.

I worked for the parks for a while and they hired more than a few folks that had mental health issues and they were great people, at times it could be hard but you just have to find a way to think outside of yourself and understand some things are really hard for them.

Good on her </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 23:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny that you mentioned that, when i created the first sound I thought it sounded a bit like this  https://youtu.be/SDAglAOcqy8?t=5m5s .....

Then remembering that song had a robotic type sample I did my best to emulate that too. 

Edit- I'm thinking of putting in the voices of the enemy soldiers from quake 2  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 23:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scout looks fucking awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 21:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes this was made with real time samples using a MicroKorg and Audacity, no edits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 21:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Beak

I just checked them out on youtube, pretty neat sound they have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 21:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually have more stuff like this, I remember I played a creepy one for my friends and they were legitimately scared of me afterwards.

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 17:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very nice OP. The track has a nice warm cozy feeling.

Did you make this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 17:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From Wiki:

On 21 February 2005, Beksiski was found dead in his flat in Warsaw with 17 stab wounds on his body; two of the wounds were determined to have been fatal. Robert Kupiec (the teenage son of his longtime caretaker), who later pleaded guilty, and a friend were arrested shortly after the crime. On 9 November 2006 Robert Kupiec was sentenced to 25 years in prison, and his accomplice, ukasz Kupiec, to 5 years by the court of Warsaw. Before his death, Beksiski refused to loan Robert Kupiec a few hundred zoty (approximately $100). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This morning I made something super creepy messing about with my MicroKorg </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 16:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My big guy is a Newf/Pyr mix, I always had Newfoundlands there great dogs they don't live to long but the The flame that burns twice as bright burns half as long.

Here is a pic of Effie http://imgur.com/gallery/xU7Cn0s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Homeless woman steals dog - gets what's coming </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 13:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 13:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea dude, I love my dogs more then myself to think somebody would try to take them is disturbing.

That said I don't think she'd make it too far with mine they both way near 100 pounds each. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 23:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you guys having a comversation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 23:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like this guy is imagining that being a huge dildo is cool as fuck.

"Not so soft after all" Baaahaaahaa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 22:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The more you know

https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC4555894/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 21:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very! hard too watch, this is absolutely heart breaking.

It must be such a rollercoaster of emotions on one hand you love her and it's comforting to have her around whilst on the other your watching somebody slowly slip away.

Sorry I didn't have a constructive comment, I am really taken by how powerful this is. 

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very Nice, Sounds like your using a MicroKorg there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 17:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://wunc.org/post/mr-rogers-bellevue-super-markets-and-coney-island#stream/0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Love You Too Mommy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 17:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 14:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is interesting, did you make this OP? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Moth Radio Hour: Mr. Rogers, Bellevue, Super Markets and Coney Island </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 03:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 17:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess that Rancho Correcto place Dr Phil sent her too didn't work out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 17:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link to original content https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WeSbUUY_pNM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daddy German Shepherd Plays With His Pups. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 17:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> M E M O R E X = M E M O R I E S - Why Can't We Play Today by </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 14:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Public Transport - Morgenrot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 14:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some very interesting movements here, Thanks for sharing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really good job, very inspiring.

I'm currently working on something a little similar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for these, Sub has been abandoned for a while.

Let me know if you want to mod perhaps with some css mods and a little love we can get this going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 20:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is fantastic! Did you make this OP? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 14:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My fault I made the gifs one at a time and i couldn't figure out how to make an album. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 13:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only redeeming quality Dr Phil has is too spread the idea that you too can get help.

It falls apart when Dr Phil sends his guests to places with very expensive treatment plans, so if your not rich and your trying to get something out of this show and apply it to a loved one, your fucked.

Also is it a good idea to air your dirty laundry to millions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Organise - Philae </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 00:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Organise - Walden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 00:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 17:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seemed to be working fine even though it was "broken". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 14:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.mechanicards.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 14:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The lightest touch and you get stung, it feels a lot like a bee sting.

I once was digging for old bottles and i guess I barley touched some and ouch dude, I actually thought i was stung by bees and it takes like an hour to go away.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 14:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Old digger with a wealth of knowledge , I'd love to make a Vlog showing others how to find locations and dig for bottles.

I have a modest collection, As you get more advanced at digging what you take home and keep becomes less and less.


The digging community is very small and very tight knit community, I have met and talked to some of the old timers and I can tell you bottle digging is a dying art,however,if people knew how satisfying it is hopefully this awesome hobby could see a come back.

What I'd like to do is set up a mentor program where newbies are matched with experienced diggers so they have an opportunity to learn.

EG~ I could be a mentor for the lower part of NY and CT area's 

I think digging is not something you should do alone it can be dangerous, further more it's hard to learn by yourself.

So what do you think of these ideas.




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 00:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good stuff! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 23:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here are more


 1 - http://imgur.com/sefbKIK

 2 - http://imgur.com/R9lBqyM



 3 - http://imgur.com/rXQXrfV


 4 - http://imgur.com/iElTj4R
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These Mechanical Gift Cards.(More in comments) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 23:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 14:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Far more interesting than I expected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Chainless Bicycle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 19:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Chainless Bicycle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 19:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 16:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here I made an attempt to make it sound like Boards Of Canada http://vocaroo.com/i/s1r1kysIwH9k </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 15:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea Gordon has done some public outreach programs where he taught prisoners how to cook so they could get jobs outside of prison.

His brother is a heroin addict and Gordon grew up poor, he never forgot his roots, he is always willing to help those who are willing to work hard no matter where they come from.

I have a lot of respect for Gordon, he is way more than what you see on TV. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 13:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you guys liked this check this out -Mike Tyson World Record Progression

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bt1DFNSNbRk

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 03:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll check it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 03:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea totally, I can't agree enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 02:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually agree.

I just want some guidance, I'd hate to be held by my hand and be shown how to make music.

That said you never know what your going to find by asking a question or putting yourself out there.


Nothing wasted, Nothing Lost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 02:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I try, One day i'll be satisfied I hope.

I will keep at it : ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 01:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fuck with the LFO waves mostly.

The best advice I can give is get an analog like synth and just keeping at it till you make a sound that moves you.

That's all I really do so far, Just mess with it till I create something that inspires me.

I actually have no method : ) 

I am trying to learn new techniques and I do have high hopes I will create a really beautiful song one day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 01:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://soundcloud.com/user-345283577 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ccDuckett - Heptagon Moon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 01:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Principles Of Geometry - Colfax </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 01:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 01:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda creepy, I've done some tracks like this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 00:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once the hammer comes out i'm all "you know what I am so wrong please forgive me,here is alll my money,i'm walking away now" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 23:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I laughed when the huge TV came out besides the pool.

Rather than a comfortable living space this house seems to be a giant status symbol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 23:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like what you did there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 21:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of-course I'd be happy to have some beats to study.

On FL, I thought it could be a neat tool for making beats,however, at the time I was not convinced It could mesh well with my real time recording methods.....This was many years ago..perhaps i can give it another go.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 21:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "lead by a blind man who just wants someone to walk with for a little bit."

Maybe the blind man can tell me some cool story's along the way.

EDIT- Also I was thinking perhaps my unique sound could lend itself to somebodies projects?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 20:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a decent piano player. I know a good bit on playing analog synthesizers, I'm creative, i have a good attitude  and i'm a pleasure to work with.

I will really put in my time to learn and show progress.

That's about all I can offer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 20:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's nice, I'm just not keen on those type of synthesizers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I will check it out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought I could get something out of asking and i did so it wasn't a waist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If only I could.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to learn beat matching and how too make samples line up with my creations.

Also get an understanding of how hip hop and rap music are produced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll look into it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This perfect loop of a train passing on a snowy day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 16:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 15:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked this too, I've been experimenting with long drowning base layers like in your song here, very cool dude! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'd love to work with someone who can teach me some new techniques. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 15:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd really like an opportunity to work with somebody who is a decent producer and who could take me under there wing and teach me some new techniques.

I know this is a long shot, I have 0 professional training and I also can't read notes.

Anyway I'm open to learning, so far all my experiments are hammered out in real time with a MicroKorg and Audasity that's it.
 
Here are my experiments, The first 2 tracks where made with a producer, I really learned a lot from him.
https://soundcloud.com/user-345283577

I'm up for a challenge.

Thanks

   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 14:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell me about it, The lady lost her daughter and she wasn't a stranger but a close family friend and the boy gave her permission to drive on public roads.

How on earth are you going to be so cold heart'd to sue somebody after that, jeeez celebrate the fact that your son is alive.

It could have been worse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 13:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also I think this kid is talking too seriously BoC's use of obscure samples too seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Moth Radio Hour: Misfits, The MET, and a Nursing Home Switcheroo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 03:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 23:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A quick look around and I saw one made in the 70's sold on Ebay for 80 USD.

I'm guessing if you had one from the first years run that might double. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 22:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For cutting and pasting loops I find it really difficult. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 21:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the vaguest memory of playing with it, even singing ''Inchworm Inchworm"  the only 2 words I remembered from the commercial.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 21:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Audacity can do multiple stems etc, It sucks for fine edits,however, it records great in real time.

I guess what i need is a very robust .wav editor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 21:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a synth hobbyist looking to work with a better sampling technique, currently I'm using Audasity as my Daw. Do you know of anything that would accompany my real time recording methods.

Here are my experiments https://soundcloud.com/user-345283577 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't get over the look of sheer bliss on the kids face at 15 seconds, just loving his Inchworm :  )  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought for sure they where going to poke through.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1970's Commercial For The Inchworm toy, I actually had one of these,Loved it! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sampling Gold! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 19:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sampling Gold! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 19:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This 4 man backflip </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 19:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 18:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean the American Stig is a  recurring theme in GT? 

I was thinking it was a One Off in the first episode....shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 18:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For your next video can you eat 11 different varieties of wet cat food?

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 18:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The Grand Tour

I just watched the first episode, I hope it gets better, seemed a bit formulaic.

It's better than nothing and leaps better than Top Gear U.S.A.

I heard that they where going to have Jay Leno as the lead for Top Gear U.S, That's too bad I think it would have been great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 14:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because of the over dub with no room noise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 21:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your music has really got me thinking of different things tro try with my own stuff.

Number 7 is an interesting idea with these long sailing notes, I really like that....I cant wait to try this out.


Very cool guys  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 20:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not even sure they knew each other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 15:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Cosmo
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 13:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a little intrusive don't you think?

"Excuse me I don't approve of your girlfriend" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 22:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it,good job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm Afraid Dave By The Fade Beta and WLFWRK </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 19:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 16:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys are really good.

If you ever want to collaborate on something let me know.

PS.  Your welcome to post your music at /r/SoundsLikeBoC we'd love to have you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 14:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very true and over time his views have become more refined. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 13:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to give her credit on her determination, 4 days without food or water that's pretty impressive.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 21:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do care thank you.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 17:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is a great way to educate people about North Korea, I half heartily clicked on this thinking it was just going to be about how foreigners view American food,however....

As the video plays out we get a glimpse of what life is like in North Korea from an unfiltered perspective that I have never seen before.

I think your method here is great,something as simple as having some BBQ opens into an understanding of the difficulties that North Koreans face.

Good job!, You've got me hooked on wanting to learn more.

     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 14:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a musician myself I liked the music not sure why everyone is ragging on it.

But ya know, you have your own tastes so can't argue with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 14:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked it so far also I love the music.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 04:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you can help me?
'
 My grandfather used to say  "Your talking like a man with a paper asshole"

I guess  he meant your talking shit?...Still not sure, have you ever heard of this saying? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> World Record: Marble Madness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 02:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 01:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think if you google "attempted robbery at gun store" your going too see a lot of wins there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 01:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The shooter did seem to pause also the guy that was spared is wearing the same clothes as the shooter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 13:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should bait them....I'm willing to help.

I think I know what there up too,  it all starts when someone gives you a realistic-looking check or money order and asks you to send cash somewhere in return. It's phony, and so is the person's story, but that may take weeks to discover. Now your bank wants the money back. However, just because you can get the cash doesn't mean the check or money order is good. Ultimately, you are responsible for the checks or money orders you deposit or cash. That's how the scam works. EG~ below 

*  The receiving of packages containing payments to my employees(your fake check)

*  Dispatching letters to my employees via 1st class mail(sending the money from the cashed fake check)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 13:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the article that explains what happened here....
http://www.grindtv.com/wildlife/bizarre-wall-frozen-fish-makes-easy-meals-bald-eagles/#7hK230UDzMf8kJm1.97 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 04:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This could be a whole new category!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Safety Last </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 04:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fish Frozen in a lake pushed up by an ice sheet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 03:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Polygon Boy - primavera 16 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 16:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 13:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never seen this thanks OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 12:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They misunderstood she was just bringing the Kool-Aid O Yeaaaa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 23:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's cool living on the fringe. This kind of reminds me of that movie Dark Days but for the middle class.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 23:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree the dude was being rude cutting in line, I myself wouldn't be so rumbled about it.

That said the women over reacted and as soon as the dude noticed that, he should've just backed down...instead he decided to roll the dice and taunt her. 

In a nut shell, stupid games win stupid prizes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 21:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Train Spotting 2 WTF? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 20:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> aww </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 13:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true, however, this is the first time a president is waging an all out war against the media.

He hasn't officially done anything yet as president and he is at such odds with the news media.

At this rate he will have ostracized himself with the news outlets in a matter of months.

He doesn't even want to answer simple questions or own anything he has said.

Trump is far from typical and that's why people like him.
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 01:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "And was the resolution for this video set to minecraft?"

Answer: Tater-vision </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 22:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You make a good point, It's all together possible that a somebody that wishes to do harm in this way, may only need pics of the victim and access to there internet connection.

Then all you would need to do is coax your victim to be at a place and time.

life ruined 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 21:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "so what's the scam?"

Binary Goal is a online stock trader program or at-least is supposed to be.

What it really does is suck you dry with all sorts of hidden fee's.

I read from multiple sources that they also make it near to impossible to withdrawal your funds.

Binary Goal is a scam.
  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 00:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would try a product like Musher's Secret It's made with bees wax and will prevent snow build up.

And it can double for muddy walks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 23:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Geez you'd think they at least shared some good times with there daughter.

It boggles the mind that this poor little girl had parents that were so disconnected emotionally.....how can that be?, shit they knew her for 14 years.

I just don't get it.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Moth Radio Hour: Live from Boston </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 22:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 16:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are just giving away money.......sounds so real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 16:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it could be Aleister Crowley. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 16:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also dude had some serious practice ...what a shot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking maybe you can get a dog, I think having a dog helps with depression.

It makes you get out of the house and you get unconditional love.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 21:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "No. Fuck. I meant hit the road"

"OK boys play it"

"Hit the road Jack and don't you come back no more, no more, no more, no more.)
(Hit the road Jack and don't you come back no more"

"STOP!"

"Woah Woman, oh woman, don't treat me so mean,
You're the meanest old woman that I've ever seen.
I guess if you said so
I'd have to pack my things and go. (That's right)
What you say?
(Hit the road Jack and don't you come back no more, no more, no more, no more.)
(Hit the road Jack and don't you come back no more."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 00:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is just a screen cap of the banner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crazy Lady at a convenience store, jumps onto the counter and drinks her own piss. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 21:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 20:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Public Freakout they said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 14:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup that's my Effie, only listens when he wants too and will never fetch,rollover or stay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 14:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my favorite "What you do?" https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8wpFrdevEhs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 21:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a post apocalyptic world a well dressed man is grocery shopping with a flashlight in a bombed out supermarket.(scene 1)

Whilst He exits the store you see the backdrop, bombed tattered remains of a once great city(scene 2)

Loading the canned goods into the side satchels of his motorcycle he suddenly freezes when he hears the sound of children playing echoing off in the distance.(scene 3)

He quickly starts his bike and races off to find the source of the noise.(scene 4)

After a few minutes he finds the source, children are outside playing in a bombed out playground and tears begin to stream from his eyes.(scene 5)

He parks the bike and sits down on a park bench to watch the kids play...he begins to laugh hysterically tears streaming from his eyes.(scene 6)

As he watches the kids play he reaches into his pocket and take out a pill bottle opens it into his palm and tape on the bottle it's empty(scene 7)

He drops the bottke to the grounds and it reads "Aripiprazole 2 reffils left) (scene 8)

We now see him laughing hysterically as the children play in the background (scene 9)

The final scene we see him again all alone laughing next to a bombed out playground laughing....nobody was ever there it was all in his head before the world came to end he being it's only survivor, our character had severe Schizophrenia.
The story could be called "off my meds" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 20:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ender sure looked special, you can see the love in his eyes.

I agree with /u/dpyrs to get another dog It really helped us to get over our loss.

I'm sorry for your loss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 17:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't mind vatted I highly recommend Big Peat, I think it's the best vatted Islay I have ever tried.

If you can get the 2014 Christmas Edition try that one.

Now onto an unpopular opinion, I don't think a Scotch review can be accurately done by trying a Dram, I find myself drinking at least half a bottle before i'm ready to talk about it.

Scotch to me is like a good book it gets more interesting as you get deeper into it.

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 16:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cutty Sark and Glenlivet 12 are garbage hows that for a unpopular opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 16:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't had the privilege of trying their single casks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In an effort to increase sales Burger King hired McDonald's executive Donald N. Smith.They made a magician mascot to compete with Ronald McDonald called "The Magical Burger King". (1978) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 02:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Toyotas new concept car.(Concept-i) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 23:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 23:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  sacrifice a few goat

"sacrifice" is that what your calling it now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 22:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Sit on the floor a lot when you are in the same room as him" This is what I would do and when hew approaches look at him and then look away and down this will show him your non aggressive. 

I also agree with pyrfostermom76 not to touch his head, if he came from an abusive place stay away from the head until mutual trust is obtained.

Every time you see him tell him how good he is using soft tones and if you can get him on a leash and walk with him for an hour or so a day he will love you very quickly.

I'm also sorry to hear that Harry came from an abusive home, It pisses me off to think your dog or any dogs are abused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 20:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just going to ask how it tasted with water Caol Ila's are very subtle single malts.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 20:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find Glenfiddich to be a boring scotch, it's not bad by any means just boring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup it breaks my heart, I buried Pauly in my backyard around the same time, planted a lilac bush.

The good news is Pauly made it to 19 you can't ask for more.

I'm not religious or anything but I love that poem called the rainbow bridge if there is a heaven i wouldn't want to be there without my dogs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 18:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My intention was to get a newfie, looking through adoption ads i discovered Effie so on a whim I went to the adoption place.....When I arrived the women in charge brought him out.

Effie was very sad and broken, he came right up to me and placed his paw onto my lap. It broke my heart, I fought hard to hold back my tears ...a big dog like him i thought, shouldn't be without love and lots of it.

After I got him home It took a long time for Effie to really bond with me.

My other dog Lacy really helped him to feel at home they became instant friends and with lots of love from all of us ...Effie changed both physically and mentally, me and him have an inseparable bond now wherever I am Effie wants to be there too.

Here is Effie and Lacy now http://imgur.com/a/YfhLD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 17:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about a one eyed madman wearing clown makeup riding on a tricycle made of pork chops on the edge of an active volcano filled with kittens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 14:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> String </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 17:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a really nice sentiment, it's nice to know how much you loved them.

I always had newf's growing up but now that i have Effie i'd like to get another pyr.

Effie is perfect for me because he is way more active then a newf, on long walks he doesn't tire and he is more loyal then any other dog i've ever had.

Pyr's are mysteriously intelligent and observant dogs...i often like to think that Effie knows more about me then I do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 16:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If your not damaging your life or anybody else and you take drugs...i say then that's your right to do so.

He is talking about those who are in need of help that have ruined there lives and the people around them because of there out of control drug use.


It has little to do with being different and not subscribing to social norms like top 40 pop tunes....it's about providing ways to reconnect with people and offering a better way to live then to be prosecuted just because your battling a destructive addiction.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 16:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your only human, I have my problems too, I'm not trying to judge you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 15:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bad then, I really think there is a difference between those who take drugs and those who have life eroding addictions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 15:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You make a good point....but think what we could do if only we legalized drugs....we could help them with programs to help them reintegrate back into society.

As it stands now people with these destructive addictions have no hope or love it's a vicious cycle.

I know first hand what your talking about, I lost 2 friends to hard drug use and near the end they where very difficult to be around(not trust worthy)

Not saying everyone can be saved,however, I do think with help rather than harm we could seriously make a difference.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 14:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm referring to addicts that are people destroying there lives with the over consumption of drugs.

Not people who take drugs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 14:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he is saying that a large number of addict's stay addicted because there ostracized/shunned from reintegrating into society.

I totally think we should stop this stupid war on drugs...addict's are people with depression let's treat it as such.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 14:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guy makes a good point, If your caught using/possessing  "illegal" drugs your slapped with a criminal record.

If you get a criminal record your most likely never going to get a good job again....it's a slow death sentence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 22:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cosmo is beautiful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 19:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy boy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 19:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to answer these one by one.

"I kept trying to use a firm voice to yell at him to get out"

I find yelling at mine will not work I use love to train my dogs EG~ sit and come, when they respond correctly are rewarded with hugs kisses,head pats. When Effie doesn't listen telling him to come will never work that will just make him extra defiant However, If i say "come here good boy" or "who's a good boy"   he listens.

My thinking is letting him feel it's his own decision to come yields better results then commanding him to do so.

"Then came bath time. I couldn't get him into the bathroom because he hates it"

Well he is always going to hate it just comfort him as best you can, reassure him he is doing a good job.  

"Then I had to keep him out on the balcony for about 1 hour to dry."

He didn't like the bath and now was separated from you when he was under stress....he needed you.

Take care to look at your dog and try to see what he is feeling if he is scared or bothered hold him, kiss him, tell him he is a good boy.

Take a dry towel and laet him lie on the floor inside near you. Sit next to him and dry him off, calm his nerves.

"he peed in the house"

He was under stress it's ok, practice what i said and he will see these things as not so bad next time.

   

 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 17:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has also saved me.

There has been times I wasn't feeling well, Effie will come rest his big head on my shoulder almost as if to say "I'm here for you buddy".

I'm convinced he knows because that's the only time he does it ...I have had many dogs but nothing like him.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 17:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guy does this thing when off the leash, he will come close when i call him but right as your going to put the leash on he darts away with a big smile on his face.

The only way i can get him to come back is to tell him he is a good boy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 16:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Darn it, I wish I could correct that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 15:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He kinda looks more like a Newf in this photo,however, the Great Pyrenees side is dominant right down to his triangle shaped ears,curly tail and double dew claws.

I love him too bits, Effie loves to be hugged and patted on his head.

He has a Very fluffy soft coat great to snuggle with on a cold day.

To be honest I love him more than words can express, Effie is my loyal buddy and protector and is always by my side.

His big booming bark is sure to keep all the Squirrels and neighbors cats at bay.


EDIT: After a few months of grooming him his coat is now a dark black and his white patches are now very bright. He was heart broken for a long time and would escape whenever he could, with patients,long walks and many hugs later Effie is now very happy.

When Effie is very happy he spins around it's so cute do your Pyr's do that?


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is my boy Effie Pyr/Newf I saved him from a kill shelter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 15:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 13:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The group recorded a comeback album in 1998, but Rob Pilatus died before the album was released. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 13:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I don't get is why the mother assumed that the skater would intentionally want to hit her son...she barks out "you didn't see him" as if to infer that this skaters hobby is to skate into little boys.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 18:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  rushed by aggressive offleash dogs and there's a switch that flips

That's what triggers Effie...he never will go after another dog however, If they start jumping on him he will get upset.

That said he let's my dog do anything to him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 17:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Effie won't start a fight but if another dog decides to try him Effie will finish it and absolutely won't back down.

Effie likes non aggressive dogs and will even lay on his back pretending to give them the upper hand/paw....he seems to be extremely tolerant of dogs he likes.

On the other hand Effie is not super interested in other dogs besides a quick sniff, whilst at the dog park he usually will go off on his own.

Other things iv'e observed that are worth noting...Effie's ability to mimic behavior Eg~ My other dog when out outside on our long leash will pretend to get stuck just to coax me to come outside to play with her....somehow Effie picked up on this and adopted the same tactic.


He loves to collect shoes and doesn't chew them, he puts them around where he naps.    

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Questions about the great Pyrenees temperament. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 14:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I adopted a great Pyrenees/Newf from a kill shelter named Effie.

Having had Newfoundland's before i believe Effie exhibits behavior  more from his great Pyrenees side.

Effie unlike a Newf will not back down from a fight EG~ At the dog park if a dog try's to challenge him he will not stop until that dog gives up or is inured.(it's  actually very scary)

On the other hand Effie is very very sweet and loyal to me, I trust him and i know he would never hurt me, my wife or my other dog.

Effie is very protective of our property, if he see's or even smells the scent of another animal he let's out the deepest scariest bark I've ever heard.

Effie likes to sleep in neutral locations in the house so he can hear both the front and back door incase of intruders.

Outside Effie likes to wonder and won't listen when you call him, he stays about a half football field away and only comes back when your near the car or home.

Overall Effie is a sweet and loyal guy who really loves to be loved my only concern is when he flips the switch when he feels threatened ....it's scary.


Are these traits to expect in a great Pyrenees?

 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 16:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My best moment in gaming was when i beat Metal Gear for the Nes.

I did it by generating save codes until I managed to create one that got me to the end of the game.


I spent more time cracking codes then I actually played the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Textbook quality as these guys jack a large pine. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 13:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 20:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not my cup of tea,however, this has been professionally produced from what I heard.

So yea it sounds clean and your voice is good.

My only problem with it is ...it sounds like at-least a dozen or so artists doing the same thing.

I think you have the Talent to do broader material, perhaps work with a different producer.

Overall it sounds professional.

    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Instrumental IDM] The Fade Beta- Like Tears, Inspired by BoC and Science Fiction. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 19:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Moth Radio Hour: Jury Duty, Walking Tests, Pepsi and NOLA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 23:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 16:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/FellingGoneWild </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
