<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2159</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 19:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course this is a highly opinionated statement and only accounts for games that I have played. No need to get your panties in a twist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 05:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Horizon's story is second to only The Last of Us (for a video game story).

I beat it yesterday and I was completely floored by it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I noticed some heroes don't have a score yet, what's up with that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much meta data do you get? Winrate per hero is one thing, but I would think a lot more information is necessary to give an accurate score. It would be cool to have like average score in dominion or something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the changes/buffs in this patch were *mainly* bug fixes (aside from Valk) and fixing unintentional mechanics like Zerk and Conqs light recovery. They probably want to wait and collect more data/do more creative thinking about how to balance all the other characters than make hasty decisions and change everything at once. They are being smart. This patch is fine, save your bitching for when something is actually worth bitching about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 23:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 23:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every game in the history of games has had servers go down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 20:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like this

https://youtu.be/A7LwQjhpZ-g </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 00:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think all maps have a ledge somewhere at least, but most can be easily avoided. Only a couple maps have a small amount of space to maneuver.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 22:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want dunkey to review every game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 22:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair points, I imagine esports would probably ban the maps that are nothing but ledge kills.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 19:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You try and push a skilled player off a cliff and you'll be the one falling. There's still skill involved and it's very high risk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 18:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in a 1v1 on a map with easy ledge kills, I kept trying to pull the fight away the ledge so we couldn't do that, but he determined to stay there. I ran at him and kicked him off. I said in chat "you made me do it." HE replied "I know T_T" and he never went by the edge again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Environment kills may seem cheesy (they kinda are), but they are also very exciting imo. When you get better at countering guard break you don't have to worry as much. But sometimes you're in a map with easy ledge drops and both players know exactly what the other is going to try to do. You can see it on their faces. Playing around this is, imo, exciting and can go both ways.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, in these kinds of games, the "progression" is just getting good. The drive to improve and learn game mechanics and better as a player is all the progression I need. I'm sure it's the same for the majority of players. What gear progression they do have is just cook for adding small tweaks to your 4v4 playstyle. Nothing major. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 03:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vsauce's show is pretty fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because if you have a bot on your team, you lose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please stop filling Deathmatch with bots, Ubisoft </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no join in progress for Deathmatch, but I keep getting matches where MM puts bots on one side. Not even split them up, they'll be two on one side and none on the other. WTF, just wait a minute and use people please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes it really helps to think about something for a few seconds before you speak. I consider that a crucial quality that I learned in life. I'm sure you'll get there.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for reading past the the first half of my post. It was the big point i was trying to make. Didn't think everyone would get so worked up with the specifics of how op the ship is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 05:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I can both try to play optimally and criticise what WG made the optimal choice to be. Hate the game, not the player." 

-/u/Roflkopt3r </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 03:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A unicum Belfast player will outplay every other ship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have given fair points as refute against these hard counters. Your refusal to address them is not an invalidation. 

This is true of every ship in the game.

Tell that to a DD vs a radar cruiser. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Often Belfasts will be undetected prior to slowing down for their smoke. It's poor play on the Belfast's part otherwise.

* As I've stated elsewhere, forcing a Belfast out of their smoke is effective, but it's not a counter. With its 8.7km detection, being able to quietly relocate when threatened is strength, not a weakness. A luxury many ships don't have.

* Shooting into smoke requires a bit of RNG because your dispersion is so poor. Also a good Belfast player might be moving.

* CVs need to be played more, I agree. CV is a counter to Belfast.

* A good Belfast player won't let a BB rush their smoke. They should see this coming way before its too late and, as stated above, being able to quietly relocate (8.7km detection) is not a weakness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being able to disengage quietly and relocate is not a weakness. Many ships don't get such a luxury. Forcing a Belfast to go quiet for a minute or so and get a better position is not a soft kill, it's good play from the Belfast and it's plays like that that often win games.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's worth pointing out that being pushed off a cap or forced to disengage without doing damage is something that is universal across all classes. Any other cruiser that doesn't have smoke will have to disengage simply if a BB starts looking at them. Any DD trying to cap can get forced out by the enemy team getting too close. Unless a BB manages to sneak up on a Belfast smoke, they will be spotted from however far out. I've had Scharnhorst try and charge but hell, they are going to lose half their HP before they even reach the smoke. If you look at ranked seasons in the past, there are certainly strong ships that get played the most, every tier will have them. But you look at ranked this season and its Belfast that beats everything. With good play, a Belfast will never be hard countered.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that's exactly my point. The way to beat it is just playing a better Belfast. This is not okay and this is something that shouldn't exist. It's not fun, it's not balanced gameplay. And it's Wargaming's stance on nerfing premiums that brings up very real issues with the game's direction (which was most of the point of my post). If Wargaming refuses to take the hit on nerfing a premium for the benefit of their game, it shows their attitude at how they care about balance. You cannot simply accept the fate of the ship behind Wargaming's own policies as they are not there for anyone's benefit but Wargaming's. Contrary to the response I've been getting in this thread, I know that I'm not the only one concerned with their current direction. When ranked was announced for T7, I saw loads of contention about how Wargaming pushes OP premiums at T7 and how they know exactly what they are doing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 01:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd argue that most of these "counters" simply involve delaying the Belfasy's potential and not stopping it. Sure a charging BB or a torp wall might force you to leave but you can just relocate with your 8.7km detection and start over. You have 4 smokes on a fast cooldown.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 01:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With 8.7km detection and a half decent amount of game sense, no Belfast player worth his salt will let a BB charge them. If such a threat seems like it might happen, you can just leave your smoke before they get within your detection.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 01:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they balance around server wide stats, it's clear the Belfast is one of the strongest ships in the game. In fact, most of the other ships that perform about as well (stat wise) are all niche premiums being played by a small group of mostly skilled players or ships that have qualified as OP and are no longer for sale. It's the one ship with the most matches played in the top ships of 2 weeks while the others fit the criteria I listed above. With its increased amount of matches, we can assume that it's not just mostly skilled players in it, but a good mix of everyone. 

The ships that are best in competitive simply perform well for the meta and with team play. Their strengths are ideal for the type of gameplay that competitive brings out but on their own this does not make them OP. Belfast is a ship outperforms all other competition on its own and it really requires a team effort to take down just a single one. It's also worth pointing out that in competitive play, there are numerous good ships. By the state of ranked, it's clear that Belfast doesn't simply outclass other cruisers, but every other ship class as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 01:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You cannot balance a game on the low skilled players. The most successful games balance around high skill play. But this goes back to the point I made in the post about the only thing that counters it is itself. Can you dispute this? Because that is the crux of the issue and just because a better Belfast player will beat a worse one does not a balanced ship make.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have summarized ranked this season. Play Belfast and do it better than the other team. It's the only viable strat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand that, and I addressed that sentiment in this post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The prospect of "is only as good as the player using it" can be applied to every ship, OP or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Belfast has hydro so you see them coming then zip out with your turbo boost acceleration.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What it is that makes a ship over powered and War Gaming's purposeful negligence. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the current state of ranked play and with the upcoming release of the USS Black and prospects of the future of Warships, I'd like to bring this discussion to you guys. 

I've been playing competitive games for a long time and I've been playing Warships for 2 years now. I've seen all kinds of things that are OP to things that people want to be OP and others that people think are OP but are not. Something that I think a lot of people misunderstand when looking at game balance is the idea that something that is strong is not necessarily over powered. In fact, I would argue that good balance requires some things to be strong for their purpose to be able to bring good diversity to the gameplay. 

Let's look at some ships more specifically that I think fit this role. The first ship that comes to mind is the Yamato. This is a ship that can tank every other BB while punishing those that try to tank it. Is this OP? Well no, it's certainly strong, but other elements like cruiser fire and torps keep it grounded (so to speak). What bout Moskva? That's a ship that is long considered OP but again I would argue that just because it is good at its job (bow tanking enemy fire) there are still ways to shut it down. Moskva can get overrun very easily, its bow overmatched, and once its engaged it has basically no way of disengaging. 

So what do these two strong ships have in common? There are ways to counter them. There is interaction that minimizes their effectiveness. This is the core principle of what can be considered balance. And it's also why (I assume) stealth firing is under scrutiny from WG. Stealth firing is a mechanic that has little interaction and in some cases, little to no way of countering. This is why it is imbalanced. 

But then again, stealth firing is a problem mechanic in the game and shouldn't really reflect the balance of whatever ship takes advantage of it. 

**Through all my years of playing multiplayer games, there is a SINGLE tell-tale sign of something that is way overpowered: it's only counter is itself.** 

BELFAST SHOULD BE REMOVED FROM THE GAME.

(or at least least nerfed)

Ranked has brought this prospect back into my perspective in an infuriating way. Here we have a meta that is dominated by smoke. Okay. Fine. Smoke is strong but there are ways to counter it, right? At higher tiers, sure. Long range radar, long range hydro, and long range torps do it well enough. But at T7? The only radar that exists (is on premiums) is very short range and getting into that range is tricky. Unless you're a Belfast with 8.7km detection and smoke of its own. So, the only viable radar counter to this heavy smoke meta is the smoke meta king himself, the Belfast. 

BBs don't counter it: you can't hit what you can't see (generally). DDs don't counter it: 10km torps require you to get dangerously close to their radar and lololol Belfast has hydro and super acceleration. So, in the end, the only actual counter to Belfast is another Belfast.

The existence of this ship in the game is incredibly troubling. Wargaming doesn't nerf premiums for understandable reasons (money backlash), but that is THEIR issue. Belfast being in this game is OUR issue and if they refuse to address that for their own benefit, I would be vary weary of continuing any support for this developer. I've defended Wargaming on many occasions and many dumb decisions. Most of the time they got it right eventually. But this is really unacceptable for any developer that claims to care about their game and their customers over their own bottom line. Be careful watching these guys moving forward. Their intentions are becoming more and more clear. I hope they prove me wrong, but with ranked being T7 this time and the current state of T7 premiums, it's hard to assume otherwise. Until then, I think it's time I found another game to play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah we had the Atlanta and Ranger to their Flint and Hiryu. The CV walked all over us once all the smoke started dissipating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turns out, most of those smokes have radar too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6 smokes per side. 6 Belfast. Zero ways to counter any of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is dumb. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you just gave the definition of standard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 18:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the correct answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 04:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well maybe at lower ranks you'll see those, but I think this post from Rank 10 on EU is a pretty good sign of what to expect. 

http://i.imgur.com/Ho7eXwy.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This ranked season will be awful. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 04:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The amount of smoke is just not fun. You're going to see 5+ ships with smoke (ON EACH TEAM) from here on until rank 1, I promise you. And the most viable radar ship to counter these smokes is a HE spam from smoke ship jajajajajaja.

This is fucking boring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "If you're not good enough to carry the team to victory, you're not good enough to win." 

-random tryhard from my CoD days </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 games, 2 losses  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh this isn't your footage then  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 08:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think your UI is messed up.  Nothing is where it should be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 20:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I do use them. But I, on average, get Confederate once every like 8.5 games. Since the achievement gives 10 flags, I will, on average, be getting more than I can use. Hence the 2000 of them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hence my upcoming payday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 16:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell man, I'd do that in a second. Most flags I have 500 or more of, I don't even where they came from </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 16:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh boy I can sell flags??? 

I have 2000 of both the +50% XP and +50% captain XP flags that I'll never go through.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 15:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell that to amazon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 15:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just shop at Amazon* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 18:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thr best at suckin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 18:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^

To be fair, a lot of clans have high winrate players who think they're the best. 

------------- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 23:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WTR is a bit more inclusive than WR but both tell you different things. On the WTR scale, they dont value WR very much (10%). I imagine they do this because divisions have better WRs than solo play. But your ability to win matches generally says more than you ability to do damage to enemy ships (which is most of WTR), imo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 02:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was a snapon salesman for several years and never met a single one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never heard of a mechanic that hates Hondas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sean is an excellent host </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 18:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The same logic applies to feeling sorry for T8 vs T9.

Difference is T7 rarely gets up tiered these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 17:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In every multiplayer game that have ever existed in the history of video games, people have been potatoes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 17:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And a single torpedo strike that gets detected by the double planes, or the bombers they intercept can be the difference between life and death. 

In my experience, torpedo strikes and CV strikes are much more common than having a main turret incapacitated. So +1 fighter it is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 17:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a good thing the hivemind doesn't make balance decisions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 13:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember when radar was coming out and reddit thought it was the end of DDs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 05:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but every other t8 cruiser would improve the same amount with a heal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 05:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hipper needs to shoot way more than 8 shells every 13 seconds to be anything close to op.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 16:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Off the top of my head, the important ones are the reload module and both steering gears. The other ones were like damage control and turret hp iirc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 14:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my first full length commentary I've done on here. I know that I'm no flamu or aerron, but I hope my Hindenburg play makes up for it!

Take a drink every time I say "situation". ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to play the Hindenburg - commentary - 284k damage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 13:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 13:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking sweet. Baltimore is even more beastly and DM gets a nice and needed buff.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 20:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A gif *with* sound??

What shall we call this absurd revalation!?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 07:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ethan needs to get soflo on his podcast.  Seems like they'd be chill together.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 00:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt I'm well known at all, but you can look at my stats and see my winrate is usually a bit better than this, lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 22:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cantcarryhardenough.jpg

Most of these losses are just our DDs dying instantly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 22:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I have a lot of games played.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That weekend life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 21:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 01:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the Vietnam expansion. Played as much of that as the base game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 02:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I only just found out it was a preorder bonus in this thread. Since half the games these days release semi broken, pre-ordering is usually "bad for your health". And it rewards shitty business practices like releasing broken games. Publishers encouraging pre-orders with bonuses that would have improved my experience with the game is distasteful. I would otherwise have no reason to pay for a product I do not own. 

I thought this was a universal reddit common ground. I'm quite flabbergasted right now tbh. I just came into this thread to share an opinion of how I would have enjoyed the game more and came out of it being called entitled and I'm pretty sure I just experienced victim blaming. 

I thought devs respecting the intelligence of their players (in this case letting them choose the difficulty) was an attribute worthy of praise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 01:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well this is the first community I've seen that encourages pre-orders. Must be an odd bunch. I think I'll not stick around.

Enjoy the circlejerk and have a nice night.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 00:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shitty business practices are certainly not my fault. Pre-ordering is bad for your health. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 22:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I don't really think apple will be passing these savings onto customers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 21:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh lord.

First off, I'm entitled for disagreeing with the developers? 

Oh lord.

Secondly, if they really didn't want people playing madhouse first, they wouldn't have even offered it as a preorder reward. 

Thirdly, I'm at fault for *not* pre-ordering? Ladies and gentlemen we have come full circle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 21:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that's why they did it, but I disagree with them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 20:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> .... wtf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 20:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see what you're saying, but that should be up to the player.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 20:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The normal game was a bit of a cakewalk though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wish Madhouse was available from the start. :( </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 20:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda shitty imo. 

I usually play games on the hardest difficulty for the challenge. The extra layer of difficulty *usually* adds to the experience and satisfaction of beating a game. This goes doubly so for a survival horror game like RE7, where tension is high and the task at hand seems impossible which *should* be matched by the difficulty. Well I just beat the game on Normal and I wasn't even aware of the Madhouse difficulty as it popped up and told me I had unlocked it. I enjoyed the game a lot but it was not a difficult game. Now I have this extra difficulty and reading up on it, it seems like exactly how the game should have been play the FIRST run through. That playthrough where you're still figuring out what is even going on. What are enemy's weaknesses? Where do I go? What are even the coins for!? Because experiencing all that on top of the mechanics of Madhouse would have been a TRULY terrifying and nail biting experience. When you FINALLY get to that safe zone with 1 HP and 1 bullet and you're *holy fucking shit man that was close*. And it's how the game should have been played from the start. These types of games I usually just play once and then maybe again later when it's not so fresh on the mind. So I feel very gibbed.

tl;dr - why the fuck do devs lock difficulties behind completion?

/rant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 20:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, "should be criminal" may be a bit of a stretch but it doesn't make much sense for multi million/billion $ businesses to pay literally pennies on the penny when everyone else is forking over large % of their salary. I mean, this is what trickle down is all about, problem is companies do everything in their power to exactly not trickle down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 13:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I've stated elsewhere, I fail to see the point of bastion as a game mode. It seems the strategies involved in winning can also be found in domination  (cap early) but bastion is one dimensional in that regard while domination can be won other ways. So bastion offers gameplay and strategy alreqdy found in domination, but brings nothing more on top of that other than more pain for DDs (that don't need it). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 06:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hero we need yadayada </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 06:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do celebrities always take such shitty photos. They need to look at gonewild and take some pointers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 05:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I like about her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 04:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well there's plenty you could do; you could kill them. It's not like they have forts doing huge damage, they can die all the same. It doesn't cap out that fast.

That said, it's not hard to stop them fully capping.

And there's 3 caps. 

I'm not saying epicenter should be the only mode, buts a good alternative to dom. Never seen an issue with the gameplay it brings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 22:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's wrong with epicenter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 21:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yet the broadside cruiser came out of it with an overpen. RNG giveth and taketh away always . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 08:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish you a pleasant night, sir.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 08:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You always struck me the type to read the first sentence and presume the rest.  

Kudos to you for cherry picking your arguments.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 07:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We were aggressive early and lost the fight. Should this be the end of the match? Perhaps all games of bastion should last only 5 minutes, the victor decided by who holds the caps at the time. This would certainly relive many the displeasure of playing the mode further, but I fail to see to depth and reason of such an implementation. Domination already offers a similar advantage and strategy for the early game, but implores also a mid game and late game that continue to evolve strategy. Bastion offers nothing that isn't already offered in other game modes and yet brings nothing new.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 06:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was the version that has two forts in the mid, our team capped one and theirs the other. Then their fort killed our DDs from our fort, which allowed them to take both. Taking them back was a futile effort and you can see just how much of input their actual team had on the situation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bastion game, can you tell which team won? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 00:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Scoreboard](http://i.imgur.com/Au99ysN.jpg)

[My team lost.](/spoiler)

The forts did 90% of the work for the winning team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 00:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one mentions the Hindenburg? 

BLASPHEMY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 19:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adrenaline Rush is so fun I would probably drop off Vigi or SI to get it in there + Priority Target.

At the end there, if you have Adrenaline Rush you *may* have been able to deal with the charging Roon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 06:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's not an issue with the game mode though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 23:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remove bastion, replace standard battle with epicenter. Game becomes better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 18:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, some of them might be obvious, but most not so much. For a lot of ships I think there are a few viable builds.  And yes of course I was kidding.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 21:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plenty of people have 19 point captains and if you dont, just get most of the major skills and save the rest for later.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 13:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just keeping you on your toes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 13:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Situational Awareness skills exist only in your mind, grasshopper.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 13:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IF HE makes the 105s do damage now. The 128s don't need it as much. At least vs DDs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 13:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I generally keep HE loaded 24/7 on everything and switch to AP if I see an opportunity. Even on ships with a quick 8 second reload, it might be too long and you miss the opportunity. 

PM is also pretty valid though imo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 06:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HEAP AFT CE is correct.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 06:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Chapy build.](http://i.imgur.com/rcbYnEn.png)

You could swap out RL for AFT if you'd like more AA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 06:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EM seems like a waste since the Khab has lightning turret rotation by default. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 05:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Khab has like 10 different viable builds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 05:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [How could I forget!?](http://i.imgur.com/et2j897.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
