<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1563</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean I have 5 horses named, but they aren't exactly what I wanted. Goliath is my giant horse, then Flash is my fastest horse, Pegasus is my white horse, Wraith is my black horse and then I have Epona. I wasn't trying to be that creative but it just sucks when you come up with a name but it's too long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because he works as Gus's cook? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember that Gus originally went to Don Elladio to work with him in distributing meth. He would have been completely fine to work for the cartel if Elladio didn't have his partner killed. It's only because that happened that Gus plotted his revenge. He never cared about the evil things the cartel did except that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aren't I so edgy??? I called someone fat online. Fuck PC culture amirite???  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> About horses... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why in God's name do we only get 9 characters to name our horses? Every name I come up with seems to have 10 or more characters.

Shadowmere, Darkwraith, Ganonhorse, Lightbringer, Blitzkreig.

Have the creators ever watched horse racing??? You can't properly name a horse when limited to 9 characters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know you're joking but I actually didn't say anything about gender. I was referring to sexuality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously people check top posts regularly, I'm more referring to a compulsive need to check top posts any time I view a new sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 05:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta live up to my name  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 03:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly don't think a person can visualize what 1000 mph looks like any more than lets just say 5000 rpm. It's pretty meaningless unless compared with something else. If we were talking say 25 mph vs 75 mph and 25 rpm with 75 rpm yeah I'd say you have a point, but at these speeds it really can't be imagined it needs to be compared with the speed of something else to understand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mario Cart


triggered </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then use rpm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This may be a dumb comment, but does it matter that the decals mess up the finish on the joycons, if you never plan to take the decals off? I mean, isn't that the point of the decal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> writing 3000 what? 3000 words? pages? characters? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE immediately check top posts of all time when looking at a new subreddit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we're concerned with how hard the spinner is hitting it, then we should be measuring the force really. Then it should be newtons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that would make the most sense. I still think it's kind of odd to measure how fast it's spinning in anything but rpm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> measuring rotation in mph

why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh god damn, I didn't even read til the end  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow dude, I'm blind you asshole </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 16:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only one who doesn't enjoy watching this? I love when fights are slugfests but this just makes me cringe to watch. No movement at all. Really ugly fighting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 16:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never seen something more fake and gay in my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I don't really think that's gonna happen either. I think the point is to show Chuck is crazy and a danger to himself, or maybe there's some other reason we don't know about. This wasn't meant to be a serious post, I was just trying to give you guys a Chuckle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SPOILER] If the theories are true... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boxers actually have come into contact with male genitalia  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't wrap my head around two straight guys holding hands and it being normal. I honestly feel like it's less gay when two guys jokingly kiss than hold hands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE feel like vomiting after brushing your teeth? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I don't hate them. For a few bucks it's a cool little gadget. I'm surprised at the people who have them though. My 12 year old brother bought one, and then I found out one of my friends has one (in his 20s). Then, yesterday in one of my college classes I noticed someone playing with one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great insight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but honestly I never notice that when people post screenshots. What I do notice is when they have 3% battery. Charge your damn phone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know way too much about movies and shows that I've never watched thanks to TVtropes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was only seven years old
I loved Shrek so much, I owned all the movies and merchandise
I pray to Shrek every night, thanking him for the life I have been given
"Shrek is love", I say, "Shrek is life"
My dad hears me and calls me a faggot
He is obviously jealous of my devotion to Shrek
I called him a cunt
He slaps me and sends me to my room
I am crying now, because my face hurts
I go into my bed and it is very cold
I feel a warmth moving towards me
I fell something touch me
It's Shrek
I am so happy
He whispers into my ear, "This is my swamp"
He grabs me with his powerful ogre hands and puts me on my hands and knees
I'm ready
I spread my ass cheeks for Shrek
He penetrates my butthole
It hurts so much, but I do it for Shrek
I can feel my anus tearing as my eyes start to water
I push against his force
I want to please Shrek
He roars a mighty roar as he fills my butt with his love
My dad walks in
Shrek looks him deep in the eyes and says, "It's all ogre now"
Shrek leaves through my window
Shrek is love, Shrek is life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you actually been watching this show? That is not at all the character of Chuck. It would make no sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, and it's being thrown in the trash...if it's an upvote it implies throwing them away </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly this. Eladio's completely relaxed demeanor is what's so scary. He's totally comfortable and joking around, while everyone else is tensed up. By their demeanor, you know what he's capable of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and yet sjws still fiercely defend Islam...I don't get ir </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 06:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like koroks and I think they're amusing. I just think a picture of a rock is just shitty low effort posting and nothing more than a circlejerk. Not a good circlejerk either. It's a circlejerk where nobody's putting in any effort and almost no one is having a good time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 06:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and yeah that's what I think too. It was clearly and intimate relationship, regardless if romance was involved. But with that level of intimacy, it raises questions. Also, he could be gay or at least mostly gay and still have a wife and kids. Sexuality is more fluid than just gay or straight often, so he very well could have a relationship with a man or woman and that wouldn't be unrealistic. Having a wife and kids is the perfect cover for a drug kingpin as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 06:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From wikipedia:

Shipping, initially derived from the word relationship, is the desire by fans for two or more people, either real-life people or fictional characters (in film or literature) to be in a relationship, romantic or otherwise. It is considered a general term for fans' emotional involvement with the ongoing development of a relationship in a work of fiction. Shipping often takes the form of creative works, including fanfiction and fan art, most often published on the internet.


Shipping implies that it's just the fans wanting something that isn't there. In the BB universe, there are a lot of implications that Gus and Max were lovers. It's not just wishful thinking by the fandom. I'd say the problem with using "shipping" is that it has such a bad connotation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's just an ignorant comment. There's a lot of hinting at it, it's not shipping them, it has been implied in many ways.


1) Gus is a highly reasonable and rational man. This kind of vengeance doesn't seem characteristic even for a close friend of his.


2) He clearly has an intimate relationship with Max. In BB, Gus is very nervous about their plan, but Max calms him down and assures him that it will be fine. Gus paid for Max's education entirely.


3) Even in BB, Hector was mocking Gus as being gay. It could just be Hector being a piece of shit but he doesn't seem to do that to anyone else besides Max and Gus. In this last episode he made the "Butt brothers" comment which to me is proof that he believes Gus is actually gay. Doesn't mean he is, but at least Hector thinks so.

4) Gilligan will not confirm nor deny that they had a relationship. Doesn't necessarily mean that Gus and Max were gay, but it shows that it's at least ambiguous.


I'm not saying for sure Gus and Max were lovers, but saying that they're being "shipped" because many people suspect it is just plain ignorant. There is good reason to suspect it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess that's true but it's just such a low effort karma grab. Very few of them are actually clever. Most are just a picture of a rock on the ground or a sunflower.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah I guess not. I wish they'd put really low damage weapons that didn't break. Like a boxing glove that does 3 damage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I didn't see. Link? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if you also used Urbosas fury and parried Ganons attacks + attack damage bonus if you could do enough damage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can there just be a separate subreddit for Korok memes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every other post is a picture of a flower or a rock outside, saying something to the effect of there's a korok sees there. It's getting really old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So now it makes sense why black men don't have fathers...it's because they're like Jesus  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is revenge of the sixth  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These kinds of antijokes are so old, yet I still laugh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I never believed in true love, until... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am provided with a compelling argument, I probably still won't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I already did that, hence "can't seem to find it anywhere." I ended up finding one anyways after enough searching. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source on that? Can't seem to find any sources that say that was fashionable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bet this same person is totally fine with children being given puberty blockers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really not if you watched the show. Yeah they hit you over the head with "the universe is random and there is no God" stuff but remember that at least in the United States, there's a good majority of people who believe that God created man and that everything goes according to "Gods plan." Other than that, the show takes sci-fi tropes and exploits them to make something humorous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The irony is that Rick and Morty haters are more pretentious than the show they hate. Lel look at me!!! I hate something that "smart" people like!!! I'm so clever and contrarian!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> damn, no offense but you need to git gud! Keep fighting lynels and you should get to a point where you can reliably beat even the more difficult ones.


Here's some tips:

Shoot lynels in the face with a bow - it staggers them (stock up on arrows)

After shooting them, you can run around back and mount them - attacks from mounted don't degrade weapons

Practice dodging and parrying - absolutely necessary to beat lynels

Other than that upgrade your armor, get stronger weapons, and stock up on meals.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (   ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eventually, she will stop associating you with sex entirely and your relationship will become strictly platonic


FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many hours have you put in so far?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 03:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could be an old newspaper though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I don't feel bad. He watched child pornography. He also made the choice to do everything the hacker said instead of facing consequences.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's purposely ambiguous. The point isn't whether or not the kid is actually spying on them, but the fact that they're really paranoid and it seems like he is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have not watched that episode in a while. As someone in a long term relationship, it makes me absolutely sick to think about something like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't think Nintendo would purposely raise the prices of the pro controller so people would use the joycons. I think they made that decision based on cost and what they thought the demand would be. Nintendo is a business. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sam Harris </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> +5 intelligence and +5 charisma. I think of myself as a fairly smart person but not anywhere near genius level, and I'm always filled with doubt. Boost both and now I'm a confident genius. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess dad jokes has a new meaning </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think about it this way, these Youtube Stars have hundreds of thousands of subscribers. How cool is it for 10-13 year olds to have hundreds of thousands of fans tuning in to watch you play video games? It's what they all wanna be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Captain Uninformed Voter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I had to have my name changed now that I'm in the witness protection program... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm Joe King </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're cancer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm American. I get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It might be on 9gag now but it all started on 4chan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was my subtle way of saying this post was funny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's funny because I've taken German and my original thought it was just funny that it was spelled how it would be in German. Thought it was a spelling error, didn't actually think you were German! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did read the whole thing lol. I still would say that affirmative action is still wrong and should be argued against. People need to be more outspoken against legacies and donations and now that I know about them I will look more into it and make sure to bring those up. If someone is opposed to affirmative action they should be opposed to these kinds of favoritism and vice versa. Also, I don't think people know as much about these kinds of favoritism. I didnt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I don't remember ever saying it wasn't. In fact, it's the very basis of my argument; discrimination is wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they aren't, it's because they don't know about it. Those things are wrong and should be opposed heavily </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> gr8 b8 m8 i r8 8/8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I refuse to acknowledge this game exists </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sommer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do I need to answer how to fix it? I don't know exactly how we combat it. That's why there are people across disciplines who study this kind of stuff and try to create social change. I'm studying computer science. I am not a sociologist. Arguing whether or not affirmative action is wrong and arguing what should be done instead of affirmative action are two different debates.


However, it's simple to me that affirmative action is wrong for the same reasons that discriminating against minorities is wrong. Logically if you are opposed to white people being favored and minorities being hurt by discrimination, on the premise that a person should not be discriminated against or favored based on race/ethnicity/gender/etc., then you should be opposed to affirmative action, since it is exactly that; discrimination based on race/ethnicity/gender/etc. Am I saying that affirmative action does no good at all or doesn't help minorities sometimes? No, but the ends don't justify the means, and I'd also say it's a problem if when does affirmative action stop? At what point can we say "okay, everyone seems to be on a level playing field, so we don't need affirmative action"? I don't see that happening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conjecture  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) I'm talking about both, and way to add some new things into your original response without putting an edit

2) I'll concede that there aren't enough protections but I stand by my point that it's either not legal or not socially acceptable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> POLITICZ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You cannot legally give a family member a job in a company, unless its a family owned business.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is bad, and I don't know the answer exactly how to combat this. That's a different debate. Two wrongs do not make a right. Affirmative action is wrong, as is discrimination.

Edit: also, if companies are refusing to hire qualified employees because of their race/ethnicity, then they are losing out on good employees and another company that doesn't discriminate will hire them and benefit. The free market only cares about money. Those who choose to discriminate will lose out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because those things are not socially acceptable and some not even legal. Still happens, but you won't find many people who will argue that nepotism is morally permissible. Personally I do know many people, including myself who think it's completely unfair for athletes to get into schools just because they are talented athletes, even though their grades are terrible. And as far as wealth giving you a better chance at getting accepted into a school or into a job, I'm not sure that is acceptable to anyone. I don't know that it happens all the time either. 

Connections shouldn't mean lowered standards and if it does, that's clearly wrong. Networking is the way people get jobs. That's just how it happens. I think everyone has seen instances of an under qualified person getting a job simply due to connections, but as I said it's not socially or maybe even legally acceptable to do that.

Edit: my point is that these aren't socially acceptable and/or legally acceptable whereas affirmative action is supported heavily in law and in society  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you that most people argue out of selfishness and don't actually care about principles when it comes to affirmative action, they only claim it when it suits their agenda. However, blindly supporting affirmative action because "if you don't you're racist" is stupid too. A lot of people do that because either they are minorities and it benefits them or it's because they want to score some minority points and look like the good guys. Affirmative action is a real moral issue. In my opinion, it is wrong to discriminate race/ethnicity/gender etc. when hiring or accepting into college. The only exceptions would be when it actually pertains to the job (e.g. hiring only an Indian actor to play the role of Ghandi in a film). It shouldn't matter if the ones benefitting from the discrimination are minorities. Discrimination is wrong regardless of who benefits and who is negatively affected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still think affirmative action is morally wrong. Race/ethnicity should never be a deciding factor in who gets a job or who gets accepted into school. It's also a stain for minorities who legitimately were the best candidates, because there will always be the question of whether or not affirmative action had something to do with it. I'm sure this girl is one that never needed affirmative action, and it's a shame that it would even be discussed in her situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *whoosh* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why I don't care to advocate for anything  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 03:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm as a lesbian man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 03:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> everything is a repost. At least OP acknowledged it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 03:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> take out "but" and it works fine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 03:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not really an antijoke because it has a humorous punchline. An antijoke would be something like, "because it makes you laugh." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you start sitting to pee, your body stops producing testosterone because your manhood is gone. Then, your balls shrivel up and fall off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I mean if you want your testicles to shrivel up and fall off from lack of testosterone  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this isn't /r/rule34 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's kind of a meme to mistake Link and Zelda, it's something people who don't know the series commonly mess up. So it probably irks them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree on crafting. As others have said, I was also a little disappointed with the final boss fight. Other than that maybe just some new weapons and armors with unique bonuses, and improve the dyeing system because certain sets like Ancient Armor don't look very different dyed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I can buy a different game? I mean I have a whole library of stuff I've never even played. I wanted to play Doom but if I can't get it to run, or it runs like shit like it originally did, I'd rather just get a different game that I can run. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
