<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2662</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just got a repressed memory foam mattress. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 04:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It holds me just like my uncle used to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 'Legalize Weed' guy at my school fell asleep at his booth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 01:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A wife is watching a cooking show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 00:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The husband walks in and says "Why are you watching a cooking show?  You don't even know how to cook!"

The wife replies, "Well you watch porn..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An airplane was about to crash. There were 5 passengers but only 4 parachutes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 22:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pilot announced of the crash and immediately took his own parachute.
The 1st passenger, the President, said ,"I am the newly elected US President , and I am the smartest President in American history , so my people don't want me to die." He took the 1st pack and jumped out of the plane.
The 2nd passenger, a doctor, said,"I've got to get to the hospital. There are hundreds of lives waiting to be saved by me!"
The 3rd passenger, the police, said "I've got to get to work too! The city's security depends on me". With that, he too, took a parachute.  
The 4th passenger , the Pope , said to the 5th passenger , a 10 year old schoolboy , " My son , I am old and don't have many years left , you have more years ahead so I will sacrifice my life and let you have the last parachute." 
The little boy said ," That's okay , Your Holiness, there's a parachute left for you. They already threw the doctor out." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A SHORT HISTORY OF MEDICINE: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 18:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
"Doctor, I have an ear ache." 


2000 B.C. - "Here, eat this root." 
1000 B.C. - "That root is heathen, say this prayer." 
1850 A.D. - "That prayer is superstition, drink this potion." 
1940 A.D. - "That potion is snake oil, swallow this pill." 
1985 A.D. - "That pill is ineffective, take this antibiotic." 
2017 A.D. - "That antibiotic is artificial. Here, eat this root!" 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is Mozart doing right now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 05:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Decomposing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A man walks into a psychic barber shop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 01:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Barber: say no more  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Out for a Hike </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 00:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend Ted and I were out hiking in the woods. I was a little depressed over my losing my job as an English teacher and felt I needed the fresh air to clear my mind. 

Well, on our hike, we came across something so incredibly sad, it put to bed all of my own problems. There, lying on the trail, was a beautiful and majestic Appaloosa stallion lying on the ground. It had obviously been there for some time and was nearing death. Vultures, silhouetted in the crisp blue sky, circled above.

I looked at the horse; he looked at me. We had an understanding. He wanted us to put him out out of his misery. But before I raised my fist, the stallion rested his head, closed his eyes, and whinnied his last.

Somewhat relieved, I told Ted what we must do now: we had to make sure.

My friend was shocked. He looked over his shoulder frantically "Who," he demanded, "Who should beat this dead horse?"

I looked him in the eye, placed one hand reassuringly upon his shoulder and said:

"You and I, Ted." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My wife left me because I'm too insecure. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 23:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
