<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3240</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Day 7,641 of having perfectly intact bones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 22:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also hello, I'm new to this sub and all of you make me laugh so thanks for that and doot doot praise skeletal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 05:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And did you vote in the primaries? I agree we both had shit choices, but I'd hope you'd vote for a new Republican candidate over reelecting Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 03:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You completely missed my point. WHAT IF??? What if you DIDN'T have health insurance through your job? Like my parents, who own their own business. They don't get health insurance through anything. They have to buy it directly from the companies. And I'm not saying to vote Dem, I'm saying to vote for a candidate that is honest and caring and aligns with your values, regardless of their political affliations. You're voting for a corrupt candidate JUST because he's Republican. There are plenty of good Republican candidates out there who aren't this corrupt.

Stop thinking about yourself and start thinking about the nation and world as a whole. I'm very liberal and I hated Hillary. It isn't about blue and red, it's about integrity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 03:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw yes, nothing like some mild Nazism to a mostly innocent question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 03:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And if you lost your full time job? Honestly, it's about a lot more than just you. Kinda sad to hear you don't care about the healthcare issue just because YOU are safe. I get voting Republican, but you've gotta see that Trump is a whole different kind of politician. You should do more research and vote for a good, caring politician with your values, not just say "oh well" and vote in a crook again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 03:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly the entire season is shit anyway so yeah, it wasn't justified or worth it at all, which is why I think it was so heartbreaking. If season 5 doesn't astound me, I'm probably done with this show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 00:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a girl, you really don't have to dirty talk us all. I'm personally not much for it, but it IS sexy to hear your partner moan, curse, grunt, etc. Shows they're  enjoying it. It's kinda awkward to have sex with 0 noise whatsoever  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
