<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3232</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 23:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love to dice up apples and cook them on the stove with a little brown sugar, vanilla, cinnamon, a small amount of butter, and a few oats sprinkled in to thicken it up. You end up with something that tastes a lot like apple pie filling, but with very few calories compared to actual pie. 

You can also grill apple rings and drizzle them with honey. It's awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 22:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're still at this? Let it go, man, you made a lousy joke and people didn't like it. You're mad that I gave you shit over it. Get over yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 22:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at their history, CptNasty, I think this person is trolling...I'm not going to step in as a mod since I'm already involved as a commenter, but I highly suspect he's just trying to stir the pot so don't invest too much into the argument.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 22:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Maybe you and I took something different away from it? Art is like that, interpretations are subjective.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 21:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol at all the people who think it's fine to beat up a 12-year-old for vandalizing your car. Good luck with your battery charges, folks. In my state that can be a first degree felony if the kid was badly hurt enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 20:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I don't know what you meant by "watery." If you mean "water leeching out" then I disagree--I have never experienced this. If you mean "moist" then I guess I'm confused as to why you'd say that's a bad thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 20:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, you weren't a dick. I felt silly, I've spelled that word before! Everyone makes mistakes (which was the point I was trying to make to him, anyway). 

The guy's comments just irked me a bit. His joke didn't land and he lost his head about it so I was just taking the piss out of him a little.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 20:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, I just do not agree. I have never gotten those results, and I do not think the science behind the conclusion is sound. Linking me to another discussion about it is not going to change my mind. 

EDIT: I recommend the [America's Test Kitchen Method](http://www.popsci.com/science/article/2012-10/your-scrambled-eggs-are-wrong-and-other-cooking-science-lessons-america%E2%80%99s-test-kitchen#page-2) which calls for pre-salting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 20:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not true. Table salt can make your eggs a wee bit gray, but beyond that it doesn't really have much of an effect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 20:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cook it for slightly longer at a lower temp. I've done it before and it works just fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 19:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I meant by "it's the worst" is that comments that nitpick and tease about typos are just so unnecessary. It's like when you say "can I eat some of these cookies" and your mom says "I don't know, CAN you?" I mean really, come on, that contributes nothing, it's just annoying. It really is a useless comment. 

And then you proceeded to lose your mind and reply to any critical comment with paragraphs, pinging me to give me crap, and doubling down on your jerky behavior. Which is why I'm saying I don't know what you have going on, but whatever it is you need to take a step back and deal with it because you're taking it out in the wrong places.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 19:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yikes, well, I couldn't finish watching that. 

"m'FANS!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 19:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a child psychologist, specifically. It just so happens my residency is working with kids--I plan on practicing with young adults and teens when I'm finally done (two months to go). 

I like the whole "love and logic" perspective rather than teaching blind obedience and fear of authority. But you can't win a debate with a three-year-old and you shouldn't try. That's a classic mistake I see parents making with the kids I work with--they try to reason with them like adults, and the children are not cognitively capable of doing so. 

Give them a motivation to comply through reinforcement, because reasoning with them won't (and, from a developmental perspective can't) work. For example I had a 5-year-old try to debate me about using the sand tray when we only had a few minutes left in the session. We didn't have the time, so it was not an option. She just kept saying "but I want to do the sand tray. Why don't we do it for two minutes? Why can't I? I want to do it! We should do it! Let me do it!" And I just had to keep saying "no, because we do not have enough time. If you would like we can do that first next time." Then I said "the longer you keep asking to play with the sand tray, the less time we have together to play with the time we have left. You can choose to keep arguing, or you can choose to play with one of these other toys here." And that was the end of arguing. That's a five-year-old's level of reasoning. They get simple cause and effect, they understand reinforcement. They think that they can wear you down by arguing, and you really, really have to be careful not to give in because then you just reinforce to them that arguing will get them what they want.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 19:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, you only call out the OP. How charitable of you. 

Whatever it is you're so pissed about, you should really just sit back and take stock. Seriously.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 18:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the guy who chimes in with "I'm your latest hater, hello nice to meet you etc." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 18:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers, my bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 17:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you should worry more about learning to read and follow a recipe first. It seems like that's the part you're having the most difficulty with. That and accepting any criticism whatsoever. 

Next time, don't be rude, and people won't downvote you. It's that simple. Or you can keep complaining about the downvotes, that's sure to work out well for you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 17:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's "sugar butter," with the comma on the inside of the quotation marks. And it's "forewarned." Obviously now we have no way of understanding what you're trying to say, since subtle mistakes render comments completely indecipherable! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 17:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or you could use your head and recognize a typo. I don't know why you're acting like this, but seriously--learn to deal. Don't go out of your way to be rude to people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 17:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He needs to see it. It's such a great indictment of White liberals who are "totally cool with the Blacks." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 17:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funnel cake is all dense--beignets are light and fluffy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 17:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, that is not a beignet though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 17:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's really cute but something about it makes me anxious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 17:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All truffles are "no bake" truffles...

These look lovely, though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 16:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually have no issues with the sub besides the broadening of the term "narcissism" but that's just a pet peeve of mine by virtue of my profession. People need support fora. My main problem is that I see people commenting "/r/raisedbynarcississts" in other subs at the drop of hat--complain about a parent's behavior? /r/raisedbynarcissists. That's not only unfair to parents, it overly dilutes a very legitimate forum for people who grew up with insecure attachment to their caregivers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 16:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it's fair to dismiss it all as black performers being uppity. 

Oh heck no, that is *not* what I am saying. I think Lee has legit criticism of Tarantino. I think Tarantino's issue is that he lacks self-examination--he has an issue with fetishizing Blackness in a way, and tries to emulate the "coolness" he associates with Blaxploitation (and with Black Americans as an extension). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 13:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope so! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 13:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think Tarantino is  a racist, at least not in the cartoonishly evil Simon Legree kind of way that those folks are probably thinking when they hear the word "racist." He thinks blaxploitation is cool, and he's kind of a simpering fanboy about it. I think it can come across as awkward sometimes, but I think he means well. He's like the white suburban kid who tries to talk just a little more "urban" when he hangs out with the Black kids at school. 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 13:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess things have changed a lot since I was in high school. My HS had weighted GPA (5 point scale) but I don't remember any one class hurting my GPA that much. And yearbook was an activity you had to do after school, not its own class!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guy does a casual AMA and only one person has questions. The back and forth gets increasingly snarky as it touches on dating strategies and libertarianism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 13:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 05:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...yearbook though? It's not AP calculus. It's one class. It can't affect his rank that much to "tank" his GPA. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 05:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ouch, he derailed the drinking question pretty fast and Letterman handled it so smoothly. 

I guess I can understand his reasons, Reed had such a problem with drinking I get why he didn't want to go into it. And he was still an active alcoholic when this was filmed--to my knowledge, to the end of his life, in fact -- with the exception of 1988 when he was too sick to drink for a year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 05:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, this is actually really good--thorough, matter-of-fact, and not weird or shaming. These kids are great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 05:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Or that the human body can deal with a few e.coli.

Well, most of the time. You can't say that for immunocompromised people, the elderly, and children, though. While I think people get too worried about food safety sometimes, I think it's important to remember that making mistakes in food prep can be dangerous, particularly for vulnerable populations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 04:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can one class tank your GPA? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 04:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If therapist is not helping, you need to talk with your therapist about the ways in which it is not helping. Is it that you are not reaching your therapy goals? Or is it that your goals were not clearly defined in the first place? Do you need another practitioner to help in addition to therapist (psychiatrist, other medical specialist, dietician, etc.)?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 04:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I'm so sorry you're going through this. Are you able to get counseling? Sometimes there are victims compensation programs that will cover it, or city-funded counseling for victims of violent crimes.  All of what you're experiencing is normal for survivors of trauma. It sounds like you could use trauma-focused therapy. It's relatively short term and it can really help a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 04:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey StreetfighterXD! Thank you for your submission, unfortunately it has been removed from /r/SubredditDrama because:

* There is not enough drama to merit an SRD submission.  Please wait and see if things develop further, or look for a subthread with more drama. Make sure you're linking with the proper context.

Events such as "X sub was hacked" or "Y sub was made private" are not drama in and of themselves - do not just link to a subreddit that was taken over. If there are dramatic happenings around the takeover, please make a self post and include links to drama that users can read.



For more on our rules, please check out our [detailed rules wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules).  If you have any questions or concerns about this removal feel free to [message the moderators](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FSubredditDrama). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 04:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's not arguing. He's just saying Linda please and Linda listen. He's not showing proofs, he's fucking mouthing off. 

This is a person with no children and no child experience, I guarantee it. 

Kid's 3. They argue like that. That's what they do. Sometimes you have to do a back and forth for five minutes before they accept the limit. It's just part of the process.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 03:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Prometheus had problems (mostly relating to characters doing unrealistic/unbelievable/stupid things just to move the plot forward) but I don't think it was nearly as bad as a lot of people said. At least it had an interesting plot, and some cool visuals--and I really enjoyed that final fight scene.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 02:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, that explanation makes sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 02:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still unclear on what David's motivation was? Why did he want to create the hybrids? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 01:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think his problem is he doesn't know anything about fine dining so he thinks "fine dining = French." I'm guessing you could find at least one super fancy Halal restaurant in LONDON of all places. He just didn't know enough to ask the question properly. 

He should look [here](http://halalgems.com/halal-michelin-starred-restaurants-in-london/) for ideas. Seeing that Maze does halal food makes me think that would be *perfect* but I'm sure they at least offer alcohol. Maze is awesome. I wonder if he could learn to live with that? It's not like anyone is going to make them order it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 01:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We both know you cut a hole in each side.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 01:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, at least he doesn't take his sexual frustration out on the hole in his mattress. BTW, it's best to flip and rotate your mattress every six months.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 00:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the orgasm is not necessary for the woman to bear children, so really, it's a luxury and who cares if they happen? Amirite? Huh?

Now lets get down to more important things, like expanding access to Hentai and more affordable Russian bride matchmaking sites.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 00:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't let 'em get you down. It's not for everyone's tastes, but guess what? Your wedding isn't about what other people think is cool, it's about what you and your closes friends/family think is cool. For those hating and calling it trashy, screw 'em.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 00:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, and people are too quick to say "ugh, parents are the *worst*!" and call someone a bad parent as almost a kneejerk reaction. It's annoying. So is using narcissist "loosely" as they do in that sub. 

And there's no need to be rude.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 00:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I agree that change is gradual, but I just don't think this is a good example of that. A good example, IMO, would be the legislation in Texas requiring fetal burials for aborted and miscarried babies. Or rape being considered a pre-existing condition. 

Making a generic statement about the importance of mothers to their families is a half-assed, pandering statement--but it's not a decree that that's all women are good for. I think he just doesn't give a shit about the day or about women in general and he had an intern spend 5 minutes on it. The larger problem, IMO, is that we have a President who just doesn't give a shit about women.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 00:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It all becomes so clear when he says this:

Maybe she shouldn't have pissed off my dad enough to divorce her then

He's got a lot of unresolved anger about this divorce. He was ready to get angry with her over this before he even got up this morning. He said to himself "I'm going to do something nice but that ungrateful bitch won't even care, god I hate her" before he even did that half-assed cleaning job. 

EDIT: He also states this:

I'm a photographer and take pictures.

I think he still lives at home because he's not a good photographer. If he is, he sure hasn't posted any of it on Reddit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 23:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/raisedbynarcissists 

You know what? This is getting to be overused. Her behavior could indicate she's burned out and doesn't cope with stress well--it doesn't automatically make her a narcissist. People need to stop calling everyone narcissists.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 23:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Jack-The-Riffer! Thank you for your submission, unfortunately it has been removed from /r/SubredditDrama because:

* Surplus Popcorn: Due to a lot of stale politicized drama crowding out niche posts and dominating the front page, certain categories of drama face greater scrutiny and greater rates of removal. Your post fell into one of these categories and was not exceptional enough to be approved. See [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules#wiki_surplus_popcorn) for more information. 

Surplus drama categories include:

* racism drama
* gender wars
* social justice drama
* Trump drama



For more on our rules, please check out our [detailed rules wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules).  If you have any questions or concerns about this removal feel free to [message the moderators](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FSubredditDrama). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 23:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't seen it since high school--even after I heard HDTGM was doing an episode about it I couldn't bring myself to rewatch it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 23:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a perfect example of why I don't like that sub. It's very mean spirited. I get making fun of someone for being entitled or having a bad attitude, but it just seems really uncool to mock someone for their tastes and to mock someone for how they choose to celebrate marriage. Seriously, screw those folks laughing at that picture. Would I have done that? No, I don't really like that kind of thing. But I also don't like cold shoulder tops, ros, or Imagine Dragons. That doesn't mean that people who like those things are bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 23:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooh, and you were so close to not dropping a big old hunk of bait in the water.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 23:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't remember in the book what happened to married who were "honorably" married but still fertile--did they honor those marriages? I know they didn't honor Offred's because he was married before. I'm fertile but closing in on "advanced maternal age" and I'm married--not sure where I'd be but since I'm also an academic they might send me to the colonies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 23:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, that's probably the least offensive statement the President has made since we got into this mess. I think it's pretty innocuous, actually.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 22:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved the show and I was psyched to see it when it came out--I was in high school and I brought a few of my friends. And then spent the rest of the afternoon apologizing for making them see it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 22:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing is, maybe I'm misunderstanding how they're using the term "liberal" here, but I don't see Blue Dog Democrats as being particularly liberal. I consider them more centrist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 22:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like the gatekeeping sub in that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 17:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work for an agency that serves traumatized children and we just got our official therapy dog! The clients are so excited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 16:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are your perspectives on big agra and what the government's role should or should not be in terms of crop prices? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 15:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you want  strong government, just not centralized government? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 15:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess it just seems like that is describing more of a libertarian perspective. What are the primary differences between being "neo-liberal" and being libertarian? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 15:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  minimally centralized power

Wait, really? That doesn't make too much sense to me... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 13:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep trying to explain this to my in-laws, who don't get that their disabled daughter is about to age out of their private insurance and will have only her medicaid, and that her coverage is going to get continually worse. They just don't get it, and are still complaining about Obamacare costing them too much in taxes. Hey, they'll have to pay a lot more down the road--they don't even realize how much yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 13:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I don't blame you for your caution, no worries.

I would say you might be being a wee hard on yourself. You haven't received a lot of positive feedback in the form of romantic attention, so you think you're a hopeless case, but then you get caught up in a cycle: if you treat yourself like you're worthless and gross-looking and hopeless, others start to treat you that way too. 

It might sound cliche, but treating yourself the way you think other people should treat you is a good first step. Be kind to yourself. Hey, you just took the first step by acknowledging that you might not be ugly--now go a little further. Find something you really like about yourself. Concentrate on the things you're proud of. Believe that you have value as a person--because you do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 13:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point, *It Follows* was amazing in that respect. The "it" didn't have a character to it, though, the way Michael Myers does. It sort of had a mythology in that there were "rules", but not in the same way. The last time I saw "scary slasher in a mask" done well was *Hush* but he took off the mask partway through... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 05:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, and I'm a little disappointed in you for it. Go sit on the naughty step until your father gets home.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 05:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have plenty of female friends who date not-the-best-looking dudes. They get girls because they're good people, charming, nice, able to hold a conversation, etc. So it's not just about looks, I promise you. You'd be amazing what the right haircut, grooming, skin routine, an clothing can do to mitigate an unattractive face. 

Plus, there's also the question of whether or not your self perception is even accurate--what if you're a lot better looking than you think? You can send me a PM if you trust me, I'll give you my honest feedback. 

EDIT: I hate myself a little bit for coming up with something like this, but it would be interesting to see one of those Liftime Channel "documentary" series in which they meet incels and then consult with them and give them makeovers. New cloeths, new hair, new skin treatments, but also counseling and social skills training. I would find that interesting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 05:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, I thought they were talking about the *Avengers* starring Ralph Fiennes and Uma Thurman made in 1998, to which I would reply YES. You made a risky movie. You made a confusing movie, and you ruined one of my favorite old spy shows by turning up the camp and then giving the characters and writers nothing to do. I HATE THEM SO. 

Still now that we've had a good Man from U.N.C.L.E. film, Guy Ritchie will you please consider giving it a go with Avengers? Pleeeease? And maybe cast someone with a legit accent, like Rhona Mitra or Emily Blunt maybe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 05:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recipient of the coveted Spanked Monkey Statuette </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 05:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you taken a social skills group? I've run a few of those and the can be very helpful. I'm not sure if you're in college, but a lot of the time there will be free ones available on campus through counseling services! Individual therapy might be very helpful, too, to work on self image and reframing negative thoughts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 05:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Baity Baiterson, why ya baitin' so hard? 

It's "could have guessed," by the way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 04:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love hummingbird cake, and so few people I meet know what it is! It's all good things combined into wonderful cake synergy!

Small tip: I would fold that flour in more carefully--it's really easy to overwork hummingbird cake batter and it comes out more bready than cakey.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 03:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I meant to type mishigas, which is how I've always spelled it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 23:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not just teenagers, everyone. Graham was big on not masturbating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 23:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey dbossy! Thank you for your submission, unfortunately it has been removed from /r/SubredditDrama because:

This post is not appropriate for SRD. Please read our rules before posting here again.



For more on our rules, please check out our [detailed rules wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules).  If you have any questions or concerns about this removal feel free to [message the moderators](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FSubredditDrama). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 23:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't it time we get a *new* faceless, voiceless, killing machine in our lives? How many times are they going to try to revamp Carpenter's original film?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 22:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boo, that makes me sad. I'll still keep this post up, though, it amuses me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 22:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think of "responsibility" as being the other side of the coin as "agency." I know it's trite, but Spiderman's Uncle Ben said it best--with great power comes great responsibility.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 20:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, you're nothing special.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 20:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course not! But you can't blame other people for you choosing to not make positive changes, because it's your responsibility--if you read my original comment, you'll see that's all I was saying. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 18:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you okay? 

BTW, no name-calling, please.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 17:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for this. This is the kind of snobby douchery I live for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You like canned beans? Heaven forfend! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 17:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 17:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got family in town this weekend, so I don't have time to follow whatever bullshit troll bait causes trouble in here, so I'm nipping it in the bud now. Boozehelps can think I'm being a bitch about it and maybe he's right, but I can live with that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 17:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not throwing a shitfit, I'm simply calling out what seemed like a blatant attempt to bait an argument. We don't need that in this thread--or any thread, actually. It'll just lead to /r/Drama and SRDD posts. Ain't nobody got time for that. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 17:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My advice would be if you can't tell the difference between you making fun of typical sexist bullshit and the typical sexist bullshit, you should think twice about submitting the comment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 16:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dumb, sexist generalizations

Yeah, they all suck. They do nothing but divide people and lead to slapfights, IMO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 16:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, that is exactly what I'm saying--maybe I didn't phrase it clearly enough. I have a great deal of empathy for people who deal with regular generalized and social anxiety--I'm certainly not saying "suck it up and deal, no biggy." But at the end of the day, people with anxiety have to decide how they want to work on it, either through therapy (CBT is a great option) or medication (often good in combo with therapy) or meditation or yoga or regular exercise or journaling or whatever else works for you. I actually see this as empowering--people with anxiety should be encouraged to recognize their own agency. In fact, feeling helpless is a contributing factor to anxiety in the first place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 16:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a therapist, I can tell you I have plenty of clients who are actively working to do something about it. I think they're amazing, courageous people. I think you'll see in my comment that I was saying they are *not* misogynist jerks. Did you even read it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 16:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh give me a god damn break. Don't drag that business in here, please.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 16:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finding strategies to cope with your anxiety is your responsibility. Learning to function socially is your responsibility. If not yours, whose? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 14:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   treat women as actual people and not a goal, they like you more.

Honestly I think this is the secret to any social interaction, regardless of gender. It's the same reason why schmoozing comes off as desperate sometimes--like you're just trying to get something as opposed to get to know someone. This is why Ricky Gervais' character on *Extras* is so painful--he's the walking personification of sweaty desperation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 13:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, your edit helped, thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 13:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have one, thanks. This is one of my favorite subs, so I couldn't help but notice your post. Hope the potatoes thing is going well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 13:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like doing a whole smoked chicken with a spicy rub. I stuff it with a lemon and onion first to keep the inside moist, and I use fruit wood. It's awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 13:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, how's your 7.5 lbs of potatoes per day diet going?

P.S. The secret it fat. You need fat. You might be able to try egg white, but that might backfire tremendously.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 13:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds amazing. I bet it would be a great accompaniment to fried chicken.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 13:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 13:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I see we've reached the part of the conversation when you go from being subtly jerky to being full-on jerky. Okay, have a good one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 13:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quite frankly, you seem like *you're* getting quite unsettled by all of this. You probably shouldn't worry too much, since there's a good chance it's not really unfolding the way it is being depicted. 

BTW, I was just being funny with my comparison. I'm not literally saying that the OP wants to kill her fictional daughter-in-law. If I were you I wouldn't get too caught up in all of this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 13:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's /r/parenting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 13:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not about the content, it's about the *way* it is written. There's something about the word choice and the construction. I'm having a difficult time articulating it, I apologize. Again, I have no doubt that there are many people in the world who believe the things that OP believes and behave that way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 13:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...I think you know why you do it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 13:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It reads like someone trying to figure out the facets of a character or another person--something about the narrative rings hollow to me. Statements like:

How is he going to accept any support I give him after he leaves her if he knows I didn't do anything about it before?

If he likes it, it is only because she doesn't let anyone in close enough to tell him he is being taken advantage of. I'm just trying to be the person who opens his eyes to the situation.

 If they know she can't have kids, the normal recourse would be for her to find something to do to contribute to the household.

his wife said her uterus was none of my concern. Of course it's my concern! She will carry my son's children in there.

It just feels so...*hollow*. And slightly exaggerated, as if written by someone who strongly dislikes this character but is still confused about their motivations. 

You can say it's overly elaborate, but I'm just telling you I think something is really off with the way those comments are written. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 13:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Pretty far from handmaid's tale stuff though.

The way she chose her wording? Not really...came off as pretty unsettling IMO. Which is part of why I think it's actually the POV of someone else in the first place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 12:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's strange to see such a decent looking guy think he's ugly

I've seen a number of cases, primarily in situations of body dysmorphia and OCD. Not saying this guy has something like that, just that I've encountered it before. It's painful, really--hard to challenge. It takes a lot of work to shift their perception.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 12:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it's unreasonable to want her to work at all. 

I don't have a negative opinion about OP necessarily--you can see up top that I actually think this isn't the real person writing, but more likely someone writing *about* their mother-in-law, which is why OP is coming off as so unreasonable to so many people. 

You and I don't agree on the grief thing--grief is highly personal, and if this girl is making it clear she doesn't want to share it and the MIL is still pushing her boundaries, it's absolutely not okay. Some people want to grieve with their family. Would I want to grieve with my MIL? Hell no.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 12:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  most everyone has had at least one shitty dating experience

Right? If this happened to me I'd be really creeped out for a while, but it wouldn't ruin dating or anything. I've had some absolute disaster dates in the past courtesy of OK Cupid. It all worked out in the end--you have to break eggs to make an omelette.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 06:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite comment from our hero:

Right after i said i catfished her, her response was "i already know" stupid ass bitch if she knew then why the fuck she fell for it???? Another side note look how fast she ran towards the end Bitch went zooooooom!

So, I really do think there are a good number of men who are legitimately socially anxious and have terrible self esteem and that impacts their social functioning. They don't hate women, they just aren't sure how to talk with them. They could get caught up into the who incel thing because it makes it seem less like their responsibility. 

But then there are guys like this guy. This guy clearly hates women. You can just see it ooozing out of every comment. I don't know where this hate comes from, but it's not healthy and it's not normal. This guy is going to do some actual damage someday. I'm not saying shoot up a mall or something, but at some point he will go too far with this mishigas. He lacks a shocking amount of empathy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 05:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's his goal? To prove that women are shallow or something? Honestly, I'd be alarmed if I made a date with one person and another showed up. I'd wonder a bit if I was being pranked, or if I was in danger. It's a fucked up thing to do to someone, does he not understand that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 05:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL, holy shit, I must be really tired...I thought they were the same guy, maybe just taken a few months apart or something. 

Is this some kind of Black Swan situation? Do we need to worry about him bleeding on stage?

Just as a side note, back when I did Internet dating, if that guy had a decent profile (able to spell, interesting things to say) I would totally consider going on a date with him because hey, cute+interesting guy is a good bet. Of course, I would probably suffer through the date with what appears to be a man crippled by insecurity and resentment, and then I would shake his hand after we both split the check and I would kindly say "no thank you" when he asked to walk me to my car.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 05:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So he posted that young guy's pictures and then revealed what he looked like, then was pissed when the woman was disappointed? And then used that "experiment" to prove that women just want to fuck Chad or some nonsense like that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 05:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, /r/Drama is a nice blend of young Republicans, petulant Leftists, neo-Nazi sister fuckers, young layabouts who enjoy it "ironically," angry masturbators, and indolent drunks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 05:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So...were those really his pictures? If so, how was he catfishing? He looks like a nice enough young man, I'm very confused as to what is going on here... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 01:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a little *Handmaid's Tale* isn't it? Can't bear fruit? Go work in the colonies or serve as a cook!

This part got me:

I would console her, which is something I never got a chance to do. Maybe we could grieve together. 

Grieve *together*. It's not her loss! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 01:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good one. I felt really bad for her--no one deserves that kind of treatment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 01:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you remove the u ping, please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 01:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your mother and [Ani DiFranco](https://dreadedwhitepeople.files.wordpress.com/2012/06/anidifranco.jpg). Wait, is your mother Ani DiFranco? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 01:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, reminds you of your mom--could very well be someone's mom, I'm just saying it's not the mom herself writing it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 00:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You walk in a non-busy side street with one foot up on the curb and one foot on the street. Walk for a while, then turn around and walk the other way. Helps the baby move into position and gets things going. My doula suggested it and it seemed to help things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 22:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really reads like someone who's been trying to figure out the thought process of another person. It just doesn't feel first-person to me somehow. And by doing this, she can vent her feelings, get validation, and maybe even understand the perspective of the person who is driving her crazy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 22:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And she is not infertile, if that matters. She was pregnant right after they married but miscarried - and when I try to talk to her alone about babies, she gets standoff-ish and says she doesn't need that kind of stress in her life.

Lol, wonder why she doesn't feel like talking about having a baby with her clingy mother-in-law after having a miscarriage?

Honestly, this feels like a troll to me. I have no doubt that there are people out there like this--hell, I've treated a few of them--but somehow I don't see them writing it all on Reddit. 

My theory is that this was actually written by a stressed out *daughter-in-law* who doesn't know how to handle her mother-in-law's clingy weirdness and is trying to process her feelings through this writing exercise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 22:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might I recommend *Severance*? It's gruesome and funny at the same time. Not a werewolf movie, though. 

If you like the more fantasy-horror stuff, try *The Company of Wolves*--one of my favorite werewolf movies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 22:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry until your doctor says there's something wrong. I got my first ultrasound at just under 6 weeks along like you are and they told me they had to do a repeat in 2 weeks to get more information. My pregnancy was normal and my baby is now 15 months and healthy as an ox. Just hang in there, go back for your next ultrasound, and try your best to stay calm. At this point, the embryo is literally smaller than a pea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 21:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have two recommendations here. First is [this recipe from the NYT](http://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2013/02/21/magazine/gnocchi-of-a-different-color.html?ref=magazine _r=0) which is eggless. Second, if you're into eggy gnocchi, there's [this recipe](http://italiandish.squarespace.com/imported-20090913150324/2008/11/15/how-to-make-homemade-gnocchi.html). I've made them with and without egg and both are good--I find the dough to be a little easier to work with if you use egg, and I prefer the way they taste when I use egg. Hope this helps! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 21:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm smart because I listen to one of the most popular instrumental pieces of the 20th century."

As a side note, I know this is a matter of taste, but personally I would call the Rite of Spring beautiful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 17:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would venture to say someone in the midst of losing it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Commenter in /r/dataisbeautiful objects to Fatboy Slim and Daft Punk being referred to as pop artists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 17:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 17:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hang in there--he will come! Remember those last couple of weeks are really important for baby's lung development. Mine hit at 40 + 2 days. I walked a ton, did curb walking, and tried to stay as active as possible to get things going. I don't know if that helped or if it just happened when it happened, but rest assured, that baby will come out when he is ready.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 16:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Praise be!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 16:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this person's particular brand of crazy, though--it's somehow way more entertaining that your average religious nuttery. 

My wit is quick because I'm smart. Take note.

I question how smart you are if it's common knowledge that the media is monopolized and you don't know it yet.

God doesn't owe you nonstop orgasms.

I'm just so happy reading through this. It tickles me so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 16:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad--I've enjoyed the first two episodes. I think it's almost distractingly stylish at times--the saturation and the camerawork don't really fit with how I pictured it when I read the book. That said, I think the casting is phenomenal. Every time a new character is introduced I feel joy. When Orlando Jones showed up as Mr. Nancy I was stunned--not who I pictured at all, but I loved him in the part. I'm hoping they follow through with Anansi Boys!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 16:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chernobog? Well, yeah...that's kind of the point. He's a dark deity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 16:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they could probably do a combination of TV ads and maybe sidebar or pop-up digital ads, plus print ads in the form of buses, billboards, etc. We still use a lot of that stuff for advertising--now we have digital billboards, too. 

You're right that "telling it like it is" doesn't have the punch it once did, but advertising is still full of crap in a lot of ways. I think you could make a film that is transparent about the strategies used by advertisers now--blatant pandering to specific social causes, heavy-handed "ironic" ads, overuse of indie music to sell a feeling, good old-fashioned nationalism in car and beer ads, etc. There's still a lot you can make fun of--advertisers are a lot of things, but they aren't honest, that much hasn't changed. 

Hah, also, I remember one of the jokes from *Crazy People* was something like "Metamucil! It makes you go to the bathroom! If you don't use it you'll get cancer and die." There's a wealth of ways you could make fun of the way medications are marketed now vs. how they could be more "honestly" marketed, IMO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 16:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey URSUSAMERICAN! Thank you for your submission, unfortunately it has been removed from /r/SubredditDrama because:

* There is not enough drama to merit an SRD submission.  Please wait and see if things develop further, or look for a subthread with more drama. Make sure you're linking with the proper context.

Events such as "X sub was hacked" or "Y sub was made private" are not drama in and of themselves - do not just link to a subreddit that was taken over. If there are dramatic happenings around the takeover, please make a self post and include links to drama that users can read.



For more on our rules, please check out our [detailed rules wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules).  If you have any questions or concerns about this removal feel free to [message the moderators](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FSubredditDrama). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 16:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what amuses me more--that this guy is not a troll and has an extensive history of posting these kinds of comments about religion, or that he posts a lot in /r/howardstern. Honestly, I cannot reconcile those two things easily in my mind. 

Also, just in case: [Archive](http://archive.is/saDNh) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Really strange drama about demonic possession and depression in /r/AdviceAnimals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 16:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 15:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Archive](http://archive.is/vpGHK) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 15:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. I don't even necessarily skip the spicy parts. I want my kid to be able to tolerate a wide variety of flavors and foods.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 15:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you mean *Crazy People?* Man, I used to love that silly movie. I think it would do well as a remake, actually--if you could get a good writer. 

I guess you're right--it's a ripoff of *Splash*. Actually, it also reminds me of *High Spirits* in a way, too--which also has Daryl Hannah in it. I would love to see them do that one on HDTGM.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Like avocados? You're a hipster. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 15:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 14:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a weird Mandela Effect moment listening to this. Like Whitney, I hadn't seen this since it came out on VHS in the late 80s, and for whatever reason I remembered it as starring Daryl Hannah. It's so bizarre. I guess in my brain I combined it with Splash somehow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 13:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I guess I should have said "simple." It's one bowl and a fairly straightforward recipe. I've made this cocoa cake before and it's and excellent, sturdy cocoa cake if you're making a layer cake for decorating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 13:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, is the gif not working?

Here is the video I made the gif from:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q8ezcpeXyU0 t=31s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 13:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The boiling water helps the flavor come out of the cocoa and helps it dissolve thoroughly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 13:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good tip--I've done it before and it works beautifully.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 13:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1 pound (2 cups) butter room temp

3 and 1/2 cup granulated sugar

8 large eggs room temp

4 cups sifted all-purpose flour

2 teaspoons vanilla extract

1/3 cup fresh orange zest

1 rounded teaspoon of good ground cardamom

Proceed as you would with any pound cake. Beat butter and sugar until light and fluffy. Beat in eggs one at a time and add the zest and vanilla. Fold in the flour and cardamom. Put in either a large greased bundt pan or two greased loaf pans (this makes a lot of batter). Bake at 350 for approximately 1 hour and 15 minutes if you're doing one large cake. Ovens vary, so you might need to add or subtract a few minutes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 04:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey thewindsleeper! Thank you for your submission, unfortunately it has been removed from /r/SubredditDrama because:

This drama has already been posted. 



For more on our rules, please check out our [detailed rules wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules).  If you have any questions or concerns about this removal feel free to [message the moderators](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FSubredditDrama). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 04:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love cardamom in sweet things. I make an orange cardamom pound cake that kicks all kinds of ass. It has such a lovely spicy fruity smell.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 04:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't try to do that--the taste and texture won't be the same. You should start out with good quality, full fat milk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 04:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cakes aren't a trend. Cakes are always popular. Cupcakes, cakepops, cake balls, macaroons, creampuffs, all will come and go--but cakes are a constant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 03:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Food awkwardly served in martini glasses and shot glasses. No, I don't want to eat mashed potatoes out of a martini glass, thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 03:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chicken mole negro. It takes me a long time to prepare, but it's so worth it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 03:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cocoa is naturally acidic. "Dutch process" cocoa is alkalized to neutralize the pH. So not all commercial cocoa is acidic, it depends on if you buy natural or alkalized. However, I would imagine that they're using the soda to react with the cocoa here. Using baking soda is actually very common in old-fashioned cocoa cakes for this reason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 03:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey odav01! Thank you for your submission, unfortunately it has been removed from /r/SubredditDrama because:

* You linked to the full comments. Please link directly to the comment tree containing the drama. If the comment you're linking to requires some context, add "?context=x" to the URL, where "x" is the number of parent comments you want displayed. If there are multiple drama threads create a self-post containing the relevant links.

"The whole thread is drama" doesn't count.

If you're unsure how to use context or to submit a write up, please check out our [wiki](/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules#wiki_using_.3Fcontext)



For more on our rules, please check out our [detailed rules wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules).  If you have any questions or concerns about this removal feel free to [message the moderators](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FSubredditDrama). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 03:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assume it's because cocoa is acidic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 02:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, I think my eyes are playing tricks on me, because I thought it was just a very pale green. I can understand it as a style choice, since you already have the handmaids in red and the wives in blue, a bright green could be visual overkill.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 02:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ingredients:

**Batter**

Sugar 2 cups

Flour 1 3/4 cups

Cocoa 3/4 cup

Baking Soda 1 1/2 tsp

Baking Powder 1 1/2 tsp

Salt 1 tsp

2 eggs

Milk 1 cup

Oil 1/2 cup

Vanilla Extract 2 tsp

Boiling Water 1 cup

**Frosting**

Butter 1 cup

Cocoa 1 1/2 cup

Powdered Sugar 2 cups

Milk 2/3 cup

Vanilla Extract 1 tsp


Preheat oven to 360F / 180C. Grase and flour two 9-in baking pans. Set aside.
In the large bowl of a standing mixer, stir together flour, sugar, cocoa, baking soda, baking powder and salt.
Add eggs, milk, vegetable oil and vanilla extract. Beat until smooth about 3 minutes.
Stir in boiling water. You can use rubber spatula to stir. Batter will be very runny.
Pour batter evenly between the two pans and bake on middle rack of oven for about 30-35 minutes, until toothpick inserted in centre comes out clean with just a few moist crumbs attached. Let it cool about 10 minutes before removing from pans. Than cool completely. In the meantime, prepare a chocolate buttercream frosting. Use a standing mixer to beat the butter until fluffy. Add in cocoa, powdered sugar, milk and vanilla extract. Mix until smooth. Cut each cake horizontally. Smear evenly 2-3 heaped tbsp buttercream frosting over the first layer of cake, cover with second layer and buttercream frosting and continue that process with remaining layers of cake and buttercream frosting. Spread buttercream frosting evenly with a spatula all over the cake.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Easy chocolate cake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 02:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 02:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author: Hebbar's Kitchen

Recipe type: dessert

Cuisine: indian

Serves: 10 Servings

**Ingredients**

3 litre milk, full cream milk

1 cup sugar

2 tbsp water

2 tsp lemon juice

 tsp cardamom powder / elachi powder

2 tsp pistachios, chopped

Instructions ( 1 cup =255 ml)

  In a large thick bottomed pan heat milk. Heat the milk on medium flame and keep stirring occasionally. Boil the milk and reduce it to half.      Also keep stirring in between till the milk reduces and thickens completely.  Now in a cup take 2 tbsp of water and 2 tsp of lemon juice. mix well. Pour the diluted lemon water onto the milk keeping on low flame.  Furthermore, simmer for 2 minutes without stirring.      Stir and allow the milk to curdle. Now add 1 cup of sugar. Stir continuously and dissolve the sugar well. keeping the flame on low as the milk splutters.     The milk will thicken and turn slightly golden brown--also the milk mixture starts to separate pan. Now add cardamom powder and mix well.     Transfer the milk mixture to greased steel vessel. Allow to cool in 12 hours or till they cool completely.  Once it is cooled completely, separate the sides with the knife.  Reverse and unmold the cake. Finally, cut the milk cake kalakand into pieces and garnish with chopped pistachios.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kalakand (Indian milk cake) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 02:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 01:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although I don't like it as much as **The Handmaid's Tale**, **Oryx and Crake** is pretty good. I would also check out **The Children of Men** by P.D. James. For a similarly dystopian view of women's rights, the **Native Tongue** series by Suzette Haden Elgin is a good bet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 01:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought green was the color of the Marthas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 23:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, it *doesn't* cook as quickly as the rest, so you have to trim it or cut it--my mother taught me to always cut a cross in the stem because it helps it cook faster.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 18:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey bourgeoisalien! Thank you for your submission, unfortunately it has been removed from /r/SubredditDrama because:

This post is not appropriate for SRD. Please read our rules before posting here again.



For more on our rules, please check out our [detailed rules wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules).  If you have any questions or concerns about this removal feel free to [message the moderators](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FSubredditDrama). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 18:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  you'd immediately assess for those issues if it was a 19 y/o guy? 

Absolutely. I agree there is a double standard for men vs. women when it comes to number of sexual partners, but in this instance I think it's a red flag for anyone that age, regardless of gender. Now if we're talking about someone in their late 20s, I wouldn't be nearly as concerned. 

Just to be clear, I wouldn't tell the client immediately that I was concerned about it--more like I'd file it away as a piece of the puzzle. Formulating a case is all about fitting puzzle pieces together before you make a final judgment. However, I'd want to pay special attention to attachment issues, mood swings, trauma history, substance use, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 16:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're definitely a rarity, then. I've met very, very few women in the U.S. who do not wear some kind of makeup on a regular basis. 

One of my old jobs used to do the whole "bare faced and beautiful" challenge where you come to work without makeup, and it was interesting to see. I don't wear much so it wasn't much of a change, while some of my co-workers looked completely different.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 14:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You absolutely can make cauliflower "rice" or "couscous" using a manual ricer. A food processor is faster, of course. 

Why do you think it's called a ricer? It's literally called a ricer because you put food through it and end up with rice-sized particles. The texture of what comes out of it depends on the food--so of course with potatoes you'll end up with mashed potatoes, but cauliflower stays more solid when it goes through.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 13:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 13:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hah, no, I meant that in addition to the fruit the skin is edible, it's just a little tough. I'll edit to make it more clear.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 13:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm all for being sex positive, but I also have a good head on my shoulders. If a 19-year-old walked into my office and reported having 50 sexual partners, a red flag would immediately be raised in my brain to assess for history of sexual abuse, bipolar disorder, drug abuse issues, etc. I might get downvoted for this but I'll stand by it--50 partners by 19, regardless of gender, is abnormal and is a possible sign that something is wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Cincinnati chili really chili? One guy in /r/cincinnati/ doesn't even think it's food </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 05:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 05:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Assuming they engaged in all that sex consensually, and there are no other influencing factors like bipolar disorder or drug addiction or childhood sexual abuse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 04:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! In addition to the fruit, the skin is edible but it's a little tough. The flavor is kind of like a lychee. There's a little seed in the middle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 04:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty neat looking though, isn't it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 03:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Washing mushrooms is really not a big deal--people always overreact to that. Oil in the pasta water though--that's just kind of a pain in the ass. It doesn't really help anything and it just gets all over your colander.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Jabuticaba or Brazilian grape tree </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 03:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 03:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fantastic! OP would you share your recipe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 03:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I seriously thought this gif was going to show me a pint-sized ice cream pop. I'm disappointed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 03:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My very large, well stocked Kroger does not carry it. They have riced broccoli sometimes, but not consistently. It's really not a nationally available product.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 03:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's literally just cauliflower that's been riced. [This is a ricer](http://www.target.com/p/weston-potato-ricer-stainless-steel/-/A-15176872?ref=tgt_adv_XS000000 AFID=google_pla_df CPNG=PLA_Kitchen+Shopping adgroup=SC_Kitchen LID=700000001170770pgs network=g device=c location=9026792 gclid=CL6R0a_T5tMCFQODaQodNLwFyQ gclsrc=aw.ds). It's called a ricer because it takes larger veg and reduces it to rice-sized particles. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 03:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bonus shout out to this comment in an adjacent thread:

I've had sushi in Japan (Jiro, Tsukiji, etc), as well as Nakazawa, Kusakabe, O ya, etc, as well as lower tier places. The thing is, if you only eat shit, you can only compare to shit. Your range of tastes is very limited. What I used to think was considered "good" about 5 years ago, is actually quite average.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 02:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How dare you talk to snapshillbot like that!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 02:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Normal? No. You'd need to understand some context before you can begin to understand how that happens, though.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 02:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Archive](http://archive.is/Da2th) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch out, this guy's been to Tokyo twice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 02:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 02:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Archive](http://archive.is/WQ7SP) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fight in /r/FoodPorn over the legitimacy of sushi donuts spirals into a massive pissing contest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 02:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 02:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love cheese, but I'll say it: there is such a thing as too much cheese.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 02:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> where's the innovation?

They no longer make it out of lead, for starters. *Huge* innovation there. Or urine. Or bile.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 23:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being pregnant and giving birth can both cause them, too. I was super worried I was going to get them but I managed to avoid it. Things down there go through...a lot of duress. 

Eating a low fiber diet and not drinking enough water can also contribute because that leads to constipation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 22:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would he lie about something like that? /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 22:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eat more soluble fiber. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 22:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's that first lady who thinks the urethra is the vagina, she's on the spectrum. It's actually pretty common for people on the spectrum to have a high level of discomfort about that kind of thing. I think part of it has to do with parental discomfort discussing it with them, and part of it has to do with how black-and-white their thought process is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 21:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Ouch, honey, STOP IT, don't put it there!"

"Hush, that's just semantics..."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 21:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the guy who says "I have a gf. She agrees." 

Dude, I guarantee you your gf is wearing a little foundation and concealer and you just don't know your ass from your elbow so you never noticed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
