<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1497</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 15:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of people forget just how powerful the entry level benzos are. Even the baby benzo -valium can help you a great deal, before you resort to xanax, clonazepam and other stuff. I've tried a good deal of them but the Valium I'm prescribed at the moment is really good. It won't turn you into a zombie but it will take the edge off some pretty nasty feelings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 14:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Diazepam. Just got 100 10 mg tabs prescribed. Should do me for a couple of months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 14:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even drink the shit. It's so overrated, it's not funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 14:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But no face. Why bother? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 14:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WTF is it, anyway? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 14:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks pretty good to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 14:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No mods. I killed the griffin - am I to notify whomever posted the contract? If so, I have not done that. That could be my downfall. 

Yes, I have tried meditating for various amounts of time. Yes, I have talked to some other NPCs (didn't really think much of it). No, I have not attempted to reinstall the game. I really hope I don't have to do that.

Thanks for your input. My next move will be to notify the contract giver. I'm starting to think that may be the issue.

Thanks again for bearing with me. I was pretty pissed off when I wrote that post! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 14:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disagree. Yeah, it hurts but you know it's not actually harmful. I'd rather not give them the satisfaction of seeing me jump around and scream blue murder. You know it will pass. The worst bit is not being able to see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 14:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not that bad, FFS. Jesus, don't acknowledge they've hurt you. The worst bit is not being able to see properly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 14:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fentanyl is just as safe as heroin, IF and only IF the dose is known and controlled. Don't forget, a staggering number of people have died, just using heroin alone - they buy some and expect it to be just as strong as it was before but it's 'too pure' and the overdose. That's no different to a fentanyl overdose - it's the wildly varying purity of their chosen drug that is the real problem. Not the drug, itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 14:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't know much about addiction, do you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 14:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another poster said that they are testing the equipment that was used by these overdose victims. They may have used more than one drug - meaning that they could have used the same gear to prepare both heroin (or what they thought was heroin) and cocaine. 

So that puts doubt on the claim that cocaine is being cut with fentanyl. And it makes sense - if you take cocaine and it makes you anything else but 'up', you would be pretty pissed off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 13:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not that they want to kill people - it's easier to smuggle that shit across borders. Would you rather try and get a tiny amount of fentanyl past the authorities or many times that amount of heroin or similar? 

You smuggle the fentanyl across in much smaller quantities, then cut he shit out of it to bulk it up. Or use it to fortify the heroin you already have.

They fuck up the dosing - you get hot spots in the batch and that's why people die. It's very, very difficult to blend powders accurately, if you do not have the right equipment. It's a very common problem in engineering - especially when you have powders where the particles are of different size and/or density. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 13:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't China White a form that is already a salt that dissolves easily in the blood - you don't have to mix it with lemon juice or some other acid, as compared to some of the brown heroin types? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 13:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look like you eat babies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 13:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can piss it in half. Is that enough? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 13:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like your neck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 13:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How so? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 13:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean? I killed the thing already. She won't talk to me to take the acid gland. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 13:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just patiently waiting for something better. Reddit admins suck. The mods of most major subs suck. A lot of things suck about reddit. It might be the best out of a bad lot right now, but I long to see its demise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 13:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surround sound, in general. It's just not that good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Witcher 3][PC] Another bugged quest. Can't give the acid to Yoana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 13:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tried a previous save. Tried meditating. Nothing will let me give her the acid. And it's an important quest. What now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 12:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw all the 3D I will ever need when I went to Expo '88. It was supposed to be great. It wasn't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 11:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the entire Mysterious Cities of Gold, Ulysses 31, Filmation's Ghostbusters and The Real Ghostbusters. Degrassi Junior High and Degrassi High, too. Took me ages to find them all. I never really watch them but it feels good to know I have them. DJH is one of my favourite shows of all time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 12:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'm a noob. OK, I just installed synaptic and then mednafen (the emulator I want to use). The instructions for synaptic says just go to system - Administration - "Synaptic Package Manager" 

Problem number one is I don't know where that is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 12:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 12:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Appreciated. I know exactly where to get the ROMs but running them on Linux is something I have not done at all. I have no idea how to compile programs and shit like that. I only know a few command line instructions and that's simply copying what I read. Hardly enough for what some of these emulating programs need, unfortunately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm. Dunno if I'm capable of anything too complex, yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a 'yardstick mine'? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw some pawn show where a guy had a training set for US soldiers, containing inert Japanese mines. At one point, the term 'yardstick mine' was used but I didn't see what it was. Can't find any decent pics or info online.

Anyone know what it is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 10:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Fire does not contain water". Wrong in almost every common setting. Burn something with hydrogen in it (like hydrocarbons, wood, etc.) and you get water in almost every situation. 

''Microwaves work by heating water". Patently wrong in the sense that water is the only thing being heated. Microwaves are not limited to heating water only. Far from it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 10:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there an easy to use Sega Master System emulator for Ubuntu? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 10:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just got started with Ubuntu. I'm hoping there's some kind of GUI based emulator for Master System? Or am I wasting my time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 09:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrong. Don't answer questions you have no clue about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 09:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fuckin' mental. I didn't ever think it would be so realistic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 07:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NOT original. Blatant repost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 07:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always wanted to hear the lyrebird imitate something. Maybe I have but how can you be sure? I don't think I've actually seen one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 07:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, you already look singed (badly). A while longer and you'll be roasted, for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 07:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://25.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_lyjm2qad021qztjn5o1_1280.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 07:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an old joke about Alfas. They are notorious for rust. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How often are google satellite images refreshed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 07:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in a small town in Australia. I can see it on google Earth, obviously. But how often is that image updated? Would it be true to say images of more crowded/busy areas are updated more frequently? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 07:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And before school. So many quality shows:

Bananaman, Superted, Mysterious Cities of Gold, Ulysses 31, Vicky the Viking, Henry's Cat, Rhubarb, Babar, The Ferals, Fat Tulip's Garden, Inspector Gadget, Pugwall, Bangers and Mash. 

Fuck, I could go on forever. Pretty sure most of them were on ABC at one stage or another. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 07:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How lame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 07:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who don't expose their kids to potential allergens early on is also a problem... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inane?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least the windscreen and tyres won't rust. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always liked the whip bird. Such a cool sound:

https://commons.wikimedia.org/w/index.php?title=File%3AEastern_Whipbird_(Psophodes_olivaceus)_(W_PSOPHODES_OLIVACEUS_R1_C2).ogg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They think they are fighting fascists wherever they go - but it's clear they don't even know what the word means. They seem to have the view that fascism is anything or government they don't agree with.

And they are violent morons. That, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are you even talking about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not include the whole car? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, if he 'approves' of this shit, why isn't it happening in Russia? He has a sort of pseudo deal with the Chechens. Some cursory reading would tell you that. But no, what happens as a direct result of muslims in Chechnya is somehow his fault. Fuck's sake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What fucking crap. He doesn't want more terrorist attacks, so he leaves them alone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 05:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They just made a new version:

http://ruf-automobile.de/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/CTR-2017-schr%C3%A4g-hinten.png

And it's a fucking ball-tearer:

https://www.motormag.com.au/news/1703/geneva-motor-show-2017-ruf-ctr-revealed

http://www.roadandtrack.com/car-shows/geneva-auto-show/news/a32845/2017-ruf-ctr-faithful-tribute-yellow-bird-930-turbo/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 05:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There comes a time in a man's life when he asks himself, "who will float my corpse down the Ganges?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you considered closing the visor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buzzword?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Balance the equation:

    Ca + 2HCl -- CaCl2 + H2

The ratio of Ca to H2 is 1:1. So, you need as many moles of Ca as you get H2. Use the ideal gas law to calculate how many moles of H2 in 8.32 L. 

Assume HCl is in excess. It should be just under 0.3 moles of H2, as one mole of any gas at STP occupies 22.4 L

So you have PV = nRT at (I am assuming standard conditions) 1 atm and  273.15 K. You need to choose which value of R to use - Since the question is in litres and atmospheres, select the appropriate value:

P = 1 atm, V = 8.32 L, T = 273.15 K, R = 0.08205 L.atm/mol.K, n = ?

Solve for n and you have the amount of H2 produced in moles. Because the ratio is 1:1, you know how many moles of Ca were needed, in the first place. 

Use the molecular weight of Ca to determine the mass needed. It will be something close to 0.3 x mol. weight of Ca.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks mate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Top shelf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. Extremely poor thermal efficiency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have heard that towing (as in removal for being in the wrong spot) can cause catastrophic damage to some cars. Which cars and what is damaged, specifically? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I read somewhere that dragging certain models of BMW onto a tow truck can basically destroy the drivetrain. Is that true? Which models and why?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lies. It's a good word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that makes perfect sense. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it happens when you are directly facing the oncoming air. I should have said that. So it's more like a ram effect. That's what it feels like to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stand by my convictions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about Auto Union? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is it hard to take a breath when you stick your head out the window of a fast moving car? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know the feeling - that funny sort of chest constriction and you have to force yourself to breathe in. Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fountain or fuck off. I'll not hear any different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck's sake, aye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you call it when you have great difficulty falling asleep and when you finally do, you are immediately (or seemingly) thrust into terrible nightmares that are so extremely disturbing you are actually afraid to go back to sleep, just to avoid them? When I wake up, it takes a few minutes to work out it's not real.

I wake up in a huge panic from dreams that are incredibly disturbing. So disturbing that I wonder of it's real. Every single fucking night.

But then, just when it's time to wake up, the dreams turn pleasant and comforting.

But if I smoke weed before I go to bed, none of that happens. It's all good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was hoping it was the "For Rectal Use Only" one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Certainly isn't helping things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Burma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh. Fucking American garbage language. Fuck's sake. Must be a poster on The Donald. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be the judge of that. Verdict:

Agreed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ol' Trayboon couldn't even spell the name of that degree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck all that. You know you want me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This chick called Brooke. She was hot AF but she went home with my mate, instead of me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See? Penthouse does have some alright articles! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something like that. I read it in a Penthouse magazine while I was sitting on the dunny, one day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 12:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Member when the Rolling Stones used Hell's Angels as security? That didn't go so well... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 12:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only AIDS can turn a fruit into a vegetable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 12:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either a TAG-Porsche turbo McLaren or the Lotus-Honda 99T at Adelaide. Two of the most iconic cars for me. Beautiful livery and turbocharged power. Back when drivers actually used a clutch and a manual gearbox. You had to manage fuel, exhaust gas temperature and make sure each turbo was matched to the other in real time. There was a lot to do in those cockpits. Not saying there isn't now but I will always be nostalgic for the 80s turbos.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 11:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one forces you to stand there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 11:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The turbopumps were able to supply fuel at 58,560 litres per minute and oxidiser at 93,920 litres per minute. The turbopumps themselves each required  55,000 brake horsepower.

Per engine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 11:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.pmslweb.com/the-blog/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/17-stop-being-a-cunt-meme.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 10:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even the very best had trouble controlling the turbocharged cars in the 80s. Qualifying videos are so much more interesting than now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 10:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More of these, please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WTF is in dishwasher tablets that allows them to clean such heavily encrusted stuff at only a fairly low temperature? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 10:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dishwasher only goes to 60 C. Not a high temp. What is in the tablets or liquids that is able to get rid of even the most dirty, crusty, caked on food? It never fails to get rid of every single bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 10:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tattoos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 10:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None. Why would you watch a movie 10 times? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 10:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Root cause. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I please not tune that PID loop? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you talking to the right person?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And pH 1.5 is pissweak. HCl can have a concentration of 12 M or something like that. The pH is fucking negative. Just like I have said our stomach acid is a strong acid by definition but the concentration/pH is weak as piss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Esomeprazole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it's hardly porn, is it? Looks like an unfinished project - because it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps you could do better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 16:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it does. Your 0.1 M "concentrated" solution pales in comparison to the maximum. Therefore, the 12 M solution is way more concentrated - and it's also the maximum concentration for normal conditions. 

We're talking about stomach acid, here. It is NOT concentrated either by definition or in practice. It doesn't cause lasting injuries from contact with the mucous membranes, does it? No, that's why I made the point. Why are you insisting on nitpicking?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 16:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. HCl is a strong acid by definition. Stomach acid is 0.05 - 0.1 M in concentration. HCl can be far, far more concentrated than that - something like ~12 M (pH -1.1). Big, big difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are you talking about, FFS? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reverberating? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gastro-oesophageal reflux disease is what it's called where I'm from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely no idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I check out your... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pfft. Doesn't do much for ya when you're 5'6''! I remain hopeful... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rock out with yer cock out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuckin' jesus. That shit is suitable for chemical warfare, without even exaggerating. Get a crop duster to sprinkle that over a town. The results would be horrendous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. It's NOT very concentrated. pH is really irrelevant here. Stomach acid is only about 0.05 - 0.1 molar. That is nothing in the scheme of things. And a pH of 1.5 isn't really that bad. pH can go a fuckload lower than that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not giant, though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuckin' hate when that happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
